<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-25T11:28:47+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why Rationalist Like Buddhism</title><link href="/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Rationalist Like Buddhism" /><published>2019-08-25T11:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-25T11:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_1.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One would see rationalist talk ill about almost all religions, but not much against Buddhism. It would look counter intuitive, rationalists are here to slam all religious practices, and why not they slam Buddhism so much? Buddhism was slammed, that too by a rationalist nation China. By the time it slammed Buddhism, this religion had become impure, and was well diverged from in initial teachings. Yes one has the right to be stupid and follow Tibetian Buddhism, but China thought its the duty of the state to teach rationalism to the people and bring them out of their stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buddhism has lot of belief that are untrue. They believe in previous and past life, they believe in Karma which is  a kind of accounting system that keeps track of ones good and bad deeds and assigns a score (very similar to loyalty score assigned by China to every citizen), Buddhist believe in spirits and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Buddhists have got many things wrong, they had invested a lot in psychological studies and had got one thing right. That is they figured out that ones happiness and sadness is not the function of external world, but lies within ones brain. Its very true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a man who has a corrosive family, none in his family respect him and they just abuse him. Just imagine Leo Tolstoy, the world knows how his family abused him. So imagine a man like him and he is very sad because of his family. Now imagine he goes to  a liquor shop and drinks. His wife, children and relatives are the same, but he finds his sadness disappears and he starts to feel a kind of forgetfulness and happiness. I wonder Tolstoy was a drunk, but writing gave him happiness despite everything around him was pulling him down. As you see from this example these people are able to ignore the sadness and are able to generate happiness. That’s what Buddhism says, it says you r feelings can be detached from the world around you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People believed that ones happiness and sadness was controlled by God, or some supernatural forces, but Buddhism said that one can manufacture these feelings in ones mind. A trained Buddhist can choose to become sad when he wants to, and can become happy when he wants to. He can observe and comment and debate about himself, a trait very very few in humanity have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ever God is knocked off, blind faith is shut down, we rationalist are happy and feel that humanity is one step closer to the truth, and hence we love Buddhism despite all its shortcomings.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The BJP has got more than an Economic Debacle</title><link href="/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The BJP has got more than an Economic Debacle" /><published>2019-08-17T19:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-17T19:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/A9VOMfY4bOo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BJP does this and that, but whats happening to the economy? Its sliding. What’s happening to the fuel prices? Its going high. Your saving looks like its dwindling. Businesses are closing down and top tycoons in India are coming out to speak against the government economic policies. Without strong economy a country is finished. I am quite sure Modi will loose all what Manmohan Singh has built up. When Modi one day goes, perhaps we will be beggars and can be happy that we were not ruled by a ruler controlled by Italy, but one controlled by the magical properties of cow dung and urine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay the econ is down, to fix it you need to have brains, not swearing, not ability to burn your midnight oil, not ultra nationalism, you need to have brains without anger, and that one Modi’s cabinet that doesn’t have. I am not worried about Modi making us poor, whats the use of worrying after giving a garland to a monkey, its going to make a mess of it, according to the monkey it did the right thing. I am worried about India becoming just another Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see once Pakistani earned more than an Indian. If Indian earned Rs 100, a Pakistani earned Rs 165, but now look what has happened to their country. They have to beg for $ 6 billion, which is actually nothing, and they are not getting it. The reason is their stupidity, obsession with something other than the economy. They were corrupt, fortunately right now we feel BJP is less corrupt than the Paki’s. Either they are un-corrupt or are good at hiding corruption. The next big mistake they made is to let religious people take over their country. When that happened, passion started to take over and development got a back seat, and down went Pakistan. Who can save them now? Not their Allah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its Allah in Pakistan and its Ram in India. That’s the only difference between Pakistan and Indian politics now. I do expect India to go down in economy quick and none should be able to do anything about it. Then what would happen? The people with relatively good economic minds, the Congress will come to power, improve economy and corruption, and then we can elect this religious fanatics once again to waste away our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And life goes on. But will that happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see when fanatics come to power, a nation goes a full transformation. When the liberal Shah was in power in Iran, a woman can wear a bikini in beach, what now? Think! Once upon a time in University of Peshawar students had bands, wore jeans, what happened now? Afghanistan was a thriving country, what happened after the Taliban rule?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Economic debacle is the first phase of transformation from civilized to religious rules. When economy goes down you can’t purchase things, you may not have a job, if you do you will not be paid well. You won’t have a good purchasing power. Life becomes harder. When life becomes harder where will you go for help? God men. And think what the BJP and RSS consists of. They have fanatic God men who think its their right to control our lives. I am very confident we are going there, and possibly no force is going to stop them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Dream of Islamic Caliphate</title><link href="/god/religion/islam/psychology/2019/08/17/the-dream-of-islamic-caliphate.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Dream of Islamic Caliphate" /><published>2019-08-17T13:39:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-17T13:39:00+05:30</updated><id>/god/religion/islam/psychology/2019/08/17/the-dream-of-islamic-caliphate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/god/religion/islam/psychology/2019/08/17/the-dream-of-islamic-caliphate.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IkYrhzhxSCQ?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some times your peace and well being is affected by some idiot thinking some thing. Have you have ever had a bad day just because your bosses brain has got crooked? Well that’s the fate of India too, and possibly the fate of Europe. There was this guy Muhammed in Arabia who thought the then Arabic religion sucked, so he came up with Islam. If some one today claimed that one had seen God or Angels, you would be put in a mental hospital, but in those day they believed in him because he was a honest tradesman. Even very honest people’s brain gets screwed up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now not being content with what he had, he said this Islam will spread to India, Rome etc. That is he just blabbered that Islam would spread to «all the countries that came up to his head», and that’s it, our fate was sealed. You see, Islam and all religions in this world are not religions of peace. We suspect Aryan’s invaded India, hence Hinduism cannot be considered a religion of peace. Buddhists masacare Tamils and Muslims in SriLanka and Burma. You have the crusades where Christians killed lot’s of Muslims. Similarly at that time Islam spread by war and conquest and not by people accepting it in a peaceful way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Islam was a peaceful religion, the original religion of Arabian’s would have peacefully coexisted with Islam, and today Kabba would have been worshiped not just by Muslims, but of the people of the old religion too. Islam just wiped them out, forced them to change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its set in Muslims brains that one has to conquer to spread Islam, now since they believe in Muhammad’s blabbers, it means that Islam must conquer India too, otherwise the God man is not really God man! Its that’s why they try to conquer India so hard.Though many Muslim nations have given up turning India into a Islamic nation, Pakistan for its strategic interest still tries to do so. It control’s Afghanistan and since it has got one of the best and most successful intelligence service, the ISI, it does have the capability and the desire to control India. We have to be terribly careful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s an Islamic Caliphate?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conquest of India by Islam is a part of the Islamic caliphate plan. Right after Muhammad’s death, Muslim’s were searching for a leader. They had the idea that there must be just one leader and under him the whole world should be ruled under the Kuran as its the book of God. So time and again some powerful Islamic ruler rises and tries to unite Muslims under him and tries to invade non Islamic territory to keep the dream of Muhammad alive. Till now they are bit successful. Islam now stretches from the gates of Russia to Indonesia. At the same time these leaders have failed too as they embraced violence and covert tactics to spread their religion, just like Muhammad has done during his life time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we must realize&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no fucking God. We all know it. We take our kids to a doctor when its ill rather than taking it to a temple alone thus avoiding science. If God with such greatness exists, it wouldn’t have freaked out just because some one has disobeyed it and ate a fruit. It could have fixed the brain of the disobeyed, perhaps reversed time and made the thing of eating the forbidden fruit never had happened. If God is sooo dumb, my God what to do about it? Its worth killing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People should realize that God is just a feeling, an illusion in one’s mind. One must come out of this trap and must embrace reason and common sense. Else we will see more bloodshed in the name of religion of peace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/B1YiDN8MT9w?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Great move on Kashmir</title><link href="/india/kashmir/2019/08/06/great-move-on-kashmir.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Great move on Kashmir" /><published>2019-08-06T20:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-06T20:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/kashmir/2019/08/06/great-move-on-kashmir</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/kashmir/2019/08/06/great-move-on-kashmir.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-bdViOY6_6zc/UIZ2hFrxZeI/AAAAAAAAAC8/I5BiOzf73yI/s1600/61809-pakistan-this-is-natural-beauty.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s really a great move on Kashmir I feel, its really a great one what the Modi government has taken. I hate Modi and the BJP and the RSS for destroying India with Hinduism and with their stupidity in general, but the move was great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kashmir is a part of India in every legal way. Pakistan with its misinformation and campaign tried to split Kashmir from India, and it tried to split Punjab from us. They failed. If you see, these states have the great rivers shared by India and Pakistan. Pakistan is terribly afraid about its water supply and don’t want these states been controlled by a power that it considers an enemy. Its a very natural feeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Right Timing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you see things happened at the right time. Now Pakistan is disrespected even by Saudi Arabia, a major money source for Pakistani terror. None knows who controls Pakistan, if its the terrorists, the elected government or the military. Plus Pakistan is failing financially time to time. Even the Chinese who want to encircle India by making Pakistan one of their hit man seems to be giving up. Imagine China pumps investment into Pakistan and its gone without right reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silent China&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China has its own Kashmir now, its called Hong Kong. China is trying to integrate Hong Kong into it and India is trying to integrate Kashmir into it. So China can’t speak a lot on this issue. The timing at which India executed this thing is great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a huge Islamic problem for China too. China has relatively peaceful Muslim population in its West, think what will happen if ISI is able to radicalize them like they did to Kashmir, Punjab and Afghanistan and ask money from China for their reduced involvement? If China doesn’t realize it and stop supporting Pakistan, then its a huge problem. So rather than supporting Pak’s, its better for China to keep silent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;India must not loose vigil&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Pakistan is weak, India must not loose vigil. A terror attack is very cheap. If you have a army, you must train people for years, they must have certain benefits, you must follow United Nations protocol and so on. For a terror attack, nothing needs to be followed. You can do it for few lakhs of rupees. Pakistan can do multiple attacks on India if India is not vigilant.
On a longer run these attacks would do nothing, but it might be enough to terrorize people and make them blame the government for taking a wrong move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must also look into funding of Islamic trusts, mosques in India, I suspect many could be receiving funding from ISI and other terror organization so that they can use them to brain wash people against India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have already let our territory to be used by LTTE and now by Islamic Tamil Terrorists to mount attacks on Srilanka, its a shame for India, technically India is terrorist state, no country has the guts now to call India a terror state, but that does not mean we are not one. We are a country who’s territory is been used to launch attacks on others. We are a terror state and we must curb it to get international respect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Economy in Doldrums&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No nation can be successful in stress and in war time if economy is down. Indian economy is down, our construction sector is gone, our automotive sector has slid, possibly irrecoverable now. SME’s are struggling and many are going down. If Modi hits at PAK and looses Indian economy, then he is a bloody fool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a feeling he will prove himself a great bloody fool.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">வருங்காலம் நல்காலம்</title><link href="/2019/07/13/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%99-%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%B2-%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="வருங்காலம் நல்காலம்" /><published>2019-07-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-07-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/07/13/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%99%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%B2%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/07/13/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%99-%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%B2-%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE.html">&lt;p&gt;ஊக்கம் உழைப்பு நற்சிந்தனை தெள்ளறிவு&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;வருங்காலத்தை நல்காலமாய் ஆக்கும்&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">ஊக்கம் உழைப்பு நற்சிந்தனை தெள்ளறிவு</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">History of Religion</title><link href="/2019/07/11/history-of-religion.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="History of Religion" /><published>2019-07-11T19:30:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-07-11T19:30:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/07/11/history-of-religion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/07/11/history-of-religion.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/religion_history.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dynastic politics in Tamilnadu is worrying</title><link href="/2019/07/09/dynastic-politics-in-tamilnadu-is-worrying.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dynastic politics in Tamilnadu is worrying" /><published>2019-07-09T15:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-07-09T15:51:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/07/09/dynastic-politics-in-tamilnadu-is-worrying</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/07/09/dynastic-politics-in-tamilnadu-is-worrying.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.behindwoods.com/tamil-movies/slideshow/post-marriage-debut-for-these-stars/images/udhayanidhi-stalin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its worrying, as a Tamilian its really worrying for me. Udayanidhi Stalin is taking the reigns of D.M.K youth wing. This was a party who’s chief Karunanidhi walked out a meeting when it was proposed Murasoli Maaran should be held up in high ranks, look now whats happening!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no idea if the D.M.K people are safeguarding Tamil, just by knowing Tamil today I am unable to earn a comfortable living. The keyboard I type in has English alphabets rather than Tamil ones. Bus signs and numbers are written in English 1..2..3 than Tamil ones, no kid in Tamilnadu knows to do math with Tamil numerals. Even people of D.M.K are polyglot for survival. Kanimozhi’s school Sunshine is a English medium school than Tamil. Many Tamil families want their kids to have a English education than in Tamil. If Tamil disappears, I won’t be surprised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing the D.M.K is doing well just like the Congress is to take care of its head family, that of Karunanidhi’s. That guy, his son and his grandson are politicians. Most of Karuna’s family are successful business people. If a Tamil wanted to have his own business, he must think a lot, he must budget, most probably he must give up that idea of having his own business and must choose to work. Even if he establishes a business, he has good chance of failing. Have you ever thought how the Karuna’s and even AIADMK families have established very successful businesses? Why their success rates are so high? Why we the people who they say they regard greater than their life have to fail and stress so much?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has a person in DMK ever thought why his son cannot become the party youth chief, but Stalin’s son can? Has AIADMK ever thought why there are many hereditary politicians in their party?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am happy about North India at least, Rahul is kind of no more and he quits, at least he is acting as though he does not have the power to run the congress any more. Politics and business, it must be run by people who have talent, not by some stupid just because he happens to be of some blood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t feel India, Tamilnadu especially will have a good time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Calling methods with &amp;amp; operator in Ruby</title><link href="/2019/07/02/calling-methods-with-operator-in-ruby.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Calling methods with &amp; operator in Ruby" /><published>2019-07-02T09:42:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-07-02T09:42:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/07/02/calling-methods-with-operator-in-ruby</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/07/02/calling-methods-with-operator-in-ruby.html">&lt;p&gt;Today I learned this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mf&quot;&gt;2.6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mo&quot;&gt;001&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;mf&quot;&gt;2.6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mo&quot;&gt;002&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;count&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;mf&quot;&gt;2.6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mo&quot;&gt;003&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;nil&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;nil&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;mf&quot;&gt;2.6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mo&quot;&gt;004&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;count&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Traceback&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;most&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;recent&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;call&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;last&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;):&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;from&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;sr&quot;&gt;/Users/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;karthikeyan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;rvm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;rubies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;ruby&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mf&quot;&gt;2.6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;bin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;irb&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;23&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:in&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;sb&quot;&gt;`&amp;lt;main&amp;gt;'
        3: from /Users/karthikeyan/.rvm/rubies/ruby-2.6.3/bin/irb:23:in `&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;load&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'
        2: from /Users/karthikeyan/.rvm/rubies/ruby-2.6.3/lib/ruby/gems/2.6.0/gems/irb-1.0.0/exe/irb:11:in `&amp;lt;top (required)&amp;gt;'&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;from&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;irb&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;NoMethodError&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;undefined&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;method&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;sb&quot;&gt;`count' for nil:NilClass)
2.6.3 :005 &amp;gt; a&amp;amp;.count
 =&amp;gt; nil
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today I learned this</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Testing Mathjax on my blog</title><link href="/2019/06/30/testing-mathjax-on-my-blog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Testing Mathjax on my blog" /><published>2019-06-30T21:53:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-06-30T21:53:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/06/30/testing-mathjax-on-my-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/06/30/testing-mathjax-on-my-blog.html">&lt;p&gt;When &lt;script type=&quot;math/tex&quot;&gt;a \ne 0&lt;/script&gt;, there are two solutions to &lt;script type=&quot;math/tex&quot;&gt;ax^2 + bx + c = 0&lt;/script&gt; and they are&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script type=&quot;math/tex; mode=display&quot;&gt;x = {-b \pm \sqrt{b^2-4ac} \over 2a}.&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Euler is beautiful:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script type=&quot;math/tex; mode=display&quot;&gt;e^{i \pi} + 1 = 0&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">When , there are two solutions to and they are</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Salem R.R Briyani Is Not Consistent</title><link href="/2019/06/30/salem-r-r-briyani-is-not-consistent.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Salem R.R Briyani Is Not Consistent" /><published>2019-06-30T10:42:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-06-30T10:42:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/06/30/salem-r-r-briyani-is-not-consistent</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/06/30/salem-r-r-briyani-is-not-consistent.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-HEZY90KwmYw/VVtTfBSNnqI/AAAAAAAABSE/tBIBqz7ykHI/s1600/salem%2Brr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t remember when, it was a day when I bought Salem R.R Chicken Briyani and ate it, it was so good that even without my realization I ate it without any side dish. My respect for Salem R.R went through the roof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next week I bought Briyani at the very same Salem R.R and I tried to eat, this time I was unable to swallow it without side dish. Compared to previous one this was crap. I am a regular buyer, and all subsequent weeks it was somewhere between crap and the good tasty one. Yesterday it came close to the good tasty one but was still far behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salem R.R is costly costs 200/- even for chicken. Though the quantity is little bit higher, it costs a bit high. For that cost they must give some justification in taste. One week its good and another its crap. I hope they hire process experts, apply some scientific management and make the taste consistent.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>