<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-08-27T08:38:45+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Life Of An Indian</title><link href="/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life Of An Indian" /><published>2020-08-27T08:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-27T08:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/life_of_an_indian.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I don’t bet on gold?</title><link href="/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I don't bet on gold?" /><published>2020-08-18T21:12:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-18T21:12:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://dailytimes.com.pk/assets/uploads/2018/04/29/today-gold-prices-in-pakistan-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of my friend, Indians of course are stumped by why I don’t bet on Gold. There are two simple reasons for that, first I still expect to live another 50 years, and I still plan to have a family and leave my values and wealth behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the exact reason why you buy gold isn’t it? It will have a exchange value even 50 years from now? The answer is no. Gold will be as cheap as iron and other materials will become throw away cheap. Why? See this video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/y8XvQNt26KI?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speed at which SpaceX is going ahead with starship, the innovative ideas that other startups are coming up like 3D printed rockets like Relativity Space, it’s going to get very easy to reach orbit and back to earth. From orbit we have ion propulsion powered by solar in inner solar system and technology like powerball nuclear reactors in external system from Mars onwards. This will make enable us to bring and park asteroids near Earth and mine it’s resources and make even gold dirt cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.teslarati.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/BFR-2018-spaceship-and-booster-sep-SpaceX-2-crop.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup with the speed of human innovation, I think this will happen sooner than later. So let’s see. So definitely saving your wealth in the form of gold for your grand kids won’t work. In Napoleon’s table cutlery was made of very precious metal called Aluminum which was much costlier than gold, we now use it to make plates and pots for jail inmates because it’s so cheap now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;References&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.spacex.com/vehicles/starship/&quot;&gt;Starship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.relativityspace.com/&quot;&gt;Relativity Space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ion_thruster&quot;&gt;Ion Thruster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/nuclear-power-balls-triso-fuel/&quot;&gt;Powerball&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://x-energy.com/reactors/xe-100&quot;&gt;Xenergy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Silencing Prashanth Bhushan - Supreme Court Destroys India</title><link href="/india/justice/2020/08/15/silencing-prashanth-bhushan-supreme-court-destroys-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Silencing Prashanth Bhushan - Supreme Court Destroys India" /><published>2020-08-15T10:12:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-15T10:12:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/justice/2020/08/15/silencing-prashanth-bhushan-supreme-court-destroys-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/justice/2020/08/15/silencing-prashanth-bhushan-supreme-court-destroys-india.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1c/Prashant_Bhushan.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Prashant Bhushan - The Victim&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hardly surprising in an ultra orthodox religious rule that the justice system fails. It was by suppressing free and fair justice, extremist like Hitler came to power, and only in a similar way Modi can attain full control of India. In my mind there is no doubt he will become the dictator monarch of India and will destroy the nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today the supreme court is testing the waters. They are seeing how the nation would react if we bring clamp down on free speech. A very prominent lawyer Prashant Bhushan has tweeted facts about judges of supreme court, and he being a person who can bring out the truth, he tweeted with undeniable evidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fSlzBd26atc?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the judges had some moral left in them, they should have resigned and begged the nation to forgive them, but just like any other banana republic, people in power want to harass those who question their wrong doing. And since this stuff is exposing the amassing of wealth by BJP people, the government will back the judges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is only the first step. But I feel the soul of India is already destroyed. A nation tolerant to stuff, and nation that can listen to any one, and a nation that should think with common sense is no more. Just few months back a channel called Karuppar Kootam was banned because it made comments about Hinduism. Hindu’s couldn’t tolerate it, Muslims were afraid they were next to be questioned, Christians would have been alarmed too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For stupids to survive, say the BJP, RSS, any religion, cults etc, you should stifle common sense, free thought and free opinion, and India is well on way to evolve back to darkness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/what_is_fascism&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Prashant Bhushan - The Victim</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Time to fight back Hindi colonialist once again</title><link href="/2020/08/14/time-to-fight-back-hindi-colonialist-once-again.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Time to fight back Hindi colonialist once again" /><published>2020-08-14T09:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-14T09:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/08/14/time-to-fight-back-hindi-colonialist-once-again</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/08/14/time-to-fight-back-hindi-colonialist-once-again.html">&lt;p&gt;I saw this video on youtube&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4FSZPJAdBtU?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like this fucking Amith shah is trying to impose something on us, possibly Hindi. It’s time to get our adrenalin pumping and fight those northern colonialists once again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The North has always fancied conquering the South for long. If you take Ramayanam, its about a victory of an unworthy destitute from northern India over a fine ruler who ruled the South. Finally the Telugus, Mughals conquered us, and no wonder and the British did conquer us too. In fact people of Chennai and wealthy community of India, who were fed up by Mughals aided the British with wealth in conquering us. But at no time we lost our language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the Telugu (Kalappar) conquest, we lost our old Tamil script and moved to new one. This was refined during Periyaar times as we needed something to take advantage of the modern printing press, no longer we need to write on palm leaves, so we can leave out squiggly like characters that appear in languages like Malayam to Burmes which were formulated to be written on tender leaves. But all the time Tamil was Tamil. It’s even said that if Thiruvaluvar popped into existence today, he would understand what we speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tamil had a grammar and reached perfection state (செம்மொழி) even like 5000 years ago. We eliminated imperfect pronunciations like sha, ha, gha, ish, long ago, possibly even before Prakrit came into being, possibly we could have done it in Mesopotamia (modern Iraq) where we got our first written form. Yes cuneiform is a Dravidian script, it was called Tal (தள்), which means push in Tamil and other Dravidian language, because we pushed sticks into clay tablets to create it. Possibly Dravidians who came to India discovered their own writing very late after that. Today Hindi still has these incomplete pronunciations. Imagine the cognitive gap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we came below Vindhyas, Dravidians became very good at resisting things from north, possibly our war techniques improved. That’s why we still exists as Tamils till today. Our military might peaked in Chola period. We did not even hesitate to invade military schools in Kerala which was set to be created by Parasuraman’s disciple and was thought as invincible. Rajaraja’s invasion of these places (with ease) for spreading descent and Terrorism in Tamilnadu shocked Kerala like hell and created centuries of hate. Imagine, schools created by disciple of God been sacked like blowing dust away. Such super might, earned respect for Tamils. But we did then what Hindi people are doing to us now, we destroyed them completely and got the shit out of them and brought them to our ways. These people haven’t forgotten about it till now. Possibly that’s why Srilankan genocide was engineered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yghtSSnk1-8?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the way from Iraq to Singapore, many places have Tamil names. Just check the name of this mountain &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Sikaram&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Sikaram&lt;/a&gt;, where it is? What sikaram (சிகரம்) in Tamil means? What is the climate in Sudan (சூடு நாடு)? How is the sea shore in Eriteria (எரி கடல்)? What language isolated people in Cameroon (காமம் ஊர்) speak even today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vWyAYGlFZjk?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We find Thaayumaanavar representation in South America. Ancient ship bells in Newzeland have Tamil inscriptions on them. And these Hindi people think of imposing stuff on us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When India got independence, it was promised made to minorities that their beliefs and culture would not be touched.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/c_hd0YZlCiQ?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But look whats happening? We almost lost our Jallikattu. How many of us name our kids based on Sanskrit and Arabic names? In Dravidian culture women can worship and do pooja to God. How many temples have women priest now? We prayed to God in Tamil before. Today in marriage you don’t know if a Brahmin tells you to fuck your wife or tells the Gods to fuck her first. Yes we pay him for that. Yes it’s true that India was sexually very independent in the past, so those stuff were tolerated, and it became ultra conservative as it is now somewhere in the middle. Every religious text describes the beauty of God and Goddess and what they did in vivid detail. Indians saw these things as very normal things like we say to our friend today that we had idlis this morning. A whole section in Thirukural is dedicated for this, but won’t it be better if a Brahmin tells to the groom who would like to fuck his wife first in Tamil rather than in Sanskrit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Islamists are so bold that they demand Tamil muslims to ditch their language and pray to god in Arabic, fuck! Some how many mulims who I know feel Arabic is the way to worship God. In this regard the Arabs are no different than Aryans invaders who tarnished our culture. The funny thing is, there is no proof that prophet Muhammad existed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/j9S_xbjIRgE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do not have Tamil literature for Science, a very serious drawback. Tiny Japan has it in Japanese. Germans do their engineering and medicine in German. I should be ashamed of typing my blog in English. We have let English, another imperfect language to conquer us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will be interesting to know about this one nation one all theory. Will Amitshah admit that his father is not his father but Gandhi is his father? Because we live in one nation so we all must have one father! Will he admit Indira is his true mother, and his mother is nothing and fake? Then why he or any one can’t admit some one else is their parent, want us to admit another language in our minds. Tamil is our linguistic mother and it will always be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New Tamil Desam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would be happy and not worried if things flare up and we get our own country. Definitely we are doing far well above Indian average. We are the most urbanized state in India. Our development is homogeneous  compared to other states. We don’t have religious violence here, and people d reject caste politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we are separate nation, lot of countries will help us too. Countries like Srilanka, Canada, Australia, United Kingdom, Malaysia, Singapore, Mauritus have Tamil as their national language and may stand by our side. Our diaspora would love to see our nation lifted. Plus we can have a say weather or not we can allow people from North can make a living here, thus we can prevent our way of life from getting corrupted. We can have our kids studying for medicine and science without an external government and cultual interference and so on.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I saw this video on youtube</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">So the 5 Rafel’s are supposed to terrorize China and Pakistan?</title><link href="/india/politics/defense/rafel/2020/07/30/so-the-5-rafel-s-are-supposed-to-terrorize-china-and-pakistan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="So the 5 Rafel's are supposed to terrorize China and Pakistan?" /><published>2020-07-30T10:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-30T10:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/politics/defense/rafel/2020/07/30/so-the-5-rafel-s-are-supposed-to-terrorize-china-and-pakistan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/politics/defense/rafel/2020/07/30/so-the-5-rafel-s-are-supposed-to-terrorize-china-and-pakistan.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nationalinterest.org/sites/default/files/main_images/K98%20%281%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s said that IAS’s officers don’t like to work under Modi because most of their job would be to publicize what Modi has done. They despite their intelligence will be reduced to public realtionship officers. It’s also gossiped that far right Hindu groups have invested a lot in Indian news channels and have almost bought them so that they are a jaalara for Modi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the happening unfolding it looks so true. Yes India has inducted new combat aircraft after decades, but its five, thats it. Just imagine you write 5 letters in your exam paper and start dreaming of how you will become rank #1 in class, if that sounds so stupid, then this should also be stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rulers are elected to rule, to manage the nation, it’s a very very big task. If publicity is all the thing that BJP thinks, I think actress like Shakeela can talk with France to purchase nuclear power tech, defense etc and no matter what she does we will get a very free publicity and likes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rafel is a engineering marvel, no doubt. I am an engineer and I understand the difficulty the engineers would have gone through to make it work. Just imagine we had one Kalaam and he was not enough to lift up the nation, similarly even a very good weapon in small numbers is not enough to defend a country. Right now we are getting a media flood about Rafel, and I think it’s not much more than that in practicality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rafel is 4.5 generation aircraft, what ever the number means, but will the aircraft be able to run away  from very cheap set of 50 ground to air missiles launched against it? I doubt so. Even if it can escape many, imagine the pilot’s fatigue trying to mitigate say 50 missiles launched one by one against him. Russians have found ways to detect and bring down 5G aircraft’s and they are a defense based economy, and they will sell it to who ever can buy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope Modi’s government does not waste a lot of money in Rafel propaganda. Imagine if we can give Rs 10 Lakhs to some one in rural area, they can set up a small business and give employment to few. Possibly 8 of 10 business will fail, but, I hope you get my point, by consistent investment you will get things going. Imagine if Modi spends that amount giving ad’s to media, it might not help the nation so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do I think will BJP, RSS, Modi will change after me blogging like this? Definitely no. Possibly if 1000’s read it, may be ten of them will think before voting. If that person learns to think about politics, he will think about other stuff too. Possibly he or she can make others think. That’s what I hope to achieve with my blogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0mBJ0N0uj2k?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">There is obscenity in every religion and you should not know about it</title><link href="/2020/07/18/there-is-obscenity-in-every-religion-and-you-should-not-know-about-it.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There is obscenity in every religion and you should not know about it" /><published>2020-07-18T16:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-18T16:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/07/18/there-is-obscenity-in-every-religion-and-you-should-not-know-about-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/18/there-is-obscenity-in-every-religion-and-you-should-not-know-about-it.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4tcjE5gMDzI?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ever the BJP, RSS and Hindu fanatics want to ban something, then it means there is truth in that. This time it’s not just Hindu fanatics, even the Muslim fanatics want to ban Karuppar Kootam an Youtube channel that broadcasts Periyaar thoughts and their own opinion. I want to stress on their own opinion. This is unfortunately India, you have the right to say your opinion about any one, anything, it’s the duty of this nation to protect you. Or all in this nation must vote for a government that will change the constitution where free speech, thought and expression of opinion is banned. I think Modi is well on the way to do that. I also see a time where bright minds, and thinkers very soon will run away from India as they ran away from Hitler’s Germany. The fact that even Muslims are going against Karuppar Kootam is a good thing. It means these guys have the guts to do what Periyaar did not have, to go against Islam. I feel it’s Periyaars very big mistake of not going against Islam, Christianity, Buddhism, Sikhism and Jainiam. All religions are flawed and misguide people and they all must be eliminated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to obscenity in religions. All religions have obscenity in them. Lord Indra, in fact the King of God’s, just research what he did. Just check the Bible and Quoran. In it God even tells a person called Ibrahim to kill his own son. They preach child killing religions to kids even in India which wants to paint itself as a nation of peace. Funny! Today ISIS tells you to send your sons to battle in the name of God. I am sure very obscene stuff is there in Abhrahamic religions too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why they don’t want you to know?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, it’s the problem with humans. The pundits, Mullahs and Fathers have shown themselves as pure and through masses and religious gathering have interpreted a 1000 year old text in their own way. They have interpreted and modified it to suit to their public life styles. We all know how their private life’s are. Now if you look at the meaning the other way, it breaks the purity cloak in which they hide. They can no longer claim pure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those guys have made you worship stone, mad you worship a figure of Jesus that’s not at all Jesus (we don’t even know if he exists, and he could be a con man), made you believe if you offer prayer pointing in a direction it will do good. They have succeeded in making you swim on land, and they have succeeded in making you believe the religion is pure, which is not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who are the people who go against Karuppar Kootam?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not saints who have touched the non existent God are going behind this gang that exposes these stuff (of course Karuppar Kootam spice up their expose), but it’s those people who are married, impure, had and are going to have kids, those who watch midnight masala are the people who are going against this Karuppar gang. It is just to be seen if the courts will uphold the law of free opinion or give in to government and vote bank pressure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dravidianism and Aryanism</title><link href="/2020/07/11/dravidianism-and-aryanism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dravidianism and Aryanism" /><published>2020-07-11T12:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-11T12:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/07/11/dravidianism-and-aryanism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/11/dravidianism-and-aryanism.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Kalaignar_M._Karunanidhi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Karunanidhi&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Karunanidhi&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know Karunanidhi could have looted and somehow escaped till last, there was another politician called R.Venkatraman who was also our president. There are no stains on Venkatraman as we know, he is so pure say like Manmohan Singh, Kalaam etc, none would even dare to think evil or try to frame up corruption against him. But this is what I heard about their families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see as government people, if there is any repair in their house say plumbing, electrical or any other civil repair, the Public Works Department (PWD) people would visit and do it, so we in the real estate would hear about them. This is what I heard about their families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/f/ff/R_Venkataraman.jpg/800px-R_Venkataraman.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;R.Venkatraman&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;R.Venkatraman&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Venkatraman’s family, if one would visit it, the worked wouldn’t even be asked if he needs water, Venkatraman family could have been a strict Iyer family, and their strict austerity would have meant that they will never mingle with workers. May be the PWD people realizing this, never even asked or dared to ask something as plain as water to drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to Karunanidhi family. If people visit there, they say they might be interrupted by his wife Dayalu Ammal or Stalins wife and will be offered coffee or something to drink. The will be invited for snack or food, the woman and daughter in law of the house that would serve them. In short though you had gone to Karuna’s home as a worker to do some task, you would be treated kind of a guest, respected as equal human. People who went there to fix things would say that how simple the women in Karuna’s home were, women sat down and used &lt;em&gt;aruva manai&lt;/em&gt; to slice vegetables they would say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the difference between Aryanism and Drividianism. In Aryanism you have created and branded yoursef as Aryan and possibly as Brahmin because you think you are somewhat superior to others just because of your birth and / or because due to grace of God. On the other side there is Dravidianism which is essentially nothing, and makes no fuss, you are just a normal human being, mingling with others as though you and they are equal. Now imagine visitors visiting these two homes, who will they like to vote for? The Congress or the DMK with Karuna championed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is also the reason many people are moving away from Hindusim in India, mainly people who belong to caste who are not treated right even today. People who belong to so called upper caste look down upon them. I don’t think the BJP or RSS would revive Hinduism, it’s Hindus themselves must realize their mistake and treat all equal. This very behavior too led to the death of Sanskrit too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prakrit was the local language talked by Indians in the North and Dravidian languages like Tamil were talked by people  in South, but Aryans wanted to be different, they want to keep themselves above all and invented an artificial language called Sanskrit which was used for nothing other than to show their superiority and maintain secrecy. Books about old Indian lives tell that even women in Brahmin homes were disalloved to speak Sanskrit because women were considered impure. Such was and possibly is their level of austerity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This also makes one thing clear, people of Aryan mindset can never fully rule India till the date Indians have rationalism and some sense of dignity left in them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Karunanidhi</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Would be happy if Nagaland banned God than Dog</title><link href="/2020/07/04/would-be-happy-if-nagaland-banned-god-than-dog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Would be happy if Nagaland banned God than Dog" /><published>2020-07-04T21:48:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-04T21:48:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/07/04/would-be-happy-if-nagaland-banned-god-than-dog</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/04/would-be-happy-if-nagaland-banned-god-than-dog.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/7/78/A_couple_in_traditional_attire.jpg/367px-A_couple_in_traditional_attire.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a plan to travel to India’s north east to eat dog. The meat served in Ambattur, Chennai, mostly in cheap mutton briyani there may be dog meat, I had eaten it, but to get real taste of Dog, I always wanted to travel to India’s north east. China would have been better, but travel inside India would make good economics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had been chased by dogs when young, and even now stray and neighbors dogs wake me up by random barks when I am sleeping. It irritates me. I wanted to have my vengeance on canniness, may be I already had and do not know, but eating dogs meat and knowing it I ate it will give a soul satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who are shrugging and feeling uncomfortable, think what you had been eating in last Ramzan or Eid? The price of goat had soared so much, the tender meat u had in briyani and the thing you had tasted in your haleem could be a cat meat mixed with goat. Nothing happened after eating that, it’s perfectly okay. In fact a good diet consists of variety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What many remote communities still preserve, the diversity of food, we have lost. We just come to rely upon rice, wheat and chicken for all our main food. Pathetic are our lives. I live just somewhat 10 Kms from the Irular community who eat tasty roasted rats, but I find no shops here selling them. We have tricked ourselves into thinking rat meat is not fit for our culture, and worst we are poisoning their cuisine with our edible habits. One of their kid can have nice 10 roasted rats a day and feel filled with almost no cost, but we want to make him an idiot, and make him order food online, and he would spend about 500/- just to get his stomach half full during lunch. We call that civilized and development! And we feel superior about it!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming back to Nagaland. I couldn’t believe they bowed into such a thing, and made themselves believe eating dog is wrong, when it’s perfectly okay to eat cow, goat, chicken and others. I simply don’t understand what’s special in dog. In fact dog is a highly dumbed and tamed version of wolf. Humans can’t tolerate a wolf because of it’s intelligence, just like most bosses can’t tolerate a intelligent and questioning employee, but are okay with goats. Pigs and cows are far intelligent than dogs, yet we eat them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish food revolution takes place in India. We must consume variety of protein sources, be it dog, cow, kittens, bats, ant eater or what ever. Just limiting to few foods is not a healthy practice, and in times of crisis where one food gets almost wiped out, having limited sources of food will put country in strain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish the world turns to eating insects as well. It’s far better for the health of this planet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Acxbx-DUkL4?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/chennai/chennai-disappearing-cats-may-end-up-in-a-plate-of-biryani/articleshow/58310192.cms&quot;&gt;Chennai: Disappearing cats may end up in a plate of biryani&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How SpaceX Will make entire world an I.T hub</title><link href="/technology/space/information%20technology/2020/07/03/how-spacex-will-make-entire-world-an-i-t-hub.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How SpaceX Will make entire world an I.T hub" /><published>2020-07-03T12:37:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-03T12:37:00+05:30</updated><id>/technology/space/information%20technology/2020/07/03/how-spacex-will-make-entire-world-an-i-t-hub</id><content type="html" xml:base="/technology/space/information%20technology/2020/07/03/how-spacex-will-make-entire-world-an-i-t-hub.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn57.androidauthority.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Space-X-falcon-heavy-space-rocket-Quad-HD-wallpapers-15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was small, the Tidel Park in Chennai was the thing, it was the place where the brainy lived and great innovations happened. It was difficult to purchase a computer, they were expensive, desktops were bulky, you cannot move them like laptops, internet was expensive. All these means one thing, only expensive enterprises could buy them and it was they who can run IT companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things changed, when I was in 3rd year of college I got a home computer, after sometime I got a dialup internet connection that connects via my phone line, it was provided by HCL. Then I progressed to BSNL and now I have direct fiber to my home offering about 5MB of download a second. That is in 250 seconds I can get a HD movie if all goes well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though those stuff looks impressive, they were done using cabling. This requires lot of manual work, lot of digging, stringing and connecting and so on. I’m in Chennai, which is an metro in India, think about Usilampatti, are we getting 24 hour power supply there? People over there enjoy a fiber connection? There will be at least 100’s of people who are more intelligent than me in Usilampatti, they can contribute to software better than me, but they are just there not getting power and not having internet and hence not practicing I.T as their profession. They must flee to a city, come out of their village comfort zone, brave an unknown, spend a lot for lodging, food, just to get started and keep going.  If given the right tools they can code one tenth of my cost and still produce better software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suppose assume they get good quality power, which is still a miracle in India, they can buy a SpaceX receiver which is said to be a size of pizza box, this will connect to one of 12,000 satellites SpaceX is launching to provide the whole globe with Internet. Say that almost all people from that unconnected region get internet and they start to compete with me, then either I must improve my quality, reduce cost or something. The end product is better and cheaper software to the client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really envy and respect Elon musk and his vision. It’s good, great, grand and sometimes foolish. If Star Link, SpaceX plan to provide whole Earth internet goes by plan and possibly unhindered by politics and management, we can see a explosion of software development. I hope it succeeds soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am happy the way tech is progressing. Before, only few powerful and rich can hold it and boast about it then, now almost all can do it because barrier of entry is decreasing rapidly. Very soon I feel I.T hubs concentrated at few points will make no sense; almost everyone can work from anywhere; even if one goes on camping all one needs to carry a solar power pack and this pizza box that will give you a SpaceX Star Link connection to the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this myth of software developers are doing something great, and they must be seen as bigger than life too will disappear. During my Grandparents time, having a B.A or having some form of education was a big thing. Possibly even schooling was a big thing then. Those who knew to read and write were respected, look up to, and they earned more than average. Today you get Engineering or Doctor degree it’s no big deal. But starting and running a software company is seen as a big thing, but it isn’t. Once people start gaining knowledge and know about it, then thousands of new software companies and mostly importantly freelancers will pop up. That’s how the world should be, more democratic.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Tamilnadu teaches India?</title><link href="/2020/06/29/what-tamilnadu-teaches-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Tamilnadu teaches India?" /><published>2020-06-29T09:42:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-29T09:42:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/06/29/what-tamilnadu-teaches-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/06/29/what-tamilnadu-teaches-india.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;we-are-historically-corrupt--casteist&quot;&gt;We are historically corrupt &amp;amp; Casteist&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/6052/6322071540_2bbf975b27_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An Auvaiyaar song goes that there are two types of castes in this world, one is the higher caste which has the heart to give and help, and another is a lower caste which is stingy. But it says one is a higher caste only if one gives in a right way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long long ago people were giving wealth in a wrong way too, that is they were bribing. That’s why she explicitly mentions we must give in a right way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The poem also talks about caste, it says there are only two castes, that is she means to say to the people please leave your caste system and just look at people as they belong to these two castes. This means back then Tamils had the cancer of caste right in their nerves and blood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;corruption-without-corruption&quot;&gt;Corruption without corruption&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://newsd.in/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Karunanidhi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Karunanidhi is considered as the father of corruption in India. It’s not because he and his family are corrupt and introduced dynastic politics in Tamilnadu, but he can be openly corrupt and escape with it. Back in Indira days, Indra tried to crush him by exposing his corruption, but the officials appointed by her gave up and termed the kind of corruption that goes on here as scientifically corrupt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though some in India are getting caught and facing arrest because of corruption, it’s this DMK template of corruption that many follow and escape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;you-can-get-away-with-any-magnitude-of-corruption&quot;&gt;You can get away with any magnitude of corruption&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://english.cdn.zeenews.com/sites/default/files/2017/12/21/648968-untitled-design-56.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2-G corruption may amount to 1,70,000 crores, an unimaginable sum. Raja and Kanimozhi (daughter of scientific looter) were charged in that, but they escaped just like that. How? Okay if no money was looted why did the CAG go so wrong and why there is no investigation against the CAG? You wasted so much resources of our nation to bring false charges on someone! Why there were mysterious suicides in Tamilnadu of people who might be related to this case? We simply don’t have the answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;proven-corrupt-can-be-the-god-mother&quot;&gt;Proven corrupt can be the God Mother&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.indianexpress.com/2014/09/jaya759.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jayalalitha is a proven criminal, yet the state of Tamilnadu is running a criminal government saying that this is Jaya’s government. That is they claim that a proven criminal is the moral head of state and whole India watches on as though…. fuckin God what to say about these Indians?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder if I can run a government saying that Kasab, Osama are the moral leaders, I might still get away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;you-are-a-shit-unless-you-are-rich-and-powerful&quot;&gt;You are a shit unless you are rich and powerful&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.newindianexpress.com/uploads/user/imagelibrary/2020/6/10/w900X450/J_Anbazhagan_EPS_Photo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When people die of Corona, their bodies are treated like shit. Literally they are just tossed into a large pit with a bleach and it’s covered. one might say that the government employees who handle the body are afraid of the infection are are too  afraid to touch the body. Okay fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a DMK leader called J.Anbhazagan who died, and he died of Corona. His body was preserved properly, put into a nice coffin, was lowered into his grave slowly and with care. This proves that if you are a commoner in Tamilnadu, perhaps in India you would get no respect. You have to be rich and powerful to be treated as human.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;its-okay-to-be-a-psychopath&quot;&gt;It’s okay to be a psychopath&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hwnews.in/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/tamil-nadu-960x540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two traders in Tamilnadu (pictured above) who were tortured and killed in Tutthukudi district. Gossip says that the police who killed him might be of different caste. Any way, the way in which the police killed him was horrific. Iron tipped lathis were sent into their butt, their hair pulled out of their chest, they were beaten like hell and so on. This incident shook the nation. But take it from me the police guys who had done it won’t be hanged, mostly they will come out unscaled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Psychopath Tamilnadu Police is there to protect Psychopaths and they will.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We are historically corrupt &amp;amp; Casteist</summary></entry></feed>