<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-02-14T20:38:59+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Ancient religious knowledge</title><link href="/2023/02/14/ancient-religious-knowledge.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ancient religious knowledge" /><published>2023-02-14T19:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-14T19:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/14/ancient-religious-knowledge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/14/ancient-religious-knowledge.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeifyyvt2hs55cfd6gwpe7mljfchdlpeeppnvjj2yo7nir2pfnpuwty &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The lion in parliament hunting Adani</title><link href="/2023/02/11/the-lion-in-parliament-hunting-adani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The lion in parliament hunting Adani" /><published>2023-02-11T11:44:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-11T11:44:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/11/the-lion-in-parliament-hunting-adani</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/11/the-lion-in-parliament-hunting-adani.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeia56vdus65fnuvgmacn5zly7xbhybbvffiijppwg2i72fuvbj5bxu &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vote for Naam Tamizhar in Erode East</title><link href="/2023/02/06/vote-for-naam-tamizhar-in-erode-east.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vote for Naam Tamizhar in Erode East" /><published>2023-02-06T11:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-06T11:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/06/vote-for-naam-tamizhar-in-erode-east</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/06/vote-for-naam-tamizhar-in-erode-east.html">&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_pCUrA-v3sA?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently a bunch of North Indians had chased and bashed Tamils in Tiruppur. Tamilnadu government says there is some fault on Tamils too. In recent Coimbatore bomb blast too DMK people claimed that it was a cylinder that went off, they defended the terrorists in open sun without shame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can’t trust DMK, all they need is to make Udhayanidhi Stalin as CM,a and after that Inbanidhi. To achieve that, they would let the northerners occupy and destroy us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;joining-hands-with-congress&quot;&gt;Joining hands with Congress&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreibzmx4dlw4cmq5k3gl4yisg5s6geytajrjvaauebj5fvkt4bgiajq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK has joined hands with Congress which is a northerner’s party. The Congress needs Hindi heartland votes. DMK needs support of a pan India party so that they won’t get persecuted in criminal and corruption cases. So DMK will behave like a Hindi party. No doubt about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus DMK and Congress want dynatic politics and never will they want to put rightful ruler on throne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dynastic-politics&quot;&gt;Dynastic Politics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/4/46/E._V._K._S._Elangovan_at_Marriage_Function_12.jpg/1429px-E._V._K._S._Elangovan_at_Marriage_Function_12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;E.V.K.S Elangovan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK is a pure dynastic party. When India got independent, I think we made 100’s of kingdoms secede and we made it into one India. When Kingdoms lost power, naturally those people were liberated from dynastic rule and rule of democracy blossomed. But DMK, Congress and even other parties are brought in dynastic politics withing democracy which I think is ultra dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Erode east does not belong to Elangovans family. I am sorry for his son’s death, this has left Erode East a void constituency, but I wish Congress was able to find a non dynastic person who truely love the people of Erode than to make a dynastic one stand in elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To his credit I must say Elangovan is a very good person comparatively to other scoundrels in politics. But the way his family (Elangovan and his living son), tried to have them nominated by congress for Erode East leaves me with bitter feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-not-aiadmk&quot;&gt;Why not AIADMK?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Palanisamy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Edapaadi Palani Samy&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t like AIADMK because it’s led by EPS. He conducted Thoothukudi massacre and AIADMK as a party watched rather than impeach him. Kodanaadu people have died under mysterious circumstances and we public have no information what’s going on. May be EPS is a super killer who knows to get away with things. We must be very careful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;vote-for-naam-tamizhar&quot;&gt;Vote for Naam Tamizhar&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/14/NAAM_TAMILAR_PARTY_LOGO_MODERN.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not believe Seeman, the leader of Naam Tamizhar is a pure person. Savukku Shankar has laid charges against him, Seeman was smart, visited Savulku in prison and stood support, now Savukku does not speak about Seeman. Maybe both have become corrupt now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/w2DNBj7abJo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further more even if Naam Tamizhar is corrupt, and they get elected, they must build connections to start looting en masse, this will give us some breathing space. They might not be as efficient looters as DMK and Congress people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to purity of soul, Naam Tamizhar is okay comparatively. I am not telling there are no robbers, scoundrels, looters, money hungry businessmen in it. I just don’t know who are there in the party. But relatively it’s pure. May be if DMK and Congress are HIV infection for India, Naam Tamizhar is Tuberculosis, maybe it will take more time to kill India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naam Tamizhar has never kept alliance with other parties that have proven or unproven corruption record. I see that as a Major plus. They speak against Noth Indians aggression against us. DMK needs Congress and ADMK needs BJP so they won’t stand for Tamils, wheras naam Tamizhar will as they do not bow to North India. I see some form of Tamil spirit left in Naam Tamizhar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a citzen of india, as a Tamil who feel we must be protected in our last refuge (we must not become like Srilankan Tamils), I urge the people of Erode East to vote for Naam Tamizhar. I am not saying they will give a golden rule, but at least we can start to escape from Hindi aggression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2zTOh2XRtwo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">USA plans war with China</title><link href="/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="USA plans war with China" /><published>2023-02-03T09:31:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-03T09:31:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeicyczvr4fks6pfm75xrq3crperwl3odipurlzqqlekg6emyszhdsy &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/dBQlE&quot;&gt;https://yu7.in/dBQlE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">People who know to code should be in the I.T industry</title><link href="/2023/02/02/people-who-know-to-code-should-be-in-the-i-t-industry.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="People who know to code should be in the I.T industry" /><published>2023-02-02T17:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-02T17:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/02/people-who-know-to-code-should-be-in-the-i-t-industry</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/02/people-who-know-to-code-should-be-in-the-i-t-industry.html">&lt;p&gt;Somehow passionate people who are greedy for money and power make it to the top. It’s a severe failure of human society. Politics in all its forms has failed humanity as people with compassion and brains are sidelined, and greedy ones take the throne. Just as I blog now, the speakers of mosque nearby blasts confirming that thinkers and rationalist are sidelined, and we still believe in God, blind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The triumph of the fools hasn’t left my business coding alone. Just last week a Machine Learning project my friend was involved was asked by the client (who claims to be an owner of a tech company for decade of more) to train a neural network without data. Imagine such person running a company. He is definitely a fool, and hence he is a BJP supporter. No wonder about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow in my industry, most coding companies are inefficient, like battle commanders who never face bullet, they are led by people who never face code every day. This is bad, really really bad. Now take a look at what I got on LinkedIn:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreid4uxgfs3q5db7qcvungcl2cmns25njqybkppz6j3yjk2y5vf5ife&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, the truth is LinkedIn is occupied by management idiots, so one should not be surprised by this message, but as you can see, a services company, just because it wants to earn money, has made it look like coding is a complex thing. Just like Boeing &amp;amp; Douglas for all these decades, and even today make it look like access to space is complex, then came SpaceX.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Somehow passionate people who are greedy for money and power make it to the top. It’s a severe failure of human society. Politics in all its forms has failed humanity as people with compassion and brains are sidelined, and greedy ones take the throne. Just as I blog now, the speakers of mosque nearby blasts confirming that thinkers and rationalist are sidelined, and we still believe in God, blind.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Meherbai Tata</title><link href="/2023/02/01/meherbai-tata.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Meherbai Tata" /><published>2023-02-01T12:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-01T12:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/01/meherbai-tata</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/01/meherbai-tata.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeid2ff7cos3dj5tadd4b2bzimlocnj2zuurpdlezisjt3yfv76mtna.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Meherbai Tata&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you zoom this photo, you will see a huge diamond worn around her neck. This is a 245 carat Jubilee Diamond and was twice as large as the famous Kohinoor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lady in this picture is Meherbai Tata who was the daughter-in-law of Jamshedji Tata and the wife of his eldest son Sir Dorabji Tata.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the year, 1924, when there was recession due to First World War, Tata Steel did not have the money to pay salaries to the employees. Meherbai had mortgaged her priceless Jubilee Diamond in Imperial Bank, so that the employees could get regular salaries and the company continues to run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After her untimely death from blood cancer, Sir Dorabji Tata established the Tata Memorial Cancer Research Foundation by selling this diamond for better treatment of cancer patients in India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies like Google, Meta, Amazon, Microsoft and many others which are laying off their employees should learn from this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/DQTdq&quot;&gt;https://yu7.in/DQTdq&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Meherbai Tata</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Saw this video when I was wondering why I am meeting so many psychopaths in my life</title><link href="/2023/01/29/saw-this-video-when-i-was-wondering-why-i-am-meeting-so-many-psychopaths-in-my-life.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Saw this video when I was wondering why I am meeting so many psychopaths in my life" /><published>2023-01-29T10:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-29T10:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/29/saw-this-video-when-i-was-wondering-why-i-am-meeting-so-many-psychopaths-in-my-life</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/29/saw-this-video-when-i-was-wondering-why-i-am-meeting-so-many-psychopaths-in-my-life.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeiatirewzelv5chi2nkegejcc5qqbyhhpoh2lezcwlfjtbvvprefb4.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DMK rule assured</title><link href="/2023/01/24/dmk-rule-assured.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DMK rule assured" /><published>2023-01-24T01:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-24T01:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/24/dmk-rule-assured</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/24/dmk-rule-assured.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/5/5e/Dravida_Munnetra_Kazhagam_logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s 12:55 in the morning when I am blogging. At 12:10 AM power went off in Sithalapakkam. I famously heard our speaker Appavu say during R.N.Ravi issue, he said that Tamil Nadu does not compete with other states in India, it competes with developed countries likes South Korea, Malaysia and so on… Tamil Nadu has surely beaten these nations in one thing, power cuts. The power came just now, and I don’t know when it will be cut again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason when the power went off, dogs started to bark, and I kinda lost my wish to sleep. We in India say that we will get rid of Pakistani jihadist, Chinese invaders and so on, in reality, we can’t even get rid of stray dogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I truly wonder how Stalin, Jayalalitha, Karunanidhi and even may be M.G.R called themselves peoples leader if they couldn’t get rid of stray dogs? Maybe they could call themselves as dogs leader. It for this kind of people we have built moseleums in Marina beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish we could kill dogs, but it’s said that PETA has powerful people. I think it has wife’s of industrialists, judges and so on. So if you kill a dog, those women will boast in their clubs about how they enforced law on a person and how they are torturing him because he killed a dog. This though is a gossip I came across, and am not sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So nearly an hour of power cut. I had thought for some time that DMK has lost power and ADMK was ruling Tamil Nadu, now this power cut assures me that DMK is still in power thus we may be powerless for some time to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">There is some magic in pure gaana and folk singers</title><link href="/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There is some magic in pure gaana and folk singers" /><published>2023-01-21T08:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-21T08:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/Delgv&quot;&gt;https://yu7.in/Delgv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wbYG8T80SOk?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the song above, it was created by Reguman and his team, but you have to listen hard to understand it. It’s a pure Tamil song, but may be the pronunciation of Ragumaan and the girls that sing look like they are foreigners who have landed in India just now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now listen to the sing below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zuVV9Y55gvc?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything in this song is easily understandable, there is nothing you need to concentrate hard. As a Tamil, this song is so understandable to me. It’s a pure Tamil song too. Maybe the singer of this song especially the women could be a pure Tamil girl, possibly a folk singer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now listen to this song:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9PYbz-UpG5Y?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a gaana song, may be because I was born and brought up in Chennai, every bit of this song is understandable and I could grasp it’s meaning just like that without any concentration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is something magical in gaana and folk singers, or may be there is some magic in folk and gaana songs. These songs ae highly understandable, needs no concentration. It’s sad that we have lot of song sung by non-native Tamil speakers, or people who have stayed away from our culture a long time, they suck compared to folk and gaana singers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now here are two songs:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gpVA5mx73UE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OxDKZ6WfD7M?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a Tamil, decide which is pronounced well and is easily understandable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Short Link: https://yu7.in/Delgv</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The lightness of being a freelancer</title><link href="/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The lightness of being a freelancer" /><published>2023-01-18T09:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-18T09:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer.html">&lt;p&gt;The kind of money we coders demand for quality means we can attract companies that make lot of money. Today if I generate billing for a project, small Indian companies run away. They ask an estimate, and they disappear once I give it to them. The result is people like me who value quality of code are stuck with big corps who like to pay us regular salary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I was working on a ticket, it was a complex one, and I didn’t have an idea how the business worked. All simple assumptions I made became false, my pull requests were rejected. Stumbling and fumbling I thought I would finish my code a day ago when disaster struck. I fell ill. I was forced to take 36 hours or so off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In corporate environments we have to show progress in every scrum call. We have to speak something. You will be paid no matter what, you will be terminated if the business don’t like you. You will be compared relatively with other people. Maybe you might come under a stare of a manager who had bad time with his family today, and your name will be struck off. You never know when the lightning bolt will strike. It’s capitalism to the max.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I were a pure freelancer, I could have had many clients, so loosing one may be a hit, but it would be cushioned by similar paying people. It would be like loosing 20% of your revenue rather than loosing 50%. Plus I can tell to my client to delay my payments till my work is done, or reduce my pay or increase my pay, the billing is what I generate. This justification of self evaluation and lightness of being honest and frank is absent in corporate world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust is very important in doing business. Entire economics is trust. In corporate world, you have no clue how the upper management trusts you, and they don’t connect with people who do the actual work. In freelancing this is opposite, you can gain trust of people and feedback very easily. That adds lightness to life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or may be this is corporate work, maybe I have to be okay with drawing money when I am inefficient, and should be content when I am efficient and the corporate does not want to hike pay for me for what ever reasons that comes to their mind.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The kind of money we coders demand for quality means we can attract companies that make lot of money. Today if I generate billing for a project, small Indian companies run away. They ask an estimate, and they disappear once I give it to them. The result is people like me who value quality of code are stuck with big corps who like to pay us regular salary.</summary></entry></feed>