<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-16T22:43:16+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Ruby 2.7 and Rails Thoughts</title><link href="/2020/01/16/ruby-2-7-and-rails-thoughts.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ruby 2.7 and Rails Thoughts" /><published>2020-01-16T22:43:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-01-16T22:43:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/01/16/ruby-2-7-and-rails-thoughts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/01/16/ruby-2-7-and-rails-thoughts.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://acupofrails.files.wordpress.com/2013/05/ror-cover-girl.png?w=620&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Ruby 2.7 is there and its fast. This very blog is powered by Jekyll and Ruby 2.7 and I can see its speed. I am happy about it, you too will be happy about it if you aren’t worried about this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;/home/ak/.rvm/gems/ruby-2.7.0/gems/activerecord-6.0.2.1/lib/active_record/persistence.rb:503: warning: Using the last argument as keyword parameters is deprecated; maybe ** should be added to the call
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;which is nothing worry some now. Matz doesn’t like keyword arguments, the way it was there till Ruby 2.6, checkout this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2g9R7PUCEXo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails is fast too. I can see it in Rails 6 + Ruby 2.7, but this bloody webpacker. I am using Rails for too long, first it was prototype and RJS and it was really cool, I loved it. Then came this bloody jQuery, and Rails move to it, we need to learn it, okay that went well, now this webpacker. Javascript ecosystem is still amateur and evolving and its causing headaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent good amount of time knowing why we need webpacker, got jQuery, propperJS, and bootstrap working. Damn. And I did it all without knowing what I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am very unsatisfied with my work, and I am now working for my own product. But once I get my hands really on webpacker I think I might appreciate with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I miss the days of Volt framework when Rubyist were promised that they never need to lay hands on Javascript. I am really sad the way Opal is not integrated into Rails. We need to put up with amateurism and changing mind of Javascript community, and just as Javascript comes of age, it could be wiped out by WASM. Well….&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I Follow This Method Whenever My Brain Is struggling With A Complicated Programming Task.</title><link href="/programming/2020/01/12/i-follow-this-method-whenever-my-brain-is-struggling-with-a-complicated-programming-task.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Follow This Method Whenever My Brain Is struggling With A Complicated Programming Task." /><published>2020-01-12T12:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-01-12T12:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/2020/01/12/i-follow-this-method-whenever-my-brain-is-struggling-with-a-complicated-programming-task</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/2020/01/12/i-follow-this-method-whenever-my-brain-is-struggling-with-a-complicated-programming-task.html">&lt;p&gt;As a software engineer, I felt stuck countless times during project development. As a programmer, you might have experienced this feeling yourself, I bet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless if it is work-related or in a personal endeavour, you usually start projects very enthusiastically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, when a specific task feels too overwhelming, you tend to lose focus, procrastinate, and sometimes even question your very decision of pursuing a career in your current field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to share with you a simple way that will greatly help you overcome technically-challenging tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether developing software or trying to solve coding challenges, applying this method will help you finish your most complicated tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I call this method: Elementary Task In Progress (ETIP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do I mean by elementary? By definition, an elementary task is a very simple and basic task that is hardly broken down into smaller, easier steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The task in progress should always be elementary so that its execution is straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me clarify this further by asking you a question: “What is the most basic step you can do to get closer to finishing your complicated task?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Identify that step. Turn it into a task on its own. Work on it. That’s your ETIP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are stuck in your project because the task in progress is too complicated, chances are, your task is not an ETIP. Turn it into an ETIP by applying the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Break the task in progress into simpler, more basic steps.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For each individual step, break it up even further until it is in its most elementary form. This is your ETIP.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pick the first ETIP and start working on it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Once done with your first ETIP, move to the next one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Never work on a task that is not an ETIP!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, the task in progress should always be so elementary that its execution is straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you feel that your next task is too complicated? Time to break it down into ETIPs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use the ETIP method every time a task feels too overwhelming. Break your task into basic and simple steps that you can execute easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it is almost unavoidable that you will encounter challenging and complex projects that are made up of complicated tasks, you should not work on a task unless you make sure its completion is simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ETIP method will help you to always progress in completing your projects no matter how big the challenges you are faced with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this advice will be helpful to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extracted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/learnprogramming/comments/encuei/i_follow_this_method_whenever_my_brain_is/&quot;&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">As a software engineer, I felt stuck countless times during project development. As a programmer, you might have experienced this feeling yourself, I bet.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gold Winner Still Polluting Sithalapakkam?</title><link href="/2020/01/12/goldwinner-still-polluting-sithalapakkam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gold Winner Still Polluting Sithalapakkam?" /><published>2020-01-12T08:27:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-01-12T08:27:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/01/12/goldwinner-still-polluting-sithalapakkam</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/01/12/goldwinner-still-polluting-sithalapakkam.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.etimg.com/thumb/msid-58721533,width-672,resizemode-4,imglength-326049/news/politics-and-nation/income-tax-department-raids-edible-oil-majors-premises/income-tax-departmenr-raids-edible-oil-majors-premises.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today morning, I went to my terrace for a walk. Apparently roads in Sithalapakkam are so bad that you can’t walk in them. Sithalapakkam main road is okay, but it has got not platform. With no police presence here you have lot of rash drivers, you will see drivers nearly grazing pedestrians here. You would walk, suddenly yoll see a car or bike heading towards you, yoll stop in confusion and at the last movement their vector would turn away from you and you will be relieved. So walking on Sithalapakkam main road is tough. Many many accidents have taken place and will take place too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay back to the story, today morning I went to my terrace for a walk, and that smell of oil fumes and something dusty hanging in the air filled up my nose. I need to walk to get my brains working, that what earns me, makes me write this blog, and so on. But these smells in air emitted by Gold Winner oil company spoiled it. Today the smell was mild, but on some other days it would be too great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So how this would happen?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the process of heating oil or something, this company releases smoke via chimney. Now when the air near the ground is cold the air coming out of the chimney cools off rapidly, if the air above the ground say a 100 meters above is hot, this toxic air because of its low temperature and high density won’t rise up and would hang near the ground. So the pollution levels in the surrounding area increases dramatically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes when going out of Sithalapakkam, while driving near Gold Winner oil company I do find that thick air, kind of dusty and oily to smell. In fact this happens when school kids go to their school in morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Solution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well you see politicians going around in Sithalapakkam giving out new calendars, giving out free rice and other stuff to people as though they really care (none of us questions how they got the money, that’s a different story), why cant they drive around Sithalapakkam and surrounding and find that this is happening?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How come they are so concerned about us and so so ignorant of this pollution problem? What shuts off their nose and duty when they are in this area? People should think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have got pollution monitoring station here and there, it is in news now ad then, there is an industry in Sithalapakkam, is there a pollution monitoring system around? If yes where can we the resident’s  of this are able to check its reading?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think politicians and bureaucrats will help us, because something else might be helping them to have a great life. They could be getting enough to buy millions of air purifiers for their home, that’s why I have taken up this blog. Its you people who can help us the residence of Sithalapakkam. Don’t buy Gold Winner. If you are an actor and are been called upon to represent this company please don’t so it, or tell them about this pollution problem and deny them your representation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you quit them, our air get little bit pure, our kids might not suffer respiratory disease tomorrow, our old may not die early due to pollution, people allergic to smoke and having other respiratory ailments might find their health improved. I can have a good walk and improve my health and brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s up to you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Python Projects for Beginners - a great book</title><link href="/programming/python/computer%20science/data%20science/book%20review/2020/01/03/python-projects-for-beginners-a-great-book.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Python Projects for Beginners - a great book" /><published>2020-01-03T09:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-01-03T09:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/python/computer%20science/data%20science/book%20review/2020/01/03/python-projects-for-beginners-a-great-book</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/python/computer%20science/data%20science/book%20review/2020/01/03/python-projects-for-beginners-a-great-book.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/148425354X/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;creativeASIN=148425354X&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=mindaslab-20&amp;amp;linkId=a0710f637e35ea0b55266870fe169588&quot;&gt;&lt;img border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;ASIN=148425354X&amp;amp;ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;ID=AsinImage&amp;amp;WS=1&amp;amp;Format=_SL250_&amp;amp;tag=mindaslab-20&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=mindaslab-20&amp;amp;l=am2&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;a=148425354X&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;border:none !important; margin:0px !important;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To become a data scientist Python is essential. Though there are other languages, Python leads it. Not just for Data Science and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.blog.pythonlibrary.org/2019/04/11/python-used-to-take-photo-of-black-hole/&quot;&gt;imaging the black hole&lt;/a&gt;, Python can be used for the following things:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data Science&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Embedded system programming like RaspberryPi&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;PyGame to develop games&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Web development with Django, Flask, Pyramid etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And many more. In fact Python is becoming ubiquitous. There are many many books for Python, I have read many of them, but to learn Python one stands out, that is &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2ZLfEUo&quot;&gt;Python Projects for Beginners&lt;/a&gt;. This book is divides into ten week course. Each week is divided into 5 days (Monday - Friday) and if you can spend 1 or 2 hours every day, you can be very proficient with Python. This book never goes into unnecessary complications. The author has got the real art of writing in him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good book needs to teach the necessary, that necessary should enable a student to think and build things on his own. It should not clutter one with unnecessary details, and this book does just that. This book would be a great buy and you will see that you have got value worth paid back once you have read it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:120px;height:240px;&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;OneJS=1&amp;amp;Operation=GetAdHtml&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;source=ac&amp;amp;ref=tf_til&amp;amp;ad_type=product_link&amp;amp;tracking_id=mindaslab-20&amp;amp;marketplace=amazon&amp;amp;region=US&amp;amp;placement=148425354X&amp;amp;asins=148425354X&amp;amp;linkId=ef25f5fc6bd80cee6db6b47e479410cb&amp;amp;show_border=false&amp;amp;link_opens_in_new_window=false&amp;amp;price_color=333333&amp;amp;title_color=0066c0&amp;amp;bg_color=ffffff&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rails How to Use Greater Than / Less Than in Active Record where Statements</title><link href="/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/2020/01/01/rails-how-to-use-greater-than-less-than-in-active-record-where-statements.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rails How to Use Greater Than / Less Than in Active Record where Statements" /><published>2020-01-01T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-01-01T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/2020/01/01/rails-how-to-use-greater-than-less-than-in-active-record-where-statements</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/2020/01/01/rails-how-to-use-greater-than-less-than-in-active-record-where-statements.html">&lt;p&gt;For example, if I want to find all users created within the last week, I would ask for all users from my &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;User&lt;/code&gt; model in which the column &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;updated_at&lt;/code&gt; is greater than 1 week ago, or &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;1.week.ago&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;1-using-rubys-infinity-range-best&quot;&gt;1. Using Ruby’s Infinity Range (Best)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Rails 5+ and Ruby 2.6+, the infinity range can be used like so:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;User&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;where&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;created_at: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;week&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;ago&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t upgraded to Ruby 2.6 yet, you can specify the end of the range as the constant &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Float::INFINITY&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;User&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;where&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;created_at: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;week&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;ago&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Float&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;INFINITY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the best option because it is the closest syntax to actuality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;From 1 week ago until infinity == greater than or equal to 1 week ago
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also doesn’t have any of the caveats that using a raw string has (explained later in this post)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;2-using-active-records-arel-table&quot;&gt;2. Using Active Record’s Arel Table&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Utilizing arel directly, we can signal to ActiveRecord the logical SQL we want to do functionally:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;User&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;where&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;User&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;arel_table&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:created_at&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;gt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;week&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;ago&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;))&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When faced with a challenging ActiveRecord Query that doesn’t fit into the core ruby-style syntax, I typically turn to Arel to provide me with a functional core and extra safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;3-using-a-raw-string-worst&quot;&gt;3. Using a Raw String (Worst)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In ActiveRecord, it’s possible to utilize a raw string to access sql’s interface directly, like so:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;User&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;where&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'users.created_at &amp;gt; ?'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;week&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;ago&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or even the keyword interpolation style:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;User&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;where&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'users.created_at &amp;gt; :after_date'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;after_date: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;week&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;ago&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this works, using SQL strings with ActiveRecord isn’t always the best due to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Higher risk of accidental sql injection vulnerabilities&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reduced database adapter compatibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">For example, if I want to find all users created within the last week, I would ask for all users from my User model in which the column updated_at is greater than 1 week ago, or 1.week.ago.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Communist are Right and I.T workers are wrong</title><link href="/2019/12/26/communist-are-right-and-i-t-workers-are-wrong.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Communist are Right and I.T workers are wrong" /><published>2019-12-26T21:41:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-26T21:41:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/12/26/communist-are-right-and-i-t-workers-are-wrong</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/12/26/communist-are-right-and-i-t-workers-are-wrong.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://yourdost-blog-images.s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/27174214/f2fu-differencebetweenfiredlaidofresignation-1-640x350.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am out of a Job. On November I asked my company whether my job was at risk as I was not treated properly, I was told that my job was secure and was assigned to a new project, on Dec 24 I was thrown out. My bank balance is running low, I need to be given 2 months of salary if the company fires me, and I don’t think I am getting it. In fact this month’s salary will be put in next month 15th. Most probably I wont get the full salary, it could be a menial amount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon after I got fired, many people from the company contacted me, they said they too felt a risk of loosing job. They were unhappy how the company was run, how the decisions are taken without any consultation. They also expressed worry about the best minds, the thinkers and outspoken ones got fired. Strange still some are rallying me to form a company. Classic Indian and Middle Eastern tale isn’t it? People suffer and people rally behind a hero, its Krishna in India, Jesus and Muhammad in the Middle east.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, its nice to feel like a hero, but the bosses you hate too were hero’s and you rallied behind them one day. They are the ones you loved one day, today you love me, and what’s the guarantee that I wouldn’t be another M.G.R, Karunanidhi or Jayalalitha who looted this people? What’s the guarantee that I won’t think cheap of you one day after you have earned me? Krishna and others are tales, they are mythical beings, I am a man, to know more about me read &lt;em&gt;The Selfish Gene&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To realize your (worker’s) rights, and for you not to be treated as shit, there is a tried and tested way. It’s called a Union. Let’s say that a bright mind in my company is shown the door, this what would happen in union, in it we all act as one, we all walk out of the company and demand justice. Is that happening in any I.T company? If you don’t have the bravery to unionize and stand for other’s pain? Then why you feel bad when you suffer the same pain? Just take as a part of life and move on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are brought up as spineless cowards, let’s admit it. I myself have seen many bright minds been shown the door and I haven’t bothered. We have been thought to survive and go about our business even if our neighbors and coworkers are undergoing enormous torture. We studied Engineering to become rich and have a great life and not to be bothered about the wellness of our commune. We ran behind money, signed documents without reading, worried about ourselves and nothing else. Now when the evil ones rule us and strike us in an &lt;em&gt;adharma&lt;/em&gt; way we squeal. Well, squeal. That’s what non thinkers and cowards can do.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Gokulam Park Sabari Sucks</title><link href="/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/21/hotel-gokulam-park-sabari-sucks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Gokulam Park Sabari Sucks" /><published>2019-12-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/21/hotel-gokulam-park-sabari-sucks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/21/hotel-gokulam-park-sabari-sucks.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.trvl-media.com/hotels/2000000/1790000/1784600/1784528/46e7bf35_z.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, a bunch of people @ office wanted to go to an unknown and untested hotel to get drunk at night. I wasn’t so sure of the idea, I just want to drive home and on the way have something, but those folks wanted to get drunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was in 50-50 mood. A friend of mine had taken me to a tea shop near Zeeshan and I had chicken sanwidch at lunch, I was kind a half to three quarter full, plus the new hotel my friends were calling for a drink was beyond tollgate and I had to waste Rs 54/- for that. Rs 50/- would be equivalent to 10Km of my drive from office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I joined this office as a consultant, I was promised work from home, liberal work ethics, but now they seem to suspect me for not working or something. I thought bad times had passed when my wife left me, then I had my partner in Trumatics who started yelling me, so I had to leave that company, and when I thought that I was in a good office at this one, and after few months of working, this boss too gets mad at me, he accuses me of taking more than 15 minutes to drink tea, and when I am not in office at 11 AM he gets upset. I have never seen this behaviour in good I.T company. Later to my happiness I found that he was behaving like this way to many other people, particularly to senior employees. So I am forced to spend a lot on fuel as my consultations is far far off from city and I must be there unless I am ill or something. So spending another Rs 54/- on a toll / travel did not look wise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then one of my friends popped in and offered me a bike ride and I was in. No need to pay tolls. The hotel we went was Gokulam Park Sabari. There was a bar at the terrace, the ambience was good and clean. There wasn’t many people there. It was a bar cum restaurant. Out of the dozen of us, only three drank. I ordered a mutton briyani, a tandoori platter, asked the waiter what he would have if he were me, he said chilli eggs and I ordered that one too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dish took long time to come, really long, somewhere between 20 minutes to half an hour. the chilli eggs came first and they were good. Then came the briyani, it was kind of tasteless, but you could eat it if you don’t mind rough meat. The raitha was good, it was made of cucumber as onions can be eaten by only the rich in India, the brinjal curry was not good, it was like brinjal’s in some kind of tasteless sauce, but they weren’t too bad either. Then came the tandoori platter, the chicken in it seemed to smell like it was soaked in some kind of medicine or something, it smelled like some kind of chemical. The prawns were okay, and so was the minced mutton tandoori, but the fish smelled, I even thought it was rotten. I just don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once eaten, the bad smells stayed in my mouth and it would stick, I just lost appetite for eating and lost happiness. I love real good food and people who make it, but this was hell. I know in pubs attached to restaurants they serve low quality food because people who drink sans the sense of taste and they would eat almost anything without complaint. Here too that seems true, but the taste was real worst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you had put some one in prison and want him to suffer, I guess you can serve him this food. One would realise that life has no meaning after eating this one. Well that’s the truth, but realising it mellows your enjoyment. I did not even eat a third of what I should have eaten. I just sat there enjoying the breeze at their terrace pub. Looks like the drunkards in our office did not seem to mind the waste food they were served.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hard part is not that. I had gone to the hotel expecting to have great food and great time, so I had my hunger raising, when I drove back home beyond 10:30 PM, all others food shops were closed and I had to sleep kind of hungry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How I see non Chennai people</title><link href="/2019/12/10/how-i-see-non-chennai-people.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I see non Chennai people" /><published>2019-12-10T19:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-10T19:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/12/10/how-i-see-non-chennai-people</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/12/10/how-i-see-non-chennai-people.html">&lt;p&gt;I am born and brought up in Chennai. I travel almost to no other place because I find all I want here. In fact my mission is to never leave my bedroom. I want to earn from my bed, buy suff from my bed, its all possible with todays technology. Trying to be a non nomadic human has made me see people outside Chennai as some what different. They seem to look like weird animals to me. Here is what I found or think about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here when I say non Chennai, that person has come into Chennai, or is a resident of Chennai and visits his so called native. The pure Chennai people are those who have no native, do no visits to their natives so that they are not corrupted by outside Chennai values, and they do not associate with some other city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Their driving is crazy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, possibly driving in Chennai is crazy, so I find it crazy when some one from outside Chennai drives here. I found a vehicle with licence plate TN 76 V… and he was driving right into potholes while we skilfully avoided it. He also drove slow and would not let us pass him. He was such a dork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I must admit that the road from Sithalapakkam to Sirusseri has one of the worst potholes in India. I also have a feeling that ITEL bribes beuracrats and politicians to deliberately keep these roads in this condition, but we somehow find a way to avoid these potholes and drive without much complaint. We certainly don’t drive into it like other people who follow traffic rules do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Absolute no respect for women&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A strange thing about non Chennai people I find is, they have very little respect for women. A guy from Kerala who is my friend and resides in Sithalapakkam once asked “why are women are there on street?”. I thought something happened to his brain, if we certainly had flying cars and bikes, why do we need to use these damn streets? I thought.  But then after further conversation I found out that in his part of India women don’t go out after 6 PM or something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t imagine that kind of situation happening here. Perhaps if the Taliban or IS or some Kaliphate conquer’s Chennai that might happen, but here you can find women almost at any time on street, it’s definitely not looked in a bad way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Women smoke, I see lot of women in Tasmac Elite, I don’t think they are bad or immoral, women now are wearing dresses that are truly good to watch ;) and it’s good! They must be able to express themselves in the way they want to. That’s freedom. I don’t understand why non Chennai people find it hard to digest it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Family Values&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non Chennai people have high family values, possibly like Nithyandha’s followers have high value on him. This doesn’t mean that family members of non Chennai people are good, or non fraud’s or something. It’s just because kids born in non-Chennai families are trained to obey elders without questioning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Chennai people however won’t hesitate to question our own elders and parent’s We behave just like lord Karthikeyaa did with his family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tradition and belief in Gods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find both Chennai and non-Chennai people believe in God equally, but all friends I know do go to temples knowing that God is spoof, and they know that these traditions suck, but they do it because they do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For non Chennai people, tradition has a real value. I don’t know what exactly. It’s not about pleasing ones mom, wife or relatives, but it seems to be about them, they say it has real value. I don’t know if they are dumb or something, but they stick by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visiting Village&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup, no matter how crowded it is, non Chennai people visit their villages during festive season. Without seeing their native they are dead. They come to Chennai to earn, Chennai gives them everything they want, but it’s the village they want, but with their beautiful villages they cannot make money somehow but they must depend on this hellish Chennai. I find it ironic. They must be brave and kick Chennai out of their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My city is Chennai, I love it and make money out of it, but tomorrow if I need to settle in Banglore I don’t mind it and I will fall in love with it. Banglore will become my city. Some how my brain does not exist a lot in fuzzy state where I am confused where I should really live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Living for some mission pission and vision&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non Chennai people seems to be soul heavy like lead. They seem to live for a cause like family, parents blah blah. Dependence on them is very high. Some how they seem to have someone depending on them and that becomes their mission, pission and vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chennai people mostly live for themselves. They seem to think the world is made for them and people are there to serve them. This thought runs through our minds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pee Outside&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find it really annoying, but non Chennai people who I know pee just outside on the road. This I don’t find a bit with my Chennai friends. Perhaps India isn’t fully sanity conscious, but I find it really unacceptable. Perhaps there is some good things in Indian tradition we Chennaites do not know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liberation and Culture shock&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find that for some who move to Chennai from other parts of Tamilnadu, Andhra, and Kerala, it’s a real liberation. Especially for girls. They really seem to enjoy the freedom this city offers. None seem to look at them and judge them, that seems to be a blessing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For others it’s a culture shock. Once outsider is in Chennai, let’s say our driving methodology, our way of talk, our mannerism seems to offend them in some way. Possibly it’s like a Brahmin going to USA and seeing some one eating beef and sinking into deep depression.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I am born and brought up in Chennai. I travel almost to no other place because I find all I want here. In fact my mission is to never leave my bedroom. I want to earn from my bed, buy suff from my bed, its all possible with todays technology. Trying to be a non nomadic human has made me see people outside Chennai as some what different. They seem to look like weird animals to me. Here is what I found or think about them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Supriya In OMR Sucks</title><link href="/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/07/hotel-supriya-omr-sucks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Supriya In OMR Sucks" /><published>2019-12-07T09:30:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-07T09:30:00+05:30</updated><id>/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/07/hotel-supriya-omr-sucks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/07/hotel-supriya-omr-sucks.html">&lt;p&gt;This hotel in Supriya, that fucking Andhra mess sucks. Really sucks. Me and my friends went there to eat briyani, the briyani over there comes in the form of a kushka, for both mutton and chicken briyani you get the same kushka. If you order mutton briyani, they give kushka with mutton gravy, if you order chicken briyani, they give kushka with chicken gravy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chicken gravy was okay, but the mutton gravy was hot to taste. For a person like me its okay, but for my friends it was too much and they struggled with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ordered two kushkas and mutton and chicken gravy. I was okay about this arrangement, but for many in Tamilnadu it would be like, you goto a tea shop and order tea, the vendor gives you a donkey, sugarcane, rights to a gas field, right to mine iron etc… You need to milk the donkey, extract sugar from sugar cane, mine iron and make cylinders and stove, from the gas field you need to extract gas, liquify it and put it in cylinder and finally make tea. But for me that’s okay, for me its like having briyani with multiple flavours at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only side dish they offer is raitha, that is chopped onions in diluted butter milk, so diluted in fact you feel its for a drink than a raitha. You kinda need to hunt for onions in it. We also ordered extra rice, and to our surprise it came with a cost too. Most Andhra mess, and Madurai mess offer rice as compliment with briyani, over here it costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing I don’t like is stinginess of the hotel, I was burning hot eating the briyani, or to say chilli mutton rice mix, for the extra plain rice I reached for moore kulambu in next table, the fucking hotel owner / manager stopped me saying that moore kulambu is only for meals. It really hurt me. As my friend outside the hotel remarked, we eat for Rs 500/- and this guy won’t spare Rs 5/- worth of moore kulambu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compared to Tamil hotels which are stingy, Andhra hotels offer bountiful food, in some Andhra hotels I have emptied a mini bucket full of pakodas because it was so tasty, I have seen these Andhra guys enjoy watch people eating their food than like Tamil’s who worry about the customer consuming his profit margin, but here, Supriya has been Tamilianized,  they are no more an Andhra mess which we all love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then back at office, we all did not feel well, I got a mild stomach upset, so I do doubt about the hotel’s hygiene. Lack of hygiene and lack of the hospitality of these Andhra people make me feel bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few days later another friend of mine ate meals over there and got stomach upset too. So….. You think abut it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This hotel in Supriya, that fucking Andhra mess sucks. Really sucks. Me and my friends went there to eat briyani, the briyani over there comes in the form of a kushka, for both mutton and chicken briyani you get the same kushka. If you order mutton briyani, they give kushka with mutton gravy, if you order chicken briyani, they give kushka with chicken gravy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Julia will eventually oust Python</title><link href="/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Julia will eventually oust Python" /><published>2019-12-01T20:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-01T20:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python</id><content type="html" xml:base="/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/1/1f/Julia_Programming_Language_Logo.svg/1024px-Julia_Programming_Language_Logo.svg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a strong feeling that Julia will eventually oust Python for data science and artificial intelligence. The reason is this, speed and distributed computing. Python is an excellent language, even if you are not from a computing background and want to write programs, Python is a good language to start. But Julia has the following advantages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julia is super fast, even compared to C it has very simmilar speed with far less complicated syntax. So if you take a machine learning package in Julia, all its source can be just in Julia. Let’s take Python for example, we use numpy a lot, and at its base its not written in Python, its written in C and is wrapped with Python. That’s not Python!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you write everything in Python, things will get really slow and your grand child will see the result of your code’s output. I don’t think people want it that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distributed Computing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julia is a new language, Python was written as a toy language for system admin purpose, Julia on the other hand is a new one and understands the modern computing needs. Distributed computing, Concurrency and true Parallelism (not multithreading), which are difficult to achieve with pure Python. Though other packages are available, they are not python.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Python for Industry &amp;amp; Julia for research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now many companies that claim can do A.I work need to do it quick. It’s more easy to get Python developers, tell them to learn some A.I in 2 months and start to code. So Python may be good for industry. But think of an A.I researcher who wants to improve a learning algorithm and finds its source code in C or C++, that guy would rather write a new implementation in Julia than using those difficult languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel in slow, but in an exponential manner Julia packages will increase and root out Python in Data Science, I feel it’s only a matter of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blessed by Scientific Community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole software industry once thought THE MICROSOFT way was the way to develop software, but the scientific industry embraced &lt;a href=&quot;https://fsf.org&quot;&gt;free software&lt;/a&gt;, now many companies are using Linux on their desktops, Linux dominates Mobile market, even Apple uses lot of free software components in its ecosystem, Microsoft has surrendered to Linux today. What was touched by the scientists, and ridiculed by the software industry won. Today I feel Julia is getting such a blessing from the scientific community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember we in the software industry are here to make money with computers, though we have the brain enough to think, the mad pursuit of money and/or climbing the corporate ladder have left us with the intelligence of fighting lions and tigers. Where’s our tax sponsors these scientists who can take time to think, they do not have to fight much, outfox some one, get into office politics and meet very strict deadlines. They have intelligence of Chimps. Evolution tells that Chimps evolved into Humans who are hunting down and made Lions and Tigers almost extinct.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>