<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-02-03T09:34:35+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">USA plans war with China</title><link href="/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="USA plans war with China" /><published>2023-02-03T09:31:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-03T09:31:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeicyczvr4fks6pfm75xrq3crperwl3odipurlzqqlekg6emyszhdsy &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short URL:&lt;/strong&gt; https://yu7.in/dBQlE&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">People who know to code should be in the I.T industry</title><link href="/2023/02/02/people-who-know-to-code-should-be-in-the-i-t-industry.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="People who know to code should be in the I.T industry" /><published>2023-02-02T17:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-02T17:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/02/people-who-know-to-code-should-be-in-the-i-t-industry</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/02/people-who-know-to-code-should-be-in-the-i-t-industry.html">&lt;p&gt;Somehow passionate people who are greedy for money and power make it to the top. It’s a severe failure of human society. Politics in all its forms has failed humanity as people with compassion and brains are sidelined, and greedy ones take the throne. Just as I blog now, the speakers of mosque nearby blasts confirming that thinkers and rationalist are sidelined, and we still believe in God, blind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The triumph of the fools hasn’t left my business coding alone. Just last week a Machine Learning project my friend was involved was asked by the client (who claims to be an owner of a tech company for decade of more) to train a neural network without data. Imagine such person running a company. He is definitely a fool, and hence he is a BJP supporter. No wonder about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow in my industry, most coding companies are inefficient, like battle commanders who never face bullet, they are led by people who never face code every day. This is bad, really really bad. Now take a look at what I got on LinkedIn:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreid4uxgfs3q5db7qcvungcl2cmns25njqybkppz6j3yjk2y5vf5ife&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, the truth is LinkedIn is occupied by management idiots, so one should not be surprised by this message, but as you can see, a services company, just because it wants to earn money, has made it look like coding is a complex thing. Just like Boeing &amp;amp; Douglas for all these decades, and even today make it look like access to space is complex, then came SpaceX.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Somehow passionate people who are greedy for money and power make it to the top. It’s a severe failure of human society. Politics in all its forms has failed humanity as people with compassion and brains are sidelined, and greedy ones take the throne. Just as I blog now, the speakers of mosque nearby blasts confirming that thinkers and rationalist are sidelined, and we still believe in God, blind.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Meherbai Tata</title><link href="/2023/02/01/meherbai-tata.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Meherbai Tata" /><published>2023-02-01T12:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-01T12:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/01/meherbai-tata</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/01/meherbai-tata.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeid2ff7cos3dj5tadd4b2bzimlocnj2zuurpdlezisjt3yfv76mtna.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Meherbai Tata&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you zoom this photo, you will see a huge diamond worn around her neck. This is a 245 carat Jubilee Diamond and was twice as large as the famous Kohinoor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lady in this picture is Meherbai Tata who was the daughter-in-law of Jamshedji Tata and the wife of his eldest son Sir Dorabji Tata.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the year, 1924, when there was recession due to First World War, Tata Steel did not have the money to pay salaries to the employees. Meherbai had mortgaged her priceless Jubilee Diamond in Imperial Bank, so that the employees could get regular salaries and the company continues to run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After her untimely death from blood cancer, Sir Dorabji Tata established the Tata Memorial Cancer Research Foundation by selling this diamond for better treatment of cancer patients in India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies like Google, Meta, Amazon, Microsoft and many others which are laying off their employees should learn from this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/DQTdq&quot;&gt;https://yu7.in/DQTdq&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Meherbai Tata</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Saw this video when I was wondering why I am meeting so many psychopaths in my life</title><link href="/2023/01/29/saw-this-video-when-i-was-wondering-why-i-am-meeting-so-many-psychopaths-in-my-life.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Saw this video when I was wondering why I am meeting so many psychopaths in my life" /><published>2023-01-29T10:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-29T10:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/29/saw-this-video-when-i-was-wondering-why-i-am-meeting-so-many-psychopaths-in-my-life</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/29/saw-this-video-when-i-was-wondering-why-i-am-meeting-so-many-psychopaths-in-my-life.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeiatirewzelv5chi2nkegejcc5qqbyhhpoh2lezcwlfjtbvvprefb4.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DMK rule assured</title><link href="/2023/01/24/dmk-rule-assured.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DMK rule assured" /><published>2023-01-24T01:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-24T01:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/24/dmk-rule-assured</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/24/dmk-rule-assured.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/5/5e/Dravida_Munnetra_Kazhagam_logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s 12:55 in the morning when I am blogging. At 12:10 AM power went off in Sithalapakkam. I famously heard our speaker Appavu say during R.N.Ravi issue, he said that Tamil Nadu does not compete with other states in India, it competes with developed countries likes South Korea, Malaysia and so on… Tamil Nadu has surely beaten these nations in one thing, power cuts. The power came just now, and I don’t know when it will be cut again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason when the power went off, dogs started to bark, and I kinda lost my wish to sleep. We in India say that we will get rid of Pakistani jihadist, Chinese invaders and so on, in reality, we can’t even get rid of stray dogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I truly wonder how Stalin, Jayalalitha, Karunanidhi and even may be M.G.R called themselves peoples leader if they couldn’t get rid of stray dogs? Maybe they could call themselves as dogs leader. It for this kind of people we have built moseleums in Marina beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish we could kill dogs, but it’s said that PETA has powerful people. I think it has wife’s of industrialists, judges and so on. So if you kill a dog, those women will boast in their clubs about how they enforced law on a person and how they are torturing him because he killed a dog. This though is a gossip I came across, and am not sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So nearly an hour of power cut. I had thought for some time that DMK has lost power and ADMK was ruling Tamil Nadu, now this power cut assures me that DMK is still in power thus we may be powerless for some time to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">There is some magic in pure gaana and folk singers</title><link href="/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There is some magic in pure gaana and folk singers" /><published>2023-01-21T08:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-21T08:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/Delgv&quot;&gt;https://yu7.in/Delgv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wbYG8T80SOk?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the song above, it was created by Reguman and his team, but you have to listen hard to understand it. It’s a pure Tamil song, but may be the pronunciation of Ragumaan and the girls that sing look like they are foreigners who have landed in India just now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now listen to the sing below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zuVV9Y55gvc?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything in this song is easily understandable, there is nothing you need to concentrate hard. As a Tamil, this song is so understandable to me. It’s a pure Tamil song too. Maybe the singer of this song especially the women could be a pure Tamil girl, possibly a folk singer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now listen to this song:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9PYbz-UpG5Y?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a gaana song, may be because I was born and brought up in Chennai, every bit of this song is understandable and I could grasp it’s meaning just like that without any concentration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is something magical in gaana and folk singers, or may be there is some magic in folk and gaana songs. These songs ae highly understandable, needs no concentration. It’s sad that we have lot of song sung by non-native Tamil speakers, or people who have stayed away from our culture a long time, they suck compared to folk and gaana singers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now here are two songs:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gpVA5mx73UE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OxDKZ6WfD7M?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a Tamil, decide which is pronounced well and is easily understandable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Short Link: https://yu7.in/Delgv</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The lightness of being a freelancer</title><link href="/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The lightness of being a freelancer" /><published>2023-01-18T09:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-18T09:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer.html">&lt;p&gt;The kind of money we coders demand for quality means we can attract companies that make lot of money. Today if I generate billing for a project, small Indian companies run away. They ask an estimate, and they disappear once I give it to them. The result is people like me who value quality of code are stuck with big corps who like to pay us regular salary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I was working on a ticket, it was a complex one, and I didn’t have an idea how the business worked. All simple assumptions I made became false, my pull requests were rejected. Stumbling and fumbling I thought I would finish my code a day ago when disaster struck. I fell ill. I was forced to take 36 hours or so off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In corporate environments we have to show progress in every scrum call. We have to speak something. You will be paid no matter what, you will be terminated if the business don’t like you. You will be compared relatively with other people. Maybe you might come under a stare of a manager who had bad time with his family today, and your name will be struck off. You never know when the lightning bolt will strike. It’s capitalism to the max.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I were a pure freelancer, I could have had many clients, so loosing one may be a hit, but it would be cushioned by similar paying people. It would be like loosing 20% of your revenue rather than loosing 50%. Plus I can tell to my client to delay my payments till my work is done, or reduce my pay or increase my pay, the billing is what I generate. This justification of self evaluation and lightness of being honest and frank is absent in corporate world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust is very important in doing business. Entire economics is trust. In corporate world, you have no clue how the upper management trusts you, and they don’t connect with people who do the actual work. In freelancing this is opposite, you can gain trust of people and feedback very easily. That adds lightness to life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or may be this is corporate work, maybe I have to be okay with drawing money when I am inefficient, and should be content when I am efficient and the corporate does not want to hike pay for me for what ever reasons that comes to their mind.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The kind of money we coders demand for quality means we can attract companies that make lot of money. Today if I generate billing for a project, small Indian companies run away. They ask an estimate, and they disappear once I give it to them. The result is people like me who value quality of code are stuck with big corps who like to pay us regular salary.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">These boxes don’t move</title><link href="/2023/01/12/these-boxes-dont-move.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="These boxes don&apos;t move" /><published>2023-01-12T16:38:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-12T16:38:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/12/these-boxes-dont-move</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/12/these-boxes-dont-move.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeibf7sr6rfxodeya2nfcjepynmj6lc47ohr3rjvhkcs3tuxdxkmvma.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Universe - 25. Why men and women in wealthy, crowded places don’t behave like men and women anymore</title><link href="/2023/01/09/universe-25-why-men-and-women-in-wealthy-crowded-places-don-t-behave-like-men-and-women-anymore.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Universe - 25. Why men and women in wealthy, crowded places don&apos;t behave like men and women anymore" /><published>2023-01-09T18:04:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-09T18:04:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/09/universe-25-why-men-and-women-in-wealthy-crowded-places-don-t-behave-like-men-and-women-anymore</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/09/universe-25-why-men-and-women-in-wealthy-crowded-places-don-t-behave-like-men-and-women-anymore.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeidzr4kn57ytvrduwd45fzbpceloikycy5v6otrjxpntnw36bksim4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The “Universe 25” experiment is one of the most terrifying experiments in the history of science, which, through the behavior of a colony of mice, is an attempt by scientists to explain human societies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of ​​”Universe 25” Came from the American scientist John Calhoun, who created an “ideal world” in which hundreds of mice would live and reproduce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More specifically, Calhoun built the so-called “Paradise of Mice”, a specially designed space where rodents had Abundance of food and water, as well as a large living space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, he placed four pairs of mice that in a short time began to reproduce, resulting in their population growing rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, after 315 days their reproduction began to decrease significantly. When the number of rodents reached 600, a hierarchy was formed between them and then the so-called “wretches” appeared. The larger rodents began to attack the group, with the result that many males begin to “collapse” psychologically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result, the females did not protect themselves and in turn became aggressive towards their young.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time went on, the females showed more and more aggressive behavior, isolation elements and lack of reproductive mood. There was a low birth rate and, at the same time, an increase in mortality in younger rodents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, a new class of male rodents appeared, the so-called “beautiful mice”. They refused to mate with the females or to “fight” for their space. All they cared about was food and sleep. At one point, “beautiful males” and “isolated females” made up the majority of the population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Calhoun, the death phase consisted of two stages: the “first death” and “second death.” The former was characterized by the loss of purpose in life beyond mere existence — no desire to mate, raise young or establish a role within society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time went on, juvenile mortality reached 100% and reproduction reached zero. Among the endangered mice, homosexuality was observed and, at the same time, cannibalism increased, despite the fact that there was plenty of food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years after the start of the experiment, the last baby of the colony was born. By 1973, he had killed the last mouse in the Universe 25. John Calhoun repeated the same experiment 25 more times, and each time the result was the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun’s scientific work has been used as a model for interpreting social collapse, and his research serves as a focal point for the study of urban sociology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently witnessing direct parallels in today’s society… weak, feminized men with little to no skills and no protection instincts, and overly agitated and aggressive females with no maternal instincts.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iOFveSUmh9U?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.the-scientist.com/foundations/universe-25-1968-1973-69941&quot;&gt;Universe 25, 1968–1973&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.facebook.com/story.php?story_fbid=pfbid0zJtXGf53RD3gSmMuPQrykZtJZaawC9UpV2fSjanuU6pKGw4xQ2hju6sp2WPHVYx6l&amp;amp;id=1456000719&amp;amp;mibextid=Nif5oz&quot;&gt;A facebook post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Let’s de-grave marina</title><link href="/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Let&apos;s de-grave marina" /><published>2023-01-06T20:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-06T20:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3c/Chennai_Marina_beach_panorama1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am shocked by Stalin’s announcement of massive 80 crore waste to decorate Karunadhi’s grave with a massive statue of a pen on an artificial island. 80 crores is massive money. It could be given to 800 people to start very small business, even if 1% of them succeed, it will be good. But what good does it do decorating a grave?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I truly wonder what gives right to these dravidian parties to put their dead bodies in Marina? It’s a beach, it belongs to people, more than us, it belongs to all nature. We have converted it into a graveyard and have put artificial structures there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A leader might be needed for a society (of people who cannot think well, for a society that could think will be leader less), but I wonder what’s the big thing in having a rotting corpse below a huge concrete structure? It looks childish and silly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the thing that outrages me is that we have mausoleum for a proven criminal Jayalaitha in Marina, and almost none opposes it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly think a person should be remembered for what he had done. Today I know English and interact with the world, thanks to Annadurai. I am an atheist and think rationally, and don’t encourage building temples, mosques, churches and mausoleum, thanks to Periyaar. I don’t remember these people because I saw their graves, but the good things that they have done to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember Abdul Kalaam not because of his grave, but he protected me from invaders, helped our nation become a space power. I don’t even know where his grave is, though I do know they have built one for him. I remember Kamaraj for his honesty and, his ability not to build grave for his mom even though he was a powerful chief minister of Tamilnadu. I don’t know where Kamaraj is burried, I don’t even know if he was cremated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst thing is that the 80 crores that Stalin wants to spend on decorating his dad’s grave is our hard-earned money. It’s not from Red Giant’s or G-squares or some binaami’s loot. I really wonder what gives the right for these DMK and ADMK to waste our money on dead bodies like this? May be if they earned honestly they would know worth of money and spend it better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe we people are powerless, coward, and have too much to lose now by protesting against dravidian rule, but I feel ultimately we must de-grave Marina. All these bodies should be taken out, put somewhere else, beach should be given back to people to walk, turtles to reproduce, crabs to crawl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage the reader to talk about this loot going on in Tamilnadu. I encourage one to think about the good ways of using money than wasting it on dead matter. I wish you would would remeber this blog when you vote again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>