<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-05-30T22:47:40+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The dark side of Fantastic Jeyachandran</title><link href="/2018/05/30/the-dark-side-of-fantastic-jeyachandran.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The dark side of Fantastic Jeyachandran" /><published>2018-05-30T22:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-05-30T22:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/05/30/the-dark-side-of-fantastic-jeyachandran</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/05/30/the-dark-side-of-fantastic-jeyachandran.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/n2z-8oLPOWY?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jeyachandran invests crores to put ads on T.V about its new showroom in Pallikaranai, and its a grand showroom. I drive past it every day and I drive back late at night everyday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Jeyachandran looks good on the outside and invests a lot of money in marketing, there is a dark side of it. This company seems to have no social consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this fantastic Jeyachandran, sales are booming, and at night crowds arrive in large numbers, and their vehicles cause a huge traffic jam. Jeyachandran could ease it but they are doing nothing about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two main ways Jeyachandran could do it. First, Jeyachandran has 100’s of people working with it, just by putting 2 people to control traffic will make a difference, now the junction is chaotic and traffic queues upto a Kilometer and none does anything about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second thing Jeyachandran could do is to clear off some of its bike parking at its space near the roads so that there will be more road width, thus easing up the traffic flow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this thing is going on for sometime and Jeyachandran seems not to care. My humble request to people, yes you might be drawn by the low price, but try avoiding Jeyachandran if its possible as they seem to have no society consciousness till now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My blog in Dat Protocol</title><link href="/2018/05/28/my-blog-in-dat-protocol.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My blog in Dat Protocol" /><published>2018-05-28T15:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-05-28T15:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/05/28/my-blog-in-dat-protocol</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/05/28/my-blog-in-dat-protocol.html">&lt;p&gt;I’m happy to have discovered Beaker Browser and my website is in dat protocol. You can access it &lt;a href=&quot;dat://06f0a59a3425002325fedbc8baefec11ef552a901bdb5200ad3aab85d622d7e2/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; . This blog is just to test how well my website is getting updated when I put a new post.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’m happy to have discovered Beaker Browser and my website is in dat protocol. You can access it here . This blog is just to test how well my website is getting updated when I put a new post.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I think Yedurappa and BJP are stupid</title><link href="/2018/05/17/why-i-think-yedurappa-and-bjp-are-stupid.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I think Yedurappa and BJP are stupid" /><published>2018-05-17T12:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-05-17T12:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/05/17/why-i-think-yedurappa-and-bjp-are-stupid</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/05/17/why-i-think-yedurappa-and-bjp-are-stupid.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://leadtech.in/infoelection/images/politician%20images/yeddyurappa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t stop laughing, our country is ruled b a party that doesn’t know elementary mathematics or it has the potential to buy or rowdy its way to power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A mark of a gentleman is that he sets out to do whats decently possible, certainly Yedurappa is not of that kind, a childish brain he has, looks like his brain is tell “I wanna be Karnataka C.M one more time even if happens to be days”. Clearly he has no majority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A politician should think ‘how to run an country efficiently?’, ‘how to better peoples lives?’, rather than think about those things BJP is acting childish in a desperate effort to gain power. Possibly its a childish move, or is there more to it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP might be sitting on large swaths of money, possibly the Reddy brothers are ready to pay the BJP to buy MLA’s, possibly they have done something terribly wrong and want the BJP to come to power for certain days so that they can hide something in those first few days so that bringing them to justice becomes not so easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever! None knows whats there, weather BJP is childish or they have something more sinister, only time will tell. But I hope we had mature politicians who are gentleman than people who cannot control themselves. People who cannot control themselves loot the nations and try to manipulate and subdue the population so that they can escape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Telephone Companies Loot You</title><link href="/2018/05/02/how-telephone-companies-loot-you.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Telephone Companies Loot You" /><published>2018-05-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-05-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/05/02/how-telephone-companies-loot-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/05/02/how-telephone-companies-loot-you.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://images.jagran.com/bsnl_logo_090614.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to surrender one of my BSNL number, I went to Velacherry BSNL office, and damn, those sight of government servants. Definitely that office was unhelpful, you don’t know which counter is for what. I went to  a lady clerk, and she keyed in my number on her terminal and found out that my bills were pending, well I haven’t used my phone for months. If I hadn’t used it for 5 months, why can’t they cut my line when I did not pay the bill for the first month? Duh!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead they were charging me for the phone as though i was using it. Damn. When I pulled out my purse that lady said she can’t take money and close my account. What? Bloody hell I am in BSNL office and I can’t pay BSNL bill!!!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to pay the bill online, then go to a place to surrender my number, then I need to write a snail mail to their account department to refund the money I had paid as deposit. Damn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All mobile companies charge you even if you stop paying a months bill. Vodafone is crap, my friend got number and he stopped paying because he did not want that number, he got another Vodafone number. Vodafone identified him with his aadhar card and stopped their service for other number too, thus forcing him to pay for the first one. Damn. Don’t ever get a Vodafone service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can’t there be a rule that if you stop paying for a month your number will be terminated, and that’s it. Why its so easy to get a new connection and so difficult to terminate it? Have you ever thought of it? Because they want to loot you. Its as simple as that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you really know its possible for people in cities to communicate without the need of mobile carriers, and it will be far far cheaper, and have you wondered why the government is not allowing that by law?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are just a bunch of slaves, that’s it, a bunch of slaves and fools that mobile companies and governments could loot.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Another admission of defeat for Windows</title><link href="/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Another admission of defeat for Windows" /><published>2018-04-16T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.wallpapersafari.com/38/59/PYHvQk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Windows is slowly but surely giving way to GNU Linux. Linux’s desktop share is just
above 2%, but on the Internet scale GNU Linux rules. All computers that power our
Internet are critical systems and they run Linux. Most mobile phones use Linux
as Android. Many people who use Amndroid never know they are Linux users and
they vocally oppose using Linux on their desktops!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Microsoft is not as foolish as the people who use its OS. Looks like many
engineers on the M$ know that defeat of Windows is imminent, and they are giving
their way slowly ao that it would not look like a humiliating defeat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First is M$’s Azure. It offers Linux on its servers, and I bet there are more Azure 
instances that run Linux than Windows. Recently I had a problem with Windows.
In my office we use Python as we are a data science company, one of my coworker
had a problem in running a flask app. It worked perfectly on my system which was
and Ubuntu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a little bit investigation it was evident the way that the way Windows OS
functioned was a problem. I had an irrational resistance for installing GNU Linux on
her computer, but it was clear the resistance was irrational. There is a way to
combat irrationality, let the irrational people finish stuff. Work stopped and
fortunately for me, the person realized loss in productivity and it was the only
the way to go ahead, so I installed GNU Lubuntu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wondered if Windows was such a crap system, why are developers using it?
Are CTO’s around the world gone nuts? Haven’t they seen such a problem? But then
to my amazement, I found that Windows 10 now allows Linux subsystem to be
installed in it! Its not as good as full GNU Linux at your disposal, but rather
than fighting the free software community, M$ has recognized Linux which once it
famously called as the toy OS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like a Spartan phalanx Linux is advancing, though M$ is doing all it can to stop
Linux, it seems not enough. As more and more developers pour in to develop Linux
during their free time, M$ simply does not have the budget to win such a war, and
they know it really well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many economic theorist will be confused to  know that a capitalistic organization
is bowing to a communal force thats not interested in making a buck. Well, we
don’t know if the Universe is infinite, but we are sure that human stupidity is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/wsl/install-win10&quot;&gt;Install the Windows Subsystem for Linux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sharpen your axe</title><link href="/2018/02/25/sharpen-your-axe.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sharpen your axe" /><published>2018-02-25T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-25T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/25/sharpen-your-axe</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/25/sharpen-your-axe.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://panasian-hk.com/image/data/Product/Handtool/Hammer-and-Axe/Axe/3240_1-1_4_lb__felling_axe_tekton.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its was in  a project named places.com, a real estate website, I was into a
company called Zanec, that company had never seen Ruby on Rails, I was the first
guy into that company who knew Ruby, some how even without knowing the
technology they were holding a project possibly for 3 months! Let me come to
the point, my job was to lead a project and since I am a Rails guy I need to
provide JSON end points for front end Angular application. When I started to
work, the front end guys got frustrated with me. I was able to give API’s really
fast and I was seen slacking off most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being brought up in a culture where one is thought work is gain, they got hugely
frustrated seeing me get away with little work. They seem not to know that in Rails
automation is built into it. That makes me just a person who needs to flick a
switch to get it done. Claiming themselves as computer engineers, I failed to
see why they failed to see my automated advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next thing is happening in a company called Trumatics, where I am a partner.
We are trying to predict the sales of customer, and its just a regression problem
with little number of sample values. Though it looks complex, its just a line
of code in GNU Octave. Thats it. Fortunately Trumatics is built up of thinkers
who can listen, so things will go really smooth there :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see computers as my slave, I don’t see a point in getting frustrated about it
and working long hours in front of it. People who work for long hours before
computers look like idiots to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most computer or I.T people in India are like this: if asked to cut a tree, they
go on to cut it. They don’t mind if they have an axe, they simply don’t care if its
sharp, they just go about swinging the axe onto the trunk and they feel happy
about working a lot and feel they deserve pay for their stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many computer graduates don’t even have an axe, they just have a pen knife or
just their nails, and they work hard to fell a tree and go almost nowhere. I
concentrate on sharpening the axe and on my swing. I learn a lot, code a lot
in my mind before I physically code. I read a lot about software engineering, and
about how complex code must be structured so that it can be managed in a simple way,
I read a lot about how testing helps if you are coding deterministic programs.
Unfortunately as far as my knowledge goes, programs that change itself based on
data like A.I ones need different thought to test them. They can be tested any
way so TDD freaks need not panic :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its these sort of skills, puts me above others. Its strange to think many computer
people in India think themselves as programmers and not as mathematicians. They
seem not to know whats the difference between concurrency and congruency of a
Triangle. Its quiet pathetic. If you just know some loops, branching and think
you can survive in I.T industry, I wonder how?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not just workers who are stupids, the I.T middle management and upto the
companies CEO’s are stupid. Most companies in India put MBA’s and PMP’s who have almost no
knowledge of math and logical reasoning in their heads, as heads of project thats
based on computers which is purely mathematical and science. Its possibly due to
these reasons, our companies are not good enough.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Narendra Modi is Anti Indian</title><link href="/2018/02/24/narendra-modi-is-anti-indian.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Narendra Modi is Anti Indian" /><published>2018-02-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/24/narendra-modi-is-anti-indian</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/24/narendra-modi-is-anti-indian.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://s3.india.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/1203.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Modi is coming to Tamilnadu in order to launch a plan thats named after
Jayalalitha who is a criminal who ruled Tamilnadu for a long long time. Her band
called AIADMK which consists of murderers, theiefs, pimps, liquor makers,
rogues and rowdies still rule Tamilnadu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jayalaitha is a declared criminal asper Indian law and for a Priminster to
support her, proves that the person who is the priminster is not worth for the
job. So its better to say Narendra Modi is an Anti-Indian and we people are
foolish and corrupt to elect him as Priminster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Good news for working women in Tamil Nadu.&lt;br /&gt;PM Narendra Modi to launch the AIADMK government&amp;#39;s Amma scooter scheme today.&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/ITVideo?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#ITVideo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More videos: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/NounxnP7mg&quot;&gt;https://t.co/NounxnP7mg&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/iC9DCckU5z&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/iC9DCckU5z&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; India Today (@IndiaToday) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/IndiaToday/status/967269608964030464?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;February 24, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BJP’s double standards</title><link href="/2018/02/14/bjp-s-double-standards.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BJP's double standards" /><published>2018-02-14T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-14T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/14/bjp-s-double-standards</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/14/bjp-s-double-standards.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://tamil.oneindia.com/img/2015/06/08-1433748608-tamilisai-soundararajan46-600.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its funny how blatantly foolish BJP people are, and yet the people of this nation
have made them our leaders. BJP is a party that has admitted openly that it
fooled people to get to power. Look what it told to people, it claimed ‘if we
are voted to power, we will deposit a sum of 15 lakhs into each and every Indian
account. this would be done by getting by money looted from our nation and
that’s sashed in Swiss banks’. So after 4 years of power and just a year more
for BJP to fall, we are all 15 lakhs richer apart from our earnings! Are we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is not about that. This blog is to say how BJP is openly showcasing
ts double standard in Tamilnadu. I blogged about the shameful event of opening
a criminals portrait in Tamilnadu assembly. To my surprise, BJP a party that
respects law says it not wrong! Thats what Tamilisiai the BJP president here
says. But wait, if Jayalalitha ruled Tamilnadu and hence its not wrong to honor
her even though she is not a criminal, Tippusultan who ruled Mysore so well,
of course not all he did wasn’t right is unrecognized by BJP, why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very similar thing can be seen how BJP likes new politicians emerging in
Tamilnadu. Rajini is a good guy, Kamal is bad. Both have the same history!
Both just talk and move in front of screen and say what they do it art. What
else? Even Shakeela does it, but its much more better!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason is very simple. BJP is not worried about good or bad, or who will
be a better ruler or who is more eligible or who has more moral, its all about
who obeys Hinduisms idiotic ideology more. Thats it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;Reference&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/02/11/a-shameful-day-for-tamils.html&quot;&gt;A shameful day for Tamils&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/07/Why-not-Shakeela-become-next-Tamilnadu-CM.html&quot;&gt;Why not Shakeela become next Tamilnadu CM?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A shameful day for Tamils</title><link href="/2018/02/11/a-shameful-day-for-tamils.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A shameful day for Tamils" /><published>2018-02-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/11/a-shameful-day-for-tamils</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/11/a-shameful-day-for-tamils.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static.bengali.news18.com/static-bengali/2016/12/jayalalithaa1-630x420.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow 12th of February 2018 will be a very shameful day for all Tamils in
India. This day will prove that we are utter fools and have misused a great tool
given to us by Independence. We have elected such a government that will
inaugurate a picture of a convicted criminal in our assembly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short this proves that we have elected a gang thats such audaciously so
criminal and such dumb minded they don’t even realize that they are
inaugurating a picture of criminal in assembly and they don’t seem to realize
its wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jayalalitha is a criminal, she is a goon and thats been proven in court. If at
all we must allow her picture to be hosted in assembly, then it must be proven
that she is innocent. Dumb ass Edapadi and Paneerselvam are so so fools they
don’t even know to respect law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we don’t realize its wrong, no force in this universe will be able to save
us.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Heroku still makes money?</title><link href="/2018/02/02/how-heroku-still-makes-money.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Heroku still makes money?" /><published>2018-02-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/02/how-heroku-still-makes-money</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/02/how-heroku-still-makes-money.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://logz.io/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/heroku-logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wonder how Heroku makes money? According to me, Heroku does just one
thing, it makes deploying apps easy. Thats it. But there are other solutions if
you sweat a bit, and they makes it much easier and cheaper than deploying on
Heroku. One such thing is Capistrano-rails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder why so many Rails and other app developers are so lazy in buying
prepackaged solutions, when just a little knowledge of Linux is all thats enough
to set up your own deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its strange to me. If you really think Heroku is easy, one must give a try for
capistrano, if one has not done it, most probably that companies tech guys or
CTO is a fool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;Reference&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coderwall.com/p/ttrhow/deploying-rails-app-using-nginx-puma-and-capistrano-3&quot;&gt;Deploying Rails App with Capistrano&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>