<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-10-31T17:57:44+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How a chorus of synchronized frequencies helps you digest your food</title><link href="/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How a chorus of synchronized frequencies helps you digest your food" /><published>2025-10-31T17:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-31T17:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html&quot;&gt;https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Biological systems often exhibit synchronization, like fireflies or fish, but the mechanics are complex, as seen in brain blood vessels.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;UC San Diego researchers studied the gut’s peristalsis to understand how oscillations synchronize, finding a “staircase effect” where similar frequencies lock onto each other.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This research used a classical model of coupled oscillators, simplified by the gut’s unidirectional nature compared to the brain’s complex vasculature.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The new mathematical solution explains how food moves and is churned in the digestive tract and could aid in understanding gastrointestinal motility disorders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The study determined key features of the staircase phenomenon in the gut, which had not been precisely understood before.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The researchers plan to apply these findings back to the more complex, multi-directional oscillations observed in the brain’s vasculature.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kafka is fast – I’ll use Postgres</title><link href="/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kafka is fast -- I&apos;ll use Postgres" /><published>2025-10-30T16:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-30T16:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks&quot;&gt;https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The tech world is divided into two camps: one chasing buzzwords and adopting popular but potentially inappropriate solutions, and the other prioritizing common sense, pragmatism, and first principles.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “common sense” camp is gaining traction due to the “Small Data” movement (acknowledging sufficient hardware for most data sizes) and the “Postgres Renaissance” (Postgres’ growing capability to handle diverse use cases).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The article argues that Postgres can effectively handle many functionalities typically assigned to specialized systems like Elasticsearch, MongoDB, Redis, and Kafka, covering over 80% of use cases with 20% of the effort.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Benchmarks were conducted for Postgres as a Pub/Sub messaging system, demonstrating competitive performance with Kafka at lower scales (e.g., 5 MB/s ingest, 25 MB/s egress on a 3-node cluster).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Postgres Pub/Sub performance scaled significantly on a 96 vCPU single node, achieving 238 MiB/s write and 1.16 GiB/s read throughput, though a custom design approach was used.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Benchmarks for Postgres as a Queue also showed strong performance, with a modest single-node setup handling thousands of messages per second and an HA setup exceeding 2000 messages/second.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The author advocates for defaulting to Postgres, emphasizing the quality-of-life benefits and reduced organizational complexity compared to specialized distributed systems for small-to-medium scale.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Premature optimization by adopting complex web-scale technologies for non-web-scale problems is deemed an “anti-pattern” due to significant organizational and financial overhead.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “Minimum Viable Infrastructure (MVI)” approach is recommended: choosing familiar, “good-enough” technology, solving real problems with minimal features, and leveraging widely adopted systems like Postgres.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “it won’t scale” argument is refuted by citing OpenAI’s successful use of unsharded Postgres for massive read loads, the long timeframe for reaching critical scale, and the concept of overdesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vegetarians, watch this: The Science of Vitamin B12</title><link href="/2025/10/29/vegetarians-watch-this-the-science-of-vitamin-b12.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vegetarians, watch this: The Science of Vitamin B12" /><published>2025-10-29T09:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-29T09:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/29/vegetarians-watch-this-the-science-of-vitamin-b12</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/29/vegetarians-watch-this-the-science-of-vitamin-b12.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pTSbh-XgxM&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pTSbh-XgxM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cobalt is a rare metal essential for lithium-ion batteries due to its thermal stability, with most production from the Democratic Republic of Congo.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cobalt is also crucial for animal life as it is a key component of cobalamin (Vitamin B12), vital for DNA, fatty acid, and amino acid production.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Animals cannot synthesize Vitamin B12 and rely on consuming it from food, a dependency that evolved because synthesizing B12 is a complex and energy-intensive biological process.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Plants do not require B12 as they have a different biochemical pathway for DNA, fatty acid, and protein synthesis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vitamin B12 deficiency can lead to severe health issues, including problems with red blood cell production, neurological problems, and fatigue.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The typical Indian diet often leads to B12 deficiency due to low per capita meat consumption, as B12 is primarily found in animal sources.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To ensure adequate B12 intake, options include consuming red meat and seafood, fortified foods, or supplements, especially for those on vegan diets or with culturally limited animal product intake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pTSbh-XgxM</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Khalid’s sucks compared to Yamohideen briyani</title><link href="/2025/10/21/khalids-sucks-compared-to-yamohideen-briyani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Khalid&apos;s sucks compared to Yamohideen briyani" /><published>2025-10-21T16:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-21T16:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/21/khalids-sucks-compared-to-yamohideen-briyani</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/21/khalids-sucks-compared-to-yamohideen-briyani.html">&lt;p&gt;This year, the day after Pillayar chaturthi, I wanted to eat briyani. I drove to Medavakkam’s Yamohideen briyani and it was closed. Though expensive, its meat quality seems to be good compared to other briyani houses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I drove down the road, towards Shollinganallur, took a U-turn, there was Khalids. Buying briyani there was a disappointment. In Yamohideen, you had lot of meat for rice, really nice to eat, that’s how briyani should be. But in Khalids there were just two pieces of meat, it was totally disappointing. Th price in Khalids was disappointing too, it was equivalent to Yamohideen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will never goto Khalids again. They just seem to rip people off. I must say though the taste of briyani in Khalids was not bad. But it rips us off, when you see the minuscule quantity of meat they offer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This year, the day after Pillayar chaturthi, I wanted to eat briyani. I drove to Medavakkam’s Yamohideen briyani and it was closed. Though expensive, its meat quality seems to be good compared to other briyani houses.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Renewables topple coal in global historic first with developing countries leading the charge</title><link href="/2025/10/20/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Renewables topple coal in global historic first with developing countries leading the charge" /><published>2025-10-20T17:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-20T17:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/20/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/20/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://scroll.in/article/1087475/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge?utm_source=firefox-newtab-en-intl&quot;&gt;https://scroll.in/article/1087475/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge?utm_source=firefox-newtab-en-intl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Renewables have surpassed coal as the top global electricity source, although progress varies, accelerating in developing nations while slowing in the U.S. and EU.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Smaller nations are rapidly adopting clean energy, electric vehicles, and battery storage, often driven by economic factors like reducing reliance on expensive fossil fuels and improving grid reliability, rather than solely climate change concerns.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bhutan, traditionally hydro-reliant, is diversifying with solar, wind, and biomass to combat seasonal power drops and meet industrial demand, transitioning from a winter importer to a balanced energy mix.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nepal, prompted by a 2015 blockade, is aggressively shifting to electric vehicles, powered by domestic hydropower, to reduce import dependence and air pollution, with significant growth in EV adoption despite political instability.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sri Lanka’s severe economic crisis in 2022-2023 highlighted its energy vulnerabilities, pushing the nation to rapidly expand solar and wind power, aiming for 70% renewable energy by 2030, supported by AI-based grid integration and inclusive projects.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Maldives is replacing diesel generators with solar arrays and battery storage across its islands to mitigate high import costs and oil price volatility, prioritizing economic survival and community benefits in its net-zero by 2030 roadmap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://scroll.in/article/1087475/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge?utm_source=firefox-newtab-en-intl</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Varq</title><link href="/2025/10/20/varq.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Varq" /><published>2025-10-20T11:07:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-20T11:07:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/20/varq</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/20/varq.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/&quot;&gt;https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The text describes the traditional craft of making “varq” (edible silver and gold leaf) in Hyderabad’s Old City, highlighting the sensory experience of finding a workshop through the rhythmic hammering sound.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Varq, used as an edible decoration for sweets and other dishes, has a long history in India, with mentions in ancient Ayurvedic texts for its medicinal properties and later refined in Mughal courts as a symbol of luxury and status.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Historically, varq was made by hand-beating silver between sheets of ox gut or cowhide, a meticulous process passed down through generations of artisans.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Despite rising silver prices leading some sweet shops to use cheaper machine-made or aluminum substitutes, the tradition of hand-beaten varq persists, with a few remaining artisans preserving this delicate art.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The term “varq” itself has Sanskrit and Persian origins, both meaning “leaf” or “sheet,” reflecting its ancient roots and cultural significance across different eras in India.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shell fish is better than fish</title><link href="/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shell fish is better than fish" /><published>2025-10-16T18:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-16T18:05:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish are presented as a superior alternative to fish for combating sarcopenia, the age-related loss of muscle mass.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish protein is highly bioavailable and rich in amino acids like leucine, effectively stimulating muscle protein synthesis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They are packed with essential minerals (zinc, selenium, iron) and B vitamins, which act as “activators” for muscle health and cellular processes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish contain taurine, an amino acid that protects muscles from oxidative stress, supports mitochondrial health, and improves endurance, crucial for aging bodies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unlike larger fish, shellfish are low in the food chain and generally do not accumulate heavy metals like mercury, making them a safe and clean food source.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Regular shellfish consumption, combined with appropriate exercise and lifestyle, can significantly reduce sarcopenia and frailty, promoting vitality in old age.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An anti-sarcopenia lifestyle encompasses not only diet (like shellfish) but also movement, adequate sleep, hydration, inflammation management, good digestion, hormonal balance, sunlight exposure, and social connection.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish contribute to overall health beyond muscles by supporting nerves (B12), protecting joints and bones (muscle pull), and aiding brain function (blood sugar regulation).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The text emphasizes that sarcopenia is preventable and reversible, not an inevitable part of aging, and small, consistent choices, including incorporating shellfish, can make a significant difference.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The ultimate vision is an active, independent, and joyful aging experience, free from the limitations often associated with muscle loss, made possible by a holistic approach centered on nutrient-dense foods like shellfish.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Plan is not execution, it’s communication</title><link href="/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Plan is not execution, it&apos;s communication" /><published>2025-10-10T12:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-10T12:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication.html">&lt;p&gt;I think Eisenhower said something like, though it does not work, plan is essential. I am in software industry, and we programmers have been asked often the question: ‘what is our plan?’, ‘when is the deadline?’, and we do give a plan and estimated deadline, and most of the time, it won’t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who are ignorant feel bad about it. In IT industry, people who work are less stupid, and usually the stupidest person gets to the top due to Dunning Kruger effect. So they don’t have intelligence to separate between plan and real world happenings. So if a plan fails or slips, the intelligent person who did the plan is put to a toss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is complex. You don’t plan to brush your teeth, it happens, you don’t plan to breathe. You plan only when you are not sure, you plan only when you are not made up for the task, when you are unsure. That is you plan only when there is element(s) of uncertainty, or some difficulty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not intelligent for a person to take a plan as execution, instead it should be treated as communication. This is what a person is going to do. It might happen happen in the way planned, but there is a good chance that it won’t, the course might change, we might even scrub it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wise person sees plan, and pads it up with more resources, to take the shock(s) of reality, he also plans for failure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I think Eisenhower said something like, though it does not work, plan is essential. I am in software industry, and we programmers have been asked often the question: ‘what is our plan?’, ‘when is the deadline?’, and we do give a plan and estimated deadline, and most of the time, it won’t work.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Buddha killed Islam, and Christianity even before they were born</title><link href="/2025/10/01/buddha-killed-islam-and-christianity-even-before-they-were-born.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Buddha killed Islam, and Christianity even before they were born" /><published>2025-10-01T21:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-01T21:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/01/buddha-killed-islam-and-christianity-even-before-they-were-born</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/01/buddha-killed-islam-and-christianity-even-before-they-were-born.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902808.us.archive.org/11/items/buddha-statue_202510/Buddha%20Statue.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you know the right facts, you can easily kill blind faith. Buddha as I know did not like Hinduism, the tradition of sacrifices, the tradition of yagnas (sacred fire offerings) didn’t appeal to him. He didn’t know what was reality, and why we suffered? So, he went on long quest to ask his inner self. In the end he emerged with something that would kill any faith that’s based on God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see in religions like Hinduism, Islam, Christianity, Sikhism etc, there is God, depending on your good or bad deeds, God rewards or punishes you. If you are rewarded, you feel happy, if you are punished, you feel sad. Right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, Buddha found out the powerful fact that happiness and sadness lies entirely within you. You can turn it on or off as per your will. That is you can stay happy, and calm, all the time if you wished too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can stay happy all the time, what can God do to you even if it exist? Of course, people in those times did not have the scientific tools to disprove God, they wouldn’t even be able to explain what lightning was, they had no idea about nuclear fusion that powers the sun. So Buddha said, it didn’t matter if God exists or not. If you can take control of your feelings, then God doesn’t matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly God became powerless before this fact. I wonder what would have happened if these thoughts had reached Arabia, there could have been no Christianity, and no Islam. Jews would have struggled to hold ground against such a powerful fact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If these thoughts had reached Afghanistan and Iran, Zoroastrianism would have had tough time, Zorastrians invented the concept of God, may be single God (Ahura Mazda), they invented the concept of heaven and hell, and these concepts stuck with later religions. What would have happened if they discovered that this God was powerless before an well trained brain which can control its thoughts and feelings? It’s really funny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They might have got mad, wanted to destroy India and Buddhism.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They might accept Buddhism and abandoned their religion.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They could have coexisted.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They could have  formed a new mixed religion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But yea, it would have made a very different world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">All major Tamil politicians have killed Innocent Tamils</title><link href="/2025/09/29/all-major-tamil-politicians-have-killed-innocent-tamils.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="All major Tamil politicians have killed Innocent Tamils" /><published>2025-09-29T09:32:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-09-29T09:32:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/09/29/all-major-tamil-politicians-have-killed-innocent-tamils</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/09/29/all-major-tamil-politicians-have-killed-innocent-tamils.html">&lt;p&gt;If you are a powerful (wo)man in Tamilnadu, you can get away with the murder. This is the writing on the wall I could see. The recent culprit is actor Vijay. He has killed 40 people, and nothing happens to him. He has failed to lead, after the deaths happened in his rally, he proved himself coward and fled to Chennai rather than stand with people who have suffered and died for him. Neither Vijay, nor his party TVK, seems to have no inkling of guilt, they are unapologetic till now. They have announced price for lives lost, and price for injury, thats it. As the courts once said, Vijay is not a true life hero, just a hero before the cameras. Vijay however filed a case and made the court retract this statement. But the statement made by the court is the truth, time has proven it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The history of killing innocent life’s, and politicians being unapologetic is a long one in Tamilnadu, the so called Tamilian leaders have been no beeter than the Brits in this regard. Now let’s see one by one, how major politicians killed innocent people and still remain unapologetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stalin&quot;&gt;Stalin&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tamilnadu under stalin I believe has at least 28 lockup deaths. Not so long ago, I think 63 people died in drinking illicit liquor. Stalin who was heartbroken by this 40 deaths in Vijay’s rally, stood firm and unapologetic when he killed these people. He simply didn’t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even before coming to power Stalin started to kill Tamilians. Watch his election rally, it took place in covid times, and DMK took no measures in preventing spreading of the disease. Once elected into power, Stalin shamelessly asked Tamils to donate, so that he can fight the disease which he spread. Not even EPS apposed to this evil preelection campaigns of Stalin, because he too followed no covid guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was an Airshow conducted in Chennai, it was very poorly organized and 5 people died in it. The DMK government closed the mater and swept the dirt under the rugs. They are unapologetic till now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eps&quot;&gt;EPS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I said before, EPS too campaigned as though there was no covid, had no regard for Tamilian lives. He is famous for killing atleast 12 activist who protested against the Sterlite copper factory in Thuthukudi. ADMK and EPS are still unapologetic about it, he played a drama to the media that, its only after watching the news that he knew the murders had been committed. The whole state knows that police will not resort to firing without orders from the CM, Its not simple matter to fire on people, it should be done only after lot of approvals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was in EPS time that all people who were associated with the Kodanaadu Jayalaitha property robbery case died in mysterious circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In EPS era too there were lockup deaths, the most famous case was that of Felix, and Jerald I think. Father and son duo was tortured in lockup and lilled by the Tamilandu police, just because they had verbal spat. None who is associated with that case is hanged yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Stalin and EPS are super weak CM’s who are unable to control the Tamilnadu police, no matter how barbaric the police becomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;karunanidhi&quot;&gt;Karunanidhi&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2G case was going on, Kanimozhi was in a soup. The civil war in Srilanka was on, the Sinhala forces had the upper hand. As a leader of Tamils, Karunanidhi should have stood up, prevented the defeat of the LTTE, but he stood down because he need to concentrate and save Kanimozhi from the 2G case. Then DMK threaded the line of Pranab Mukerjee and said that the war was over, while Sinhala troops were mascaraing Tamils en-masse. Finally this led to the death of Velu Pillai Prabhakaran, the hope of Tamils. Even Prabhakaran’s young son was killed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to save his girl, Karunanidhi wiped of an entire Tamil civilization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;jayalalitha&quot;&gt;Jayalalitha&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jayalalitha is one of the worst Chief Minister’s ever to rule in india according to me. She cared nothing about people. Traffic need to wait for hours, just because she wanted to take a walk on the roads. She was shameless, totally irresponsible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was some holy festival called Mahamagam. Jayalaitha had gone to some crowded place to take a dip in some holy pond or something. There was a private area for her to be drenched in holy water. Her arrival itself added more congestion to the crowds. Just to disperse the crowds, its said that some police guy called Walter Devaram shot rounds in the air, the crowd panicked. There was stampeed, and people died. ADMK is still unapologetic till now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Periyaar was right when he said that independence of India is a black day. He said the only the skin color of the rulers will change. Just like General Dire has no concern for life and killed a lot in Janian-wallah-bagh, India’s post independence leaders have no concern for the lives of people. They are intoxicated by the power, wealth and richness, and they think they are untouchables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A society is like a stew, scum floats to the top often and it need to be stirred often to break the scum. I feel that we Indians are  ot stirring up India often, we are not scaring politicians often, neither we have &lt;a href=&quot;/2010/01/31/dynamic-democracy.html&quot;&gt;Dynamic Democracy&lt;/a&gt;, and we have decided to be their slaves forever.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">If you are a powerful (wo)man in Tamilnadu, you can get away with the murder. This is the writing on the wall I could see. The recent culprit is actor Vijay. He has killed 40 people, and nothing happens to him. He has failed to lead, after the deaths happened in his rally, he proved himself coward and fled to Chennai rather than stand with people who have suffered and died for him. Neither Vijay, nor his party TVK, seems to have no inkling of guilt, they are unapologetic till now. They have announced price for lives lost, and price for injury, thats it. As the courts once said, Vijay is not a true life hero, just a hero before the cameras. Vijay however filed a case and made the court retract this statement. But the statement made by the court is the truth, time has proven it.</summary></entry></feed>