<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-07-02T20:33:12+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Covid, and the lack of data</title><link href="/2025/07/02/covid-and-the-lack-of-data.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Covid, and the lack of data" /><published>2025-07-02T20:32:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-07-02T20:32:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/07/02/covid-and-the-lack-of-data</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/07/02/covid-and-the-lack-of-data.html">&lt;p&gt;It was the second covid wave recently. In the first one we had decisive announcement from the government and strict actions were taken. In the second none. Experts were saying covid was spreading, but people behave like fools, like they were immune, as though they had the ultimate control, and as though nothing bad could happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make matters worst, I used to go and sit in my friend’s office because he requested me so, and from their behavior (just by seeing how they approach tech issues), I could infer none would sanitize their hands, none would use masks, the office was packed, filled with non thinkers, ignorance dominated their brains. I feel sorry and not sorry for them. I also knew from the behavior my friend, that he will not declare holiday to slow spread the virus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What appalled me was the lack of data and information this time. I had to go to X, type “Covid India” in search and try to find out. There were deaths, and there were people who acted as though nothing happened. The government gave no solid information which people could follow. On one hand they said they were ready with beds and oxygen, and on other hand they said that there is nothing to fear. I wondered what’s the truth?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;None were following precautions, I think herd immunity saved us this time. I wonder what would have happened if COVID found a new way to kill us all of a sudden. Thankfully it did not happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;modi-and-lack-of-data&quot;&gt;Modi and lack of data&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a Prime Minister called Modi, who is an illiterate person. I think he himself has admitted that he worked in tea shops. Under his rule, I think the stats department is dysfunctional. Being uneducated and non-intellectual, under his rule, India could have hid true COVID deaths. During the first covid, during the 19’s and 20’s, a lot of people migrated to their hometowns and died on the way. Modi has no data collected about their deaths.  We have our leader with such immense stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stalin-and-covid&quot;&gt;Stalin and covid&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was during last COVID, my state chief minister Stalin got elected. You must have seen his election campaign, there would be no COVID precautions. He or his supporters never wore masks. I don’t think anyone sanitized their hands. Yet after winning the elections and becoming the chief minister, he was shameless enough to ask Tamil people to donate money for the governments fight against COVID.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;will-we-ever-have-responsible-honest-and-intelligent-politicians&quot;&gt;Will we ever have responsible, honest and intelligent politicians?&lt;/h2&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It was the second covid wave recently. In the first one we had decisive announcement from the government and strict actions were taken. In the second none. Experts were saying covid was spreading, but people behave like fools, like they were immune, as though they had the ultimate control, and as though nothing bad could happen.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Read Same As Ever in 5 minutes</title><link href="/2025/06/15/read-same-as-ever-in-5-minutes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Read Same As Ever in 5 minutes" /><published>2025-06-15T10:28:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-06-15T10:28:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/06/15/read-same-as-ever-in-5-minutes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/06/15/read-same-as-ever-in-5-minutes.html">&lt;p&gt;This is the short of the book:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you do not know history, you cannot know the present or the future.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Risk is something which you do not see coming.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you want to be happy, you should start with low expectations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;One person can be brilliant in one thing and terrible in another.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;People always crave certainty, no matter how false it may be.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stories are more powerful than any reason or data.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There are always events happening in the world which are of low probability.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In uncertain times, stress can be channeled in positive ways.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Progress takes time while catastrophes occur suddenly.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Always leave room for error in whatever you do.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Compounding can turn tiny into huge, over the long run.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Anything worthwhile takes time to grow and pain is inevitable.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Most of the things in this world are driven by incentives.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The experience you had is more convincing than anything else.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The best financial plan is to save like a pessimist and invest like an optimist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This is the short of the book:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why we will never know the truth about the Rafael’s</title><link href="/2025/06/04/why-we-will-never-know-about-the-truth-about-the-rafaels.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why we will never know the truth about the Rafael&apos;s" /><published>2025-06-04T09:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-06-04T09:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/06/04/why-we-will-never-know-about-the-truth-about-the-rafaels</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/06/04/why-we-will-never-know-about-the-truth-about-the-rafaels.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Rafale_-_RIAT_2009_%283751416421%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think BJP has got a history of corruption in defense procurement and in war. RSS that wants to promote hindutva in India, and is happy to see some sort of BJP power in India, not matter how corrupt it is. I think RSS leaders have got accustomed to money and high life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the Kargil war, there was a corruption in procurement of coffins, the Congress raised it in the Parliament, and to that I think Advani replied ‘we must not disturb the sanctity of the army’. To my ears it sounds like ‘oh yeah, we looted, just ignore it’. Pakistan is Pakistan because of its corrupt armed forces, are we moving to that state? I don’t know. Now we have got this brainless Narendra Modi ruling our country, and India is no better than Pakistan. Islam is replaced with Hinduism. That’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder how Vajpayee got away with that corruption? Still we all believe he is a good man. Shame on us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to this Rafael. Rahul Gandhi had already made fiery speeches in the Parliament about corruptions in Rafael deal. Modi tried to duck it, and just like this coffin stuff it died out. In the last war with Pakistan, Pakistan claims to have shot down jets well within Indian border, French seem to acknowledge it, while India denies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a tweet by The Hindu about the downing of Indian aircraft, then it was taken down. Hindu could have just said this tweet was false and could have left it there. They could have said how this misinformation convinced them to put a tweet, and what had convinced them now it was wrong. But it was taken down without any reason. That’s a hallmark of Godi media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why India denies? I think it’s to defend Modi. Certainly Rafael’s deal is not a clean deal. If Rafael’s were downed and if once again the congress pounces, Modi will be on the back foot. The only defense like the Vajpyee era would be to say, let’s not probe it so that the sanctity of the army is not questioned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are lots of things we need to think about. Why did the Modi did no know about Chinese weapons? Don’t we have enough spies in China and Pakistan? If we do not have, what’s the use of having this government for so long? If yes, why on earth they went on to purchase Rafael’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are we a nation if we cannot even dominate the skies of a banana republic, which has not other job than to get Islamic money to spread Jihad and terrorism across the planet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;investigate-rafael-deal&quot;&gt;Investigate Rafael deal&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need a proper investigation into the Rafael deal, we need to know how it got through. We also need a proper audit of BJP people wealth before and after this deal took place. Who are their relatives, what are their purchases and spending, and what’s their value now? We need to see which companies were involved and how much money was donated by them to the BJP via electoral bonds? But will that happen if Modi is in power?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly feel Rafael compared to Chinese tech is a dud, and Modi cheated our nation, despite having intelligence about it. If he couldn’t develop sufficient spying about our neighbors, is he fit to be a Prime Minister?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-are-terror-camps-attacked-only-now-and-then&quot;&gt;Why are terror camps attacked only now and then?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder if India had no idea about terror camps in Pakistan before Phelgham? It just after the terror attack, India claimed to have destroyed the terror camps. Are they no terror camps in Pakistan operating now? Why India is not destroying them? Are these Madaras preaching ahimsa?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This whole attack I feel is a media stunt, just to satisfy the people that something has been done. Just bomb some roofs and runways, and that’s it. India spent some billion dollars for Modi advertising, so that we don’t realize he is shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;strong-godi-media&quot;&gt;Strong Godi media&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One problem India faces is, that it has strong Godi media. That is Media that might be sponsored by Modi, and it praises Modi and hindutva. These people have no brains enough to think and find out that there is no God, or any other supernatural forces. They are brain-dead and hence can’t realize that the vedas are fake and void, and they can never infer that religion is removed from the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They think something glorious can be achieved by the way this mythical God Ram ruled this nation. That’s bull shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since BJP talks hindutva, these Godi media support Modi irrationally. I have also seen videos where people in Godi media say that India sent decoys with Rafael’s electronic signature, and these were destroyed by the Chinese missiles. While France acknowledges that Rafael’s were shot down. Such a misinformation we are flooded with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-government-that-hides-and-manipulates-data&quot;&gt;A government that hides and manipulates data&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi government denies data to the public. It’s shameless and lethargic. It seems not to have estimate of how many died in COVID migrations, it didn’t even bother to find out after the viral threat subsided. It simply doesn’t seem to care about knowing its people, while it licks and polishes the shoes of Ambani’s, Adani’s, the Tata’s etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even the current GDP calculation is a spoof. Unable to give high growth numbers that Manmohan gave, the government reframed the calculation to look high, and it’s just to save Modi’s face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I have a lot of reasons to believe Modi is hiding a lot of losses, and exaggerating successes to hide his corruption about Rafael deal.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why are Indians so obsessed with shit?</title><link href="/2025/04/14/why-are-indians-so-obessed-with-shit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why are Indians so obsessed with shit?" /><published>2025-04-14T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-04-14T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/04/14/why-are-indians-so-obessed-with-shit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/04/14/why-are-indians-so-obessed-with-shit.html">&lt;p&gt;I was at an house warming festival of my friends. Usually I don’t goto functions, I don’t think that defines friendship, but this one I had to go, because I was dealing with a guy who doesn’t think like me. He helped me when I was down, so I cannot let him down. I went. The first thing I noticed was that there was a lump of cow dung before his house, as I am a Hindu (but practically a atheist), I knew what had happened. A cow must have be brought in for worship to his car porch and it did its job. Just meters away were laid tables where we must eat. Fucking God! None bothered about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did see a old lawyer friend sitting and I approached him to talk, I said ‘why do you sit here, it smells because of the dung…’, and his reply shocked me. He claimed this stink was good for health. What the fuck!!!! I didn’t know what to say, I moved away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Science has progressed a lot. Yes once we destroyed most of our forests for agriculture and we did not have much logs to burn, and cow dung was a source of fire. It was also used a binding material to make plaster for walls and floors because quick lime was bloody expensive. But now? We have electricity to cook, in older homes there are still bottled gas, and we don’t need cow dung any more. We have cement these days. We have education and people who did attend that house warming, I am sure wil claim themselves as educated. Yet they are so obsessed with dung, and don’t even care to eat even if its meters away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even today I am sure some Indian is openly defecating somewhere. This happens even though back in 1970’s I think Indira Gandhi government realized shit as a threat to Indians health and campaigned to use toilets. This had a positive effect on Indian society, death rates dropped dramatically, and along with agricultural revolution our population exploded. But yet when I talk with my college friend who is from rural India, he swore by the convenience of open defecation, and swore against toilets. I was stunned. He is now in Singapore, I wonder if he defecates on Singapore’s roads now :) ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-vegetarianism-a-culprit&quot;&gt;Is vegetarianism a culprit?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200127-how-a-vegan-diet-could-affect-your-intelligence&quot;&gt;article in the BBC&lt;/a&gt;, how vegetarianism could affect ones brain. We humans cannot produce essential protein needed for us, and some of these are produced later in our digestive track and will not be absorbed into our body. To compensate for lack of these compounds, some animals eat their own droppings, but we humans don’t do it. Indians are mostly vegetarian and to get at least traces of these compounds, we have evolved a life where shit is available here and there, so that if some woman handle cow shit and cook or serve food, these compounds go into us, and possibly kids play in a playground which has defections, they get some amount of it too. I am not sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;come-out&quot;&gt;Come out&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish people will get more educated, they should not ignore what they have learned, and they must apply it. This unhealthy lifestyle, no matter how much its promoted by tradition and religion should be shunned. A healthier and more knowledgeable society should be created.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was at an house warming festival of my friends. Usually I don’t goto functions, I don’t think that defines friendship, but this one I had to go, because I was dealing with a guy who doesn’t think like me. He helped me when I was down, so I cannot let him down. I went. The first thing I noticed was that there was a lump of cow dung before his house, as I am a Hindu (but practically a atheist), I knew what had happened. A cow must have be brought in for worship to his car porch and it did its job. Just meters away were laid tables where we must eat. Fucking God! None bothered about it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What has gradually disappeared over the last thirty years without people really noticing?</title><link href="/2025/03/13/what-has-gradually-disappeared-over-the-last-thirty-years-without-people-really-noticing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What has gradually disappeared over the last thirty years without people really noticing?" /><published>2025-03-13T18:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-03-13T18:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/03/13/what-has-gradually-disappeared-over-the-last-thirty-years-without-people-really-noticing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/03/13/what-has-gradually-disappeared-over-the-last-thirty-years-without-people-really-noticing.html">&lt;p&gt;I live in Chennai, and these have disappeared in the name of development:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gardens around the house.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of garden wildlife, from insects to mongoose to snakes etc.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Verandah.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Large Balconies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Socializing with neighbors.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Playgrounds.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Spacious parks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clean air.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Accessible and clean groundwater.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Free water (never thought water would be sold one day).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Giving free food.  (when I was young, anyone could knock our doors for food and they will get it)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Following traffic rules.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fast travel across city.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Slow paced lifestyle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not being greedy for money.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Functions taking place in home. No need for marriage halls.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Home cooked food. (I feel Kitchen should be eliminated to liberate women).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We buying our own groceries.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Going to office.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Library.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Teachers and principal having control of educational institutions. They being respected as Gods.  (Today, the money minded politicians and businessmen don’t respect teachers).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fountain pens &amp;amp; Writing. (I feel they are making a comeback)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not smoking, drinking in public.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Talking in tea shops.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Talking to people while sitting on culvet under a tree.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trees&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Walkable platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Financial Stability.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Telegram&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Writing Letters&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Long distant trunk calls (STD / ISD)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;FAX&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Computer Printers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Compact Disk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;USB (Almost Gone)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Floppy Disk.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Theaters and going to movies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Less populated cities.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Receiving and visiting relatives and friends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I live in Chennai, and these have disappeared in the name of development:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Heirs of corrupt should surrender 80% of their wealth in India</title><link href="/2025/03/08/heirs-of-corrupt-should-current-80-of-their-wealth-in-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Heirs of corrupt should surrender 80% of their wealth in India" /><published>2025-03-08T12:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-03-08T12:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/03/08/heirs-of-corrupt-should-current-80-of-their-wealth-in-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/03/08/heirs-of-corrupt-should-current-80-of-their-wealth-in-india.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3a/J_Jayalalithaa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Jayalalitha the Corrupt&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure if today is corrupt Jayalalith’s birthday, AIADMK people were celebrating with the corrupt women’s picture for something. My blood boiled. Will any person with dignity join a party that accept a declared criminal as their leader? Yet we have got tens of thousands of undignified people in Tamilnadu, electing undignified persons as our leader. Shame. Bloody shame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also thought what will happen if we had a dignified person as our Chief Minister? We have graves of Jayalalitha who is a corrupt leader, yet Stalin is not dignified enough to remove her grave from Marina, neither he is dignified enough to resign. Stalin knows very well that Karunanidhi, MGR, and Annadurai watched corruption and were mute. So these people graves should be removed too, and Marina should be kept clean. Yet those graves are there advertising the undignified politics we have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just because Annandurai, MGR, and Karunanidhi are not proven criminals, it cannot be said that they can never be proven criminals. What to do if they are proven criminals? Most people loot for their families to prosper generations, or the heirs of their wealth to prosper. So I feel India should enact a law that says when someone is proven criminal who has looted the state and is no more, then 80% of the wealth of their heirs should be confiscated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A audit of loot should be done, and 18% per annum compound interest should be calculated, if the surrendered wealth is not matching up, then their heirs should be arrested for treason. If the 80% is more than the looted amount and the compound interest, then their heirs can be let out to live as guilt free citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This should not just apply for politicians, it should apply for deceased bureaucrats, and normal citizens as well. The heirs of any deceased who has given and taken even 1 paisa as bribe, should loose 80% of their wealth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This strict measure will make people aware of what they inherit, and people will be more educated, and will know from where their finances come from. We won’t have lethargic bitches and bastards roaming around the nation like kings and queens, while a honest man works like hell and dies in poverty and vain.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Jayalalitha the Corrupt</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The consequence of India having idiot Modi as Prime Minister</title><link href="/2025/02/16/the-consequence-of-india-having-idiot-modi-as-prime-minister.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The consequence of India having idiot Modi as Prime Minister" /><published>2025-02-16T09:56:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-02-16T09:56:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/02/16/the-consequence-of-india-having-idiot-modi-as-prime-minister</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/02/16/the-consequence-of-india-having-idiot-modi-as-prime-minister.html">&lt;p&gt;India had great intellectuals like Nehru as Prime Minister, the one we have now, Modi  is a absolute idiot, only fit for drinking cow urine and feeding on cow dung. Let me explain what I mean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;maldives-criticizing-modi&quot;&gt;Maldives criticizing Modi&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime ago Maldives ministers criticized Modi, there was huge uproar in India. Though Modi was criticized, it was promoted by Godi media as thogh India had been criticized, and Modi went to Lakshadweep island and said that India should quit Maldives. Well, a critic on one person was projected by Godi media as a slap to India. In fact &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindu.com/news/international/maldives-govt-distances-itself-from-derogatory-remarks-against-pm-modi-by-minister/article67715983.ece&quot;&gt;Maldives did suspend three of its ministers&lt;/a&gt;. But a big buzz was created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;indians-treated-like-shit&quot;&gt;Indian’s treated like shit&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently USA deported about 100 Indians, they were illegal, yet they should be treated as human. They were handcuffed, their legs too were chained, and they were made to travel 40 hours, I have no clue what they did for nature calls. India raised no protest against this animal like treatment of Indians. The Godi media too never took it in a big way. May be for the Godi media, its criticizing Modi is criticizing India, whereas even though 100+ Indians were treated as animals, it meant nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trump-abusing-india&quot;&gt;Trump abusing India&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/PPrxCLMI1iI?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent India, US joint press brief, you can see trump abusing India right before Modi. Modi who claims he is super nationalistic and super patriot, just stood there. Either he was so dumb that he had no clue what was going on, or though he knew, he is an idiot and coward who cannot counter it. I wish he had at least a ball. Just one at least, a broken one would have done something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Godi media too was silent, I am not sure if they hailed his trip as a great triumph, but they just kept quiet when India was bashed like hell by Trump. In this blog I will tell you how Modi if he had some brains could have countered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;need-for-imbalanced-tariff&quot;&gt;Need for imbalanced tariff&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were long a slave nation to the Brits, and hence we are still a very weak nation today. We were abused by the west, and still proper retributions have’t been paid. In this blog I will explain how USA stalled India’s progress, and you decide if there should be a tariff imbalance or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;yale-university&quot;&gt;Yale University&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/36/Enoch_Seeman_the_younger_-_Portrait_of_Gov._Elihu_Yale_%281648-9%E2%80%931721%29_-_1789.1_-_Yale_University_Art_Gallery.jpg/500px-Enoch_Seeman_the_younger_-_Portrait_of_Gov._Elihu_Yale_%281648-9%E2%80%931721%29_-_1789.1_-_Yale_University_Art_Gallery.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elihu_Yale&quot;&gt;Elihu Yale, the looter of Chennai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s start with a History. The Yale university in USA was created with the wealth looted from my city Chennai, India. Yale amassed his wealth by not so genuine practices, and he took his loot to England. USA was a poor nation then, and when they wanted to build a university, Yale donated part of wealth he looted to the university, thus the university was named after him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact it was my city that is solely responsible for the existance of this university, and I don’t think USA acknowledges it and I don’t think its thankful for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think Modi is literate enough to know this, but at least he could have asked the “learned men” who accompanied him and told facts like this to correct USA, and to humble it. But he was dumb like the statue of Lord Ram erected in Ayodhya.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;global-warming&quot;&gt;Global Warming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USA is the largest emitter of green house gases, it’s the leading cause of Global warming, and we in India too are are experiencing the consequence. USA should be infact be paying trillions of dollars to all countries on this planet to cope with the damage it causes. Yet it’s foolish leader Trump want to drill for more oil and increase fossil fuel usage. Modi could have pointed this simple fact out to Trump. Yet he stayed dumb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1972-nuclear-threat&quot;&gt;1972 Nuclear Threat&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1972 war, USA sent its naval fleet and threatened India with a nuclear strike, it was hell bent on defeating India, Soviet Union saved us by sending its subs to our East Coast. Till today, USA hasn’t asked a sorry for it. This act of USA should have prolonged the war, costed more lives, it also put the independence of Bangladesh into jeopardy. USA never paid us any compensation for this cruel act. Modi could have pointed this out, yet he stayed dumb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;promoting-jihadist&quot;&gt;Promoting Jihadist&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uqZ-ToXjCz0?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch this video, Ronald Regan, another dumb leader, named a launch of space shuttle after Taliban. The bureaucrats of USA cannot think, they thought that snakes thrown at backyard of some one will never bite them, and here they are after loosing twin towers, and they lost the war in Afghanistan. They supported the terrorist nation of Pakistan which shielded Osama Bin Laden who was responsible for killing thousands of US citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even today, our soldiers are been killed by the Jihadist promoted by USA, and USA does not pay us single penny for damage it still causes to India. Modi stood there along with Trump as though he does not know this fact. Fucking ball less coward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sanctions&quot;&gt;Sanctions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India, or any other nation on this planet has the right to test nuclear weapons. But when we did it, USA slapped sanctions on us. Why? Because according to them we are an inferior species who are not worthwhile to have nukes. Such is the animalistic attitude of US people. Because of their sanctions, many of our programs like the space program, our fighter jet program, our nuclear program stalled. India lost billions of dollars due to sanctions, yet Modi did not have the courage to raise this issue on the podium with Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-killing-of-indian-scientists-and-lal-bahadur-sastri&quot;&gt;The killing of Indian Scientists and Lal Bahadur Sastri&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Homi_Jehangir_Bhabha_1960s.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Homi_Jehangir_Bhabha&quot;&gt;Homi Bhabha&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mysterious way in which Homi Baba died, if he had lived, our nuke programs could have been much faster. Who killed him? There is a strong suspicion that USA did it. Did USA open up its gates for Indian investigators? No. Why? Most probably because they killed Homi Baba. Till today USA has not said that it will let India to investigate people in USA, nor it had asked sorry. Such an evil nation it is. Any way how will a nation that kills millions every year be sorry for causing a plane crash? You need to be a human to feel sorry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/22/Lal_Bahadur_Shastri_%28from_stamp%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lal_Bahadur_Sastri&quot;&gt;Lal Bahadur Sastri&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One our excellent Prime Ministers Lal Bahadur Sastri mysteriously died in Tashkant. Hand of CIA is suspected. Yet USA did not throw open the gates for investigation, neither it admitted to its mistakes and asked sorry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vickram Sarabhai too died in mysterious circumstances. Was USA involved? We don’t know, did USA throw open its gates for investigation? Once again no. Modi could have brought up these issues, and could have said how much potentially USA costs us, and how it never paid us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;going-against-indias-nuclear-plans&quot;&gt;Going against India’s nuclear plans&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USA never wanted India to be a powerful nuclear state, it had done what ever it could to destabilize us. Sanctions, mysterious disappearance of scientists, causing brain drain and so on. It forced us to open up our reactors to USA’s dog IAEA. Modi could have easily pointed these out, yet he stood like dumb before the world press and Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nambhi-narayanan&quot;&gt;Nambhi Narayanan&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/0/0a/Nambi_Narayanan.jpg/672px-Nambi_Narayanan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nambi_Narayanan&quot;&gt;Nambi Narayanan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the case of Nambi Naryanan. He himself says USA could be behind he being falsely charged by Indian police on espionage case. ISRO is an open organization and they don’t hide their plans. But all of a sudden, Kerala police accused him of selling public domain ISRO data to other countries, its a laughable allegation. Till today who is behind it is not fully clear. If my memory is right A.K.Antony is one among the person who conducted this treason against India. Was his church any way controlled and / or connected with USA? Modi could have raises this issue too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;still-not-late&quot;&gt;Still not late&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay Modi is a coward and cannot speak on the podium with Trump. At least after the press meet Indian bureaucrats could have held another press meeting and have put forward these issues and have argued how much damage USA caused to India, and thus imbalanced tariffs are justifiable. They could have boldly said that just tarrifs are not enough, but USA owes tens of billions of dollars as retribution to India. Under a coward and unlearned priminster, how will they open their mouth? Even though Modi is back in India, I don’t think its late to point these out to brain dead Trump and his nation, but I am sure coward India will not do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish someone as knowledgeable as Sashi Tharoor is our priminster, some one who would  turn his back on Trump, or oppose him as soon as he abuses our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Indians should become intellectuals enough so that intellectuals become our leaders, not some school quitting religious fanatic who can’t even table facts and argue at the right time. Modi has costed a lot for India, and I am sure he will be expensive and cost us a lot more in times to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">India had great intellectuals like Nehru as Prime Minister, the one we have now, Modi is a absolute idiot, only fit for drinking cow urine and feeding on cow dung. Let me explain what I mean.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Perils of work from office</title><link href="/2025/01/29/perils-of-work-from-office.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Perils of work from office" /><published>2025-01-29T17:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-29T17:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/29/perils-of-work-from-office</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/29/perils-of-work-from-office.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;healthy-living&quot;&gt;Healthy Living&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing this blog with a throat and sinus infection. Just two weeks ago people in my office carried it, I had to go to office because it was the norm, the result, last week I took 3 days of leave and once I got better I went, and this week I am down again. Some virus is circulating. The COVID years were my healthiest, those who stayed clean were spared. I worked from home for a company that was efficient, (there were technical idiots in it mixing ReactJS Development with Rails, that’s another story,) but when it comes to work from home they got it spot on. So when it comes to healthy living, work from home wins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;traffic&quot;&gt;Traffic&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In work from home, I could think more. I could think in times I should worry about Chennai traffic, while people who are drunk drive freely, people get license not by passing driving exams, but by bribing the RTO (there is no other way). In my current office parking is crazy, and I have to go at odd times compromising my sleep. A person who is fully awake at 11AM, is forced to wake up at 5AM. Just to avoid traffic and parking issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am using an electric car, so I am a bit lucky on transport cost, else it would cost me Rs 300 every day to go to my office, thanks to Modi’s inflation. What I can say is even this can be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;money&quot;&gt;Money&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was once in an office where I was working, suddenly a boy jumped besides me asking for Rs 200/-, I asked for what, then he said “boss, that(fucking) …… has her birthday, we must buy cake and treats for her birthday.” Bloody damn. If prostitution was legal in a big way why would these people have to run behind girls dogs behind a bitch I thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to work from home, you can simply say congratz or a thumbs up on WhatsApp and that’s it. Who cares who has the dream of fucking who?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But ya in my previous office there was bloody inefficient team that did want work from office, thankfully it did not materialize. We had to attend in person ceremonies of our manager, because there was no way to avoid it. Fortunately I was in a team that was a bit efficient. I did attend those functions because my project manager was a good person and not because we saw each other every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in work from office you have to shed money for some fucking person just because the fucking person exists, and its no fault of you that one exists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;team-that-does-not-know-remote-work&quot;&gt;Team that does not know remote work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my present office, people went on Pongal leave, out of the 5 or so days they were out, only 2 days were supposed to be holidays, I tried contacting a team member, but to no avail. Teams in my present company are stuck if they are out of office. I wonder if they will survive if they need to work as independent freelancers, launch a product that challenges us and so on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;just-a-paying-club&quot;&gt;Just a paying club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though people put scene they work 10, 11 hours a day, in reality I don’t think one can work, or code more than 3 - 4 hours a day. I have worked just 1 hour a day and have completed stuff on time. But yes I did use highly productive languages like Python, Ruby, Clojure and so on, with a rock solid test suite. I would in fact encourage a programmer to restrict himself to just 4 hours of work a day (including mindless, depressing and unproductive meetings), to be productive and steady on the longer run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In software industry, if you claim more than 4 hours of work per day, then it means you do not know to use a computer that makes you highly productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In work from office it’s just a club you attend where your boss pays you for your socializing, that consumes the hours more than 4 that you claim to be working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;leaders-insisting-on-work-from-office&quot;&gt;Leaders insisting on work from office&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do leaders insist on work from office, even though software today is the transfer of data that can be done from anywhere? One simple reason. Control. Of course in companies where bosses are dumb, and I had to work from home, control was done by having no so transparent appraisal process, everyone in my previous office knew appraisal was a spoof, but in most office, the boss wants to be seen as a strong guy / gal, and it’s far easier to control you in an environment owned more by your boss than owned by you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;office-rent&quot;&gt;Office Rent&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In city like Chennai, damn the office rent! Damn the greedy and lazy real estate holders. Who will pay so much? Instead of paying rent, just convert small part of your home to office just for this stupid Indian government compliance purpose and make all things remote. I.T industry is literally loosing billions because ignorant people have risen to the top, and they want to put scene by having large offices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Healthy Living</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Understanding Quantum Computing</title><link href="/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Understanding Quantum Computing" /><published>2025-01-12T20:36:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-12T20:36:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing.html">&lt;p&gt;Richard Feynman said, if anyone says they understood Quantum Physics, it means they haven’t understood it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineering is more about practicality than about science. Fuzzy Logic was hated by mathematicians while we engineers are using it for a long time, similarly, we have looked at practical applications of stuff and used it, without having a full understanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently Google announced their willow processor. They claimed what was done by their computer in 5 minutes will take the best super computer today \(10^{25}\) years to complete. That’s a staggering claim. In this blog I would like to explain to you the reader how such feats are possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computers are here to solve problems, so here is one. Imagine you are in a room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%20%280%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are the green dot, and you want to reach the red X. So there are four pathways. One way to reach this path is like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%281%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, that’s one way, there are three ways left. You chose the path at your free will right? Well if you say yes, then you are absolutely wrong. The physics of this universe made you choose that path. In fact there are an uncountable number of universes with uncountable numbers of you, you just experience one of them, that to a short time interval of it. All that had happened is happening, and all that lies in the future has already happened, and there is no time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay lets keep it simple, now imagine there are four universes where it had made you choose four different paths as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%282%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subatomic particles communicate across multiple universes which our brain can’t comprehend, but even before you start a problem, all possible solutions and failures to solve it exists. In many universes you would (in truth that universe would have made you) have solved the problem with flying colors, in many universes you would have failed miserably, in many universes that problem simply would not exist. So say at quantum level if you know how you solved all problems in all universes, in our simple case it might look like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%283%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As indicated above, you would know all possible solutions of the problem you are solving in an instant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s say we have a problem where only 2 out of 4 paths lead you to the solution, a traditional you, or a computer should test each way to find a solution, but a quantum you, or a computer, since it communicates with parallel universes will know exactly which path leads you to red X, and in which paths you have banged yourself onto a wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%284%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Richard Feynman said, if anyone says they understood Quantum Physics, it means they haven’t understood it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Signs of a Highly Intelligent Employee</title><link href="/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Signs of a Highly Intelligent Employee" /><published>2025-01-07T20:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-07T20:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee.html">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They cheat on their job with a side hustle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They treat everybody equal (including the cleaner).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They rebel against micromanagement and dictator leaders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They know when to say no to a meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They help others advance in their career.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They don’t respond to most emails.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They don’t attend meetings, but find efficient ways to communicate.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They stay away from gossip and corporate politics.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They create passive income so if they get fired it matters less.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They try entrepreneurship at least once to see what it feels like.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re fine to be the dumbest person in the room.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They ruthlessly protect their time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They focus on outcomes not KPIs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re wildly open to new ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They create stuff people want.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They learn without being told.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re humble.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">They cheat on their job with a side hustle. They treat everybody equal (including the cleaner). They rebel against micromanagement and dictator leaders. They know when to say no to a meeting. They help others advance in their career. They don’t respond to most emails. They don’t attend meetings, but find efficient ways to communicate. They stay away from gossip and corporate politics. They create passive income so if they get fired it matters less. They try entrepreneurship at least once to see what it feels like. They’re fine to be the dumbest person in the room. They ruthlessly protect their time. They focus on outcomes not KPIs. They’re wildly open to new ideas. They create stuff people want. They learn without being told. They’re humble.</summary></entry></feed>