<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-12-27T15:41:09+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">I Love Ruby comes to top</title><link href="/2017/12/27/I-Love-Ruby-comes-to-top.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Love Ruby comes to top" /><published>2017-12-27T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-12-27T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/12/27/I-Love-Ruby-comes-to-top</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/12/27/I-Love-Ruby-comes-to-top.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ilr_at_top.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a pleasant surprise for me to type “I Love Ruby” on Google and to find that
my book has bubbled to the top finally. There were many reason why it did not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First I had no dedicated website for it. I was lazy and first published it out
of Dropbox. But Dropbox was an unethical company so I switched to Open mail box.
Open mail box had own cloud in it. But ll of a sudden open mail box maid these
features as paid and I was left in dust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally I moved to github and now the project is hosted there and it seems to
be okay. Any way if you are Rubyist you can get my book in the links provided
below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mindaslab.github.io/I-Love-Ruby/&quot;&gt;I Love Ruby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Employee Skill and Business Needs</title><link href="/2017/12/05/Employee-Skill-and-Business-Needs.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Employee Skill and Business Needs" /><published>2017-12-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-12-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/12/05/Employee-Skill-and-Business-Needs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/12/05/Employee-Skill-and-Business-Needs.html">&lt;p&gt;You are a proud programmer, you know Ruby and there is no programming language
like it, and all of a sudden you are caught up in a situation thats unrelated to
you. Sales of the software slumps and your boss yells at your team. You don’t
know what’s happening, but you are made to work hard, atleast sit in your office,
make some cold marketting calls. What you must do? The best answer is to leave
the business and find something else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find not so easy as a programer and as an artist that businesses are not able
to understand ones skills and are unable to utilize ones talent. Imagine you are
an author in 1960’s, you write a novel, a publisher likes it and pays for you
to complete it. You complete it and goback to him, then he says that as a writer
you must understand the publishing business, you say you do, then he shows a
press machine and tells you to operate it. Imagine how stupid it will be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think its absurd to tell the writer to operate the press machine, you
should think how absurd Info Tech companies are operating in India and around
the world. People with money seem to have no clue how to run a company. People
have left programming a while ago and seem to forget how to be a programmer,
they seem to forget the pressures programmer faces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its like press or publishing house been run by a person who doesn’t know what
it means to be a writer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You are a proud programmer, you know Ruby and there is no programming language like it, and all of a sudden you are caught up in a situation thats unrelated to you. Sales of the software slumps and your boss yells at your team. You don’t know what’s happening, but you are made to work hard, atleast sit in your office, make some cold marketting calls. What you must do? The best answer is to leave the business and find something else.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unfair expectations</title><link href="/2017/12/02/unfair-expectations.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unfair expectations" /><published>2017-12-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-12-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/12/02/unfair-expectations</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/12/02/unfair-expectations.html">&lt;p&gt;I am consulting for a company now in Python web development. My team is in a
state where it does not know what HTTP 500 error is. That too one is 10 year
experienced developer and another is 4. I raised an alarm that we may not make
it this sprint, and what I get as a reward? It was told to me that I am been
projected as a great guy who will fix things up, a kind of guy who will not fail,
a kind of Rommel under Nazi’s and hence I must make things to work. I was told I
am granted all powers which means I can torture any one I want to get things done.
Thats far far away from who I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These type of expectations put me down. I know who and what I am more than anyone
else (may be Google knows more as it spies on me all time) and I know my
capabilities, I know my laziness and how an hurricane would not
move me when I am lazy. I know what I can do and what I cannot. And some one
places a blind expectation on me and that person controls my earnings I surely
don’t know what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not just in profession, its in society. A engineering mishap in my street
led to water stagnation. Some one had built an elevated barrier that obstructs
the flow of rain water to nearby pond. People in my street came up with an
idiotic idea for flood prevention, by elevating our road which would give us dry land but just would
push this problem further. When I pointed out we need a drain and not more barrier
I became a villain, but few people realized my logic and told me to run for elections!
Damn!!! I ain’t do this for power and popularity, I am just raising a problem
that my common sense put up to me. Thats it!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And not just society too, my family thinks I am a superman, some one who can do
my office work, attend family functions and a person like Gandhi who lives for
others than myself. Months ago my refusal to attend a family function led to
a torrent of blames and politics. People simply fail to grasp its not wise to
attend a function 100’s of kilometers away that too on an inconvenient time.
My request to attend function on another day at a good time that suits me was
rejected and I was villanized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frankly I don’t know what to do with these humans. They constantly need me to
boost up their image and wealth. They would trade my brand shamelessly for their gains. I
feel I am becoming more of a show piece, a piece of carbon thats been called a diamond
and sold for millions when I am just what I am. I am a man who loves to live in peace,
not any more, not any less.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I am consulting for a company now in Python web development. My team is in a state where it does not know what HTTP 500 error is. That too one is 10 year experienced developer and another is 4. I raised an alarm that we may not make it this sprint, and what I get as a reward? It was told to me that I am been projected as a great guy who will fix things up, a kind of guy who will not fail, a kind of Rommel under Nazi’s and hence I must make things to work. I was told I am granted all powers which means I can torture any one I want to get things done. Thats far far away from who I am.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why not MSP rather than CTC?</title><link href="/2017/11/19/why-not-msp-rather-than-ctc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why not MSP rather than CTC?" /><published>2017-11-19T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-11-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/11/19/why-not-msp-rather-than-ctc</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/11/19/why-not-msp-rather-than-ctc.html">&lt;p&gt;Your company cares about you. It has given you the opportunity to succeed right?
And they make your life better and simple right? Okay in that case why don’t
your I.T company say that this is the Minimum Salary Paid (MSP) paid to you
rather than you are a Cost To The Company (CTC)?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, why am I proposing this. Its simple. CTC is a degrading term. It means that 
you are costing that company, possibly not worth it. Well, that what it really means.
You are an liability rather than an asset. Customer brings in money and
magically it turns into profit, and you bite away those profits being an cost to
and rather not an asset to the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies that truly care about people should not advertise that if you are
employed and it costs the company so much, saying that you cost a bite out of
their fortune, rather they must praise your worth. Companies must say that you
are worth so much, so this is the minimum salary that we can pay you. That means
at the end of working for that year your account will have that much amount
credited by the company. And that is a minimum amount. It can go up and not down.
This means that your minimum worth is so much and maximum is yet to be explored!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wouldn’t that be nice?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your company cares about you. It has given you the opportunity to succeed right? And they make your life better and simple right? Okay in that case why don’t your I.T company say that this is the Minimum Salary Paid (MSP) paid to you rather than you are a Cost To The Company (CTC)?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Stubbing with Python in built server</title><link href="/2017/11/12/Stubbing-with-Python-inbuilt-server.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stubbing with Python in built server" /><published>2017-11-12T07:41:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-11-12T07:41:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/11/12/Stubbing-with-Python-inbuilt-server</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/11/12/Stubbing-with-Python-inbuilt-server.html">&lt;p&gt;Its sometimes required that you need to have some url returning some data to
finish your client server software. But you may not have the luxury of server
side thing completed as it may involve some complexities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lets say that I have a json file like this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-json&quot; data-lang=&quot;json&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;name&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Karthik&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;age&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;28&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;name&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Murugan&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;age&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;32&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All I need to do is to create a folder. Create a file say called &lt;em&gt;people.json&lt;/em&gt;
with the data above in it. In my terminal goto that location and type
&lt;code class=&quot;highlight language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;python -m http.server&lt;/code&gt;, launch my browser and type
&lt;em&gt;http://localhost:8000/people.json&lt;/em&gt; and I will be having that data to stub and
complete my work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See my result here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/stubbing_json.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Its sometimes required that you need to have some url returning some data to finish your client server software. But you may not have the luxury of server side thing completed as it may involve some complexities.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Water logging problem in Skylab Avenue Sithalapakkam</title><link href="/2017/11/08/water-logging-problem-in-sithalapakkam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Water logging problem in Skylab Avenue Sithalapakkam" /><published>2017-11-08T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-11-08T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/11/08/water-logging-problem-in-sithalapakkam</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/11/08/water-logging-problem-in-sithalapakkam.html">&lt;p&gt;In Sithalapakkam, we the residents did a stupid thing out of panic. In third
street Skylab Avenue, due to an construction, water levels started to
rise up during November rains. The residents fought against people who blocked
natural water flow and broke the construction which was a good thing, but then
for some reason panic set in. Rather than thinking of building a channel for
water to drain into Sithalapakkam lake, the residents of 3rd street started to
collect money to rise up the road level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes raising up the road level will prevent water from coming in, but till what
limit? Shouldn’t water be let to flow along down the land in efficient
manner than damming it? Now Water stagnates. Stagnates like hell before the
place where road level has been risen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make matters worst, the water has no place to drain and it stagnates on a
piece of land where residents for long had thrown their garbage. The water has
turned black, foul and is leaching into soil. The collective action of us has
proven to be collective stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In Sithalapakkam, we the residents did a stupid thing out of panic. In third street Skylab Avenue, due to an construction, water levels started to rise up during November rains. The residents fought against people who blocked natural water flow and broke the construction which was a good thing, but then for some reason panic set in. Rather than thinking of building a channel for water to drain into Sithalapakkam lake, the residents of 3rd street started to collect money to rise up the road level.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Chennai people feel about the rains?</title><link href="/2017/11/05/what-chennai-people-feel-about-the-rains.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Chennai people feel about the rains?" /><published>2017-11-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-11-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/11/05/what-chennai-people-feel-about-the-rains</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/11/05/what-chennai-people-feel-about-the-rains.html">&lt;p&gt;Chennai had good rains I would say, and as usual the government even though it
was warned by the met department and the opposition to be prepared for rains,
let the city flood. We the Chennai citizens are unhappy about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Do you think Tamilnadu government was prepared for &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/ChennaiRains2017?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#ChennaiRains2017&lt;/a&gt; ?&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Karthikeyan A K (@karthik_ak) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/karthik_ak/status/926497890863681536?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;November 3, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just conducted a poll on twitter and it wasn’t astonishing that most people
feel that the government wasn’t prepared for it. Whats astonishing for me was
22% felt that government was prepared for it! Thats a huge number infact. If
these are the people who are going to vote for AIADMK like fanatics, who knows
it would come to power once again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another poll was about IT companies in Chennai. IT companies are worst managed
things. They are extremely inefficient piece of management, thats because we get
cheap labor in Chennai and hence they can be abused a lot. In fact slaves in
ancient Rome were able to work for just 6 hours and were able to get away and
they had 4 months of holiday! But we are forced to work so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the poll I conducted:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Did your IT company in &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/chennai?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#chennai&lt;/a&gt; made Saturday working because of &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/ChennaiRains2017?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#ChennaiRains2017&lt;/a&gt; ?&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Karthikeyan A K (@karthik_ak) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/karthik_ak/status/926495453645901824?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;November 3, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and not surprisingly looks like 50% of IT companies are inefficient and force
their employees to work on Saturday because of the rain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here is a food for thought, we the people of Chennai too pay taxes like
people in Tokyo:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/o85teh1vU_0?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thehindu.com/opinion/op-ed/should-robots-be-nationalised/article19919764.ece&quot;&gt;Should robots be nationalised?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chennai had good rains I would say, and as usual the government even though it was warned by the met department and the opposition to be prepared for rains, let the city flood. We the Chennai citizens are unhappy about it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kamal has come up to stage 3?</title><link href="/2017/11/05/Kamal-has-come-up-to-stage-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kamal has come up to stage 3?" /><published>2017-11-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-11-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/11/05/Kamal-has-come-up-to-stage-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/11/05/Kamal-has-come-up-to-stage-3.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://media2.intoday.in/indiatoday/images/stories/kamal-hassan_647_082116071527.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are 4 stages in winning a battle against bad people:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;First they ignore you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Then they laugh at you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Then they fight you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Then you win.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To enter politics, especially in Tamilnadu and then to win will take a long time,
no matter who ever it is, Kamaraj, Annadurai, and other looters, they took lot
of time and mentoring and to establish themselves, but for Kamal it seems to be a
quick path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a rationalist and possibly an excellent thinker I guess, he is able to make
his moves quickly and hit opponents in the right spot. Signs are out that Hindu
extremist groups and political wing the BJP are starting to piss their pants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently a person from some terror group in India has called for the execution of
Kamal and his fans just because he wrote an article saying that Hindu terror
is rising in this nation. I am really surprised, rather than ignoring and laughing
at Kamal they have gone to start a fight with him, this is exactly what a truthful
person wants, when wrong doers start to fight, it means one is closer to victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However history cannot be judged, anything could happen. Gandhi agreed to Pakistan,
after its creation he had plans to arose the conscience of people across both
sides and start a non violent struggle for unification, but then Hindu extremist
shot and killed him. The same thing could happen to Kamal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hindu’s, Aryans have no moral defense against Dravidians. Research
proves that Indus script closely matches Tamil than any other language. Possibly
we Dravidians are the true owners of Afganistan, Pakistan, and Infian main land,
and were slowly
pushed down to the peninsula till we became finally powerful and undefeatable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aryans are awry of history and wanted to disagree with findings and wanted people
to believe
they own India 100% and its Hinduism is everything that India needs. This is as
stupid as Pakistan which says its Islam is all that it needs. Now look at
Pakistanis, look how they are? Till yesterday they were slave to United states,
now they are slave to China. Of course this that not vindicate India as it has
become 100% slave and colony of United States now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So lets see, whats your opinion, try voting the poll I created. Who do you
support Kamal or the extremist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Who do you support &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ikamalhaasan?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@ikamalhaasan&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/BJP4India?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@BJP4India&lt;/a&gt; ? | &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/india?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#india&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/politics?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#politics&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/TamilNadu?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#TamilNadu&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/Tamil?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#Tamil&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/HinduTerror?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#HinduTerror&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Karthikeyan A K (@karthik_ak) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/karthik_ak/status/926994092776611840?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;November 5, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.greaterkashmir.com/news/265095-story.html&quot;&gt;Kamal Haasan should be shot dead, says Hindu outfit leader&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thehindu.com/news/national/tamil-nadu/indus-script-early-form-of-dravidian-iravatham-mahadevan/article6600394.ece&quot;&gt;Indus script early form of Dravidian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thehindu.com/features/friday-review/history-and-culture/dravidian-proof-of-the-indus-script/article10310982.ece&quot;&gt;Decoding the Indus Script&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">News reporter Jebersan threatened by BJP</title><link href="/2017/11/02/News-reporter-Jebersan-threatened-by-BJP.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="News reporter Jebersan threatened by BJP" /><published>2017-11-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-11-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/11/02/News-reporter-Jebersan-threatened-by-BJP</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/11/02/News-reporter-Jebersan-threatened-by-BJP.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/52075142.cms&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its alarming how religious violence is increasing in Tamilnadu. Even during
partition of India, Tamilnadu experienced no Hindu and Muslim violence. We
people simply did not know the difference, but now it looks like we must rethink
things. There are people who want to polarize us so that they can come to power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today there was a news in Polimer channel in which Thanthi T.V news person asks
Tamilisai (chief of BJP in Tamilnadu) a question. Tamilisai complains about
the rising corruption in the state and how politicians have turned a blind to
people and how because of that 2 kids have died due to electrocution due to
watter logging because of rains. For that Mr. Jebersan ‘why is BJP so against a
movie Mersal, but its not showing that much intensity against corruption?’,
unable to answer Tamilisai becomes sentimental and flees the spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then comes the drama. BJP cadres threaten and corner Jebersan, they question
him how can he ask such a question. What? Bloody hell, when will this BJP
realize they operate in India which is a democracy? And you should be able to
answer it. Is there room for dumb people like Tamilisai in India or do we want
a leader who can make us understand things well?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By answering Jebersons question, BJP could have unearthed an weakness in it, and
could have proceed to fix it, instead they simply want to hide it from the
external world by threatening others.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Renaming class in Ruby (a kinda)</title><link href="/2017/10/30/Renaming-class-in-Ruby-a-kinda.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Renaming class in Ruby (a kinda)" /><published>2017-10-30T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/10/30/Renaming-class-in-Ruby-a-kinda</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/10/30/Renaming-class-in-Ruby-a-kinda.html">&lt;p&gt;Lets say that you have a situation where you need to code about dogs. You know
that there are different kind of dogs and you end up with  a code structure as
shown&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;table style=&quot;border-spacing: 0&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;gutter gl&quot; style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8
9
10
11
12
13
14
15
16
17&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;module&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;Animal&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;module&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;Domestic&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nc&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;sound&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;woof&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;

  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;module&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;Wild&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nc&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;sound&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;grrr&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there are two kinds of dogs, one is wild that can be accessed like
&lt;code class=&quot;highlight language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Animal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Wild&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt; and other one is
Domestic which could be accessed in similar way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you want to print out how Domestic and Wild dog sounds like you can
write a program as shown:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;table style=&quot;border-spacing: 0&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;gutter gl&quot; style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# using_dog_in_animal_module.rb&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;require_relative&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;dog_in_animal_module.rb&quot;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;include&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Animal&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Domestic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;sound&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Wild&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;sound&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if you look I am using something like this &lt;code class=&quot;highlight language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Domestic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;sound&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt; which is
long to code and tax my fingers, what if I could do something that would make
my typing shorter? Fortunately you can do that in Ruby. See the program below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;table style=&quot;border-spacing: 0&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;gutter gl&quot; style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8
9&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# renaming_class.rb&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;require_relative&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;dog_in_animal_module.rb&quot;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;DomesticDog&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Animal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Domestic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;WildDog&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Animal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Wild&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;DomesticDog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;sound&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;WildDog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;sound&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the code above, notice line 5 and line 6, we are kinda reaming the class.
Rather using the long form &lt;code class=&quot;highlight language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Animal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Domestic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;
we simply assign it to a constant name &lt;code class=&quot;highlight language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;DomesticDog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;  as shown 
&lt;code class=&quot;highlight language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;DomesticDog&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Animal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Domestic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt; and
in line  8 we can use it short like &lt;code class=&quot;highlight language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;DomesticDog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;sound&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a large programming environment, we would have reduced lot of typing. Happy coding! :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mindaslab/ilrx/tree/master/rename_class&quot;&gt;Code Samples&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mindaslab.github.io/I-Love-Ruby/&quot;&gt;Download my Ruby Book&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Lets say that you have a situation where you need to code about dogs. You know that there are different kind of dogs and you end up with a code structure as shown</summary></entry></feed>