<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-01-12T20:38:02+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Understanding Quantum Computing</title><link href="/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Understanding Quantum Computing" /><published>2025-01-12T20:36:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-12T20:36:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing.html">&lt;p&gt;Richard Feynman said, if anyone says they understood Quantum Physics, it means they haven’t understood it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineering is more about practicality than about science. Fuzzy Logic was hated by mathematicians while we engineers are using it for a long time, similarly, we have looked at practical applications of stuff and used it, without having a full understanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently Google announced their willow processor. They claimed what was done by their computer in 5 minutes will take the best super computer today \(10^{25}\) years to complete. That’s a staggering claim. In this blog I would like to explain to you the reader how such feats are possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computers are here to solve problems, so here is one. Imagine you are in a room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%20%280%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are the green dot, and you want to reach the red X. So there are four pathways. One way to reach this path is like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%281%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, that’s one way, there are three ways left. You chose the path at your free will right? Well if you say yes, then you are absolutely wrong. The physics of this universe made you choose that path. In fact there are an uncountable number of universes with uncountable numbers of you, you just experience one of them, that to a short time interval of it. All that had happened is happening, and all that lies in the future has already happened, and there is no time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay lets keep it simple, now imagine there are four universes where it had made you choose four different paths as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%282%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subatomic particles communicate across multiple universes which our brain can’t comprehend, but even before you start a problem, all possible solutions and failures to solve it exists. In many universes you would (in truth that universe would have made you) have solved the problem with flying colors, in many universes you would have failed miserably, in many universes that problem simply would not exist. So say at quantum level if you know how you solved all problems in all universes, in our simple case it might look like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%283%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As indicated above, you would know all possible solutions of the problem you are solving in an instant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s say we have a problem where only 2 out of 4 paths lead you to the solution, a traditional you, or a computer should test each way to find a solution, but a quantum you, or a computer, since it communicates with parallel universes will know exactly which path leads you to red X, and in which paths you have banged yourself onto a wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%284%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Richard Feynman said, if anyone says they understood Quantum Physics, it means they haven’t understood it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Signs of a Highly Intelligent Employee</title><link href="/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Signs of a Highly Intelligent Employee" /><published>2025-01-07T20:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-07T20:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee.html">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They cheat on their job with a side hustle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They treat everybody equal (including the cleaner).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They rebel against micromanagement and dictator leaders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They know when to say no to a meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They help others advance in their career.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They don’t respond to most emails.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They don’t attend meetings, but find efficient ways to communicate.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They stay away from gossip and corporate politics.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They create passive income so if they get fired it matters less.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They try entrepreneurship at least once to see what it feels like.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re fine to be the dumbest person in the room.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They ruthlessly protect their time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They focus on outcomes not KPIs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re wildly open to new ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They create stuff people want.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They learn without being told.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re humble.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">They cheat on their job with a side hustle. They treat everybody equal (including the cleaner). They rebel against micromanagement and dictator leaders. They know when to say no to a meeting. They help others advance in their career. They don’t respond to most emails. They don’t attend meetings, but find efficient ways to communicate. They stay away from gossip and corporate politics. They create passive income so if they get fired it matters less. They try entrepreneurship at least once to see what it feels like. They’re fine to be the dumbest person in the room. They ruthlessly protect their time. They focus on outcomes not KPIs. They’re wildly open to new ideas. They create stuff people want. They learn without being told. They’re humble.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DMK is incompetent and intoxicated</title><link href="/2025/01/01/dmk-is-incompetent-and-intoxicated.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DMK is incompetent and intoxicated" /><published>2025-01-01T11:44:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-01T11:44:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/01/dmk-is-incompetent-and-intoxicated</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/01/dmk-is-incompetent-and-intoxicated.html">&lt;p&gt;I feel DMK has become incompetent and intoxicated in its ruling years, I am sure the Stalin family cares about getting Inbhanidhi on stage during DMK’s meet, than solving our problems. In this blog I present case why I think DMK is intoxicated and incompetent, and why we Tamils need to choose alternatives. I am not sure though if alternatives are ready, but it would be foolish as a civilization if we are not looking for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;failure-to-select-a-right-leader&quot;&gt;Failure to select a right leader&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK failed even before Stalin became a CM. It’s a party that says it likes to be democratically represent us, but inside DMK, there is no democracy. Somehow Stalin, Udhayanidhi and Inbhanidhi have risen to the top. What qualification do they have? They just come from a single bloodline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even PTR comes from a blue blood, but he is intellectually sound. On the other hand Karunanidhis’s heirs looks like fools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stalin-is-a-fool&quot;&gt;Stalin is a fool&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stalin is a fool, or he thinks we Tamil’s are fools who will forget what he has done, here are my cases:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;senthil-balaji&quot;&gt;Senthil Balaji&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QUZ8X55WdUs?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw a video where Stalin slams Senthil Balaji, about his corruption, look what has happened now, Stalin kneels to Balaji, he is dependent on Balaji’s money so much so that when Balaji was arrested, Stalin and DMK came forefront to defend him. Such a……. God, what to say? What to say? To be descent, I would just put, such a shameless character now leads DMK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;campaign-against-drugs&quot;&gt;Campaign against drugs&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hb5BGb_vixU?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was funny when I watched this video. Here Stalin says a word &lt;em&gt;bothai&lt;/em&gt; which means intoxicated. He does not want Tamils to be intoxicated with drugs, but just from Medavakkam to Sithalapakkam, a 3Km stretch, there are 7 Liquor shops run by Tamil Nadu government. Don’t they give &lt;em&gt;bothai&lt;/em&gt; or intoxication? Does Stalin say it’s right to drink, but it’s wrong to take drugs? If yes how? Does he say that my neighborhood and I have not been affected by TASMAC (Tamilnadu Liqour Shops)? Does he claim no one sat on our street and drank? Does he claim drunk don’t roam our streets? Or does he claim a drunk does not come in the way when we drive and increases the potential of accidents?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stalin looks like an idiot when he intoxicates people, but says they must not get intoxicated by a competitive intoxicant like drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;covid-spreading-election-campaign&quot;&gt;Covid spreading election campaign&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must have looked at election campaigns in Tamilnadu, they took place in Covid era and none of protective measures were followed. Stalin and other leader’s grouped people and addressed them. They were mask-less, and no visible proof of hand sanitizers were present. Okay Stalin is a fool, no wonder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funny part is after coming to power, the same Stalin who helped to spread Covid, asked people to donate money to prevent the spread of Covid. I think he thinks we are absolute fools who do not watch him. I felt very bad that DMK came to power with such a stupid as leader. Or at least he thinks we will be stupid enough not to notice these things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-murder-near-court&quot;&gt;A Murder near court&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.indiatoday.in/india/tamil-nadu/story/tamil-nadu-tirunelveli-murder-man-hacked-district-combined-court-2653271-2024-12-21&quot;&gt;murder near court campus&lt;/a&gt;, okay, the issue is when reports asked the law minister, he almost disowned the murder as though it never happened in Tamil Nadu. He was proud that it happened out of the court campus than inside it, and it sounded like it was the triump of the DMK that enabled one be mudered outside court campus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shouldn’t a minister feel asamed when one is murdered in Tamil Nadu? Okay we know that politicians are scoundrels, but at least act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tungsten-mines-in-tamil-nadu&quot;&gt;Tungsten mines in Tamil Nadu&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindu.com/news/national/tamil-nadu/whats-the-row-over-tungsten-mining-near-madurai/article68959810.ece&quot;&gt;conterversy over tungsten mining in Tamil Nadu&lt;/a&gt;. The opposition leader EPS asked questions about it and the CM M.K.Stalin couldn’t answer it properly. When stalin came to power, what ever problems he faced, he blamed it on the previous leader EPS. This showed us that he likes to deflect off things than to think about solving it, once again in the tungsten issue, he blamed it on center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes the center wants to mine tungsten, and it might want to auction Tamilian lands, but you are a ruling party in Tamil Nadu. Have you protested against it? If not why all of a sudden you are blaming the center? Why were you sleeping till now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;blast-in-coimbatore&quot;&gt;Blast in Coimbatore&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindu.com/news/national/tamil-nadu/all-about-coimbatore-car-blast-case-2022-terror-probe-and-more/article66061346.ece&quot;&gt;bomb blast in Coimbatore carried out by Islamic terrorists&lt;/a&gt;, it was unprofessional and sloppy, probably made by a terror intern or trainee. It was bomb made from domestic gas cylinder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than acknowledging it was a terror attack, DMK people to get Islamic votes said that it was an accident, I couldn’t believe it. At that time a DMK guy came to my home to get trained in web development, and he swore that cylinder blast is an accident and not a terror attack. I was baffled. This shows to what length DMK people will go to keep their vote bank intact even though national security is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;arrest-of-savukku-shankar&quot;&gt;Arrest of Savukku Shankar&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.livemint.com/lm-img/img/2024/05/04/600x338/SavukkuShankar_1714814864098_1714814873937.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Savukku Shankar&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Savukku Shankar is a whistleblowing journalist in Tamil Nadu who is equated to Julian Assange. He somehow knows and accurately predicts what’s going to happen in politics. He also exposes corruption in such a way that infuriates the DMK. Rather than proving that Savukku is wrong, or placing an argument against him, DMK arrests him in false cases, so much so that Supreme Court of India has given stark warning to the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This proves that DMK does not like democracy, and does not like people questioning them and speaking against it. The reason why this happens is, DMK is intoxicated with power, and has become incompetent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-eliminating-cows-from-road&quot;&gt;Not eliminating cows from road&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/lT4pqto-140?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 6 months ago I think, an IAS office named Radhakrishnan told on TV that after the incidence shown in above video (it shows a little girl being attacked by a cow), cows in Chennai’s roads will be eliminated. I am sure even if I take a stroll now, I would be able to spot cows on road, cow dung all over roads, and worst, the cows affecting traffic, and causing a potential for accidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lies, lies, lies from Radhakrishnan. Absolute lies. The government, even it knows the truth, it hasn’t apologized for this guys lying, neither has announced how it will remove cows from roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-eliminating-dogs-from-road&quot;&gt;Not eliminating dogs from road&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An incident occurred in Chennai where a little kid was bitten by stray dog, when the mayor Priya was asked about it, she said the city will take census of dogs. What? Idiot, eliminate dogs idiot, eliminate it. Good or bad, dogs are like terrorists across border who still don’t attack us. Don’t be a fucking sitting coward like Modi, eliminate them. DMK doesn’t seem to have the guts to change such a mayor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I ask my friends why such an incompetent and inefficient person is a mayor, they say it’s because she is from a backward community. Okay you need a person from backward community for votes, but then why can’t you find an efficient one from backward community and make her or him mayor? If one is not performing, shouldn’t that one be eliminated?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is DMK a lazy party? Selecting a president because someone is a son of Karuna than someone who has the will to think about the people? Is the same laziness happening in Chennai mayor stuff too, though one is not performing, the party is reluctant to take her out and put new one in?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;flood-prevention-for-chennai-complete&quot;&gt;Flood prevention for Chennai complete?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent light rain, Valluvar Kottam was flooded, and I put it in my WhatsApp status, a DMK friend of mine replied that only 1800 of 4000 crores allocated for flood relief has been spent. What? I thought. Mayor Priya said within one rain Chennai will be flood proof, now Valluvar Kottam the work is still going on. I think in next light rain, or may be the next day, Moggapair was flooded. In how many places the anti-flood systems are still being implemented? In how many places it has been implemented and when it was last checked for maintenance? Who are the contractors who implemented it and how much money was given to them? Who are the people who worked for the project? How much money they got? From where the raw materials were procured, and what’s the supply chain? As a citizen why it’s hard for me to find this information online? What’s so secret about implementing a drainage system?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-ptr-is-not-coming-up&quot;&gt;Why PTR is not coming up?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b5/PTR.Thiagarajan.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Palanivel Thiagarajan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is an excellent leader called Palinivel Thiyaga Rajan in DMK. Of course, he is a leader in party because his family is close to that of Stalin’s, but he is not a tainted man, and he is an intellectual who does his job right. An audio leaked where PTR exposes 30,000 crores looted by Udhayanidhi, PTR claims that’s a fake audio, but after that, PTR who was finance minister declined. Now I think he is I.T minister.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A man who speaks with statistics and hard facts, PTR should be chief minister I say, we need such a talented man, not some idiot nod head like Stalin who is only good for photo shoots and propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;murugan-festival&quot;&gt;Murugan festival&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK which is supposed to be an atheistic party, to the dismay of many atheists who supported it, it held a festival for &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/chennai/dmk-govt-to-hold-global-lord-murugan-fest-faces-bjp-flak/articleshow/108507745.cms&quot;&gt;lord Muruga&lt;/a&gt;. I have always maintained, Dravida Kazhagam is the atheistic party and DMK is an Aryan Brahminical party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay things have deteriorated to a level the members of DMK follow God. Even if we treat that as personal belief, as a party which is now governing Tamil Nadu, I expect DMK to free people from the shackles of religion and move the masses towards science rather than plunging into the darkness of blind faith. DMK is in-fact dead, the DK soul of it has long rotted and vanished, DMK is just a name now that means nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dmk-people-in-my-area&quot;&gt;DMK people in my area&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you seen how ruthlessly cars with DMK flags drive? First I wonder what’s the use of cars to identify themselves with a party when all humans are equal? Why can’t people be normal and civil? Identifying oneself with a party sends a signal that that person is incompetent and needs a huge organization to support him to shield him from in societal misdeeds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay let me tell about DMK people in my area. First on December 18th gone, I returned from office and there were speakers blasting about Aiyappan praises just one house from my home. Even if all doors and widows were closed, the sound penetrated our home, kids were crying. I was told that some DMK guy is going to lord Aiyappan temple and wants the world know about it. I got a headache, and this speaker blasting went till 10PM. None dared to asked them to shut up because we know DMK people are bone head rowdies. Police won’t be of help too. Things ended at 10PM, next day I was unwell because I couldn’t take rest and did not go to my office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a second incident happened in EPS rule. There were rains and floodwaters in our street rose rapidly, this should not happen, Sithalapakkam is no flood zone where people have been living for more than 1400 years. The flood was because a DMK guy at the end of our street had built a bund so that his car can roll down from his property onto the road, this bund was blocking the draining of water to Perumbakkam lake. This DMK guy was asked to remove the bund did not relent. He said if it broke, the flood water will reach the slums.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He doesn’t seem to know we bought our properties legally, his bund construction that obstructed water and caused flooding is illegal, and the slums are illegal settlements too. As the waters rose, amazingly middle class people started amass and booked a JCB and the bund was broken. This is one simple example, if people wake up, DMK or no other party can stand before them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A party is built from ground up, and if people without simple civic sense constitue a party? Why should we vote for it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dmk-is-a-brahmin-party&quot;&gt;DMK is a brahmin party&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/af/Gandhi_Rajagopalachari.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Seen with Gandhi, at the right, Rajagopalachari&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK is a brahmin party, consisting of God believers. Whereas we Tamils want administration be separated from one’s beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/lhjNR66YGTg?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact DMK came to power by licking the feet of Rajagopalachari (Rjaji), a corrosive man who want to implement Vedic and Aryan traditions in our land subjugating our people. Periyaar supported Kamaraj who implemented his schemes, Rajaji unable to stand the march of rationalism in our land supported DMK, so that Periyaar and Kamaraj could be defeated. By this way Aryans could get their wishes implemented in Tamil Nadu in the name of Dravidian politics and cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;karunanidhi-shouldnt-have-become-dmk-president&quot;&gt;Karunanidhi shouldn’t have become DMK president&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think Karunanidhi should have become the president of DMK in the first place. I feel more honest, and more atheist Neduncherian should have been its president. Somehow politics do not favor gentlemen and uncorrupted and honest people, after the death of Annadurai, Karuna became CM and Tamil Nadu was scotched by the rising sun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes lack of education, foresight and thought might have been prevalent in uneducated masses then, there must have been a lot of people who can’t think well in DMK then, but what now? Haven’t your parents sent to school? Haven’t you learned to think? If not, why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-new-party-a-new-rule&quot;&gt;A new party, a new rule&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not saying to put back EPS in power, far worst will be BJP who are hell-bent on destroying our culture and language. What I am saying is look at alternative parties. Vijay has formed one, Vijayakanth has formed one, Seeman has formed one, there is Pazha Karupaiah who I really respect, he has a party, there are the communists (but yes they have become DMK feet licker’s now), and so on. Vote for different people, let us use this election and show that we need a change from this duopoly of DMK and ADMK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I feel DMK has become incompetent and intoxicated in its ruling years, I am sure the Stalin family cares about getting Inbhanidhi on stage during DMK’s meet, than solving our problems. In this blog I present case why I think DMK is intoxicated and incompetent, and why we Tamils need to choose alternatives. I am not sure though if alternatives are ready, but it would be foolish as a civilization if we are not looking for it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My thoughts on HAL AMCA</title><link href="/2024/12/20/my-thoughts-on-hal-amca.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My thoughts on HAL AMCA" /><published>2024-12-20T11:08:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-12-20T11:08:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/12/20/my-thoughts-on-hal-amca</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/12/20/my-thoughts-on-hal-amca.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/25/AMCA_model_displayed_during_Aero_India_2021.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am happy that India has taken up the challenge of 5&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; generation aircraft. I am very skeptical about its success, I do think India has the talent to develop it, but I am not sure to what pressures we will succumb to and make this aircraft a failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example HAL Marut failed because we did not have the right engine. The same case with LCA, it’s underperforming, but at least we can say it’s a partial success, at least it’s deployed into the armed forces with a foreign engine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The engine is the problem for us. For some reason we boast we are a superpower, but just outside my room, water logs as puddles when it rains, there is garbage strewn on the street, and stray dogs roam around. In such a nation, where simple problems cannot be solved, I am not surprised we don’t have our own jet engine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kaaviri&quot;&gt;Kaaviri&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Kaaviri engine, dream child of Kalam hasn’t materialized yet. It’s a government project, so there is no surprise it has failed, you may call it a success if it had made someone in` the creamy layer rich. I strongly feel we should have our own engine, and not rely on others. So, how do we go about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;publicly-funded-private-engine-company&quot;&gt;Publicly funded, private engine company&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need to remove government and bureaucracy out of engine manufacture. I feel we the citizens of India should crowd fund a private company that can develop a fighter jet engine. This company’s goal should be only to develop a fighter jet engine in India, and to sell it to who ever wants to buy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By keeping government and corruption out, I think there is a better chance of success. But yes corrupt politicians, having nexus with foreigners will try to ruin it. I am not sure how to defend against them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ai-in-lca-and-amca&quot;&gt;A.I in LCA and AMCA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want A.I navigation for LCA and AMCA. I want these planes to go autonomous. This will save tens of human lives during war. Pakistan has become a radical Islamic nation, so is Bangladesh approaching it quick, we may have two pronged war. Though China has eliminated Islam from its land, its supporting Islamic Jihadist in Bangladesh and Pakistan, so may be three-pronged war is also possible. In that case we need lots of autonomous fighter drones defending our ariel borders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nuke-missiles-missiles-missiles&quot;&gt;Nuke missiles, missiles, missiles&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If nuclear missiles are cheaper to make, let’s stockpile it. When ever someone enters our territory, thousands of them should be launched on the aggressors important cities, along with lots of decoys to confuse them. We should ensure war ends in minutes rather than months or years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am certain that AMCA will be a failure because we won’t be able to make our engine, so mass nuking of aggressor might be the only solution.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why they didn’t teach this in college?</title><link href="/2024/12/11/why-they-didnt-teach-this-in-college.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why they didn&apos;t teach this in college?" /><published>2024-12-11T18:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-12-11T18:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/12/11/why-they-didnt-teach-this-in-college</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/12/11/why-they-didnt-teach-this-in-college.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/soldering_202412/1%20Post%20LinkedIn-01.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I studied in Panimalar Engineering College, Chennai. It’s a super waste college, I am an electronics engineer (on paper) and have soldered nothing. I saw the video above on the internet and my heart broke. A Chinese video it is, and it shows how one can solder. But here I am a electronic’s engineer, and cannot solder a thing. Shame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineering in my state, Tamil Nadu is a bogus thing. The colleges that teach it does not understand that engineering is a technical thing and one needs hands on with it. Almost every thing I read was from books, and nothing was practical. I remember how few labs we had, we can’t stay late in labs, our access to it was controlled. We could enter college only by college bus and leave only by college bus, this severely restricted our movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our college chairman became bald at a young age, and he had a very ugly wife, because of that he did not want any of us to have girlfriends, so boy and girls were forbidden to speak with each other. I know people in west would be laughing reading about this rule, I swear it’s true. I am not gay to be happy about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The theoretical examination conducted by our state government is bogus, you can pass it with ease. There are practical exams, but colleges bribe the external examiners that visit and makes students pass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you ask my friends, they will praise my college. Yes these types of colleges are okay for people who want a paper that says they are engineers, even though they are not, but for me, a person who truly wanted to become a engineer and build things it’s a loot of my money.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tata Motors is a Buffalo and you can do nothing about it</title><link href="/2024/11/10/tata-motors-is-a-buffalo-and-you-can-do-nothing-about-it.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tata Motors is a Buffalo and you can do nothing about it" /><published>2024-11-10T19:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-11-10T19:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/11/10/tata-motors-is-a-buffalo-and-you-can-do-nothing-about-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/11/10/tata-motors-is-a-buffalo-and-you-can-do-nothing-about-it.html">&lt;p&gt;Here I am recording one of the least traumatic experience with Tata Motors. A month or two back, when water was poured into the car for wiper, it just drained out. I was not sure what happened and almost at the same time a person called Viji from FPL Tata Motors called. I booked an appointment and went to their Guindy service centre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I told the problem, a person sat us down and prepared a huge list of things that needs to be done with my car. I said ‘no’, all I wanted was this leaking problem to be fixed. That guy felt dismayed, but agreed he will fix it. I booked a cab and came home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think on the next day I got a call that the wiper tank had broken, and it needs 3 days to replace as they have no spare parts. I told them that I need the car as I have work, I went to FPL using call taxi, and took posession of my car. When I saw my car I was dismayed, it was covered in dust, nose to boot, and the person responsible seems to show no sign of shame. There were so many mosquitoes in my car. Even at that time I asked, will you call me when you get the wiper water tank, that person said ‘sure’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it’s a moth or two now, I don’t remember exactly when, now the Viji of FPL Tata Motors who has amnesia calls me again, and asked if I need my car to be serviced (I should not blame here, she could be just a pawn in the chess game of Tata Motors to squeeze out money from our pockets for their cheap quality of service). I said ‘no’. She asked me why, I said to here Tata Motors is like a buffalo, it stands at the middle of the road, if you honk it will move, and the same buffalo will stand again the next day at the middle of the road. There is no use one complaining, or there is no use in Tata Motors service people acting as though they care about their customers. The buffalo on the next day will be at the middle of the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, all the service centres in Tata Motors are buffalos, and you can do nothing about it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Here I am recording one of the least traumatic experience with Tata Motors. A month or two back, when water was poured into the car for wiper, it just drained out. I was not sure what happened and almost at the same time a person called Viji from FPL Tata Motors called. I booked an appointment and went to their Guindy service centre.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Flow Vs Productivity</title><link href="/2024/11/03/flow-vs-productivity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Flow Vs Productivity" /><published>2024-11-03T08:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-11-03T08:51:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/11/03/flow-vs-productivity</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/11/03/flow-vs-productivity.html">&lt;p&gt;Rich Hickey was absolutely right about sprints in software. Watch the video &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtube.com/shorts/liUiRfN9NzQ?si=6tJW0tkwWIt5yQeR&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. But for some reason, managers in the I.T industry have always relentlessly pushed productivity via more work, and consistent work, thus proving that they are ultra stupid. It happens in all the companies where I have worked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next there are these productivity books like Atomic Habit, Mindset, and The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People. All of them try to convert a human into  a machine. Are we machines? No. For some reason, the coaches, and authors fail to recognize that they are writing books for humans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A machine that works 16 hours a day might be twice as productive as the one that works 8 hours a day, but humans are biological and emotional systems, and humans are not linear. A human needs rest, a human needs thought, reflection, we are emotional beings, we are a complex cocktail of chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We humans think, we see our boss, and we can’t bear to see someone above us, our juniors can’t bear to see us commanding them. They want to be us, we all want to be the richest man ever. It’s a very natural feeling, it’s part of being human.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans can’t win over their desire, I don’t think any conscious lifeform can win over desire. I think the best system for progress is the one that forgets about productivity, realizes that feeling of success is a myth, though one seeks for power, forget about getting power, forget about control, and it’s better to go with the flow by trying to be valuable to the people around you, try to enhance their life. I don’t mean to say that if you are among stupid people, you must be a stupid and hence increase your perceived value, I mean be of real value by hugging facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One way not to treat people as machines, is to be happy with what you have. Do you really need that luxury boat? Do you really need to send your kid to school that charges so much? Do you really require those expensive foods? That remote and exotic holiday? Or do you want to empower people who work under you and see what happens?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By letting the flow happen, rather than using force, if you become the next Alexander, good, or if you accomplish nothing, then still good too. Try to lower your desire, so that you don’t force something upon people, let things flow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By letting the flow, you don’t try to be productive, but you try to be comfortable and happy. You don’t create sorrow in many hearts. This is the way to manage people, I feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today mostly one’s basic needs are met, one works for his emotional needs, you can get almost nothing by forcing that person. Else, you must find a starving beggar to staff your company, so that his or her poverty will make him / her do anything for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your personal benefit, never go against the flow, do passionate things, this doesn’t mean you have to impose your passion on others. This style of non-management I think will create a super successful company.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rich Hickey was absolutely right about sprints in software. Watch the video here. But for some reason, managers in the I.T industry have always relentlessly pushed productivity via more work, and consistent work, thus proving that they are ultra stupid. It happens in all the companies where I have worked.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Astrology never worked for me</title><link href="/2024/10/31/astrology-never-worked-for-me.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Astrology never worked for me" /><published>2024-10-31T20:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-10-31T20:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/10/31/astrology-never-worked-for-me</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/10/31/astrology-never-worked-for-me.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dd/Trouver-signes-astrologiques.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Astrology is not true, it’s a spoof, and it never worked for me. Once I was taken to  a great astrologer, I am a rationalist and don’t believe in God. God is a spoof too. That astrologer examined my date of birth, time of birth and my astrological chart. He said at the age of 27, I will go and fall at the feet of God, become a great believer. I am 42, and am still not moved by God belief shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my friend is a great proponent of astrology. He was the one who encouraged me to read daily astrology, and I did. One day what was predicted for Gemini suited me, another day what was predicted for Scorpio suited me. I asked him how to know which astrological sign it is for me today, because I need to read 12 predictions to know what am I that day, plus if possibly the planets are transitioning, some in say Virgo comes true, and say some in the fish sign thing comes true on that day. So is my astro sign changing on that day or something?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though this was a genuine question, as I was unaware at that time, my friend thought I was teasing his beliefs. Looks like the astro sign of yours never changes, and looks like you have to accept these astrologies what ever it is, even though it says non-realistic things will happen to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think people are psychologically damaged, and since it’s a taboo in India to seek a psychologist, they end up with religion, astrology, and numerous other blind faiths. I wish people get educated a lot, so that they can see what they must see, and not be corrupted by these shit stuff that has no proofs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Good that Chennai people have lost trust in Tamilnadu</title><link href="/2024/10/15/good-that-chennai-people-have-lost-trust-in-tamilnadu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Good that Chennai people have lost trust in Tamilnadu" /><published>2024-10-15T13:53:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-10-15T13:53:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/10/15/good-that-chennai-people-have-lost-trust-in-tamilnadu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/10/15/good-that-chennai-people-have-lost-trust-in-tamilnadu.html">&lt;p&gt;It takes good education and freedom of thought to see through the glare. For millennium we Indians were made to believe a ruler, be it ancient Kings, the British or the bogus democracy called India. At least now, in the time of crisis, I am happy that people of Chennai have stopped trusting the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mudichur-being-vacated&quot;&gt;Mudichur being vacated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People of Mudichur, near Tambaram are vacating their homes because of rain warning. I think it was flooded atleast twice in the past, the government did nothing about it. Now rather than being there under the reign of unhelpful government, people are abandoning that place. Thats good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;parking-on-velacherrys-bridge&quot;&gt;Parking on Velacherry’s bridge&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people have parked their cars on Velacherry bridge to avoid the vechiles from getting drowned. They are not believing the fucking Tamilnadu governments Chennai flood control system. We know who comes to power in Tamilnadu, and how they come tp power. Is it because of merit? Is it because that person has done something good to the nation? No. No. We all know how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder how people even bought property in Velacherry? It is bough area and naturally it will get flooded. I wonder why the government even allowed people to settle there? I still feel strongly that Velacherry and Pallikaranai should be returned back to nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To return back to nature, the Tamilnadu government should stop all registration of properties in that region, so no new real estate activity takes place. This will plunge the value of property over there. The government I feel should put restriction to stop any human building activity. May be in the span of 100 years it will become a swamp again and would absorb some amount of floods Chennai gets in future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be the citizens of Velacherry can sue Chennai corporation of Cheating them, making them believe that Velacherry is a habitable area, thus draining their millions. I wish the court will force the government to buy back the property from people in Velacherry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why&quot;&gt;Why?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think 20cm of rain per day in Chennai is drainable (that’s what government claims, we do not know how much corruption and malpractice are involved), the question is why not 40cm?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is Chennai storing rain water to be used in drought months? If not, why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How much water is sent to the ocean? Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why Chennai can host a F4 car race, air show, but not fend of flooding? It’s just water that comes down, not molten metal. Are we so tech incompetant?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many engineering colleges in and around Chennai, are they sleeping? Why can they even publish a proposal? If they can’t what’s the use of their existence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;quit-chennai&quot;&gt;Quit Chennai&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If such incompetent, corrupt governments are ruling Chennai, people think, why you should buy a property in Chennai? Why you must work here with higher spending, higher pollution, higher risk of floods, murders and rowdyism, drugs and intolerable traffic, garbage, stray dogs and cows to name a few? Why can’t we have stable power supply, in rain? Why are we so weak in technology to achieve these?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It takes good education and freedom of thought to see through the glare. For millennium we Indians were made to believe a ruler, be it ancient Kings, the British or the bogus democracy called India. At least now, in the time of crisis, I am happy that people of Chennai have stopped trusting the government.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Times I felt bad using Ruby on Rails</title><link href="/2024/10/10/times-i-felt-bad-using-ruby-on-rails.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Times I felt bad using Ruby on Rails" /><published>2024-10-10T08:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-10-10T08:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/10/10/times-i-felt-bad-using-ruby-on-rails</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/10/10/times-i-felt-bad-using-ruby-on-rails.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/34/1936_Paraparaumu_train_derailment_rescue_work.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your happiness does not depend just on your intelligence, but also on the place, and community you live in. Imagine Galileo amongst the Christians, helpless and hopeless because he was right, but to the world around him, he was wrong, a witch, and punishable. What should I do in situations like this? I have no clue. I am not even Galileo, and the world will forget me as soon as I die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog, I would like to note that I regret using Rails because of people around me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;zanec&quot;&gt;Zanec&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first was this company, Zanec. Till then, I was involved in small Rails projects and large PHP projects, but in Zanec when I could code fully in Rails, I was happy. It was for a real estate website, &lt;a href=&quot;https://places.com&quot;&gt;https://places.com&lt;/a&gt;. I don’t think places work now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, at that time, we had to work with a Ukrainian called Dennis Volchov or something, I am not sure of his name. And at that time, Ukraine was invaded by Russia (2014). This Dennis does not know Rails, half-baked in Ruby, and he insisted that Rails migrations are antipattern; he does not want migrations, no matter what we said, he did not want it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a Rails guy, it was frustrating for me. According to him, SQL (Data Definition Language) should be noted in a file, he simply did not understand what migrations are and how easy it is to reverse them. He did not like the concept of a lot of migration files in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;db/migrate&lt;/code&gt; directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost hope and thought this was my fate. But by some miracle, the client believed in me, and though he did not stop Dennis sabotaging Rails migrations, he did support me on many occasions. The client name was Joe Mathew, he was from a company called Software Worx, which he ran. Till that date, he was the best client I ever had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also shielded me from internal politics at Zanec, without which I wouldn’t have lasted so long. I am a technician, not a politician.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trumatics&quot;&gt;Trumatics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I met an excellent guy at Zanec called Umashankar (Uma as we called him). I was captivated by his philosophy and leadership. He created a company called Trumatics, I wanted to join it, and he let me in. Things did go well initially. But then, when it came to the Rails project, Uma did not understand incrementally building a Database as we went along with the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For him, the database should be defined first using Entity Relationship Diagrams (ERD), and then the database should be created, and only then should the app be coded. He is an affirmative person, but he did let me do the project in my own way, maybe I explained to him, and he got to know what Rails was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike the people who ran Zanec, he was not a person who totally lost touch with tech, so he let me do my way. I think I worked on a project for a company named Zynalog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as my bad time would have it, something changed in him, he stated to shout at me,  at the people in office in an intense way, and we had no clue what was going on. One day I couldn’t bear the pressure, and though I was one of the directors of the company, I quit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the last things I knew about him was that he was bad-mouthing about me, but who cares? I am sure people who are closely aligned to facts have better chance of succeeding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a few years back we did have a friendly call where he was saying how engineers (freshers) knew nothing, and should be significantly coached up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dream of creating a better Zanec, that would be technically good, and a company that would be loved by employees went up in smoke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;healthicity&quot;&gt;HealthiCity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I worked for a company called HealthiCity, and I would say that its VP Kekin Gada was my best client to date. In the JD it was said that one must have basic / little knowledge of React. I thought there would be a front-end developer, and when he is absent, I would need to consult him and make some minor front-end changes. The interview was about Ruby, and it was nothing for me. I cleared it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once in the company, I regretted,  I was made to learn ReactJs, it sucked. &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/29/rails-killed-reactjs-now-its-burning-the-corpse.html&quot;&gt;Rails had already killed ReactJs even before it was born&lt;/a&gt;. I wondered what made someone who claimed they knew Rails, make a Rails developer code in ReactJS?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out the people in HealthiCity are from a services company called Big binary, and for them, ReactJS is like God, no matter how unproductive it is, it should be used in the Rails project. They made the mistake of choosing React, and since the top leadership till now has failed to acknowledge their mistake, they are making people code in ReactJS + Rails at gunpoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was forced to learn ReactJS; there was a class for ReactJS held, I was forced to code CSS; and I don’t know if blue goes well with orange or what. I don’t give a damn about font and design. Design bugs were assigned to me. It was hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One good thing born out of this was &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/injee&quot;&gt;Injee&lt;/a&gt;. Since I needed to learn ReactJS, I needed a back end, I thought, why not code a zero-configuration instant backend, and so was born Injee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a back-end developer who was forced to learn front-end against my will, but I feel Injee will free up front-end developers to learn back-end. So even though I suffered, it led me to create something that will reduce the suffering of others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;would-love-to-work-with-pure-rails-people&quot;&gt;Would love to work with pure Rails people&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/Shanghai_maglev_train.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still think Rails is one of the best frameworks for developing web apps. Though my knowledge of &lt;a href=&quot;https://clojure.org/&quot;&gt;Clojure&lt;/a&gt; is challenging it. I would like to work with pure Rails people. That would be really refreshing. In my country, India, most people are half-baked when it comes to knowledge of tech. They are willing to work extra hard but are not willing to come out of their pea-brain thought, and people are not willing to change, be efficient and follow the Rails way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want really stable, awesome apps created, contact me, and I will be able to help you. If you are a pure  Rails person and want me to work with you, I am thrilled.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>