<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-11-13T11:04:05+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Prostitute</title><link href="/2018/11/13/prostitute.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Prostitute" /><published>2018-11-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/13/prostitute</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/13/prostitute.html">&lt;p&gt;I was at Star Briyani in Chennai One road, the table next to me was a guy bragging about how much gold he is getting from his in-laws for his marriage. It brought shame to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t really understand women, possibly its okay for them to get money for sex, but that guy was a man. As a man I feel that men should not become prostitutes. Its a shame. We fought the British not to get their wealth, but to stop them from seducing us with their power and wealth. We are men!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In India, male prostitution amounts more than female ones. Female prostitutes usually don’t marry and do it with many males, prostitute males usually get a lump sum amount from the females family and try to be dedicated for them by marrying them. In soul both these female and male prostitutes are the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am  a prostitute too :( , yup I usually had a vision of a simple marriage, a calm life. I thought I would marry a girl, i.e we will have a very good understanding, but circumstances made me a prostitute. I should have walked away if I were a pure soul, but I stayed put for my convenience and for the sake of not hurting others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought my engagement would be simple. My family said that it will be in a temple with two families exchanging confirmations of marriage, but it turned out to be different. First there was a expensive suit purchased for me by my wife with my money :(. Okay I thought, she might be intoxicated with the feeling of getting married. There were shoes purchased (with my money). I am in Tamilnadu, a hot country where I see only idiots wear shoes and it sweats. But people do it because copying European culture seems to make them feel secure and superior. Europe is a different region dumbos! Its far far away from the equator, look at the map. Tamilnadu is near the equator. I often wondered why people don’t think, but they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though all was bought, I had a feeling that engagement would be simple. On the day engagement, I was asked to come to a hotel, as soon as I got out of the lift there were photographers shooting me and directing me how I must pose. I was a puppet and not myself. Of-course prostitutes are puppets :( . It was very clear that the lavish expense was just for show off. There were nearly 100 guests, they all ate food while I stood near my wife on the podium could only watch in hunger as they ate and enjoyed. I felt like I was in prison. When I finally came to eat in all hunger, there was almost no food. I left the place hungry and got myself a tandoori in my hotel room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My marriage was even more lavish. it was all about money and show off than about two hearts understanding each other. My in-laws never really knew even my name. My name on the podium was wrong and none seemed to care about it. The irony was I was marrying a to be doctor in English literature, and they did not know to write my name well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a few days after my marriage, just like a horse is stamped they stamped me as prostitute. My inlaws presented me a gold chain, bracelet, I had a engagement ring too. I am supposed to wear these at every function to show off my status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We remember Thiruvalluvar not for the gold he wore, we remember Auvaiyaar for the dress she wore, but we remember them. If we ask who was the richest person in the Pandiyas period, none knows. That’s our Tamil culture. We have never valued wealth, we have valued what one stood form what ones ideas were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I heard the person speak so proud about his dowry in Star Briyani, my prostitute days flashed before me. I wish I had a pure soul.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was at Star Briyani in Chennai One road, the table next to me was a guy bragging about how much gold he is getting from his in-laws for his marriage. It brought shame to me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Finally some one speaks against Single Page Apps</title><link href="/2018/11/07/finally-some-one-speaks-against-single-page-apps.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Finally some one speaks against Single Page Apps" /><published>2018-11-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/07/finally-some-one-speaks-against-single-page-apps</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/07/finally-some-one-speaks-against-single-page-apps.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/c/c3/Ruby_on_Rails_logo.svg/800px-Ruby_on_Rails_logo.svg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was going through Rails mailing list some time ago and something caught my eye. A guy called Greg Navis had written a blog against single page apps. I read it. In my opinion Single Page Apps are a piece of shit. At least shit can be converted to manure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was working in a company that was dominated by people who do not know tech, but they had the illusion that what ever they heard first and thought first was right. They got a contract for developing a financial product and they choose Laravel. Good choice. It was chosen by a guy so that once he got an hold of it, he could leave that company to search for less hellish job. Laravel was good choice and they chose Angular for front end. What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was all done because people over there saw these job requirements peak and they wanted to switch job. I watched the comedy as the team size grew. They employed close to 10 people to build a financial app, I was wondering whats going on, I could do with just 2 or 3 people with Rails. Laravel is good, I have nothing against it, partly because I haven’t used it a lot, but against Angular and most JS front end frameworks I have lot against. Lot of boiler plate and decision making must be done before we start to attack the business of delivering results to clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have used these JS front end frameworks in my work, it does reduce the load of backend developer significantly, all you need is to generate JSON and not worry about the crappy CSS and design. Being a hardcore programmer, design thought was not in me, I am a person of logic, but the project went at a very slow pace. I used to finish a bunch of API’s and watch team of 3-4 front end developers toil with Angular for days. They envied me because it looked to them that I did almost no work, and yes I did almost no work, I used Rails and it di  lot of stuff for me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes if you look at the architecture level, SPA’s looks good. A clean separation between the client and the server, but when it comes to practicality it increases the time to deliver result. The increase in time comes in the form of communication. The front end dev needs to understand the business, the API’s back end devs provide, next he needs to interact with the designer. There is lot of people to people communication and its a bottle neck, consumes lot of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies in India do love SPA’s, that’s for another reason. If you can show many busy programmers to the client, you can bill more. When I was telling a company in Chennai and offered them a deal in which I can reduce the time and money by reducing head count needed for a project, they seem to worry about profit dropping, because their money comes from increasing complexity and head count. It a curse in India where people use tech for their selfishness (like Apple and Microsoft) rather than common good for humanity and the economy (like free software foundation). Its very bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as my personal experience goes, I use middleman for small sites and the moment complexity increases, I switch to Rails (nope I haven’t used Sinatra commercially, but its a good one too). Everything I need is there in Rails, the Database to the Front End, all is there and it works like Rolls Royce. You just don’t need to think about it. Rails migration from version to another too is okay, there are clear migration guides, but yes, if your apps are big and not tested, then you might be screwed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails is evolving too. It seems to have some process which I don’t really know what, but the community seems to pick the right stuff. When they moved from prototype + RJS to jQuery I was furious, but they seem to have done the right thing. When they moved to Coffeescript, I was very happy at least I may not need to touch this Javascript directly. I wish they integrated with Opal and ended the web developers misery altogether, but….. WHY ITS NOT HAPPENING? I am telling good people on this earth to kill this evil Javascript because I don’t have the power enough to do it. Please consider…..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are saying that I am too biased against Javascript and single page apps, then bloody yes I am. I am because I am biased against inefficiency and things that brings sorrow to programmers. An those who love SPA’s, I curse you, go to hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big companies need something that I don’t understand, I don’t know what they need, perhaps lengthy talks about their app architecture, perhaps lengthy talks about their engineering, bragging to people about how they used their engineering skills and tech insights to have hand picked each and every bit of their application and stitched it together loosing their night sleep. Well, that’s not me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am  a person who likes to sleep at night, earn handsome, do projects to people who do not have deep pockets. How can I go for a SPA?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Behaving like a successful rule</title><link href="/2018/11/06/behaving-like-a-successful-rule.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Behaving like a successful rule" /><published>2018-11-06T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-06T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/06/behaving-like-a-successful-rule</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/06/behaving-like-a-successful-rule.html">&lt;p&gt;Its funny what the BJP is doing, its behaving like it has ruled India in a very successful way. It has started celebrating despite adding misery to many, and RSS is trying to use violence to polarize Hindus. Let me tell you what I mean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-patel-statue&quot;&gt;The Patel statue&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes Sardar Patel is a great man no doubt about it, he needs to be remembered for ever, but I think putting a bust of him in parliament is more than enough, yet we have built such a high statue and it costs a lot. It has been built with public money and the public needs to pay Rs 350/- to see it. Yup, we the people of India paid for it and we need to pay further to see what we have created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a Thiruvalluvar statue in Tamilnadu, it too is a waste I feel, we love that man, but spending so much money just to glorify a person hmmm… There are lot of effective things you can do with money so that it can work for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That statue costs Rs 2,989 crores. If you can give 10 lakhs to a business aspirant in a village, then you can create 29,890 businesses, think of it. Even if 10% of them succeed and generate 20% growth, you will get back the money in 13 years. I really don’t understand the value of investment in liability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Patel, the U.P government and idiot Adithyanath wants to build a Ram statue. What for? Bloody hell what for? Ram has been surviving all along without a giant statue and he will survive more. Its this BJP and RSS acting as though they are the custodians of Hinduism and as though this religion won’t survive or become helpless without them is bothering me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;violence-creation&quot;&gt;Violence creation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people knew the BJP because of its violence. All of a sudden we knew it because they bashed a mosque like mads. They bashed because a Muslim ruler bashed a Hindu temple hundred years ago. This savage act by the BJP made people know them and got them recognized by Hindus. Nice PR!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now having got a majority and ruling India for long, they have done things that has plunged the nation in economic disaster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first s demonetization, it caused wide spread chaos and even deaths. Some how we haven’t seen any one getting life sentence or a jail term for possessing black money, and I don’t know how that’s possible in law abiding government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second economic slip-up was this governments inability to to arrest tycoons who have looted us and are hiding in various countries. Rather than taking steps and arresting them quick, they blame the congress rule. If congress has messed up the nation so much that it cannot be recovered by subsequent ruler, then why did the BJP contend in the election saying that it will give a golden age?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the GST. Now small and medium businesses do not know how to file taxes and everything is confusing. The Rafel deal where the french government and Dassult CEO have exposed that its Indian government that wanted to give this deal to Ambani.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how to get support of people when you have ruined the nation? Margret Thatcher got it by a war with Argentina, but Indian army, is it well uncorrupt to face the paks? I don’t know. So the cheap way is to bring in internal war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Hindu men are angry with women because of Aiyappan temple issue, and the case for it was put filed by the RSS, and we see a instability because RSS has won the case. Now RSS is using the verdict to act against it by encouraging mobs to attack women who want to enter the temple. The second is to rake up the issue of Aiyodhya Ram temple. That’s going on. If Indians are stupid enough they will fall into the RSS trap thinking that its RSS that’s saving Hinduism. But none will think from what its saving Hinduism?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-the-alternative&quot;&gt;Whats the alternative?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know whats the alternative. Congress is highly corrupt too, plus they encourage dynastic politics that this nation is still not been able to end. They have become very good in escaping court cases. The DMK, their allies have escaped from the 2G, and congress and Rjiv Gandhi has escaped from Bofors case. The congress will be going into the election like they are the good guys and BJP are the bad ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage the reader to think, think of an alternative. Can you discuss with your neighbors and place and fund some one able to rule the nation as a MP candidate?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Its funny what the BJP is doing, its behaving like it has ruled India in a very successful way. It has started celebrating despite adding misery to many, and RSS is trying to use violence to polarize Hindus. Let me tell you what I mean.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Buddha Posters</title><link href="/2018/11/03/buddha-posters.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Buddha Posters" /><published>2018-11-03T23:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-03T23:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/03/buddha-posters</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/03/buddha-posters.html">&lt;p&gt;Created some Buddha posters in my spare time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_1.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_2.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_3.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_4.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_5.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Created some Buddha posters in my spare time</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Emotional Nation</title><link href="/2018/10/20/emotional-nation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Emotional Nation" /><published>2018-10-20T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-20T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/10/20/emotional-nation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/20/emotional-nation.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;winning-election-with-tears&quot;&gt;Winning election with tears&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was Chennai floods, the Taminnadu administration had failed, the Chief Minister Jayalalitha was no where to be seen. The last time any one saw her was when she named two white tiger cubs born in Wonderloo zoo. Then this woman Valarmathi appeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/valarmathy_crying,jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was two things she did. First she sabotaged the the efforts of public helping public to come out of the floods. Its said that she and her goons trashed relief and people waiting at Chennai borders, next she went to the flooded zones and she cried, thus washing away her sins from the minds of people with her tears and emotions. The next election, the party that failed Chennai people in the floods still won.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-criminal-leader&quot;&gt;The criminal leader&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.financialexpress.com/2016/10/Jayalalithaa-PTI-L-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everywhere you go in Tamilnadu, you can see the pictures of Jayalalitha. The truth is, Jaya is a criminal who has been found guilty. Yet the ruling AIADMK is able to use her image to get traction in state. They have given hard earned taxpayers money to their party workers as presents like grinders, blender, television sets. They cleaverly disguised them as presents, thus winning emotional support from the people of this state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;law-fails-before-blind-faith&quot;&gt;Law fails before blind faith&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-0ahClFGH4bw/TmYsfvuXvFI/AAAAAAAAAmM/Nsj6d7WHM3Y/s1600/swami-ayyappan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, two woman who tried to enter Aiyappan temple in Sabarimalai were blocked by blind faithers. In  a nation that says all Humans are equal, these people are successfully holding onto a system which gives preference to certain human over others depending upon their gender and who their parents are. Neither the Kerala government or any other political party said a word against these emotional religious extremist for the want of votes in coming elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-train-driver&quot;&gt;The train driver&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/sX8QMTMqU9E?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday evening, a mob watching Ram leela festival were standing on two tracks while the law of the land says tracks should be used for only brief moments, just to cross it and one must be super cautious about it as there is a chance that you will get over run by train. Two trains on schedule bashed and killed more than 50 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite knowing the law, the people became emotional saying that the train times should be altered and some how the trains should have magically slowed down. That’s rubbish. Yet none have the courage to say that these 100 or so people were idiots. Neither did their own lord Ram came to their rescue seeing their stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now think about the train drivers fate. He might be a logical and a good citizen, now he has got headache just because he is living in a nation where majority cannot think and act logically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;more-train-deaths&quot;&gt;More train deaths&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have a button on a switch that leads a fast train to two tracks, one is a track that’s been in use but 50 children are playing in it ignoring reality, other one is a decommissioned and there is a clear marking its a decommissioned one and two children are playing in it knowing that’s its safe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the train is unable to brake, which track would you choose? The one with 50 idiots or one with 2 wise?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;emotional-nation&quot;&gt;Emotional Nation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are all humans. We are guided by ancient behavior that’s been in our blood for millions of years. These things lead us to think emotionally. Today we have sexual education that’s been widely implemented in all schools, why don’t we have a emotional education program? In fact India is one of the first nations to have emotional education. There was a person called Buddha doing it, we have forgotten him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sexual feeling will be mostly for 30 years years in our life, but emotions will stay till our death. There must be a program in our schools to look beyond emotions and look at logic, to understand how our environment works, and to think of the best ways to improve and change it for the betterment of society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well-being of nation consists of empowering the wise people and making the unwise wise. If our nation fails, it won’t be just us, like the United States we will be pulling humanity to abyss.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Winning election with tears</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sabarimalai</title><link href="/2018/10/17/sabarimalai.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sabarimalai" /><published>2018-10-17T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/10/17/sabarimalai</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/17/sabarimalai.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a6/Sabarimala2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, funny things are happening in India. A god called Aiyappan is treated like a men’s toilet. This god should not be worshiped or seen by women says Hindusism, but women do love to see Gods. In a judgment given by the apex court, women were allowed into the temple. Now some hindu fanatics acting against this judgment are blocking women  from entering this temple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;women-can-enter-other-aiyappan-temples&quot;&gt;Women can enter other Aiyappan temples&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whats really confusing to me is women can enter other Aiyappan temples. There are several temples of this God here in my city Chennai and I have seen women entering it and praying it. So isn’t Aiyappan in Chennai something greater and more powerful than men’s toilet in Sabarimalai?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;girl-animals-are-in-sabarimalai&quot;&gt;Girl animals are in Sabarimalai&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sabarimalai is surrounded by forests, and it has girl animals in it. These animals menstruate like human women and they must have wondered on the porch or even come close to Aiyappan there. If girl animals can do it, why can’t girl humans do it? We are part of the same kingdom. I am sure a girl bird would have once flown over aiyappans house and put its dropping on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think human girls would do such a disgusting thing because they have more intelligence, so why can’t they be allowed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sabarimalai-is-a-sham&quot;&gt;Sabarimalai is a sham&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One should note that Sabarimalai and Aiyappan is a sham. The Hindu has prove that makarajothi, a event where Aiyappan appears before humans is not a divine but a man made event. Aiyappan is just a cult, unlike a mortal Saibaba, Nithyananda, we just have a cult revolving around a statue, and statues last long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-feelings&quot;&gt;The feelings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people claim that feelings of believers are hurt by women entering this temple, but the same people say triple talaq system of divorce by muslim is wrong, and they too say that Saudi banning women from driving is wrong too. Aren’t they hurting muslim feelings then? Do they mean to say muslim feelings can be hurt wheras Hindus cannot? Or do they mean to say Indian and Saudi laws should change to empower only muslim women and not Hindu women?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-cant-aiyappan-handle-women&quot;&gt;Why can’t Aiyappan handle women?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why can’t Aiyappan handle women? Whats wrong with him? Is he a gay and don’t like women? Or is he a pervert who would jump out from his idol and have a fuck with a beautiful girl once he sees her?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-cant-law-reverse&quot;&gt;Why can’t law reverse?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a difference between facts and beliefs. Facts can be proven time and again and thus they can be verified, beliefs can and cannot be facts. Most religious beliefs aren’t facts and hence breaks down. Any progressive society will naturally weed out unwanted beliefs and will become a society that runs on facts so that it can become efficient and competitive and that’s what is happening to India. For India to go back to vedic times where women can be oppressed like animals, we need a revolution and Taliban like force occupying the power here. The RSS is one such organization that has a huge potential and they are in power. So women oppressors should support them so that women’s rights could be silenced one day. Till they the day they can oust democracy, you retards cannot do a thing in India.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why religion is stuck?</title><link href="/2018/10/13/why-religion-is-stuck.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why religion is stuck?" /><published>2018-10-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/10/13/why-religion-is-stuck</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/13/why-religion-is-stuck.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/e/e9/A_Hindu_princess_committing_suttee_against_the_wishes_of_the_Wellcome_L0022809.jpg/800px-A_Hindu_princess_committing_suttee_against_the_wishes_of_the_Wellcome_L0022809.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pictured above: the Hindu act of Sati, where it was believed that the woman should be burned along with the husbands pyre so that she could serve him in his afterlife.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a funny thing, one would worship the almighty God, and when something happens to his or health, the person would go to a doctor who follows scientific ways. Buddha once said “Nothing is constant. Everything is meaningless”. Though this is even ignored even by buddhists, this kind of thought never erupted in any other religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many religions was born out of thought, philosophy. How would you explain our existence? What happens to us when we are no more? Not having proper scientific thought and tools, they said or to be precise they blabbered what ever came to their mind and passed it down the generations. They thought what they thought was final and hence built an inflexibility into the system. This inflexibility would prove a moral death blow to religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, the bible says we all came from Adam and Eve, and we lived in a garden and fell to earth possibly without parachutes. And the bible is projected as the ultimate truth. Now we know its bull shit. But Christianity, Islam and other Abrahamic religions are not willing to ditch these stories. This inflexibility, inability to recognize faults in the system and throw away the old and embrace the new trend is causing doom to religions. And today no sane mind believes truly in God, or any religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Science on the other hand operates in other way. You can put what ever beautiful theories you want, but if it does not agree with reality its thrown out. This ability to provide practical theories to mankind, thus enabling him to understand about himself and his environment has made science thrive. Religious people are too egoistic and adamant to accept truth or ask sorry for misleading humans into a wrong path.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I Love Ruby’s new avatar</title><link href="/2018/10/12/i-love-ruby-s-new-avatar.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Love Ruby's new avatar" /><published>2018-10-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/10/12/i-love-ruby-s-new-avatar</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/12/i-love-ruby-s-new-avatar.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i-love-ruby.gitlab.io/images/cover.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t imagine that I have been writing this book for 10+ years. I Love Ruby is getting a new avatar, its been ported from &lt;a href=&quot;https://mindaslab.github.io/I-Love-Ruby/&quot;&gt;https://mindaslab.github.io/I-Love-Ruby/&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://i-love-ruby.gitlab.io/&quot;&gt;https://i-love-ruby.gitlab.io/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some one long long ago told me about Asciidoctor, I did not consider it much then, then it became evident to me that people love to read from mobiles now than PDF, so I started to port this book. Though I am Data Scientist now, and am using Python for it, Ruby is my love and I can’t forget it. It was sad for me to hear Matz say that Ruby isn’t cool any more, I would rather say Ruby isn’t used in cool ways anymore. Its the greatest programming language I have seen, it suits to my personal needs than any other. I never thought I would see a language better than Perl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of this port, even though I don’t find much time, is quite ambitious. First more than 250 pages must be ported, its a lot of work. I was planning to write a book called Solid Ruby which would talk to people about design patterns in Ruby, I have decided to scrap it and bring it under I Love Ruby thus making my life far simpler. I also wish to throw in some sample ruby projects in this book, and I wish to put out video tutorials. Since this book uses Asciidoctor, I dream of producing good quality epub and pdf, well, its quiet out of my hands though as I am not a contributor but a mere spectator to Asciidoctor. I wish to receive lot of feedback’s, they are really important as they give motivation or a chance to improve my work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I port this book, I am re-reading it and finding many places to correct it, and they are been applied then and there. This book as always is a continually improving book, possibly bit more professional now that it was released 10 or 12 years ago. I also thank my company Trumatics for sponsoring it, well it was easy to get it as I am one of the partner :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will be reporting the progress now and then in a sporadic way. Thanks for reading and happy coding.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Misinformation</title><link href="/2018/10/04/misinformation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Misinformation" /><published>2018-10-04T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-04T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/10/04/misinformation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/04/misinformation.html">&lt;p&gt;I was on a bike, my friend was driving it and he said that in November the Sun won’t be shining for 15 days, and this was confirmed by NASA said he. I was thrown back. A person who has read well and is in a decent profession, a profession where sanity of mind is very important and he said this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another friend of mine some day said that in next two weeks there will be so much rain in Tamilnadu that it will become like Kerala. Well, there is rain now in Chennai as I type and the power is cut and I can’t work without the internet and I had to write this blog to pass my time. But its certainly not like that one in Kerala. But in Tamilnadu, infra is so weak that even a drizzle can put the state and its capital Chennai into tail spin. The government we have simply doesn’t know what to do. We don’t even implement rain proof infrastructure, if we do, then rains will have no effect and disaster measure wouldn’t be needed and hence corrupt P.W.D contractors won’t be able to loot our tax money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What baffles me is this misinformation, how it spreads and how people believe it and tell to others, like it was the truth even without verifying the facts. I asked my friend on bike “how do you think we will survive for 15 days without the sun?”, “we can use electrical lights” said he. So so dumb. Its not just light that sun gives us, its the heat. The sun puts out so much heat that almost all water on earth is liquid. Switch it off for two days and almost all seas will go to near freezing or would have been frozen. Water inside our cells would freeze and we will all die a gory death. And how would you reckon that a nuclear reactor so big as the sun could be shut down for 15 days and then be restarted?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder whats happening to people? They said world will end in C.E 2000, then in C.E 2012 and now this. You can say things, but it must be backed by sane thought and proofs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was on a bike, my friend was driving it and he said that in November the Sun won’t be shining for 15 days, and this was confirmed by NASA said he. I was thrown back. A person who has read well and is in a decent profession, a profession where sanity of mind is very important and he said this.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baba Ramdev a fraud?</title><link href="/2018/10/03/baba-ramdev-a-fraud.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baba Ramdev a fraud?" /><published>2018-10-03T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-03T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/10/03/baba-ramdev-a-fraud</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/03/baba-ramdev-a-fraud.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.indianexpress.com/2017/08/ramdev-baba-film-ye-hai-india-759.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Baba Ramdev&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a Yogi in India who is called as Ramdev. He is advocate of how things Indian are superior to those of the west. He portrays himself as the savior of Indians from western influence and products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He promotes yoga and has got a product line called Patanjali which produces FMCG products so that Indian’s don’t buy western brands. All good, but what happens when Ramdev falls sick? Even though he calls himself a Yogi and promotes Indian stuff, when there is a real  issue with his health, he runs abroad for treatment says gossip. What a shame on him!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not just him, late M.G.Ramachandran, an actor and ex-chief-minister of Tamilnadu had a famous song line in one of his movies that say “Whats not there in this divine nation (India), why should we stretch our hands to foreign nations?”. Yet when he had a major illness with his Kidney what did he do? He ran to USA to get a treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0CNplJ-qiN4?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can only pity the people of India, how stupid they are and how they start to believe people who are in lime light so easy, and how they forget and forgive what the famous say and give in to sentiments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/_SNvusPdNHDc/TTFdpbANlFI/AAAAAAAAAlI/eyRVaccPDp4/s1600/annadurai.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;C.N.Annadurai&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should also be noted that another leader in India, C.N.Annadurai was critical of Tamils ignorance. He never boasted about Indian superiority over the West, at the same time he never said the West are superior to us. He acknowledged reality that West was highly developed compared to us and advocated close partnership. He got treatment for his cancer from USA and that’s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Annadurai once said, when asked a Tamilian “whats the capital of USA?”, a Tamil would not know the answer, but when asked “whats the vehicle of Yamadharamn?”, “its buffalo” a Tamil would say without hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will the people of my nation become more intelligent?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Baba Ramdev</summary></entry></feed>