<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-05-26T17:45:46+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Saw The Accidental Priminister</title><link href="/2019/05/26/saw-the-accidental-priminister.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Saw The Accidental Priminister" /><published>2019-05-26T17:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-05-26T17:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/05/26/saw-the-accidental-priminister</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/05/26/saw-the-accidental-priminister.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmJmYjU4ZmMtNTFjZC00MWYzLWFjNDktMzRmNGZhZDU0ZGU0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjE1OTQ0NjA@._V1_QL50_SY1000_CR0,0,691,1000_AL_.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I saw the movie “The Accidental Priminister”, well thats how I spell it :). It was good, wonder why congress supporters don’t like it? Don’t they think that it would be good for Congress and nation if the party does not cater to a single family and caters to people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this movie they say Manmohan Singh is just a jaalra to Sonia Gandhi. I believe it’s true. Indira Gandhi was a jaalara to the Soviets, Narasima Rao was a jaalar to the USA. Vajpyee was a jaalara to communal forces and the RSS and so does Modi follows in his footsteps (Vajpyeee did not have the opportunity to commit a genocide though). All our leaders were jaalara to something. So I don’t think its really says bad about Manmohan Singh. He was doing what many so called leaders of our nation did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One good thing is Sanjaya Banu wrote a book about Manmohan, imagine if some had wrote a book exposing Modi, (s)he would have been named Anti Indian, either he and his family should have fled India or would have disappeared or would have been killed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So showing Manmohan as jaalara, a truth coming out about a gentleman was not a surprise for me. What I noticed was the movies accuracy of star casting and how they portrayed the PMO and Sonia’s house in detail. Here I am in Sithalapakkam, worrying about my water supply, worrying whether it would be cost effective to turn on my A/C to quench the sweltering heat, worrying about whether to give my car for repair or not, having no clue how will I be 25 years from now, or will I exist 25 years from now? Or before I die will I live in a house that stands besides a tar road. I don’t have water, clean air, future is doubtful, yet the opulence with which these servants of mine who eat my tax money live with stunned me. The parties they attend are top class and they don’t pay for it. Its free for them :(.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure none in power ever sweats or feels cold, they are been cooled and heated by our sweat and blood. The infrastructure they enjoy is like a five seven service every day. I think their medicine too is free. That would explain why many old guys stick to power. While we citizens wait for busses under direct sun, they travel in convoys in nice and cozy environment. Thats what I noticed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder what makes a Indian accept that a Priminister or President who is our mere servant can have a unrealistic better life than us which we cannot even imagine? Or is it that I am the one who just thinks and all are dumb?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">India under Nazi Rule</title><link href="/2019/05/23/india-under-nazi-rule.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="India under Nazi Rule" /><published>2019-05-23T18:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-05-23T18:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/05/23/india-under-nazi-rule</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/05/23/india-under-nazi-rule.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s4.scoopwhoop.com/anj/hitler-modi/359878701.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the BJP has won. I wonder weather there will be another central government election in India. Or whether we will spiral into wars defeating our neighbours and so a leader who will be our warlord will rule our country forever? Let’s see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For beef lovers, the days are done. I think its time for them to quit India and go to a liberal nation. There is no guarantee that there would be no lynching and killing of people who love to eat beef.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any one who questions the government will be called an Anti-Indian, would be put into trouble by government officials and would be jailed, poisoned there and if they are still not yielding they would disappear. For example loot at the fate of Piyush Manush, he is been tortured now and then, Thirumurugan Gandhi is poisoned, and Mugilan has disappeared, most probably he has been killed in a brutal way, who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was looking at the behaviour of Modi, his behaviour and that of Adolf Hitler are very similar. Let me tell you waht I found:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both Hitler and Modi started from humble beginnings. Hitler was a simple solder, a painter dreaming big for his nation and Modi was working in a tea shop.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both Modi and Hitler love their nation. Thats unquestionable.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both have a strong feeling that what they think and do is the right thing for the nation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both don’t listen to intellectuals around them, take for instance the demonetisation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both are narcissist and, love do grand things so that people praise them. They want for their names to be eternal.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both have high self discipline and are relatively uncorrupt.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hitler had Himler with him and Modi has Amit Shah.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both Nazi party and BJP has a violent and ultra nationalist wing attached with it, for Nazi’s its the SS, for BJP its the RSS.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both have a reason to hit at neighbours. For the Nazi’s its the greatness of Germany. Here I strongly suspect how there could be a bomb blast in Pulwama if we have strong Chowkidars who guard the nation. Or they are Chowkidars for name sake and are real dummies?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Modi is loved by international committee and so was Hitler, until the day realised his true intentions.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Both Hitler and Modi have got the reputation of manipulating governments data. Modi is a economic debacle, so he has told statisticians to manipulate data so that the economy looks good. Hitler manipulated government economic data too. Almost none in public knew the money spent for killing jews. But under Hitler, economy improved, under Modi it slides down.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The press in Nazi Germany was highly controlled by the Nazi party, and so is the same case in India. Watch the news channels, there would always be a pro Modi news that has no substance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Freedom of expression was highly controlled.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Take for instance women trying to enter Aiyappan, God is equal to all, but they are still been denied the right despite the court ruling in favour of them.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Take for instance the killing of Gauri Lankesh and how the case is still unsolved.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;In Tamilnadu take for instance ruining of the life of Perumal Murugan by Hindu’s.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So lets see what the future holds. I feel Modi’s brain and attitude is on a knife edge he could be just a normal PM and he could be a psycho like Hitler. Unlike Vajpyee and like Hitler he has no patience and self control and could let loose. In fact Modi has done it, in Nazi Germany Jews were persecuted and in Modi Gujarat Muslims were slain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this land, miracles have happened, Chand Ahoka became Ashoka The Great, Alexanders Violent push to rule the Earth came to an end, we defeated the greatest empire at that time (ruled by Winston Chruchill, a blood thirsty Englishman who starved us to death) without firing a shot. Lets see whether this land would go into dark ruins because of this mad man called Modi and his Hindu clan, or lets see whether our soil turns him into nice one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sithalapakkam dries up</title><link href="/2019/05/19/sithalapakkam-dries-up.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sithalapakkam dries up" /><published>2019-05-19T21:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-05-19T21:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/05/19/sithalapakkam-dries-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/05/19/sithalapakkam-dries-up.html">&lt;p&gt;We were forced to drill a bore in our home in Sithalapakkam today. This region has totally dried up. Our previous bore made a decade ago was just 60 feet, and it had water at 6 feet. We thought thats good! It will never dry up, but it has, thanks to human exploitation. Now from 60 feet, we have gone to 200 feet. Very soon sea water will seep in and take the place of fresh water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not the mistake of people of Sithalapakkam 100%, it’s because of exploitation of people around us. Where the the water for fancy companies in OMR comes from? It’s from us. Where most big hotels draw their water from? It’s our water. Just stand in Medavakkam junction and see. All the lorries and vans carrying water that come out of Sithalapakkam will give a bribe to the police and move on, and we foolish residence capture rainwater and send it to the ground so that these people can dry it without paying us a single rupee. Thats what happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The simple thing here is we are idiots and have let the water sellers sell our precious resource for OMR and hotel guys. What else?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We were forced to drill a bore in our home in Sithalapakkam today. This region has totally dried up. Our previous bore made a decade ago was just 60 feet, and it had water at 6 feet. We thought thats good! It will never dry up, but it has, thanks to human exploitation. Now from 60 feet, we have gone to 200 feet. Very soon sea water will seep in and take the place of fresh water.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Christchurch Call violates freedom of expression</title><link href="/2019/05/18/christchurch-call-violates-freedom-of-expression.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Christchurch Call violates freedom of expression" /><published>2019-05-18T14:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-05-18T14:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/05/18/christchurch-call-violates-freedom-of-expression</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/05/18/christchurch-call-violates-freedom-of-expression.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6c/Jacinda_Ardern%2C_2018.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Christchurch Call simply does not stand in accordance with freedom of expression. It says violent and terrorist videos that are online must be eliminated, but why? Why it’s wrong to portray violence online? I don’t understand. Are we humans going to act as though we are not a violent species? That sucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right from the time of chimps we have been violent. There are documented evidences showing that chimps do conduct genocide and mass murder, we just continue it. It’s just part of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next comes the issue of what’s terrorism. Bhagatsingh is a hero in India and terrorist in the U.K. Osama Binladen is a hero to many Muslims around the world, to others he’s a terrorist. Nathuram Gotse is a nationalist to hardline Hindus in India, but a terrorist to rationalist. When whats terror and not terror, and whats violent and whats act of war and self defence varies from perspective to perspective. In that case we can’t say a stuff is violent or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take for example a man slaying his goat for his family. His kids would love to eat it. According to them, their father is kind and non violent person, but according to the goat he is a killer and a terrorist. It all depends on the perspective and we must respect it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Terrorism, violence, good and bad, etc are all human defined terms and they vary from place to place. It’s stupid to say that what few countries that have signed the Christchurch Call, call as violent and hateful acts are violent and hateful. You in the western world would not call USA’s and UK’s war as a violent act do you? But imagine how many lives it has affected. How many people have felt helpless because of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The priminister if Newzeland I suppose has got no other job after her loosing her post, so she is trying to portray herself as a global leader who is soooo good so that she can win again and again. Any way time has presented a very good chance for her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India too happily signed it because here now cow eaters are being killed, so if any one shares the video of killing on social media, India can show this call and take down the video, thus putting up a scene as though India is a pure nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.christchurchcall.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.christchurchcall.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Coward India</title><link href="/2019/05/09/coward-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coward India" /><published>2019-05-09T15:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-05-09T15:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/05/09/coward-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/05/09/coward-india.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/4/41/Flag_of_India.svg/1200px-Flag_of_India.svg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt very bad last week or the beginning of this week, Hamas lauched rockets into Gaza and Israel within no time retaliated and cease fire was reached between two sides. Israel is a tiny tiny nation with a tiny population, yet the are able to defeat the entire Arab world, strike their enemies when ever they are hit. Here we are second massive nation, 6th largest economy, if Pakistan terrorist strikes, we need to wait, plan and execute action fearing their army. Even if we kill less than a 100 of them we celebrate as a surgical strike. Are we really a nation that can defend itself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Masood Azad gets listed as terrorist and we celebrate, what the heck if he gets listed as terrorist or not? We haven’t killed him yet, even at this very instant he keeps plotting against India and rest of the world on how to bomb and kill some one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a impractical nation, we stay terror should be abolished and it hasn’t been abolished yet. From the 60’s we were saying we will abolish poverty, from the age of Periyaar we say we will do away with the caste system, we say politics and religion should be kept apart, we say bribes are illegal. Yet not one of the things we say and dream have materialized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This phenomenon points to one thing: Indians are cowards, they say and they cannot do. Indian men should roam around wearing sarees and women should roam around wearing nothing. That’s what we are worth for.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Can you sleep when the wind blows?</title><link href="/2019/04/29/can-you-sleep-when-the-wind-blows.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Can you sleep when the wind blows?" /><published>2019-04-29T19:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-29T19:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/29/can-you-sleep-when-the-wind-blows</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/29/can-you-sleep-when-the-wind-blows.html">&lt;p&gt;The following story circulated on the Internet - a superb metaphorical exposition of the level of preparedness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Years ago, a farmer owned land along the Atlantic seacoast.
He constantly advertised for hired hands. Most people were reluctant to work on farms along the Atlantic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They dreaded the awful storms that raged across the Atlantic, wreaking havoc on the buildings and crops. As the farmer interviewed applicants for the job, he received a steady stream of refusals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, a short, thin man, well past middle age, approached the farmer. ‘Are you a good farm hand?’ the farmer asked him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Well, I can sleep when the wind blows,’ answered the little man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although puzzled by this answer, the farmer, desperate for help, hired him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The little man worked well around the farm, busy from dawn to dusk, and the farmer felt satisfied with the man’s work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then one night the wind howled loudly in from offshore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jumping out of bed, the farmer grabbed a lantern and rushed next door to the hired hand’s sleeping quarters. He shook the little man and yelled, ‘Get up! A storm is coming!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tie things down before they blow away!’ The little man rolled over in bed and said firmly, ‘No sir. I told you, I can sleep when the wind blows.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enraged by the response, the farmer was tempted to fire him on the spot. Instead, he hurried outside to prepare for the storm. To his amazement, he discovered that all of the haystacks had been covered with tarpaulins. The cows were in the barn, the chickens were in the coops, and the doors were barred. The shutters were tightly secured. Everything was tied down. Nothing could blow away. The farmer then understood what his hired hand meant, so he returned to his bed to also sleep while the wind blew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you’re prepared, spiritually, mentally, and physically, you have nothing to fear. Can you sleep when the wind blows through your life?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hired hand in the story was able to sleep because he had secured the farm against the storm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above story goes on to talk about trials and tribulations in life and if we do our best to understand, accept, and implement the principles learnt by us we will experience a deep sense of security, peace, and joy from within.  We will then be able to ‘sleep when the wind blows.’&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The following story circulated on the Internet - a superb metaphorical exposition of the level of preparedness.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Don’t buy side dish from Yaa Mohaideen Perumbaakkam</title><link href="/2019/04/29/don-t-buy-side-dish-from-yaa-mohaideen-perumbaakkam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Don't buy side dish from Yaa Mohaideen Perumbaakkam" /><published>2019-04-29T08:10:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-29T08:10:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/29/don-t-buy-side-dish-from-yaa-mohaideen-perumbaakkam</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/29/don-t-buy-side-dish-from-yaa-mohaideen-perumbaakkam.html">&lt;p&gt;Yestarday I was in Yaa Mahaideen in Perumbaakkam. We bought some khushka to eat and side dishes. One was Chicken 65 and other was Hydrabadi mutton gravy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The khushka arrived promptly, and later I found out that it was mutton khushka and not chicken, thats great, but at the hotel we were irritated to our limit. Once the khuska was given as parcel to us, the guy told us to go outside and show the bill and get the side dish parcel, so we went out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a small counter outside and there was all these Zomato and Uber guys. It was chaotic. Our token number was 70 and only token 29 was done with. We waited for 30 mins and our token wasn’t called.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took the bill and went inside and aked the billing guy to refund the side dish money and to my horror he would say he wouldn’t. What? They will make us wait, they won’t tell us any information about our order, we have to keep standing for so long and if we want to cancel our order they won’t do it. Is that a way to treat a customer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The billing guy said that our side dish was cooked and has been rushed to the counter just now. So we ran out to get it, the guy at the disposing counter said the billing guys knows nothing. We had to endue such pillar to post running. It took a great deal of protest from me and after nearly 1 hour they said they has lost our bill, took the copy we had and delivered our side dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not just me, as soon as I entered the restaurant, a customer was shouting at the waiter, he ordered a briyani, he was unable to eat it and hence wanted a lemon juice to go along with it. It never arrived. He shouted and and canceled it. The juice arrived 10 minutes later, that too when that guy had struggled and had almost finished with the briyani. He was really pissed off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To deliver briyani Yaa Mohaideen is great, but for other things their cooking and delivery chain is broken. A Uber or Zomato guy there said he had been waiting for nearly 1 hour for side dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I would suggest is to buy briyani there and order side dish from from places around it. There are other restaurants in the same block and they sell tandoori and other side dish stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally lets come to the taste. At home the khushka was okay, the hydrabadi mutton gravy was good, but the chicken 65 tasted like cardboard. It had almost no marination and was hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think Yaa Mohaideen is like Apple, a brand who’s name is well established, highly priced and not really worth it. My suggestion is to try other small genuine briyani shops.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yestarday I was in Yaa Mahaideen in Perumbaakkam. We bought some khushka to eat and side dishes. One was Chicken 65 and other was Hydrabadi mutton gravy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Good that people are turning away from engineering</title><link href="/2019/04/25/good-that-people-are-turning-away-from-engineering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Good that people are turning away from engineering" /><published>2019-04-25T00:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-25T00:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/25/good-that-people-are-turning-away-from-engineering</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/25/good-that-people-are-turning-away-from-engineering.html">&lt;p&gt;Its good that people are turning away from Engineering. We have lot and lot of terribly bad engineers. A lot of greed from families who want to become quickly rich from their kids has spoiled a generation, and the result, like a buildings built out of cardboard, we have extremely low quality engineers all around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Market is market and it responded. Engineers today don’t get respect and they are treated like shit. Lot of people who never ever would have been interested in Science and Technology hold an engineering degree today. And they do menial jobs like data entry and get paid low, really low. I Think I saw it in reddit, a person has complained that an engineering graduate earns less than a pani poori vendor. True, very true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So as price for an engineer drops, people are moving away from it, and that’s good. Because good engineers who are passionate about their jobs will stick with it, and people who hold engineering degrees and who are not passionate about it will leave. This is a very good correction. I welcome it with a huge smile.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Its good that people are turning away from Engineering. We have lot and lot of terribly bad engineers. A lot of greed from families who want to become quickly rich from their kids has spoiled a generation, and the result, like a buildings built out of cardboard, we have extremely low quality engineers all around.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Money money money, Sulekha wants my money</title><link href="/2019/04/24/Sulekha-wants-my-money.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Money money money, Sulekha wants my money" /><published>2019-04-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/24/Sulekha-wants-my-money</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/24/Sulekha-wants-my-money.html">&lt;audio controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;/sounds/Call@0091%2089391%207(00918939178428)_20190424185841.mp3 &quot; type=&quot;audio/mpeg&quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the audio element.
      &lt;/audio&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the audio element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Banning TikTok is a violation of freedom of expression</title><link href="/2019/04/21/Banning-TikTok-is-a-violation-of-freedom-of-expression.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Banning TikTok is a violation of freedom of expression" /><published>2019-04-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/21/Banning%20-TikTok-is-a-violation-of-freedom-of-expression</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/21/Banning-TikTok-is-a-violation-of-freedom-of-expression.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.theweek.co.uk/sites/theweek/files/2018/12/tiktok.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is a democracy, which means one has got freedom of expression. One should have the right to express himself and herself in the form of text, voice, images, videos and action. And we should be okay and tolerant with it. We can ignore those expression, that’s our right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example I am an atheist living in a highly religious nation. I do get irritated and feel sorry when people worship God, and to put it mildly, God is not present. Yet we as a nation spend billions in the name of God every year, and still our policy makers have not banned this blind faith. Why? Because it interferes with the freedom of expression. Even we rationalist try to explain the stupidity of blind faith to the faithful than to lobby the government and seek a ban on God and religion. Because being a stupid is your right and expressing your stupidity is your right too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same is the case with TikTok. one can use it for entertainment to cajole himself, or one can use it to waste away his life. One can use it to share a cooking tip or a scientific experiment, or one can use it to share porn. Its ones wish. Democracy should be tolerant and should not obstruct the flow of information and should not affect ones will and ability to express in any way possible. Its unfortunate that India is not a democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Harassing China&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From being a Soviet colony, India has now become colony of the USA, so India must do something that pleases its ruler. USA is harassing China recently, like giving trouble to Huawei. USA is unable to control China diplomatically, neither China can be contained economically and it cannot be defeated militarily. Unlike India, its leaders can’t be bribed easily and hence harassment to submission could be one strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly European leaders will not obey the will of USA as they head sovereign nations,and hence USA has picked up India as one of its hit man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to use TikTok&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though you cannot download TikTok from Google app store, you can get its APK else where. Just visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://apkpure.com/tiktok/com.ss.android.ugc.trill&quot;&gt;https://apkpure.com/tiktok/com.ss.android.ugc.trill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/17/tiktok-india-bans-video-sharing-app&quot;&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/17/tiktok-india-bans-video-sharing-app&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>