<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-20T11:54:08+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Are Tamils naturally foolhardy?</title><link href="/2020/04/20/are-tamils-naturally-foolhardy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Are Tamils naturally foolhardy?" /><published>2020-04-20T11:53:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-20T11:53:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/04/20/are-tamils-naturally-foolhardy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/20/are-tamils-naturally-foolhardy.html">&lt;p&gt;Iran cancels Ramzaan, a thing I wouldn’t expect to happen. A Nation that turned completely Islamic 40 years ago, now listens to its doctors and science. It was an excellent transformation! As a rationalist I am joyed to see it. But then few days back on April 14th, we Tamils celebrated our new year, people ventured out even in Corona intense places, they seem not to be concerned about the consequence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possibly going back a month or a month and a half ago, I was telling about Corona to my team back in Trivandrum, all were Kerala people and young, when I briefed them about corona their pupils dilated, their eyes became bigger, they had their desire to go home to their native. It was very different feeling I had, because in Tamilnadu, if I brief yong people about something, say like server crash or about some disaster, say warn about floods (which I did way back), they would take it into account, but would brush it off and go to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Kerala seems to have contained Corona, people over there are cautious about it, over here Corona is accelerating, and none seems to be bothered about it. Living in Kerala for a month, I feel Kerala people are gentle, and Tamils have some kid of rock in them, determined, they travel towards a goal or something not been bothered much about their feelings and fear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be something in people in Tamilnadu that I feel is making them more adventurous. Take for instance our sport Jallikattu, we want to match ourself with this big beast. It’s only now the sport which is done in a bit sane way, but before liquor was fed to the cow, chilly powder rubbed on its privates and it was made to face the youth to have a aggressive Jallikattu. We simply did not bother about been pierced and torn by it, we welcomed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not now, we have a saying ஆறிலும் சாவு, அறுபதிலும் சாவு (death at 6, death at 60), which means death comes at any age and don’t be bothered about it. The book of Pura-naanuuru hails of moms sending their young sons to battle, and feeling proud that they will die for the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even in war, at the battle field Tamils followed tactics that would make others feel that we are crazy. War elephants were made to drink and sent amok in the battle field, bringing in panic and killing friend and foe alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of all civilizations in India, it was the Tamils that ventured far into the oceans, as far as Newzeland. And for what purpose? We simply don’t know. Even places in Japan that are suitable for habitation are named kudil (குடில்), why so? We may not know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right at the place I live, in Sithalapakkam, I find foolhardiness of people, and it has got a philosophical base. It was after coming to this place I heard about Hans, Mawa and Supaari, these are drugs which people use, especially the youngsters over her. When asked why, and asked wont it bring early death? Their reply was ‘கோள் புடிக்கும் முன் சாவு நல்லது’, that is it’s better to die before I need a staff for my support. I was astounded by this philosophy of a drug addict who possibly did not attend his scool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s only after interacting with people of other states that I find there is something different in Tamil, a form of bravery, a form of foolhardiness, not being afraid of death, ignoring facts and Tamils feel comfortable being a stupid, perhaps unique to this region. Possibly it was this adventurous nature that made our language spread far and wide. Today our children call their parent’s mummy and daddy, whereas Korean kids call their parents Amma and Appa.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Iran cancels Ramzaan, a thing I wouldn’t expect to happen. A Nation that turned completely Islamic 40 years ago, now listens to its doctors and science. It was an excellent transformation! As a rationalist I am joyed to see it. But then few days back on April 14th, we Tamils celebrated our new year, people ventured out even in Corona intense places, they seem not to be concerned about the consequence.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Don’t write complex SQL queries</title><link href="/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/anti%20patterns/2020/04/17/don-t-write-complex-sql-queries.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Don't write complex SQL queries" /><published>2020-04-17T09:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-17T09:51:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/anti%20patterns/2020/04/17/don-t-write-complex-sql-queries</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/anti%20patterns/2020/04/17/don-t-write-complex-sql-queries.html">&lt;p&gt;Say that you want to be a musician, so you buy a nice violin, but you don’t know how to play it and don’t have the patience to learn how to play it, so to produce music you trash the violin on rock and call it music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the case I find with many teams using Rails. They pick up Rails because it’s fancy, a buzz word and they fail to stick with it’s best practices. Yesterday my team mate called me and asked me a doubt, there was a function that just had one line of ORM and it was easy to test, so I told him how. There was another in which a complex join was used, the function spanned 10 lines or so and mostly it was occupied by SQL query.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The function was badly written and it did not have any other documentation that said what it did. I simply couldn’t tell the poor fellow how to test it. It might have been an old code written before the dawn of humanity and it was crap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One reason I’d been told by the so called Rails people is that writing SQL is efficient than using ORM. The strength of Rails, well, most of it is in ActiveRecord, it’s ORM layer. If you don’t want it why on earth are you using Rails?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to Rails, it’s true that ORM is inefficient and firing lot of SQL slows down the DB. But haven’t you chosen the Rails and Ruby path because you are concerned with human productivity than with computer efficiency? Is your application so big that it spans more than 100 servers all scaled to max vertically that is making you to take such a drastic decision?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now what about making computers do lot of work so that humans are productive? Isn’t that progress? There are ways to scale Data Base, be it MySQL or Postgres. Postgres comes with very excellent scaling which you can use to make many servers act like one Posgres DB. For MySQL there are stuffs like ProxySQL that catches and make the DB run more cooler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making computer’s work hard makes economic sense too. An Engineer who is supposed to follow computing trends should know that computing costs are getting cheaper and human costs are getting higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder why people are bring up so much bane on themselves when there are so much boon that’s been given to us by the Free Software Community? One thing is due to ignorance. Managers push programmers so much and make them accountable for everything, that programmers become like narrow visioned horses which concentrate just on their destination than to think out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any technical house should trust it’s engineers, should give them enough resources to them to explore, when you are faced with a problem, the team should come up with 5 to 10 solutions which should be put to the test, out of that which is the most suitable for the team should be chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you like to bang things around and want to be a musician, choose to play drums rather than a violin.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Say that you want to be a musician, so you buy a nice violin, but you don’t know how to play it and don’t have the patience to learn how to play it, so to produce music you trash the violin on rock and call it music.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Don’t change constants in Ruby</title><link href="/programming/ruby/rubocop/anti%20pattern/2020/04/14/don-t-change-constants-in-ruby.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Don't change constants in Ruby" /><published>2020-04-14T20:42:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-14T20:42:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/ruby/rubocop/anti%20pattern/2020/04/14/don-t-change-constants-in-ruby</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/ruby/rubocop/anti%20pattern/2020/04/14/don-t-change-constants-in-ruby.html">&lt;p&gt;I am reviewing a lot of code now, kind of projects that have million plus lines of Ruby code that been (un)maintained for 13 years or so. That’s lot of code and lot of years. Still the project goes strong. I once encountered a thing that crashed our server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take this one&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for some reason, this hash constant changes, don’t ask me why, this changes, so the code is like this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:some_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:some_value&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually in the above code, ruby just warns and lets you a free run. I am kind of against that, but that’s how Ruby works. But now when I run rubocop auto correct against it, the above code get’s transformed to something like below&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{}.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;freeze&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:some_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:some_value&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/code&gt; is frozen, and it cannot be changed. Rubocop is right, constant should not change, that’s why its a constant! Common!! That’s why rubocop froze it. So when it encounters this line &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH[:some_key] = :some_value&lt;/code&gt;, what was set not to change, now changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i0.wp.com/theverybesttop10.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/Top-10-Best-Images-of-Surprised-Cats-2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Ruby throws an error and stops code execution. The basic thing is CONSTANT IS CONSTANT and don’t ever change it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I am reviewing a lot of code now, kind of projects that have million plus lines of Ruby code that been (un)maintained for 13 years or so. That’s lot of code and lot of years. Still the project goes strong. I once encountered a thing that crashed our server.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Will I.T companies realize the goodness of work from home?</title><link href="/2020/04/12/will-i-t-companies-realize-the-goodness-of-work-from-home.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Will I.T companies realize the goodness of work from home?" /><published>2020-04-12T15:06:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-12T15:06:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/04/12/will-i-t-companies-realize-the-goodness-of-work-from-home</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/12/will-i-t-companies-realize-the-goodness-of-work-from-home.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://fm.cnbc.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/img/editorial/2018/08/08/105384527-1533749153652manworkingonlaptopatdiningtable.1910x1000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I.T companies are simply marketing agents, they just sell your talent to those who seek it and they keep a huge amount of profit. Its just like a pipe that connects your water tank and sink and demands a chunk of money because its at the middle. In fact many of you who work in I.T would have known that I.T companies just forward the client emails to you and your emails back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before, say 30 years from now, working in I.T company made sense. Computers were so expensive that an individual cannot buy it. One needed salary and time to get trained in learning to write software. Training and training material were expensive. Computers were fragile and needed air-conditioning and static and dust free environment. All of these cannot be afforded by a single person and hence there were companies that did it and hired people. Today every one can buy a laptop and equipped with knowledge and internet connection can start a I.T business. Then why on Earth I.T companies sill exist and gobble off money that needs to go directly to workers and not those bosses that do almost nothing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I.T companies have become good at is to control their employees. Employees in I.T companies mostly believe that they need the company. It’s possibly because of our culture. We Indians were uneducated 4 generations ago, most of us were brought up with middle class thought that we must study hard get a job and work hard. So using this inferiority complex of ours, certain foxes are able to run their I.T business successfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s come to the point of working from home. Today many I.T companies let their employees work from home due to pressure from the government, and if not they would have asked their employees to come to office and wouldn’t have bothered a sliver if their employees die out of Corona. In fact I know certain I.T bosses who went up to the level of saying Corona is a fake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I.T companies and their bosses are always afraid that you, the tech guy / gal will know your potential and would start a parallel business. Even websites that say that it will connect you with potential clients are afraid  of you having contact directly with the client. Try creating your profile in Freelancer, Fiverr, or UpWork, you simply can’t list your phone number and email (but &lt;a href=&quot;http://nyoboo.com&quot;&gt;nyoboo&lt;/a&gt; allows you to do it).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work from home is also used to black mail you. In my previous company Francium, the bosses were psychos to put it mildly. There was an excellent devops guy, they did not realize his potential because of their limited knowledge and tunnel vision, all of a sudden work from home was cut for him. As it turns out that they wanted to fire him for some reason and hence they started to torture him. They couldn’t do it with me because I came to office anyway, so they told me to come to office at 11:00 AM every day, when I failed a spy would tell my arrival timing to the boss who will use it to make me feel bad. All were spied as far as I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I certainly believe freelancers will head the I.T industry of the future. It is good economics, why the middle man so called your boss or an I.T company get the lions share of money when it is just a pipe? Why can’t we develop automated tools that will market you depending on your activity and customer satisfaction?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can be done and that’s what we are doing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fragile and Strong India</title><link href="/india/philosophy/economics/infrastructure/life/2020/04/09/fragile-and-strong-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fragile and Strong India" /><published>2020-04-09T23:04:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-09T23:04:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/philosophy/economics/infrastructure/life/2020/04/09/fragile-and-strong-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/philosophy/economics/infrastructure/life/2020/04/09/fragile-and-strong-india.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://freesvg.org/img/papapishu_Beagle_dog.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It started to rain at 3:20 PM, not much, a light drizzle, there was distant thunder and lightning, and the power was cut, we got it back at nearly 9:30 PM. Just like that a 6 hour power break. I was wondering what to tell my boss. Corona has forced us to stay at home, and at home because of the fragile infrastructure of my nation I am unable to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is India’s fragility. Modi wants to go abroad, speak on radio and T.V about the golden rule he is offering us, but no matter what scene you put, this is the ground reality of India. A nation capable of building a cutting edge nuclear reactor not more than 100 Km or so from my home, is unable to offer power due to a drizzle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s come to India’s strength. What strength do we have? Well, the population. ‘Are you married?’, ‘How is your family?’, ‘How many kids do you have?’, are the questions we as Indians are asked every corner we turn. No one want’s to discuss politics, general knowledge, puzzles, economics any more, neither do they any other brain flexing activity of significance is liked by the populace, we talk to talk rather than to have a intellectual exchange. Even if Corona kills 10% of us, we will still be 900 million plus. That’s a huge number, remember you can’t even really comprehend what 900 million human’s are. That’s our strength.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every life reproduce, from a virus (which is half life) to us. That’s the basis of life, and we Indian’s have become really good at executing the genetic code that’s set into us. Our population has has become our strength. But at what cost?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a dog at a rich man’s house. It chews away beef, chicken, if one is really rich possibly mutton and pork, or been fed dog food, and having a peaceful life and so on. Now imagine a stray dog, it has to eat fast, because if not some other might grab its food. It has very limited supply of food, just those thrown away in garbage, its life is free but with danger, it eats and multiplies and has kids like we Indians do. It’s life is really unsatisfactory like that of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rich dog rarely has an offspring. Like fertility centers that caters to rich couple, there are breeding programs for rich dogs too, but for the poor it just breeds like us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A politician is like the person in tea shop. Stray dogs approach him, wait patiently, he eats most of the biscuit or samosa or whatever and throws some luxurious food to the stray, and the stray is grateful for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most Indian families are like stray dog families. You live to get married, gets kids, depend on some one else, hope that even if some of us are dead others will survive up to the breeding age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The advanced civilizations, that has made the processors of the device you are using to read my blog are like the rich dog. They can’t tolerate a power cut for a drizzle, they look at quality, try to keep numbers low, maximize productivity and resource availability for every one and depend on quality than quantity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which way our nation goes is in each and every family’s hands.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Junior Kuppuna Closes for Good and Bismi Briyani Review</title><link href="/chennai/velacherry/restaurant%20reviews/food/briyani/2020/04/04/junior-kuppuna-closes-for-good-and-bismi-briyani-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Junior Kuppuna Closes for Good and Bismi Briyani Review" /><published>2020-04-04T22:27:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-04T22:27:00+05:30</updated><id>/chennai/velacherry/restaurant%20reviews/food/briyani/2020/04/04/junior-kuppuna-closes-for-good-and-bismi-briyani-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="/chennai/velacherry/restaurant%20reviews/food/briyani/2020/04/04/junior-kuppuna-closes-for-good-and-bismi-briyani-review.html">&lt;p&gt;I think on 21st morning, just hours before the Corona curfew, I took the car out to buy supplies for my home, our journey took us past Velacherry, actually we went deep into Chennai, then while returning we first checked for Briyani at Samco Velacherry, it was closed, and driving down the 100 feet road, we checked out Milan which was closed too, and finally we found Bismi Briyani (Velacherry) to be open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ordered a briyani parcel, because at that time the orders from the government was none should eat in hotel. Actually I like parceled food. With a parcel I can eat @ the comfort of my home rather than some strange place called hotel, I can watch what ever I want on T.V and have it, I can even lie down and have it. It would be rather great if I had five to seven beautiful girls feeding me while I played my favorite games (I mean computer games), but economy is down now :( I envy the Romans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way while driving above the railway bridge in Velacherry, I was told that Junior Kuppana hotel had closed. Thank God it did. When I was running Trumatics, me, my partner Umashankar and another friend Vimal went there. We ordered full Briyani, I think mutton and was served a quarter, my partner told the waiter that we ordered full briyani, and the waiter pointed out to the quarter briyani and said that was the full here. WHAAAAATTTT!! We were shocked! I swear even if 7 plated of that full went in, I would have still place for 3 more. And I think this one costed  more than Rs 200/-. These servings of gold and diamonds are designed for girls who are on  a diet or something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People warned us of not going there but we went, possibly Vimal was a favorite of Umashankar, and it was Vimal’s recommendation. I remember ordering some side dishes too, but I forgot what they were. All I remember was having a lengthy conversation with Vimal on that day, before we returned to office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ever we went out with Uma, he paid the bill. His hospitality and respect for friends excelled. But still what was utter costly, it was. I never felt good about eating there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now its closed, I feel its closed for good. I just feel a plunderer had just died. What ever be the reason for the high cost, I am happy that they are gone. I want Chennai to have cheap, clean and tasty food that serves the masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming to the Bismi briyani I got as parcel, first I had to tell about this Bismi briyani. First time I went to this hotel I was with my mom and uncle, and they made us wait, before we finished our food and came out it was nearly or possibly more than 2 hours. The wait was frustrating. That was long time back. Now, thanks to Corona  the hotel was empty and our parcel was served in minutes. We took it and headed back home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The briyani was okay, I think one half costs about Rs 130/-, that’s the kind of standard rate in Chennai, the rice was non aromatic. It was made in kind of Nizam style, kind of the Triplicane kind, but not as good as Triplicane. The brinjal curry was okay to good, an half came with an egg, though I am personally against serving egg eith briyani, that’s the norm here. I don’t remember eating onion raitha. The meat was hard. For a Rs 90/- briyani if the meat was hard, I would say okay, but this one is Rs 130/-. I should also review cheap briyani’s around Sithalapakkam. Who knows? Some might have quality and cheapness too. Any way let’s see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then what to say, that’s how the briyani was. Compared to Hotel Milan at Vijaynagar signal, Bismi is nothing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I think on 21st morning, just hours before the Corona curfew, I took the car out to buy supplies for my home, our journey took us past Velacherry, actually we went deep into Chennai, then while returning we first checked for Briyani at Samco Velacherry, it was closed, and driving down the 100 feet road, we checked out Milan which was closed too, and finally we found Bismi Briyani (Velacherry) to be open.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Modi’s Tuglak Rule in India - The Half Baked Lockdown</title><link href="/2020/03/29/modi-s-tuglak-rule-in-india-the-half-baked-lockdown.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Modi's Tuglak Rule in India - The Half Baked Lockdown" /><published>2020-03-29T11:41:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-29T11:41:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/03/29/modi-s-tuglak-rule-in-india-the-half-baked-lockdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/03/29/modi-s-tuglak-rule-in-india-the-half-baked-lockdown.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/crowd_in_delhi_bus_stand.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture above is a bus stand in Delhi yesterday. Crowds of migrant workers want to flee to their native due to the fear of Corona virus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture below shows a dad and daughter in exodus, they have no option but to walk thousands of kilometers to their home town&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dad_daughter_exodus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now ask the BJP and Modi, ‘why this is happening?’, they would immediately reply that its because of Corona virus and they are helpless. This helplessness has become the trade mark of Modi’s rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black money should be eliminated, so Modi bans nearly 86% of the monetary value in India by demonetization over night. People died because of it, and almost no black money was caught. What about the deaths? The Modi and government is helpless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sardar’s status was built, it was built with our tax money and massive donations from us, yet we need to pay to see the statue. Plus people working there did not get the salary and they left. Now Modi government is helpless,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muhammad Bin Tuglak too was a fool who ruled India. He is famous for taking decisions just like that because he had the feeling that great strong rulers took decisions in a stupid way, without listening to any one and he stood by it, just like Modi stands by his decisions, and thousands died in his rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like Tuglak, when Modi takes a decision and see a catastrophe happening, these both idiots watched. When thousands are migrating, there is no assistance for them to reach their home towns. There is no food and toilet facilities for them. Modi just watches from the comfort of him home, praying to his fucking God’s in Sanskrit, just like Tuglak would have prayed to his fucking Allah in Urudu or Arabic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine how foolish we are? We have almost always made idiots to come to power. Be it Indra, Rajiv etc, but twice in history we have made utter idiots aka brain dead to come to power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking decisions over night would look sexy and bold, but now look, it is fool hardy one. What will Modi answer to those strained legs? Will he massage them? What will he answer to those who are without food in their own country? Will he feed them? What will he say to those families that will loose their loved ones not due to Corona, but due to exhaustion an starvation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking decision and looking like a strong man may be sexy, but what good a decision or policy holds if its taking without any solid footing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just imagine how stupid are those BJP guys who are still supporting this Modi dick.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Twitter shouldn’t have censored Rajinikanth</title><link href="/internet/censorship/2020/03/22/twitter-shouldn-t-have-censored-rajinikanth.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Twitter shouldn't have censored Rajinikanth" /><published>2020-03-22T21:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-22T21:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/internet/censorship/2020/03/22/twitter-shouldn-t-have-censored-rajinikanth</id><content type="html" xml:base="/internet/censorship/2020/03/22/twitter-shouldn-t-have-censored-rajinikanth.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Rajinikanth_at_the_Inauguration_of_MGR_Statue.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I don’t watch news much. I am becoming like an hermit, concentrating on my job, concentrating on people I manage, trying to bring them up to my level and perhaps if I am good enough they will become far better than me. My knowledge of Corona and other stuff is very limited, but I just saw a news that disturbed me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this self containment in India that’s going on, Rajinikankanth gave a explanation on Twitter on how he supported it, and why this containment was necessary, it seems to have contained many mistakes and Twitter has taken down his video. That’s disturbing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twitter represents free speech&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first reason why I feel disturbing about Twitter censorship is because Twitter was found on the basis of freedom information sharing, whether the information was right or wrong, you must be able to share it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many Christians, Muslims, Hindus, Jediist’s on Twitter talk about their religion as truth. Many politicians speak on Twitter that that they are here for their nation, and they loot, yet they have not been censored. Advertisements put out by companies lie, they are not censored. Companies and corporation tell that they support environment, worker’s right, but they pollute, and fire people when they sense slightest financial stress and they are not censored. The reality is those all are bullshit too and they are not banned. Why Rajini’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am stunned how biased the world is. If a parent tells to a child, or minister tells to his mass in Church or on social media that God is there, its wrong and misinformation, but the world bears it because of ignorance and we rationalist bear it because we respect ones free speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel Twitter must support free speech, be it a Pakistani terrorist who says he want’s to destroy India because God told him to do so,  Twitter must allow it. As a human, it’s his right to speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Posting something one feels on social media is not wrong I feel, because one can debate about it. With debate there is a good chance of truth coming out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know that Nithyanandha is utter nonsense, but we enjoy his comedy. We enjoy Modi, Tamilisai (though she has become a governor and is entertaining us no more, that’s sad!), H.Raja etc. We know that Rajini is ill educated and speaks nonsense, so let’s enjoy and ridicule it. Why Twitter is taking away that pleasure from us?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twitter could die&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Banning or putting a hold on debating culture and trying to curb free speech and misinformation is bad for Twitter. There are platforms like Diaspora, Mastadon, ZeroNet. Many who truly respect freedom of speech are using these platforms. If time is right, it might just take weeks or months for people to switch to other platforms en-mass.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Chicz and Cafe Elisa closes</title><link href="/trivandrum/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/22/hotel-chicz-and-cafe-elisa-closes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Chicz and Cafe Elisa closes" /><published>2020-03-22T15:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-22T15:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/trivandrum/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/22/hotel-chicz-and-cafe-elisa-closes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/trivandrum/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/22/hotel-chicz-and-cafe-elisa-closes.html">&lt;p&gt;I was new to Trivandrum, the hotel my company made me stay called as Le Franc wasn’t a hotel at all. Apart from complementary breakfast it has no other food. Even water wasn’t delivered to room, there ws a can and we had to drink from it. It was a lodge but those idiots called themselves a hotel!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to order food from outside, I think the very first day for dinner I ordered parotta and chicken liver fry from hotel chicz. The parotta came with a gravy which I never tasted because I ate it with chicken liver fry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The liver fry was semi gravy and awesome and I loved it, for Rs 80/-, they gave a whole plate of liver fry. Afer eating it I had no trouble, the food was good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then moved into New Lotus PG after a week, and I took walk in the nerby main road, to my suprise I found out that hotel Chicz was there, I went in, the guy said he had some dishes, I asked for parotta and asked what side dishes are there, and he said a few and liver fry was not one among them. I told him I ordered it on swiggy and it was awesome, for some reason the hotel owner was thrilled and he was moved emotionally. They prepared it, this time with lot of pepper and dry, and with parotta it was awesome again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was surprised why this guy was moved so emotionally, I think he was kind of shocked and surprised when some one praised his hotel just before closure. I never knew they would close, because to me that hotel was a really good one, but now it’s closed and I am sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding good food in Trivandrum for a Tamil guy is tough, one of my PG mate has hard time here, he travels long to Tamilian hotels to eat, due to my family restrictions I never had chance to learn to drive a bike and I had to eat bad local food and live with it here in this new city. I had food poisoning twice, three people in my team too suffered from poisoning, one like me was poisoned twice. Plus the food here is too expensive, restaurants which charge the right rates are closing down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had found another restaurant named Cafe Elisa in Bhavani, Technopark. By mistake I first ordered Kappa briyani, and bloody hell, it wasn’t even briyani, it was some kind of thick beef stew. Yak. One thing in Kerala, Briyani is not Briyani. They simply don’t know Nizam or Mughal cooking. Some foods in Cafe Elisa costs, like chicken briyani is Rs 130/- and its okay compared to Swad aka Flavours and Platters, but the quantity is too little. But fish gravy meals is of good quantity, you get unlimited Kerala rice, fish gravy with a small pice of fish, along with gravy’s for rice and some side dishes, and it’s good. It costs Rs 90/-, but if you eat it for lunch, you can skip dinner, so its economical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt Cafe Elisa was good when it came to fish gravy (here the people say it Fish Curry) meals, but now it too has closed down. I really don’t know what’s happening and why these hotels that don’t spoil health are closing down. The shops like Travancore Rasavada which gave me food poisoning twice are thriving. So sad…&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was new to Trivandrum, the hotel my company made me stay called as Le Franc wasn’t a hotel at all. Apart from complementary breakfast it has no other food. Even water wasn’t delivered to room, there ws a can and we had to drink from it. It was a lodge but those idiots called themselves a hotel!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My another take on marriage</title><link href="/2020/03/12/my-another-take-on-marriage.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My another take on marriage" /><published>2020-03-12T23:26:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-12T23:26:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/03/12/my-another-take-on-marriage</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/03/12/my-another-take-on-marriage.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hOIp5pmJizA/maxresdefault.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have heard women complain about how hard it is to do household chores, how hard it is to take care of children, how hard it is to have a married life. I have heard men complain less, but many spend time outside family, long times out and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a man I was able to understand men. The constant nagging of women, how it corrodes us and so on. As men, all we want is sex. Men are dogs and we want nothing more. We are genetically programmed to transmit our genes to many offspring’s as possible. If a man says he really likes / loves a woman and none other, then its a spoof, we are programmed to track, analyze and target all women from adulthood to death. Yup we may sugar coat it as love, marriage, family, dates and blah blah, it all depends on ones social and emotional quotient, but the base is the same animal instinct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For woman I believed what they said about their difficulties. Now I feel I haven’t understood them. I got a job outside my city and accepted it. The first week of stay was sponsored by my company and now I am all by myself. Not in a hotel as before, but in a paying guest accommodation. In Chennai I was treated like Buddha in my family. All my friends drink, but they don’t to drink before me, I was eposed to almost no evil. Coming here I saw how a drunk would behave, I saw how much it would cost for a man to live. But two things went wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First my friend Umashankar, when we ran the company Trumatics (&lt;a href=&quot;http://trumatics.com&quot;&gt;http://trumatics.com&lt;/a&gt;), he said I was treated like God in Chennai and I would know the difficulty of living when I am out. I am out now, and am feeling happy and have the same feeling as living in Chennai. The theory that I would suffer when I go into an uncomfortable zone became false and wrong. I don’t know why. There is something in humanity to help, and that has kept me comfortable all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second is this, listening to women I thought family work was hard, but its not. I wash my cups and utensils, wash my clothes, and it looks fun at least to me. It does not look difficult at all. I don’t know why women complain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just began to think. There are two types of coding I do, the coding I like and coding I hate. It all depends on the love of the task I have to complete. Similarly I think doing household chores depends on the woman’s love for her husband, in-laws, kids and so on. If that love falters, the family crumbles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might think love is constant, but that’s not true, like a graph it sways. It depends on ones hormones, training of ones mind, what others say about the person you love, your ego and many factors. In fact the same circuits in the brain that is responsible for love is also responsible for hate, that’s why when the circuit switches you start to hate the person with same intensity as you loved that person. Sometimes your brain is so locked, love and hate becomes irreversible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This begs the question. So what is marriage if love is not constant? All I can only say ‘I don’t know’. I simply don’t know. What I can say is, your love and hate for a person is independent of what relationship you have with them. The more intimate the relationship, the more intense is the feeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This also begs the question of woman’s freedom. In India, still, a woman is tied to a man if marriage has happened. Everything in her life is pinned around her husband, if she leaves her husband because of hate (which should be respected as well), she is blamed, and ashamed. Sometimes it’s the husband that abandons a woman, in that case its more pathetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel people don’t give as much attention to right of a person to hate another as they give respect and attention to right of a human to love another. The people who have respected and studied those who hated them have come up in life. Take the case of Alexander and Purushothaman, each studied each other in the battle of Hydrapass. Take for instance Indian freedom movement. Indian leaders never hated British, they simply wanted their self rule, whereas the Brits hated us, so they ran away when they realized no more money can be made in India. Take Nelson Mandela, he studied those who hated black, those wo hated whites and those who hated him. When he had the nation in his hand, he forgave them. He even forgave his own wife Winney. Almost all great people have studied hate, and studied those who hate them. So rather than getting pissed off by a hateful person, study them, it could give crucial information on how to take the next step in your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what it tells to me about marriage. Well it’s simple. As a man I know that no man is fit to marry. Now I am beginning to realize almost no woman is fit to be married either. But ya, to have easy sex, people stick to what ever social framework and do what evolution has set us to do.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>