<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-10-31T21:17:30+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">For my GenZ - Curing the cancer that grips Mother India</title><link href="/2025/10/31/for-my-genz-curing-the-cancer-that-grips-mother-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="For my GenZ - Curing the cancer that grips Mother India" /><published>2025-10-31T21:17:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-31T21:17:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/31/for-my-genz-curing-the-cancer-that-grips-mother-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/31/for-my-genz-curing-the-cancer-that-grips-mother-india.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5c/Bharat_Mata_bronze.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Mother India&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corruption&quot;&gt;Corruption&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a cancer that grips most nations, as well as our mother India. Corruption. Though we drove out the Brits, one of the reasons why we drove them out is because they looted our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Periyaar, being a wise man said that Independence is a dark day. He went on to say, that we are merely replacing white skinned looters with dark ones. 70 years on, that’s the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right in my state in Tamilnadu, while we struggle to make a living, the deputy CM, Udhayanidhi Stalin, flies to Thailand in a private jet, celebrates diwali with his family, and comes back. Over here he puts a scene that he will destroy sandhana dharma (a draconian Talibanistic Hinduism), while he shamelessly celebrates a religious function being in an atheistic party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the center, Jai Shah’s wealth jumps. Nitin Gadkari’s sons company shares soar because he seems to run an ethanol company, and Gadkari passed a law that Indian fuels should have ethanol blend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine, what did Udhaya, Jai, and Gadkari do to deserve an opuluent lifestyle? What gave them the right to control the lives of millions of people, live a lifestyle where electricity never flickers in their homes, they drive on roads without potholes, get excellent health, they no need to worry about the tution fees of their kids, while we struggle?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;think&quot;&gt;Think&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was happy to see the protests in Bangladesh and Nepal. It put the power of people before the few elite. The people thought them who is really the master. In India, even though the GenZ works more than 10 hours a day, are of slaves of the capitalists, they can’t afford insurance, and family, they are keeping quiet. It’s a mystery for me why they do so, but calm an steady is a blessing. Plus sudden disruption does cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GenZ might not create a physical storm, but don’t let the storm in your mind, that could extinguish the flames of people who loot, and create inequality in our nation, die out. Keep feeding the storm with facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think about the opulence of elite, think why you can’t live like them? Never stop thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;talk&quot;&gt;Talk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the use og thought if you keep it with yourself? So talk. Though we call ourselves democratic, India is not a democracy. If you talk, as I do in this blog, you will face trouble. If you question, you will face trouble. But then what choice do we have?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all cannot migrate to Scandinavian countries where corruption is low. This is our land and we must clean it up. Else you must be happy to accept the elite, the lords, you must be happy enough that your child, grandchild, and generations following them  will be servant of theirs. If that’s okay, be happy. It’s your choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are happy to see your mother gripped in forever disease, which cannot be cured, then think who you are?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;act&quot;&gt;Act&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Protests are good, but they are dangerous, if something really drastic should be done, then yes thats one of the ways to achieve it. I am not against protest. But then imagine the cost, you go out, just because someone looted our nation, at the end of the day your family could be crying over your dead body. Worst the police could pick you up and make you live the life of a cripple. They could make you walk in and out og courts forever. If that’s okay, I salute you. I don’t have the bravery and resources to do it, but if you are a brave, all my heart goes to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a better way. You goto a polling booth, how many symbols / candidates you see? Just two? Many right? About how many of them you know? Only two? Why? Or worst, you just vote for one among that two, so that you can feel satisfied that the person whom you voted for has won. But at what cost? You have given a poison injection to your mother India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When there is an election, and you are going to vote, why don’t you do research about say five to ten candidate, not just the top two? Why don’t you tell people around you, what you like about those candidates, what you don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could form groups, where members of the group can meet the not so known candidates, you can discuss about those candidates on tiktok (ah free speech! banned in non democratic countries!), insta, youtube, facebook or whatever. People will become more aware of them. Votes will spread. This will put pressure on the duopoly, duopoly is a cancer to democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T.N.Seshan once said, ‘today’s election is like this, you have to choose between one who shoots you, or one who strangles you.’ or something like that. But there are so many candidates on the voters list, isn’t the duty of every citizen to know about at-least 5 of them? Then come to a conclusion on whom to vote? Out o f the 5 you researched, maybe, 3 of them, the part they are representing has been involved in corruption, may be 2 of them have no black marks on them. Isn’t it wise to give chance to those who are clean?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure if elections are rigged, I am not sure even if India is democratic, there seems to be a huge gap between the elite and us, there seems no ladder for us to climb and reach up to them. If we don’t stop them now, think, will we be lucky enough again to get another Gandhi? Bagat Singh? Or Netaji? Think.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Mother India</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When you’re drained but your brain won’t switch off</title><link href="/2025/10/31/when-you-re-drained-but-your-brain-won-t-switch-off.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When you&apos;re drained but your brain won&apos;t switch off" /><published>2025-10-31T20:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-31T20:51:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/31/when-you-re-drained-but-your-brain-won-t-switch-off</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/31/when-you-re-drained-but-your-brain-won-t-switch-off.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.indiatoday.in/lifestyle/wellness/story/when-youre-drained-but-your-brain-wont-switch-off-2809567-2025-10-30&quot;&gt;https://www.indiatoday.in/lifestyle/wellness/story/when-youre-drained-but-your-brain-wont-switch-off-2809567-2025-10-30&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cultural Shift and “Productivity Anxiety”:&lt;/strong&gt; Modern society ties self-worth to productivity, leading to “productivity anxiety” where people feel uneasy or guilty when not actively working or improving, viewing rest as a form of failure.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Societal Pressure and Social Media:&lt;/strong&gt; Constant competition, the celebration of busyness, and social media comparisons exacerbate the pressure to be constantly productive, making individuals feel like they’re falling behind if they rest.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fear of Unresolved Thoughts:&lt;/strong&gt; Many avoid rest to prevent confronting buried thoughts, worries, or unresolved emotions that surface in moments of stillness, making true rest uncomfortable.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chronic Stress and Other Factors:&lt;/strong&gt; Chronic stress, fear of judgment, perfectionism, over-identification with roles, and constant digital connectivity further hinder the ability to truly relax.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital “Rest” is Not True Rest:&lt;/strong&gt; Engaging with screens (Netflix, social media) is often mistaken for rest but is actually another form of mental exhaustion, preventing genuine mental and physical rejuvenation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redefining and Learning to Rest:&lt;/strong&gt; True rest is essential for well-being, involves disconnecting from digital devices, practicing mindfulness, setting boundaries, and acknowledging thoughts rather than escaping them, thereby recharging for better focus and energy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.indiatoday.in/lifestyle/wellness/story/when-youre-drained-but-your-brain-wont-switch-off-2809567-2025-10-30</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How a chorus of synchronized frequencies helps you digest your food</title><link href="/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How a chorus of synchronized frequencies helps you digest your food" /><published>2025-10-31T17:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-31T17:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html&quot;&gt;https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Biological systems often exhibit synchronization, like fireflies or fish, but the mechanics are complex, as seen in brain blood vessels.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;UC San Diego researchers studied the gut’s peristalsis to understand how oscillations synchronize, finding a “staircase effect” where similar frequencies lock onto each other.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This research used a classical model of coupled oscillators, simplified by the gut’s unidirectional nature compared to the brain’s complex vasculature.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The new mathematical solution explains how food moves and is churned in the digestive tract and could aid in understanding gastrointestinal motility disorders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The study determined key features of the staircase phenomenon in the gut, which had not been precisely understood before.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The researchers plan to apply these findings back to the more complex, multi-directional oscillations observed in the brain’s vasculature.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kafka is fast – I’ll use Postgres</title><link href="/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kafka is fast -- I&apos;ll use Postgres" /><published>2025-10-30T16:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-30T16:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks&quot;&gt;https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The tech world is divided into two camps: one chasing buzzwords and adopting popular but potentially inappropriate solutions, and the other prioritizing common sense, pragmatism, and first principles.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “common sense” camp is gaining traction due to the “Small Data” movement (acknowledging sufficient hardware for most data sizes) and the “Postgres Renaissance” (Postgres’ growing capability to handle diverse use cases).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The article argues that Postgres can effectively handle many functionalities typically assigned to specialized systems like Elasticsearch, MongoDB, Redis, and Kafka, covering over 80% of use cases with 20% of the effort.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Benchmarks were conducted for Postgres as a Pub/Sub messaging system, demonstrating competitive performance with Kafka at lower scales (e.g., 5 MB/s ingest, 25 MB/s egress on a 3-node cluster).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Postgres Pub/Sub performance scaled significantly on a 96 vCPU single node, achieving 238 MiB/s write and 1.16 GiB/s read throughput, though a custom design approach was used.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Benchmarks for Postgres as a Queue also showed strong performance, with a modest single-node setup handling thousands of messages per second and an HA setup exceeding 2000 messages/second.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The author advocates for defaulting to Postgres, emphasizing the quality-of-life benefits and reduced organizational complexity compared to specialized distributed systems for small-to-medium scale.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Premature optimization by adopting complex web-scale technologies for non-web-scale problems is deemed an “anti-pattern” due to significant organizational and financial overhead.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “Minimum Viable Infrastructure (MVI)” approach is recommended: choosing familiar, “good-enough” technology, solving real problems with minimal features, and leveraging widely adopted systems like Postgres.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “it won’t scale” argument is refuted by citing OpenAI’s successful use of unsharded Postgres for massive read loads, the long timeframe for reaching critical scale, and the concept of overdesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vegetarians, watch this: The Science of Vitamin B12</title><link href="/2025/10/29/vegetarians-watch-this-the-science-of-vitamin-b12.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vegetarians, watch this: The Science of Vitamin B12" /><published>2025-10-29T09:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-29T09:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/29/vegetarians-watch-this-the-science-of-vitamin-b12</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/29/vegetarians-watch-this-the-science-of-vitamin-b12.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pTSbh-XgxM&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pTSbh-XgxM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cobalt is a rare metal essential for lithium-ion batteries due to its thermal stability, with most production from the Democratic Republic of Congo.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cobalt is also crucial for animal life as it is a key component of cobalamin (Vitamin B12), vital for DNA, fatty acid, and amino acid production.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Animals cannot synthesize Vitamin B12 and rely on consuming it from food, a dependency that evolved because synthesizing B12 is a complex and energy-intensive biological process.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Plants do not require B12 as they have a different biochemical pathway for DNA, fatty acid, and protein synthesis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vitamin B12 deficiency can lead to severe health issues, including problems with red blood cell production, neurological problems, and fatigue.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The typical Indian diet often leads to B12 deficiency due to low per capita meat consumption, as B12 is primarily found in animal sources.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To ensure adequate B12 intake, options include consuming red meat and seafood, fortified foods, or supplements, especially for those on vegan diets or with culturally limited animal product intake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pTSbh-XgxM</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Khalid’s sucks compared to Yamohideen briyani</title><link href="/2025/10/21/khalids-sucks-compared-to-yamohideen-briyani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Khalid&apos;s sucks compared to Yamohideen briyani" /><published>2025-10-21T16:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-21T16:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/21/khalids-sucks-compared-to-yamohideen-briyani</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/21/khalids-sucks-compared-to-yamohideen-briyani.html">&lt;p&gt;This year, the day after Pillayar chaturthi, I wanted to eat briyani. I drove to Medavakkam’s Yamohideen briyani and it was closed. Though expensive, its meat quality seems to be good compared to other briyani houses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I drove down the road, towards Shollinganallur, took a U-turn, there was Khalids. Buying briyani there was a disappointment. In Yamohideen, you had lot of meat for rice, really nice to eat, that’s how briyani should be. But in Khalids there were just two pieces of meat, it was totally disappointing. Th price in Khalids was disappointing too, it was equivalent to Yamohideen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will never goto Khalids again. They just seem to rip people off. I must say though the taste of briyani in Khalids was not bad. But it rips us off, when you see the minuscule quantity of meat they offer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This year, the day after Pillayar chaturthi, I wanted to eat briyani. I drove to Medavakkam’s Yamohideen briyani and it was closed. Though expensive, its meat quality seems to be good compared to other briyani houses.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Renewables topple coal in global historic first with developing countries leading the charge</title><link href="/2025/10/20/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Renewables topple coal in global historic first with developing countries leading the charge" /><published>2025-10-20T17:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-20T17:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/20/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/20/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://scroll.in/article/1087475/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge?utm_source=firefox-newtab-en-intl&quot;&gt;https://scroll.in/article/1087475/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge?utm_source=firefox-newtab-en-intl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Renewables have surpassed coal as the top global electricity source, although progress varies, accelerating in developing nations while slowing in the U.S. and EU.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Smaller nations are rapidly adopting clean energy, electric vehicles, and battery storage, often driven by economic factors like reducing reliance on expensive fossil fuels and improving grid reliability, rather than solely climate change concerns.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bhutan, traditionally hydro-reliant, is diversifying with solar, wind, and biomass to combat seasonal power drops and meet industrial demand, transitioning from a winter importer to a balanced energy mix.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nepal, prompted by a 2015 blockade, is aggressively shifting to electric vehicles, powered by domestic hydropower, to reduce import dependence and air pollution, with significant growth in EV adoption despite political instability.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sri Lanka’s severe economic crisis in 2022-2023 highlighted its energy vulnerabilities, pushing the nation to rapidly expand solar and wind power, aiming for 70% renewable energy by 2030, supported by AI-based grid integration and inclusive projects.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Maldives is replacing diesel generators with solar arrays and battery storage across its islands to mitigate high import costs and oil price volatility, prioritizing economic survival and community benefits in its net-zero by 2030 roadmap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://scroll.in/article/1087475/renewables-topple-coal-in-global-historic-first-with-developing-countries-leading-the-charge?utm_source=firefox-newtab-en-intl</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Varq</title><link href="/2025/10/20/varq.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Varq" /><published>2025-10-20T11:07:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-20T11:07:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/20/varq</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/20/varq.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/&quot;&gt;https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The text describes the traditional craft of making “varq” (edible silver and gold leaf) in Hyderabad’s Old City, highlighting the sensory experience of finding a workshop through the rhythmic hammering sound.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Varq, used as an edible decoration for sweets and other dishes, has a long history in India, with mentions in ancient Ayurvedic texts for its medicinal properties and later refined in Mughal courts as a symbol of luxury and status.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Historically, varq was made by hand-beating silver between sheets of ox gut or cowhide, a meticulous process passed down through generations of artisans.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Despite rising silver prices leading some sweet shops to use cheaper machine-made or aluminum substitutes, the tradition of hand-beaten varq persists, with a few remaining artisans preserving this delicate art.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The term “varq” itself has Sanskrit and Persian origins, both meaning “leaf” or “sheet,” reflecting its ancient roots and cultural significance across different eras in India.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shell fish is better than fish</title><link href="/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shell fish is better than fish" /><published>2025-10-16T18:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-16T18:05:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish are presented as a superior alternative to fish for combating sarcopenia, the age-related loss of muscle mass.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish protein is highly bioavailable and rich in amino acids like leucine, effectively stimulating muscle protein synthesis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They are packed with essential minerals (zinc, selenium, iron) and B vitamins, which act as “activators” for muscle health and cellular processes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish contain taurine, an amino acid that protects muscles from oxidative stress, supports mitochondrial health, and improves endurance, crucial for aging bodies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unlike larger fish, shellfish are low in the food chain and generally do not accumulate heavy metals like mercury, making them a safe and clean food source.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Regular shellfish consumption, combined with appropriate exercise and lifestyle, can significantly reduce sarcopenia and frailty, promoting vitality in old age.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An anti-sarcopenia lifestyle encompasses not only diet (like shellfish) but also movement, adequate sleep, hydration, inflammation management, good digestion, hormonal balance, sunlight exposure, and social connection.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish contribute to overall health beyond muscles by supporting nerves (B12), protecting joints and bones (muscle pull), and aiding brain function (blood sugar regulation).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The text emphasizes that sarcopenia is preventable and reversible, not an inevitable part of aging, and small, consistent choices, including incorporating shellfish, can make a significant difference.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The ultimate vision is an active, independent, and joyful aging experience, free from the limitations often associated with muscle loss, made possible by a holistic approach centered on nutrient-dense foods like shellfish.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Plan is not execution, it’s communication</title><link href="/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Plan is not execution, it&apos;s communication" /><published>2025-10-10T12:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-10T12:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication.html">&lt;p&gt;I think Eisenhower said something like, though it does not work, plan is essential. I am in software industry, and we programmers have been asked often the question: ‘what is our plan?’, ‘when is the deadline?’, and we do give a plan and estimated deadline, and most of the time, it won’t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who are ignorant feel bad about it. In IT industry, people who work are less stupid, and usually the stupidest person gets to the top due to Dunning Kruger effect. So they don’t have intelligence to separate between plan and real world happenings. So if a plan fails or slips, the intelligent person who did the plan is put to a toss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is complex. You don’t plan to brush your teeth, it happens, you don’t plan to breathe. You plan only when you are not sure, you plan only when you are not made up for the task, when you are unsure. That is you plan only when there is element(s) of uncertainty, or some difficulty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not intelligent for a person to take a plan as execution, instead it should be treated as communication. This is what a person is going to do. It might happen happen in the way planned, but there is a good chance that it won’t, the course might change, we might even scrub it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wise person sees plan, and pads it up with more resources, to take the shock(s) of reality, he also plans for failure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I think Eisenhower said something like, though it does not work, plan is essential. I am in software industry, and we programmers have been asked often the question: ‘what is our plan?’, ‘when is the deadline?’, and we do give a plan and estimated deadline, and most of the time, it won’t work.</summary></entry></feed>