<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-04T22:28:05+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Junior Kuppuna Closes for Good and Bismi Briyani Review</title><link href="/chennai/velacherry/restaurant%20reviews/food/briyani/2020/04/04/junior-kuppuna-closes-for-good-and-bismi-briyani-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Junior Kuppuna Closes for Good and Bismi Briyani Review" /><published>2020-04-04T22:27:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-04T22:27:00+05:30</updated><id>/chennai/velacherry/restaurant%20reviews/food/briyani/2020/04/04/junior-kuppuna-closes-for-good-and-bismi-briyani-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="/chennai/velacherry/restaurant%20reviews/food/briyani/2020/04/04/junior-kuppuna-closes-for-good-and-bismi-briyani-review.html">&lt;p&gt;I think on 21st morning, just hours before the Corona curfew, I took the car out to buy supplies for my home, our journey took us past Velacherry, actually we went deep into Chennai, then while returning we first checked for Briyani at Samco Velacherry, it was closed, and driving down the 100 feet road, we checked out Milan which was closed too, and finally we found Bismi Briyani (Velacherry) to be open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ordered a briyani parcel, because at that time the orders from the government was none should eat in hotel. Actually I like parceled food. With a parcel I can eat @ the comfort of my home rather than some strange place called hotel, I can watch what ever I want on T.V and have it, I can even lie down and have it. It would be rather great if I had five to seven beautiful girls feeding me while I played my favorite games (I mean computer games), but economy is down now :( I envy the Romans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way while driving above the railway bridge in Velacherry, I was told that Junior Kuppana hotel had closed. Thank God it did. When I was running Trumatics, me, my partner Umashankar and another friend Vimal went there. We ordered full Briyani, I think mutton and was served a quarter, my partner told the waiter that we ordered full briyani, and the waiter pointed out to the quarter briyani and said that was the full here. WHAAAAATTTT!! We were shocked! I swear even if 7 plated of that full went in, I would have still place for 3 more. And I think this one costed  more than Rs 200/-. These servings of gold and diamonds are designed for girls who are on  a diet or something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People warned us of not going there but we went, possibly Vimal was a favorite of Umashankar, and it was Vimal’s recommendation. I remember ordering some side dishes too, but I forgot what they were. All I remember was having a lengthy conversation with Vimal on that day, before we returned to office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ever we went out with Uma, he paid the bill. His hospitality and respect for friends excelled. But still what was utter costly, it was. I never felt good about eating there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now its closed, I feel its closed for good. I just feel a plunderer had just died. What ever be the reason for the high cost, I am happy that they are gone. I want Chennai to have cheap, clean and tasty food that serves the masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming to the Bismi briyani I got as parcel, first I had to tell about this Bismi briyani. First time I went to this hotel I was with my mom and uncle, and they made us wait, before we finished our food and came out it was nearly or possibly more than 2 hours. The wait was frustrating. That was long time back. Now, thanks to Corona  the hotel was empty and our parcel was served in minutes. We took it and headed back home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The briyani was okay, I think one half costs about Rs 130/-, that’s the kind of standard rate in Chennai, the rice was non aromatic. It was made in kind of Nizam style, kind of the Triplicane kind, but not as good as Triplicane. The brinjal curry was okay to good, an half came with an egg, though I am personally against serving egg eith briyani, that’s the norm here. I don’t remember eating onion raitha. The meat was hard. For a Rs 90/- briyani if the meat was hard, I would say okay, but this one is Rs 130/-. I should also review cheap briyani’s around Sithalapakkam. Who knows? Some might have quality and cheapness too. Any way let’s see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then what to say, that’s how the briyani was. Compared to Hotel Milan at Vijaynagar signal, Bismi is nothing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I think on 21st morning, just hours before the Corona curfew, I took the car out to buy supplies for my home, our journey took us past Velacherry, actually we went deep into Chennai, then while returning we first checked for Briyani at Samco Velacherry, it was closed, and driving down the 100 feet road, we checked out Milan which was closed too, and finally we found Bismi Briyani (Velacherry) to be open.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Modi’s Tuglak Rule in India - The Half Baked Lockdown</title><link href="/2020/03/29/modi-s-tuglak-rule-in-india-the-half-baked-lockdown.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Modi's Tuglak Rule in India - The Half Baked Lockdown" /><published>2020-03-29T11:41:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-29T11:41:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/03/29/modi-s-tuglak-rule-in-india-the-half-baked-lockdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/03/29/modi-s-tuglak-rule-in-india-the-half-baked-lockdown.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/crowd_in_delhi_bus_stand.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture above is a bus stand in Delhi yesterday. Crowds of migrant workers want to flee to their native due to the fear of Corona virus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture below shows a dad and daughter in exodus, they have no option but to walk thousands of kilometers to their home town&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dad_daughter_exodus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now ask the BJP and Modi, ‘why this is happening?’, they would immediately reply that its because of Corona virus and they are helpless. This helplessness has become the trade mark of Modi’s rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black money should be eliminated, so Modi bans nearly 86% of the monetary value in India by demonetization over night. People died because of it, and almost no black money was caught. What about the deaths? The Modi and government is helpless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sardar’s status was built, it was built with our tax money and massive donations from us, yet we need to pay to see the statue. Plus people working there did not get the salary and they left. Now Modi government is helpless,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muhammad Bin Tuglak too was a fool who ruled India. He is famous for taking decisions just like that because he had the feeling that great strong rulers took decisions in a stupid way, without listening to any one and he stood by it, just like Modi stands by his decisions, and thousands died in his rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like Tuglak, when Modi takes a decision and see a catastrophe happening, these both idiots watched. When thousands are migrating, there is no assistance for them to reach their home towns. There is no food and toilet facilities for them. Modi just watches from the comfort of him home, praying to his fucking God’s in Sanskrit, just like Tuglak would have prayed to his fucking Allah in Urudu or Arabic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine how foolish we are? We have almost always made idiots to come to power. Be it Indra, Rajiv etc, but twice in history we have made utter idiots aka brain dead to come to power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking decisions over night would look sexy and bold, but now look, it is fool hardy one. What will Modi answer to those strained legs? Will he massage them? What will he answer to those who are without food in their own country? Will he feed them? What will he say to those families that will loose their loved ones not due to Corona, but due to exhaustion an starvation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking decision and looking like a strong man may be sexy, but what good a decision or policy holds if its taking without any solid footing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just imagine how stupid are those BJP guys who are still supporting this Modi dick.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Twitter shouldn’t have censored Rajinikanth</title><link href="/internet/censorship/2020/03/22/twitter-shouldn-t-have-censored-rajinikanth.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Twitter shouldn't have censored Rajinikanth" /><published>2020-03-22T21:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-22T21:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/internet/censorship/2020/03/22/twitter-shouldn-t-have-censored-rajinikanth</id><content type="html" xml:base="/internet/censorship/2020/03/22/twitter-shouldn-t-have-censored-rajinikanth.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Rajinikanth_at_the_Inauguration_of_MGR_Statue.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I don’t watch news much. I am becoming like an hermit, concentrating on my job, concentrating on people I manage, trying to bring them up to my level and perhaps if I am good enough they will become far better than me. My knowledge of Corona and other stuff is very limited, but I just saw a news that disturbed me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this self containment in India that’s going on, Rajinikankanth gave a explanation on Twitter on how he supported it, and why this containment was necessary, it seems to have contained many mistakes and Twitter has taken down his video. That’s disturbing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twitter represents free speech&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first reason why I feel disturbing about Twitter censorship is because Twitter was found on the basis of freedom information sharing, whether the information was right or wrong, you must be able to share it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many Christians, Muslims, Hindus, Jediist’s on Twitter talk about their religion as truth. Many politicians speak on Twitter that that they are here for their nation, and they loot, yet they have not been censored. Advertisements put out by companies lie, they are not censored. Companies and corporation tell that they support environment, worker’s right, but they pollute, and fire people when they sense slightest financial stress and they are not censored. The reality is those all are bullshit too and they are not banned. Why Rajini’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am stunned how biased the world is. If a parent tells to a child, or minister tells to his mass in Church or on social media that God is there, its wrong and misinformation, but the world bears it because of ignorance and we rationalist bear it because we respect ones free speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel Twitter must support free speech, be it a Pakistani terrorist who says he want’s to destroy India because God told him to do so,  Twitter must allow it. As a human, it’s his right to speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Posting something one feels on social media is not wrong I feel, because one can debate about it. With debate there is a good chance of truth coming out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know that Nithyanandha is utter nonsense, but we enjoy his comedy. We enjoy Modi, Tamilisai (though she has become a governor and is entertaining us no more, that’s sad!), H.Raja etc. We know that Rajini is ill educated and speaks nonsense, so let’s enjoy and ridicule it. Why Twitter is taking away that pleasure from us?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twitter could die&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Banning or putting a hold on debating culture and trying to curb free speech and misinformation is bad for Twitter. There are platforms like Diaspora, Mastadon, ZeroNet. Many who truly respect freedom of speech are using these platforms. If time is right, it might just take weeks or months for people to switch to other platforms en-mass.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Chicz and Cafe Elisa closes</title><link href="/trivandrum/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/22/hotel-chicz-and-cafe-elisa-closes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Chicz and Cafe Elisa closes" /><published>2020-03-22T15:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-22T15:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/trivandrum/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/22/hotel-chicz-and-cafe-elisa-closes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/trivandrum/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/22/hotel-chicz-and-cafe-elisa-closes.html">&lt;p&gt;I was new to Trivandrum, the hotel my company made me stay called as Le Franc wasn’t a hotel at all. Apart from complementary breakfast it has no other food. Even water wasn’t delivered to room, there ws a can and we had to drink from it. It was a lodge but those idiots called themselves a hotel!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to order food from outside, I think the very first day for dinner I ordered parotta and chicken liver fry from hotel chicz. The parotta came with a gravy which I never tasted because I ate it with chicken liver fry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The liver fry was semi gravy and awesome and I loved it, for Rs 80/-, they gave a whole plate of liver fry. Afer eating it I had no trouble, the food was good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then moved into New Lotus PG after a week, and I took walk in the nerby main road, to my suprise I found out that hotel Chicz was there, I went in, the guy said he had some dishes, I asked for parotta and asked what side dishes are there, and he said a few and liver fry was not one among them. I told him I ordered it on swiggy and it was awesome, for some reason the hotel owner was thrilled and he was moved emotionally. They prepared it, this time with lot of pepper and dry, and with parotta it was awesome again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was surprised why this guy was moved so emotionally, I think he was kind of shocked and surprised when some one praised his hotel just before closure. I never knew they would close, because to me that hotel was a really good one, but now it’s closed and I am sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding good food in Trivandrum for a Tamil guy is tough, one of my PG mate has hard time here, he travels long to Tamilian hotels to eat, due to my family restrictions I never had chance to learn to drive a bike and I had to eat bad local food and live with it here in this new city. I had food poisoning twice, three people in my team too suffered from poisoning, one like me was poisoned twice. Plus the food here is too expensive, restaurants which charge the right rates are closing down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had found another restaurant named Cafe Elisa in Bhavani, Technopark. By mistake I first ordered Kappa briyani, and bloody hell, it wasn’t even briyani, it was some kind of thick beef stew. Yak. One thing in Kerala, Briyani is not Briyani. They simply don’t know Nizam or Mughal cooking. Some foods in Cafe Elisa costs, like chicken briyani is Rs 130/- and its okay compared to Swad aka Flavours and Platters, but the quantity is too little. But fish gravy meals is of good quantity, you get unlimited Kerala rice, fish gravy with a small pice of fish, along with gravy’s for rice and some side dishes, and it’s good. It costs Rs 90/-, but if you eat it for lunch, you can skip dinner, so its economical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt Cafe Elisa was good when it came to fish gravy (here the people say it Fish Curry) meals, but now it too has closed down. I really don’t know what’s happening and why these hotels that don’t spoil health are closing down. The shops like Travancore Rasavada which gave me food poisoning twice are thriving. So sad…&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was new to Trivandrum, the hotel my company made me stay called as Le Franc wasn’t a hotel at all. Apart from complementary breakfast it has no other food. Even water wasn’t delivered to room, there ws a can and we had to drink from it. It was a lodge but those idiots called themselves a hotel!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My another take on marriage</title><link href="/2020/03/12/my-another-take-on-marriage.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My another take on marriage" /><published>2020-03-12T23:26:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-12T23:26:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/03/12/my-another-take-on-marriage</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/03/12/my-another-take-on-marriage.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hOIp5pmJizA/maxresdefault.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have heard women complain about how hard it is to do household chores, how hard it is to take care of children, how hard it is to have a married life. I have heard men complain less, but many spend time outside family, long times out and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a man I was able to understand men. The constant nagging of women, how it corrodes us and so on. As men, all we want is sex. Men are dogs and we want nothing more. We are genetically programmed to transmit our genes to many offspring’s as possible. If a man says he really likes / loves a woman and none other, then its a spoof, we are programmed to track, analyze and target all women from adulthood to death. Yup we may sugar coat it as love, marriage, family, dates and blah blah, it all depends on ones social and emotional quotient, but the base is the same animal instinct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For woman I believed what they said about their difficulties. Now I feel I haven’t understood them. I got a job outside my city and accepted it. The first week of stay was sponsored by my company and now I am all by myself. Not in a hotel as before, but in a paying guest accommodation. In Chennai I was treated like Buddha in my family. All my friends drink, but they don’t to drink before me, I was eposed to almost no evil. Coming here I saw how a drunk would behave, I saw how much it would cost for a man to live. But two things went wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First my friend Umashankar, when we ran the company Trumatics (&lt;a href=&quot;http://trumatics.com&quot;&gt;http://trumatics.com&lt;/a&gt;), he said I was treated like God in Chennai and I would know the difficulty of living when I am out. I am out now, and am feeling happy and have the same feeling as living in Chennai. The theory that I would suffer when I go into an uncomfortable zone became false and wrong. I don’t know why. There is something in humanity to help, and that has kept me comfortable all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second is this, listening to women I thought family work was hard, but its not. I wash my cups and utensils, wash my clothes, and it looks fun at least to me. It does not look difficult at all. I don’t know why women complain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just began to think. There are two types of coding I do, the coding I like and coding I hate. It all depends on the love of the task I have to complete. Similarly I think doing household chores depends on the woman’s love for her husband, in-laws, kids and so on. If that love falters, the family crumbles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might think love is constant, but that’s not true, like a graph it sways. It depends on ones hormones, training of ones mind, what others say about the person you love, your ego and many factors. In fact the same circuits in the brain that is responsible for love is also responsible for hate, that’s why when the circuit switches you start to hate the person with same intensity as you loved that person. Sometimes your brain is so locked, love and hate becomes irreversible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This begs the question. So what is marriage if love is not constant? All I can only say ‘I don’t know’. I simply don’t know. What I can say is, your love and hate for a person is independent of what relationship you have with them. The more intimate the relationship, the more intense is the feeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This also begs the question of woman’s freedom. In India, still, a woman is tied to a man if marriage has happened. Everything in her life is pinned around her husband, if she leaves her husband because of hate (which should be respected as well), she is blamed, and ashamed. Sometimes it’s the husband that abandons a woman, in that case its more pathetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel people don’t give as much attention to right of a person to hate another as they give respect and attention to right of a human to love another. The people who have respected and studied those who hated them have come up in life. Take the case of Alexander and Purushothaman, each studied each other in the battle of Hydrapass. Take for instance Indian freedom movement. Indian leaders never hated British, they simply wanted their self rule, whereas the Brits hated us, so they ran away when they realized no more money can be made in India. Take Nelson Mandela, he studied those who hated black, those wo hated whites and those who hated him. When he had the nation in his hand, he forgave them. He even forgave his own wife Winney. Almost all great people have studied hate, and studied those who hate them. So rather than getting pissed off by a hateful person, study them, it could give crucial information on how to take the next step in your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what it tells to me about marriage. Well it’s simple. As a man I know that no man is fit to marry. Now I am beginning to realize almost no woman is fit to be married either. But ya, to have easy sex, people stick to what ever social framework and do what evolution has set us to do.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tiffin @ flavors and platters (Technopark - Trivandrum) is good</title><link href="/trivandrum/technopark/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/05/tiffin-flavours-and-platters-is-good.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tiffin @ flavors and platters (Technopark - Trivandrum) is good" /><published>2020-03-05T21:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-05T21:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/trivandrum/technopark/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/05/tiffin-flavours-and-platters-is-good</id><content type="html" xml:base="/trivandrum/technopark/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/05/tiffin-flavours-and-platters-is-good.html">&lt;p&gt;In one of my blogs I had slammed flavors and platters for their briyani, and ya, briyani over there is pathetic. I must however say that their tiffin is good, or should I say okay enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I was in Bhavani and went to Taste 6 because my friends recommended it. Then my location was shifted to Pamba and Flavors and Platters was the nearest thing I had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had purchased poori. In both Taste 6 and Flavors and Platters we get three poori’s. But here comes the difference, in taste 6 the poori looks larger and thinner, in flavors the poori looks bit small and I feel its more bulky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Taste 6 the poori when torn get crumbly and flakes off, in Falvors its not like that. Poori is a poori and you would feel the top layer of the poori is bit crunchy, the bottom layer is soft a nicely cooked. So Flavors wins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Taste 6 we get a white coconut chutney, a spicy orange coconut chutney, and potato curry. But the quantity of side dish in Taste 6 is very small. In flavors we just get potato curry, and it tastes okayish to good sometimes, but they have a nice shallow side dish plate with a handle. In case you have a hot side dish that handle will help you and if the side dish is liquidy you can turn the plate into a huge ladel and pour it onto your main plate. Crockery of Flavors is exceptional compared to other restaurants in Technopark. This side dish plate is half filled with porato curry and its copious, that won my heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ambiance of Flavors and Platters is good. The poori in Flavors costs Rs 50/- whereas in Taste 6 costs Rs 52/-. I wish Taste 6 either reduces their price or improves their quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I ate parota and Egg Masla in Flavours and it was good too. I loved the smell of burnt onions, some people outside India may not like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one sentence, Flavors is not for Briyani, but its good for tiffin.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In one of my blogs I had slammed flavors and platters for their briyani, and ya, briyani over there is pathetic. I must however say that their tiffin is good, or should I say okay enough.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Don’t declare private function on top of class</title><link href="/programming/ruby/best%20practice/2020/03/04/don-t-declare-private-function-on-top-of-class.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Don't declare private function on top of class" /><published>2020-03-04T20:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-04T20:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/ruby/best%20practice/2020/03/04/don-t-declare-private-function-on-top-of-class</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/ruby/best%20practice/2020/03/04/don-t-declare-private-function-on-top-of-class.html">&lt;p&gt;I find that some people are declaring private function at the top of class, like this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nc&quot;&gt;SomeClass&lt;/span&gt;

  &lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;private&lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;private_function&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# some stuff&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt; 
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;public_function&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# some stuff&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
  
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, if you do like that then the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;public_function&lt;/code&gt; defined below the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;private&lt;/code&gt; key word is also a private! Duh!!.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A remedy would be to do something like this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nc&quot;&gt;SomeClass&lt;/span&gt;

  &lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;private&lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;private_function&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# some stuff&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt; 
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;public&lt;/span&gt; 
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;public_function&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# some stuff&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
  
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is as soon a private function(s) definition(s) ends you can call &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;public&lt;/code&gt; thus making all functions that follow it public. But, though it’s right, it would be better to design an class like this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nc&quot;&gt;ClassHowFunctionsCouldBePlaced&lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# put all public functions here&lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;public_function&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
   
  &lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;protected&lt;/span&gt;
   
  &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# put all protected functions here&lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;protected_function&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
  
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;private&lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# put all private functions here&lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;private_function&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
   
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you put functions as &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;class ClassHowFunctionsCouldBePlaced&lt;/code&gt; is defined, then you will have no  access problems or other access issues.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I find that some people are declaring private function at the top of class, like this</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Crap Briyani @ Flavours and Platters - Technopark Trivandrum</title><link href="/trivandrum/briyani/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/03/crap-briyani-flavours-and-platters-technopark-trivandrum.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Crap Briyani @ Flavours and Platters - Technopark Trivandrum" /><published>2020-03-03T21:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-03T21:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/trivandrum/briyani/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/03/crap-briyani-flavours-and-platters-technopark-trivandrum</id><content type="html" xml:base="/trivandrum/briyani/food/restaurant%20reviews/2020/03/03/crap-briyani-flavours-and-platters-technopark-trivandrum.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/flavours_and_platters.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are times when you are sick, you will be offered a awful tasting gruel prepared @ your home. Its tasteless and awful. You would wonder what wrong you had done to deserve such a fate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine you are in a restaurant, ordered Briyani and you are offered something that tastes like that awful gruel, tasteless. Its like eating liquid styrofoam, that was my experience today in Flavours and platters in Technopark today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went there because one of my friends suggested it to me and he said it will be good. The first thing I found was this restaurant was kind of disorganized. A lady puts a bill for briyani and she keeps it to herself and tells me to goto a counter to collect it. I go to the counter and find a lady laying out a white rice kind of thing on plate, she asks me ‘are you here for briyani?’, I say ‘ya’ and she hands it over to me. I serve myself some pickle and raitha, and another person asks for Briyani, its then she realizes that this briyani is for him, and I hand my plate to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now she goes to the counter and asks if I did order a briyani, the lady at the counter says ‘ya’, this serving lady come back and accuses me (not in a offending way) of not giving the bill. Well the lady in counter would not give me the bill for some reason, all she said was go there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I get a serving of briyani (yak, thats not briyani, its actually white rice, two pieces of chicken meat and a boiled egg). Usually Kerala Briyani is not as good ad Hydrabadi, but it would have enough masala to mix into the rice and make it spicy. Here no, the masala was almost non existant. You just had white rice, boiled two pieces of chicken tossed into it along with an egg. All these stuff when sold for Rs 20/- might be okay, but they are charging it whoppy Rs 160/-. Thats an absolute waste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend back at office told me that once Malabar briyani @ Flavours and Platters was good, but now I feel its truly crap.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My work @ Trivandrum</title><link href="/2020/03/01/my-work-trivandrum.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My work @ Trivandrum" /><published>2020-03-01T12:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-03-01T12:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/03/01/my-work-trivandrum</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/03/01/my-work-trivandrum.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/f/f0/Technopark_Trivandrum_Ariel_View_June_2014.jpg/1200px-Technopark_Trivandrum_Ariel_View_June_2014.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would have never imagined I would work in Kerala. As a Chennai kid, for me Kerala is a place to go and get relaxed, where you can get a massage, live in boat house with food served by beautiful girl hostesses. I never imagined I would come here for work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was given a good cop and bad cop treatment at a company called Francium before, I hated that treatment. The same was happening to many good minds there, then we were fired saying that they wasn’t enough money in the company, while juniors were told that we were fired because of lack of performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ill treatment of us, despite our professionalism, cut a deep wound in us, we were desperate to redeem, and out of many offers I got, I analyzed a lot. I must not get caught with another mad man or mad system once again I thought, the people of this company Guide House seem to have been behaving properly during interview and I chose it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got calls from Change Pond, a company near my home, and I think another company called VThink Global, just 5Km from my home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change Pond was pushy, they desperately want me in, they couldn’t control their desperation. They needed money from Ruby on Rails and a project was staring at them, they wanted me to negotiate with the client to bag the project. Well, I thought, these people don’t even have a RoR project and they want me. Let’s say a situation where the project doesn’t go well, they were denied payment by the client, don’t these people who are desperate for money pounce on me for not getting it? Possibly terminate me? So I said no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VTink Global had no professional leadership, (very much like Francium Tech) it could be seen under the sun. Since it was near my home, I wanted to work as part time and try out my other stuff, like setting up an non I.T business. I offered to work there for 25 hours a week, they negotiated a lot / look uncomfortable on rates, then all of a sudden they wanted me to work there for 40 hours a week. This instability of their thought, without proper reason given made me reject it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The H.R of Guide House behaved in professional way, the interview was done in professional way, the first round went about for 3 hours, I enjoyed talking to this girl Suma who was a technician too. Next I talked an hour with a guy called Suresh who was a director there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now one must not think Change Pond and VThink are evil and Guide House is holy, as with everything there is a mixture of all in everything. At that instance i was impressed by guide house. They did not change their mind, their talk was direct. I liked it. Unlike my previous company there seem to be no indication that they were hiding something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its like this, you know AIADMK and DMK are evil, so vote for Seeman or Vijaykanth. Does that make Seeman and Vijaykanth good or uncorrupt? No. When faced with madness, annoyance, loose talk and deception, I went with an unknown hoping it would be different if not better. That’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thank You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank the H.R department of Guide House. People like Neeraj and Neetu assisted me well. Plus my friend Honest Raj who reffered me. He has that fire that an engineer should have and Guide House should be fortunate to have him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have I stopped doing freelancing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hell no. I am doing or should I say helping out people doing Data Science and Numerical Computing projects with Julia. My age old clients still pay money to keep their servers running. I have a bunch of friends in Chennai, Namakkal, Pondicherry who do Spark, Ruby on Rails and mobile app development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love tech and would like to talk to any one who wants to know how technology can improve their life and business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love freelancing, you can earn $40 an hour, get away with working 20 hours a week and have work life balance, but shouting out among many minnows and showing off to people aka marketing is difficult, so I have opted for a stable income as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus freelancing will have an enthusiastic client this week, next week the payment will be delayed and the next week you may not be able to contact him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Instant feedback for programmers</title><link href="/2020/02/20/instant-feedback-for-programmers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Instant feedback for programmers" /><published>2020-02-20T14:07:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-02-20T14:07:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/02/20/instant-feedback-for-programmers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/02/20/instant-feedback-for-programmers.html">&lt;p&gt;As an architect, its not just enough if I look at the code architecture of a project, I have to architect the scaffolding too for creating a good programming environment. Take for instance a building site, even before building a structure you must have the site made. Water facility, toilets, and temporary shelters for the workers must be there, the site must be marked where to excavate, where a foundation must be laid and so on. It quite similar in software project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One good thing about construction is its visual, w can see if a brick is laid right or its jutting out visually. even slightest deviation of a straight wall construction can be found out with  a plumb line, a truly a miracle invention indeed! With code some errors might be there which are not visually identifiable. It may be easy to look or inspect a building, but to inspect code is not so intuitive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So part of a building a great scaffolding for code is to set up reporting tools that report you visually about code quality and other things. This is how we had done code mostly:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/project_structure_old.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a developer we would have pushed code to source code repository, this would have been staged and tested by tester and it would have been deployed to production if things are okay. There wasn’t much emphasis given to code quality and other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maintaining code quality, and checking that the code this release did not break the code of last one was hard, and it was avoided and ignored until it was really necessary. Or we took the convenience of saying to us that we will do it in free time and that had never happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully we now  have tools to run our tests, so we can automate tests, see how our code adheres to programming best practices (code smells), we can see how much of our code is tested. So this is how our new way of coding should be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/project_structure.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when the developer pushes the code, these tools that do Testing, Code Smell Estimation and Test Coverage must pull the code and must do their job. Their output should be instantly available to the programmer as a very visual report, if all reports are okay, then we must go on for staging deploy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once staging deploy is done it is the job of manual tester to test it, if the manual tester is okay, then we must goto production deploy. In the production deploy we must gather as much performance metic as possible and the programmer an tweak his or her code to improve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If all these are followed religiously then we have a good chance of creating a better software.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">As an architect, its not just enough if I look at the code architecture of a project, I have to architect the scaffolding too for creating a good programming environment. Take for instance a building site, even before building a structure you must have the site made. Water facility, toilets, and temporary shelters for the workers must be there, the site must be marked where to excavate, where a foundation must be laid and so on. It quite similar in software project.</summary></entry></feed>