<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-09T15:00:03+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Could Kandahar have been the capital of Murugan’s empire?</title><link href="/2023/08/09/could-kandshar-have-been-the-capital-of-murugan-s-empire.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Could Kandahar have been the capital of Murugan&apos;s empire?" /><published>2023-08-09T14:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-09T14:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/08/09/could-kandshar-have-been-the-capital-of-murugan-s-empire</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/09/could-kandshar-have-been-the-capital-of-murugan-s-empire.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreic3lns4rjkwmgtsnotlftsuivemmyefurccaxa3lhupce67xlnq3a&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People in my neighborhood are disturbing my tranquility by shouting praises for lord Muruga. Somehow people seem to think you need to show off your devotion for God to be in his good books. For some reason, the almighty God’s these days needs publicity, PR, lots of money, and people like priests to survive. Requiring so much support just for survival, we still consider her as the almighty, and claim ourselves Homo sapiens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thoughts ran, I was told by my mother that Kandahar, the present capital of Afghanistan is actually Gandhari Nagaram, that is, it was given as the gift to Gouravas as dowry when Gandhari was married to their family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listening to these praises of Murugan / Kandhan, I began to wonder could it be even older, could it have had the name Kandhan Nagaram, the city of Kandhan, today a God, but then a mighty warrior king who was undefeated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His armies might have marched from the Himalayas to the Peninsula, he might have been instrumental to have laid the basis of formal Tamil language, maybe he and Pandiyas were great friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kandan was so victorious, that Afghans when they saw Alexanders war tactics and victories started calling him Sikandar. They still call him like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreiggbc73r74d5fuvg4xfzviazfq7pyigisz6kebp6zirlyxx3ngyi4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What ever it was, I am sad that India which should have stretched from Afghanistan to Burma (both inclusive). And from Kashmir to Srilanka is not complete yet. We need a great leader like Murugan again to unite our nation and get back the lost bits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current Indian government is unable to pick up garbage, unable to vanquish dogs that bark and disturb my night sleep, it’s unable to eliminate cattle that litter streets and causes accidents, it’s unable to even reduce the prices of essential food items. Me expecting another Murugan emerging in a crippled nation like India is a tall wish that might never happen.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I think Hinduism will outlast Islam</title><link href="/2023/08/03/why-i-think-hinduism-will-outlast-islam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I think Hinduism will outlast Islam" /><published>2023-08-03T09:34:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-03T09:34:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/08/03/why-i-think-hinduism-will-outlast-islam</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/03/why-i-think-hinduism-will-outlast-islam.html">&lt;p&gt;Taliban’s banned beauty parlors, they burned musical instruments saying that music is evil and corrupts the youth. Aurangzeb, an Islamic ruler in India, did ban arts and music when he ruled. They are the true believers of Islam and almost follow the Quran to the dot. How many true Muslims are there in this world if you count that a person is a Muslim if he only follows Quran exactly, it would be near zero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live in India where none of the women in Muslim families I know wear Hijab, they go for job, they are progressive, they marry who ever they please and they don’t face resistance from family, they go to temples, and churches. This is not just in India, this happens in Tunisia, and in lots of African countries where Islam is the primary religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taliban and ISIS were formed to mend that. They want to conquer the whole world and make it pure Islamic, so that we can’t even fly kites for entertainment, we can’t even get medical treatment for our mother, spouse, sister and daughter because Allah want them to suffer and die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Image how long that kind of pure Islam would last? Won’t human nature of caring for people outshine the words of Allah and get women in our family a medical treatment if they are in pain? Aren’t we brave enough to face eternal hell for caring for our people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Islam is a joke. People who do believe in Islam do so without analyzing it thoroughly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fvC8kscL_6w?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s come to Hinduism, it’s not even a religion, people think it’s a religion because the Brits said so to Indians. Once even Sikhs were classifieds as Hindus, today Lingayat (who are Hindu’s by law) are fighting to have their own religion. So what is Hinduism? It seems to be a set of beliefs that people in the land of India have. There are so many beliefs in India and nothing is fixed. Indiran was worshiped like hell in my state Tamilnad, but now Shivan and Vishnu dominate, and yet these people claim they are the same. The value of morality greatly vary when our God takes avatar. The values for Ram is different from the values of Krishna, the values of Krishna are different from values of Nithyanandha. Each God comes, changes the society for that time and goes off. Yet these people say they follow the same religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change is the only constant in Hinduism, in Islam it’s not. What Quran says is ultimate, and it cannot be changed. This inability for God to change, the inability for their God to send another messenger will make Islam so incompatible and intolerable to modern society, and it should vanish. The current form of Hinduism too will vanish bit Hinduism will last in some form, because Hindus will claim themselves as Hindus no matter however they change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeifynukirtpv5m6pnp5mjeqynyjbn576x43muix3nhtwmsycicrjxu.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If in another 500 years, if Jesus is considered son of Hindu God and Mother Mary who is Amman’s avatar, and Joseph is a mere uncle of Jesus, it’s not surprising. Similarly, I feel Islamist in India will be so different from Arabs they will totally lose their identity. If you feel that’s a remote possibility think of lord Ganesh, is it and Hindu God?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Taliban’s banned beauty parlors, they burned musical instruments saying that music is evil and corrupts the youth. Aurangzeb, an Islamic ruler in India, did ban arts and music when he ruled. They are the true believers of Islam and almost follow the Quran to the dot. How many true Muslims are there in this world if you count that a person is a Muslim if he only follows Quran exactly, it would be near zero.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">htmx is far far better than ReactJS</title><link href="/2023/07/27/htmx-is-far-far-better-than-reactjs.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="htmx is far far better than ReactJS" /><published>2023-07-27T22:32:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-07-27T22:32:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/07/27/htmx-is-far-far-better-than-reactjs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/07/27/htmx-is-far-far-better-than-reactjs.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreigd6jwvqv3afn3cfcf3gdycp7xij5fia3bjqdwvt263gl6nczibwm&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my last job interview I was asked to solve problems in Ruby, it was nothing for me and I did it with ease, I was told I will be developing in Ruby on Rails, that was cool, that’s the framework of my choice, and still I would recommend it if you want to start and deliver your projects fast. The downside is if your project becomes large, then if you don’t have good enough programmers you will pay the price that’s a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company was a good company, fortunately my boss is not an evil one, a very rare thing to find these days, but my contribution was bad. The reason? ReactJS. I was told I would code in Ruby on Rails, but when I came in people over here called themselves full stack developers, used Ruby on Rails at the backend and React at the front end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? Why, Why, Why? Why people don’t realize Ruby on Rails is a full-stack framework? Truly God only knows. Rails has given the most productive way to produce web apps yet, and people switch its front end to ultra low productive ReactJS, Angular or View. One of my hypothesis is, I am in India, here we bill clients based on head count, and the more complex you make the project, the more head counts, more bills and more profit. I can’t think of any other logical way. Or may be the project got started with speculation without bothering to look into facts about tech stacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way I was told I am a 19+ years experienced programmer and I have to be productive with this React. I should have quit, but I did not and tried to learn React, and till now, for more than a year I can say I have not learned it, I feel very uncomfortable using it. Ruby on Rails never embraced these clunky front end frameworks and evolved its own better one called HOT Wire which is 10X faster to develop than ReactJS. There is no work to convert something to JSON, and then there is no worry to convert JSON back to HTML in the front end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Rails purists, telling to use JavaScript is torture. The creation of JavaScript is an example how badly project could be managed and how an embarrassing software could be produced. May be if researchers are searching for proof of decline of human intelligence, JavaScript should be considered the top most proof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ReactJS takes this dirty imperfect, embarrassing JavaScript and makes it more dirty, imperfect and embarrassing. It’s a struggle for anyone who wants to write clean code to come to terms with the messiness of React.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one of the Clojure forums, I found htmx, and WOW! It was just like HOT Wire that is Rails default front end these days. ReactJS makes you write more and more JavaScript, htmx reduces it, it gives so much power that even a backed developer can become a front end developer, I saw htmx for a weekend and I can say I am a htmx developer. It reminded me of Ruby, I read a Ruby book, the one with two giraffes in it, I think that evening I was writing software for my mother to rank her students. That’s how productive Ruby was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I will become better in ReactJs and the so-called full stack (I call it hell-stack), and I will be considered better developer, or maybe I won’t, but what ever I do next, I am sure I should not lay hands upon these React, Angular, Vue, and what ever that ravages human minds. Unfortunately I cannot avoid React as my pay depends on it :(. I wish my clients project started today rather than when React was in its heyday. I work with really smart people, they catch the smell of good tech soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My advice to all those people choosing software to make people in your company code, there is a simple solution, you start the project with tools you pick, you do the initial developer, if you are leader, then lead, don’t just sit in a chair and talk. Once you think a thing is easy enough to use, then recommend it to the team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have seen in my many friends companies, people just think something is better due to speculation, and they push their teams to that hell and hope that their teams stay professional. That’s not tech leadership.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Boycott Modi</title><link href="/2023/07/21/boycott-modi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Boycott Modi" /><published>2023-07-21T21:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-07-21T21:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/07/21/boycott-modi</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/07/21/boycott-modi.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeial33zzq3yhcxh5qy7bbjcgpxbioa7ddzhozla4t4isb66y7alulq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Boycott Modi&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opposition is demanding that Modi should be present during discussions about violence against women in Manipur. What the opposition if failing to realize is the fact that Modi is not a capable leader to face failure and distress. The opposition thinks that Modi is the Prime minister of India, which is not true. Modi is a person who holds that post for prestige, power and for boasting about stuff to others. Other than that maybe he is worth enough to eat cow dung and drink cow urine. That’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of great leaders, Alexander led battles, charged into enemy when things were bleak, he was leader. He did not charge in only when he knew victory was imminent, there are many accounts where he led by his bravery and courage during the darkest hour. That’s bravery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of Nehru, he did not write apology letter to British when he was in jail begging his release. He faced their batons, faced possible extermination and stood up as a leader. He stood up in Parliament when India lost to China in 1962, faced criticisms like his balled head should be cut off and given to the Chinese. He withstood it. That’s a mark of a great leader. In-fact he was called the light of humanity for his great soul.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here we have got this “Prime Minister” Modi who can’t even face journalist bravely, my question is, knowing that he is coward and incapable, why the opposition wants him in the parliament floor? Let that idiot go to some country and boast India is this great thing and that great thing, we should not care about him. I wish the opposition seeks facts from the government (which can function better without Modi), and makes sure that the women who were raped, paraded naked in their villages gets the right retribution and justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t expect a good action or good thought from a rotting corpse, its foolish, so let’s leave the corpse and see how we can soothe the wounds of the people Manipur with the help of people who are alive and have soul of a human in them, and let’s possibly liberate the nation from religious rule and form a rationalist state.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Boycott Modi</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why BJP and RSS should be destroyed</title><link href="/2023/07/11/why-bjp-and-rss-should-be-destroyed.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why BJP and RSS should be destroyed" /><published>2023-07-11T21:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-07-11T21:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/07/11/why-bjp-and-rss-should-be-destroyed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/07/11/why-bjp-and-rss-should-be-destroyed.html">&lt;p&gt;Let’s take chief minister of Andhrapradesh, his name is Y.S.Rajashekkar Readdy. The Readdy in his name is a caste name, a sign that says what is his status amongst other humans in India is. India claims it’s a country of equals, but those who say they uphold these values, and seek to rule people, shamelessly put their caste name in their name. They aren’t a bit ashamed of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take my state Tamilnadu, I have no clue what caste M.K.Stalin is, people in his family have married people of different castes, and possibly married people of different states. I am proud of my chief minister, and I am proud about his dad Karunanidhi to have pushed caste aside and put people front.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at this video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeidmcrrlonljs75b5gigiwxfskdjijan5mh2h3bcbk6lqo72nugx64 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our state BJP leader Annamalai is falling at the feet of some guy just because Annamalai thinks he belongs to a lower caste than a Brahmin (to whom he is falling to). So he willingly subjugates himself. Look at the eyes of those little boys, feeling so uncomfortable when a elderly man falls almost onto their feet, these boys will be trained to accept it, they will be told that god favors them and not the majority of the people in India who think and work. Those boys will be trained to live like lords because they are brahmins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These boys will grow up and train their kids saying that they are superior Aryan race and others in India are inferior to them. It’s this kind of blind faith BJP and RSS wants to cultivate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We should think. Are we Tamils here to watch these humans subjugating humans for no reason, or are we here to put rational thought into the brains of Indians and make our country developed and equal to all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a wow to destroy BJP, RSS, Muslim League, Khalistan, or what ever that keeps humanity in the dark by spreading blind faith.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Let’s take chief minister of Andhrapradesh, his name is Y.S.Rajashekkar Readdy. The Readdy in his name is a caste name, a sign that says what is his status amongst other humans in India is. India claims it’s a country of equals, but those who say they uphold these values, and seek to rule people, shamelessly put their caste name in their name. They aren’t a bit ashamed of it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dog and flies in Sai food court, Sithalapakkam</title><link href="/2023/06/27/dog-and-flies-in-sai-food-court-sithalapakkam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dog and flies in Sai food court, Sithalapakkam" /><published>2023-06-27T23:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-27T23:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/27/dog-and-flies-in-sai-food-court-sithalapakkam</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/27/dog-and-flies-in-sai-food-court-sithalapakkam.html">&lt;p&gt;Today I stepped into Sai food court in Sithalapakkam and was surprised to find a stray dog in there. Just a day or two ago I went to eat pani poori, and today I found that the potato masala kept for pani poori was infested with flies, flies were everywhere in hotel. I couldn’t find a fly catcher there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Sithalapakkam, all hotels and food shop has flies thanks to cow dung and dog shit on roads. Nobody cares to clean it, nobody cares to prevent it, for some reason Tamils I find seems to love shit and love flies that sit on them to sit on their food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out leaders Stalin and Modi will talk about achieving 1 trillion and 5 trillion economy, but are incapable of scrapping of dog and cow shit from roads. It’s this kind of leaders we have elected. Now think about our intelligence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our state leader thinks that he must be CM, because his dad was a CM, I am sure he feels his son and grandson should be CM too. There are a bunch of people who cal themselves DMK who have no brains and back this kind of family politics. The result, our CM can’t even scrap dung from roads. He is incapable for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our national scene is even worst, he is a genocide specialist who thinks he must rule India because he knows Sanskrit, and licks brahmins feet etc. He thinks demonetization will kill off terrorism and black money, ignores scams made by his friends companies, and is incapable of keeping my areas street free of dung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, are we intelligent enough to elect at least a dung scrapper from now on?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today I stepped into Sai food court in Sithalapakkam and was surprised to find a stray dog in there. Just a day or two ago I went to eat pani poori, and today I found that the potato masala kept for pani poori was infested with flies, flies were everywhere in hotel. I couldn’t find a fly catcher there.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Resume Vs CV</title><link href="/2023/06/21/resume-vs-cv.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Resume Vs CV" /><published>2023-06-21T15:28:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-21T15:28:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/21/resume-vs-cv</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/21/resume-vs-cv.html">&lt;p&gt;One of my friends seems to have got a Ruby on Rails project, he kept calling me till I got annoyed and picked up, he was ready to pay me well if I sent him 2 Ruby on Rails people trained by me. It was not possible because even the last Rails guy trained by me seems to have an offer, any way I convinced the last guy to consider another job too depending on the nature of boss and payment and I sent his resume to my friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend called minutes later and said the resume lacked detail. I did not read the resume, and so I read it, it looked perfect to me, in further calls it looked like my friend was expecting a CV and not resume. It’s funny that people who are in tech industry for so long are not familiar with the difference between resume and CV. I wish HR’s are familiar what’s the difference, else it would be really laughable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One must also know what’s the purpose of resume and CV and why and when you must ask. I felt bad for putting a good tech guy’s fate in the hands of a person who claims to be an engineer but is unable to be clear, or at least he must admit he does not know something so that one can serve better and create economic value.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">One of my friends seems to have got a Ruby on Rails project, he kept calling me till I got annoyed and picked up, he was ready to pay me well if I sent him 2 Ruby on Rails people trained by me. It was not possible because even the last Rails guy trained by me seems to have an offer, any way I convinced the last guy to consider another job too depending on the nature of boss and payment and I sent his resume to my friend.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Facts are unmasking Kushboo and Chennai Mayor Priya</title><link href="/2023/06/19/facts-are-unmasking-kushboo-and-chennai-mayor-priya.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Facts are unmasking Kushboo and Chennai Mayor Priya" /><published>2023-06-19T08:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-19T08:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/19/facts-are-unmasking-kushboo-and-chennai-mayor-priya</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/19/facts-are-unmasking-kushboo-and-chennai-mayor-priya.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;kushboo-is-a-waste&quot;&gt;Kushboo is a waste&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeib4s4jaubxjbuo2eg2e454remwheahhqxkfy2f4egzwbky6c3dqt4.ipfs.nftstorage.link/kushboo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Actress and Politician Kushboo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I saw news that a DMK speaker was removed because he told some remark about Kushboo, and Kushboo gave a crying interview before the press saying how she felt hurt by the derogatory remark and how she wanted to slap the DMK worker with her slippers, but felt that her slipper will get morally dirty by slapping him. After this emotional interview DMK removed that stage speaker Sivaji Krishnamurthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now DMK has sent a message to BJP, if women’s rights are stepped upon, then DMK will act upon it. Or may be DMK people love cinema people and want to be associated with them, who knows? I am saying this because Udhayanidhi Stalin went on a hunger strike because Nayantara refused to act with him. May be her policy is to act with actors (that is people who can act), so unable to get associated with her, Udhayanidhi went to extreme measure. May be DMK still wants to please Kushboo. Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Kushboo is in a tight spot, if her rights are violated, then she puts up all scene, but if women wrestlers of India are molested by a BJP guy Brij Bhushan, Kushboo is almost mute. She won’t cry for them, she won’t call a press meet, she won’t put a sentimental show to get that guy out, her slippers will be under her feet, and she won’t feel like slapping him with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mayor-priya-deceived-us&quot;&gt;Mayor Priya deceived us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeib4s4jaubxjbuo2eg2e454remwheahhqxkfy2f4egzwbky6c3dqt4.ipfs.nftstorage.link/mayor_priya.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;DMK Politician Priya&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s raining in Chennai, I woke up to and found in News that Chennai is not flooded, it wwas a shock to me. Last year Mayor Priya told us to excuse the DMK, and this year there will be no floods, I couldn’t believe that DMK did what they promised. I was shell shocked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the truth set it, I was watching Sun TV a DMK channel. I switched to other channels and found that Santhome, lot of subways are flooded. I don’t think Chennai corporation has produced any official briefing that it’s better to avoid traveling in these routes and these routes are clear. Looks like the corporation still hasn’t woken up to the fact that Chennai is under rain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my place Sithalapakkam, the place where I live Skylab Avenue has no metalled roads, even on sunny days we get a bumpy ride, water gets puddled up here and there during rains. Governments that claim that they care about people, still seem not to recognize we are people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lets-wake-up&quot;&gt;Let’s wake up&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreiho5mapxmrr5xospm6xjpkdspazeqflusiwkpsnwychpr3dhv4tzi.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Learn before you vote&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheaters dominate the parties we vote for, there are more symbols and names to vote than people standing for DMK, ADMK, Congress, BJP etc. Learn about politics, learn about people who stand for elections and let’s try to create a corruption free and honest India.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Kushboo is a waste</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why bad things happen in batches?</title><link href="/2023/06/16/why-bad-things-happen-in-batches.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why bad things happen in batches?" /><published>2023-06-16T07:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-16T07:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/16/why-bad-things-happen-in-batches</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/16/why-bad-things-happen-in-batches.html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t believe in astrology, even if you believe, it’s just a set of words that could or could not happen. A great astrologer once told me that I will start believing in God by age 27, I’m 40 now and wonder how nonexistent God is going to pop out of nowhere and make me believe in it. When I do ask questions about astrology, my friends who believe it and even some astrologers get furious, I don’t get why. Just for sun, when friends come to me with problems, I do ask them what did the astrologers say, they get really serious and say something, and I laugh inside seeing their ignorance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish I knew psychology, sometime some incidents seems to happen in batches, and they seem totally unrelated to each other, it looks like you are destined to receive it. Here are two of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, one of my relative bought a house in Bangalore, so he told the elders in my family that I should attend the housewarming, I did not want to travel in bus, it robs my sleep and next day would be somewhat, I never got a train ticket, and flight would be prohibitively expensive, so I said no, and thought that was the end of matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like that jerk got really pissed off because I said no, and he started to pull string, and gave 
me unnecessary problems. I saw good people turn evil, the guy causing the problem was comfortably hiding behind them like a coward, unable to confront me. People behaved like psychopaths with me. I was baffled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dealing with those psychopaths, I thought what could go wrong? And it did. I was working in a company called Trumatics, and something happened to my co-director. He started to shout, he started to shout at me and every one like psychopath. I even saw him shout at my friend, because he was angry that he could not blame me that day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really started to wonder if fate had decided about me, (even though I had eliminated some psychopaths out of my life and was recovering,), if it wanted to be keep me encountering more psychos or something. In brief, I was wondering if there is some destiny or something?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next incident happened recently, I was traveling in car with few people, the person sitting next to instructed me on every thing, he said which lane I should drive, when to put the indicator, when to brake and blah blah, I was frustrated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A week after that his son was sitting next to me, and he told me when to switch on the wiper, he asked me to pick up speed in densely packed road that was almost dead still in traffic. I thought, okay this is a son of a psycho and no wonder. I brushed it off, maybe it’s genetics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The very next day I was with a another friend whose company I am investing in, historically he was not like the father son psychos, a well tuned mind he was, he started say do this and that while I was driving. These three driving incidents happened within a span of week and few days, and I was wondering why am I encountering such a strange behavior of people in my car. I started to think about destiny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though coincidence, very similar stuff happening at very short intervals looks spooky.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I don’t believe in astrology, even if you believe, it’s just a set of words that could or could not happen. A great astrologer once told me that I will start believing in God by age 27, I’m 40 now and wonder how nonexistent God is going to pop out of nowhere and make me believe in it. When I do ask questions about astrology, my friends who believe it and even some astrologers get furious, I don’t get why. Just for sun, when friends come to me with problems, I do ask them what did the astrologers say, they get really serious and say something, and I laugh inside seeing their ignorance.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Stalin says about Senthil Balaji</title><link href="/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Stalin says about Senthil Balaji" /><published>2023-06-14T16:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-14T16:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeigc2rfxdghs6hycj5ord2qzo7kw3citwc7qzvmnwcbmi6n2rtengu &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry></feed>