<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-06-16T17:19:47+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How A.I will make every software a Free Software</title><link href="/2024/06/16/how-ai-will-make-every-software-a-free-software.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How A.I will make every software a Free Software" /><published>2024-06-16T17:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-06-16T17:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/06/16/how-ai-will-make-every-software-a-free-software</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/06/16/how-ai-will-make-every-software-a-free-software.html">&lt;p&gt;I was watching &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ucXYWG0vqqk&quot;&gt;Richard Stallman interview&lt;/a&gt; on Youtube, it was sad how evil capitalists destroyed the hacker culture and brought in the reign of proprietary software. Most software we use, like in our phones and computers or other gadgets, hide something malicious. We are unable to see and reverse engineer what it is. Big money wants to shackle and spy on us, and almost everyone on this planet has submitted to them for convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I strongly recommend every one to learn who &lt;a href=&quot;https://stallman.org&quot;&gt;Richard Stallman&lt;/a&gt; is, and what &lt;a href=&quot;https://fsf.org&quot;&gt;Free Software&lt;/a&gt; is. You will understand you are most probably shackled by proprietary software, and maybe you will think about getting unshackled from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is about the light at the end of tunnel I see. I feel A.I will make every software a Free Software in near future. Say there is a binary on your computer, or mobile, or your microwave, one day you will be able to feed it to a neural network, and it will output the source code that can create the very same binary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way to create such a neural network is very straight forward. You have lots of source code in Github, GitLab, Codeberg and so on, take look at the image below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/every-software-a-free-software/Every Software a Free Software.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All we need to do is to take those code / library / projects, compile them to machine code for various processor architectures (say Risc V, ARM, x86), feed the compiled code and source to a neural network for it to learn. With lots of examples, neural network will learn to create source code from binary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The software is created on ones computer, so, one can claim he / she has reverse engineered it (with the help of A.I), and release it in the license one wishes. I am sure many free software enthusiasts will release it under &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.en.html&quot;&gt;GPLV3&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we can automate this process, we can have a distributed computers scanning for binaries on the internet, reverse engineering it to code, and releasing equivalent Assembly, C++, Rust, Zig or what ever under GPLV3, thus making them libre to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe we can have some programs in our computers that will scan it for binaries and feed it to this A.I liberator, so that all our software could be unshackled.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was watching Richard Stallman interview on Youtube, it was sad how evil capitalists destroyed the hacker culture and brought in the reign of proprietary software. Most software we use, like in our phones and computers or other gadgets, hide something malicious. We are unable to see and reverse engineer what it is. Big money wants to shackle and spy on us, and almost everyone on this planet has submitted to them for convenience.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shameful swearing in ceremony of Chandrababu Naidu</title><link href="/2024/06/13/shameful-swearing-in-ceremony-of-chandrababu-naidu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shameful swearing in ceremony of Chandrababu Naidu" /><published>2024-06-13T17:42:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-06-13T17:42:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/06/13/shameful-swearing-in-ceremony-of-chandrababu-naidu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/06/13/shameful-swearing-in-ceremony-of-chandrababu-naidu.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Chandrababu_Naidu_2017.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Chandrababu Naidu, 13&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; CM of Andhrapradesh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was watching news today, Chandrababu Naidu took oath as Chief Minister of Andhra. I wish him all the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did not like the way his swearing in ceremony went. Administration is about giving a good rule to people. It’s about having constant touch with people and responding to their needs. You need workers who go from door to door and listen to them, you need people who care about people so that plans get executed, and you need people who are good brained ones to make things efficient. These sorts of people should be besides you to rule a state, but the kind of people I saw was appalling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think Pawan Kalyan (a cine star) is the deputy CM. All you need to rule people these days is to jump around like a monkey before camera it seems. There was Chiranjeevi, Rajinikanth. Why? Why are these people needed for swearing in? It looks absolutely stupid from an intellectual point of view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish there was no Modi and Venkaiya Naidu. These people represent a party (BJP) that’s based on religion and blind faith, they do not represent rule by facts and statistics. But yes, compared to film stars, the presence of these people is okay, but it could have been avoided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine, what will happen if Mamooty or Mohanlaal became the leader of Kerla’s parties, and finally became its CM? I am sure all Malyali’s will commit suicide in shame. If a state of Kerala can be so alert and choose right people (relatively right, definitely not absolutely right they are) compared to its neighbors, why can’t people of Andhra wake up?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think Tamilnadu is far behind Andhra when it comes to shamefully allowing cine stars to become politicians. I have no hope that in another 100 years, Tamilnadu will have a golden Chief Minister like Kamaraj.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chandrababu Naidu, 13th CM of Andhrapradesh</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Questions about Modi’s meditation</title><link href="/2024/06/03/questions-about-modis-meditation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Questions about Modi&apos;s meditation" /><published>2024-06-03T08:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-06-03T08:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/06/03/questions-about-modis-meditation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/06/03/questions-about-modis-meditation.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c.ndtvimg.com/2024-06/8vtunh5_modi-meditation_625x300_01_June_24.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never knew Modi Meditated in Vivekanandha rock. It’s nice to see that Tamilnadu’s media ignores this narcissist psychopath.  I also feel sad that killers like Modi, and Edapaadi Palani Sami are able to be in Tamilnadu, and they can walk this land without any fear. It does not mean that I don’t accuse DMK, look at all the cyanide deaths of people associated with them. They are yet to kill Savukku Shankar, and I am sure they will succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping those thoughts aside, this is about Modi’s meditation on Vivekanandha rock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-much-did-it-cost&quot;&gt;How much did it cost?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How much did it cost? I do have a comfortable living, but huge sums of my earnings goes as taxes, so when ever leader take a break, why don’t we have a public announcement in paper that Modi had gobbled up say 1000 crores of your money to meditate for 45 hours? Why do government hide this kind of data, and put full page ads, saying that this and that are their achievements, when all they have done is their duty? These kinds of transparency will make the people wake up, and ask the right questions so that our mirage of democracy gets exposed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So does it mean this government want people to be dumb so that they can rule this nation unchallenged?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-should-i-pay&quot;&gt;Why should I pay?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Modi opens a nuclear plant, or a scientific institution, a library, a education place, yes I am ready to pay. Why should I pay for this psychopath to sit in at place for social media likes? That’s absurd. If this guys wants to do this stupid stuff, why can’t he pay from his pocket? Or ask the party of terrorist (aka the Bharathiya Janatha Party) to pay? They are stupids, and so would believe Modi without a question and would pay.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fascist DMK attacks journalistic freedom in Tamilnadu</title><link href="/2024/05/20/fascist-dmk-attacks-journalistic-freedom-in-tamilnadu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fascist DMK attacks journalistic freedom in Tamilnadu" /><published>2024-05-20T08:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-05-20T08:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/05/20/fascist-dmk-attacks-journalistic-freedom-in-tamilnadu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/05/20/fascist-dmk-attacks-journalistic-freedom-in-tamilnadu.html">&lt;p&gt;I saw a video where a Netherlands politician was speaking how Islam is incompatible with democracy and European values, his remarks were tolerated in Europe. In Europe, I think they have draw Muhammad day, where people draw pictures of prophet Muhammad. For some reason Muslims don’t like the picture of their own prophet dawn, that’s strange. In Arabia, even if you love the prophet, and draw his picture, I think you will be beheaded. For some reason their culture is so intolerant. For reasons, I can’t understand they can’t tolerate their own God been drawn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ALOlZTcghZg?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These incidents have made me think, yes Europe is a democracy, whereas the Arabs are undemocratic who curtail freedom and thought of human mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tamilnadu kind of projects itself as modern state in India. Like Islam, the north of India is drenched in Hnduism, and there is no press freedom. Almost all press channels are bought by the ruling BJP, and what ever the BJP thinks should be in the news, will be in the news. Tamilnadu does not have BJP rule, and there is a bit more press freedom. In fact Tamilnadu is more democratic than North India. But recent acts by the DMK, has made journalistic freedom questionable in Tamilnadu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;savukku-shankar&quot;&gt;Savukku Shankar&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.livemint.com/lm-img/img/2024/05/04/600x338/SavukkuShankar_1714814864098_1714814873937.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Savukku Shankar&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Savukku Shankar is referred to as Julian Assange of Tamilnadu. He is able to get information about Tamilnadu government and political families, and is bold enough to publish them. The transparency he brings is unprecedented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is excellent in exposing the DMK family. For three generation, this family is ruling Tamilnadu like the North Korean Kim family. The party DMK is totally undemocratic, members of one family, the Karunanidhi family dominate it. None in the party is brave to question the family and bring a system where people with merit become leaders. I think Savukku Shankar has exposed people like the Chief Minister Stalin, Stalin’s wife, Stalin’s son Udhayanidhi, Stalin’s daughter-in-law and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK desperately want’s Udhayanidhi Stalin, the current chief ministers son to be become next Chief Minister, and they desperately want Inbha Nidhi, the current Chief Minister’s grandson to be Chief Minister after that, so that families closer to the leader’s family could loot the nation. Savukku Shankar’s expose is embarrassing them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;talk-about-some-police-guy-called-arun&quot;&gt;Talk about some police guy called Arun&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Savukku Shankar got a tip off about a police guy Arun. He claimed on television that lady police working under Arun got promoted because they had affairs with Mr. Arun. Now the police and the DMK political family of Tamilnadu was waiting for something to get revenge on Shankar. On the basis that he defamed lady police, Savukku Shankar was arrested, in the Jail cell his arm was broken, and its alleged that he is tortured every day. Some sources say , its the goal of DMK to kill Savukku Shankar in jail, as they are unable to digest his boldness and his fighting spirit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;defaming-shankar&quot;&gt;Defaming Shankar&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To defame Shankar, police has claimed he possessed narcotics. If this isn’t true, it would give a hard time for the police. There are sponsored moth pieces on Youtube, may be sponsored by the DMK and Tamilnadu Secret Service who bad mouth about Shankar to change public view about him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;multiple-cases&quot;&gt;Multiple cases&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tamilnadu police is collecting multiple cases against Shankar, so that he could be kept in jail for a long time, maybe they don’t want him to contest against Udhayanidhi Stalin in upcoming Tamilnadu elections, as intelligence gather by Shankar about Stalin’s family could give him an edge and possibly a victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;falix-and-redpix&quot;&gt;Falix and Redpix&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i0.wp.com/www.cinefellows.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Felix-Gerald-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Felix - runs RedPix&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Savukku Shakar’s opinion was aired on a Youtube channel called Redpix. It’s run by a person called Felix. Though this channel in it Disclaimer, displayed that it detaches from the opinion of the people interviewed by it, the channel’s owner Felix is arrested. This I feel is true murder of democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Felix is super innocent, and by arresting him, what DMK is trying to say is, if anyone talks bad about DMK, they and people who propagate such information will be squashed using the law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-democracy-should-allow-freedom-of-opinion&quot;&gt;Why democracy should allow freedom of opinion?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is a democracy and opinion’s even if its false should be tolerated. For example, there is no God, yet India tolerates religion that say God’s Satan’s and spirits exists. We don’t keep arresting holy men for propagating false information and deceiving people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arab people can’t tolerate if someone gives shape to their God Muhammad, but Europe being a democracy tolerates it as I have written at the starting of the blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current Chief Minister Stalin himself violated many things and cheated people, yet we tolerate him. For example, he campaigned without taking Covid precautions. See his campaign video’s on YouTube. He accelerated Covid in Tamilnadu. Yet after coming to power, he shamelessly asked people to donate to fight Covid. He hasn’t been charged yet for killing Tamils, and he hasn’t been charged for cheating people by asking funds to fight Covid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Democracy is tolerance of opinion. Savukku expressed his opinion on Redpix, either accept it or think it’s false. All Mr. Arun could have done is to issue a statement of denial, and asked Shankar for evidence. If Shankar did provide evidence, then we can think he is right, or we can think he is wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s how simple democracy is. Democracy is all about debating, educating people so that they can see through lies, think deeply about stuff and tell their opinion what ever it may be, and accept or reject other’s opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What DMK does is pure fascism. A rule of terror, unprecedented since the last Jayalalitha’s era, and I feel we people must strongly support journalists like Savukku Shankar and Felix.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I saw a video where a Netherlands politician was speaking how Islam is incompatible with democracy and European values, his remarks were tolerated in Europe. In Europe, I think they have draw Muhammad day, where people draw pictures of prophet Muhammad. For some reason Muslims don’t like the picture of their own prophet dawn, that’s strange. In Arabia, even if you love the prophet, and draw his picture, I think you will be beheaded. For some reason their culture is so intolerant. For reasons, I can’t understand they can’t tolerate their own God been drawn.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">99.99% of engineers are going to be junk</title><link href="/2024/05/15/99.99-percent-of-engineers-are-going-to-be-junk.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="99.99% of engineers are going to be junk" /><published>2024-05-15T09:39:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-05-15T09:39:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/05/15/99.99-percent-of-engineers-are-going-to-be-junk</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/05/15/99.99-percent-of-engineers-are-going-to-be-junk.html">&lt;p&gt;Saw in News today that 1.3 Lakh Tamils are applying for the course of engineering. It startled me. I thought people would be aware that Engineering colleges are junk, in fact student goes in and comes out even forgetting the calculus he learned in 11&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; and 12&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; standard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would be so out of touch with industry. I feel that once finishing 10&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; standard, one must take internship in industry, no matter what, if its software, foundry, steel forging or something. I am sure within 3 years they can come up to industry standards, and work better than a new college graduate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since people who go for mad rush for engineering, with just money in their mind, they tend to be too low quality, unemployable, utter waste to society may be even 10 years after graduation. It’s only after that they seem to pick up something, but lose their race in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Colleges have sprung up, and are working for decades to tap in peoples desire to study engineering in an attempt to become rich. These colleges are nothing but social clubs, where bunch of people meet for 4 years and leave as more idiots than they were  at their 12&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; standard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are student, or a parent, and if you want to live a proper and fulfilling life, think. Think what has happened to our nation? Why are roads built don’t last long? Why are streets so hot? And why people who have built it never knew we are a summer land and have planned accordingly? Why are there floods and drought? Why don’t we have a system so simple that it can save water?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think why things are not managed properly? And think why our bosses are stupid? And how could stupid us be bosses of so many people better thinkers than us?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think why don’t things last, and why things cannot be repaired easily, though we claim we are progressing technically? Think why our lives are difficult than our grandparents?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think why we don’t see first class mathematicians, poet’s, artists and movie-makers who could make a decent and intellectual films that are entertaining?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think do you want to spend for years in a stupid factory voiding your family’s fortunes, or you want to have a life of a human?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Saw in News today that 1.3 Lakh Tamils are applying for the course of engineering. It startled me. I thought people would be aware that Engineering colleges are junk, in fact student goes in and comes out even forgetting the calculus he learned in 11th and 12th standard.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Looting employees in the name of variable pay</title><link href="/2024/05/08/looting-employees-in-the-name-of-variable-pay.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Looting employees in the name of variable pay" /><published>2024-05-08T20:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-05-08T20:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/05/08/looting-employees-in-the-name-of-variable-pay</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/05/08/looting-employees-in-the-name-of-variable-pay.html">&lt;p&gt;Some companies have this concept of variable pay. They say this is your salary, and then they say this much is what you get because other part is a variable pay. Then they have cheated you. They have told an amount, but have effectively reduced your salary by play of words. I wonder what the labor minister in India does even if such practices are done on huge scale, costing the country crores?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another way companies loot employees in the name of variable pay is, they give the variable pay. Let me say how it’s looting. Let’s say I should have got a pay of Rs 10,000/- last month, but I am getting it after 3 months, since it’s variable. Now, let’s do the math. If I put 18% pa as interest, for a month I would have earned Rs 10149.99/-, that is about Rs 150/- as interest. Now compounding this for 3 months, it would be Rs 10456.78/-, or I had lost Rs 456.78/-, the company since it’s doing business, it would have made far more money by holding my variable pay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though company makes this money, company does not give me the right of ownership, voting rights or nothing. They just loot me and make money out of it. In fact its looting of Indian’s in broad daylight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will The Government Wake Up?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This variable pay thing is happening in lots of offices. It’s a blatant loot of India’s labor force, it’s a form of cheating. Will the sleeping government of India wake up and make it illegal?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Some companies have this concept of variable pay. They say this is your salary, and then they say this much is what you get because other part is a variable pay. Then they have cheated you. They have told an amount, but have effectively reduced your salary by play of words. I wonder what the labor minister in India does even if such practices are done on huge scale, costing the country crores?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What I don’t understand about rape charges against politicians?</title><link href="/2024/05/04/what-i-don-t-understand-about-rape-charges-against-politicians.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What I don&apos;t understand about rape charges against politicians?" /><published>2024-05-04T18:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-05-04T18:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/05/04/what-i-don-t-understand-about-rape-charges-against-politicians</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/05/04/what-i-don-t-understand-about-rape-charges-against-politicians.html">&lt;p&gt;Recently H.D.Deva Gowda’s son and grandson are accused of raping their domestic worker I think, and law has let his grandson Prajwal escape and go to Germany.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Prajwal_Revanna.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Prajwal Revanna&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also this Nirmala Devi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.assettype.com/tnm%2Fimport%2Fsites%2Fdefault%2Ffiles%2FNirmala_Devi_750.jpg?w=640&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Nirmala Devi&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who worked for ex-governor of Tamil Nadu Banwarilal Purohit and supplied girls for him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Banwarilal_Purohit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Banwarilal Purohit&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, we all know that practically Indian politicians are immune to law, and they can do what ever they want. What surprises me is this, say for example Prajwal, he is from Gowda family, which must have looted tens of thousands of crores from nation, he can get any willing girl for himself, the world is awash with call girls. Then why go on a difficult path of forcing someone, and rape them? It makes no sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://luxurylaunches.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Influencer-Busted-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know Instagram influencer’s suddenly go to Arab Nations, that’s because it’s said that Arabs offer $50K, just to spend time with them for a week. In Arabia the rich are immune to law too, just like India, and they buy as many girls as they want. They have infinite money flow from oil, our Indian politicians have infinite money flow by looting us. So why can’t our politicians and their families follow the Arab way and just buy girls when ever they want, rather than get caught in scandal and lose their loot in subduing the law?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Recently H.D.Deva Gowda’s son and grandson are accused of raping their domestic worker I think, and law has let his grandson Prajwal escape and go to Germany.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Good and bad about Naam Tamizhar</title><link href="/2024/04/14/good-and-bad-about-naam-tamizhar.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Good and bad about Naam Tamizhar" /><published>2024-04-14T07:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-04-14T07:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/04/14/good-and-bad-about-naam-tamizhar</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/04/14/good-and-bad-about-naam-tamizhar.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b9/Naam_tamilar_katchi_flag.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel &lt;a href=&quot;/2010/01/31/dynamic-democracy.html&quot;&gt;Dynamic Democracy&lt;/a&gt; is the only way for a country to be democratic. Maybe it will never be achieved in India as we are extremely corrupt, and corruption triumphs here all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is about urging you to vote for Naam Tamizhar Katchi, I will lay down why I think you must vote for them, and why you should not vote for them. At the end you decide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-good&quot;&gt;The Good&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s look at the good parts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;clear-communication&quot;&gt;Clear Communication&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JA3n5hg_q1Y?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naam Tamizhar’s communication is clear. Clear communication is what made Anna win elections. Anna did not speak rubbish, he spoke about how the Sanskrit culture oppresses us, and how we must wake up. Look at the above video how Kaaliammal expresses her thought, it’s very clear. It’s very clear to listen to Seeman too. He does not speak rubbish like the ABCD (ADMK, BJP, Congress, DMK).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unwavering-support-for-eelam&quot;&gt;Unwavering support for Eelam&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/11/Tamil_Eelam_Champion_Seeman_Speech_Outside_UN_headquarters_Geneva_002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like Vaiko, we see Seeman supporting Eelam and LTTE. It’s unwavering. I also like the Taliban, good or bad, they are unwavering. They said they will fight USA even if it takes 100 years, and they won. Usually unwavering people with clear goals win. Individuals might fall, eons might change, but unwavering thought and desire from a race of people always has a good chance that it will capture the crown one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe Naam Tamizhar will win one day, may be Eelam could one day be real.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;may-be-non-dynastic&quot;&gt;May be non-dynastic&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ABCD parties are dynastic. We can find many examples about it. Somehow children of politicians get insanely rich even though they claim India is a level playing field for all its citizens. Still I haven’t seen anyone from Seeman’s family coming into power in Name Tamizhar. That’s good. But how long this goodness will last?  Do Naam Tamizhar’s cadres have the balls to stick to Tamil’s cause and dissuade Seeman from making the party a family stuff? Or will they be cowards like DMK people who watched slaughter of LTTE just to get Kanimozhi out of 2G case? It needs to be seen. But till now it’s non-dynastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;may-be-less-corrupt&quot;&gt;May be less corrupt&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think Naam Tamizhar will be uncorrupted all the time. Evil people should be in it, and they will grow in strength when the party comes to power, but I don’t think they can loot like DMK and ADMK when they come to power. They will have two things working against their ambition to loot, the first being their lack of looting expertise, second the fear that if loot gets exposed, they will be wiped off by Tamil people, unless their strength is like DMK or ADMK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;upholding-tamil-dignity&quot;&gt;Upholding Tamil dignity&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened to all those LTTE and innocent Tamil lives lost in fight for Eelam? Why a server in a restaurant in Tamilnadiu speaks Hindi to us? Why are there so many Tamils unemployed while there are so many Noth Indians employed in Tamil Nadu? Why is Karnataka not giving us water, and why is Tamilnadu not boiling about it? Why is Srilankan navy killing our fishermen, and why we are unable to anything about it? Why Modi sucks Srilankan balls? Why are we acting like cowards?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These issues and questions cannot be answered by pan India party, or a party that serves few families. It can be answered by  a party that has dignity in it, and it should be brave too. I find right now Naam Tamizhar is the only party that ticks these checkboxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;water-issues&quot;&gt;Water issues?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Congress and BJP in Karnataka don’t want to share water with us, so does the Congress and BJP in Kerala. Isn’t it a betrayal if a Tamil party allies with it. DMK has allied with congress. Isn’t it a betrayal if someone who claims to be a politician, and who cares for Tamil people to be in BJP or Congress? Yet there are Tamils who betray us. There are people in BJP and Congress who blatantly lie to us saying that they care for the Tamils. There are regional parties who back them up and stab us on the back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Congress and DMK is responsible for the defeat of LTTE in Srilanka, else we Tamils would have had our own nation. The BJP and EPS are responsible for Tuthukudi Vedanta Steralite plant massacre. Yet, these parties survive in Tamilnadu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naam Tamizhar on the other hand has done no anti-Tamil politics. I think they genuinely want to get our fair share of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;never-ally-with-cowards-and-corrupt&quot;&gt;Never ally with cowards and corrupt&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naam Tamizhar is bold, till now they have never allied with cowards and corrupt parties, that’s a very good sign. But we must see when they come to power, loot, then if the raids happen, who knows what compromised they will make. But till now, they’re allying with none other than the Tamil cause is saluteable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;volunteer-contribution&quot;&gt;Volunteer contribution&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I heard from my friend that Naam Tamizhar’s lot of work is done by volunteers. That’s good. Maybe they are not getting corporate backing, thus maybe they are not allying with the rich and becoming anti-people. But as Savukku Shankar say’s, we need to think why Seeman defends G-square? Why can’t a mighty company defend itself and need a politician to defend it? Why is Seeman defending it rather than solving problems of commoners?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-lakshmi-scandal&quot;&gt;The Lakshmi scandal&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s gossiped DMK sent two girls named Laksmi to defame Seeman, one of the girls seems to have published nude video’s of Seeman. Yet, Seeman has come out at the top. No matter what the girls did before camera’s, Seeman looked straight, and emerged out strong. That’s great I think. This is a good test of his resolve and he passed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-bad&quot;&gt;The Bad&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now lets what could be the bad stuff in Naam Tamizhar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;just-one-recognizable-star-leader&quot;&gt;Just one recognizable star leader&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be one recognizable leader in Naam Tamizhar. If Seeman is dead tomorrow, looks like the party is gone. I don’t think that will be the case for DMK if Stalin dies, won’t be the case of ADMK if EPS dies, or won’t be the case of BJP if Modi dies. They have all got array of leaders, but yes those array of leaders lick the sandals of the supreme leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Naam Tamizhar too, looks like people lick the sandals of Seeman, there is no credible opposition or alternative view from the party. So, yes like every other party, looks like Naam Tamizhar is undemocratic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;savukku-shankars-allegations&quot;&gt;Savukku Shankar’s allegations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the allegations that Savukku Shankar has laid again Naam Tamizhar and Seeman:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/w2DNBj7abJo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NzyYfMsqthw?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like there is no counter for the party. Even if there is, it has not been spread properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;never-know-how-will-they-be-in-power&quot;&gt;Never know how will they be in power&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We never know how they will be in power. We never thought a party headed by Gandhi will be corrupt, yet here is the congress. Furthermore, we never thought party started by Anna will be corrupt, and here there is DMK and ADMK. Power corrupts. Today Naam Tamizhaar reaches people, but there could be a time when they are dominated by the rich, just like the ABCD parties, and they don’t care about the masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;no-white-paper-about-corrupt-people-in-their-party&quot;&gt;No white paper about corrupt people in their party&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no white paper about the corrupt people in Naam Tamizhar’s party, by Naam Tamizhar itself, so, are they claiming their party consists exclusively of un-corrupt people? There is no external research on that too, these look a bit odd to me. We don’t know what cases are pending against who?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;terror-supporting&quot;&gt;Terror supporting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no doubt that Naam Tamizhar  supports the terrorists, the LTTE. LTTE did use some very bad war techniques in wars against the Sinhala people. They killed Rajiv Gandhi, which is a needed stuff, but they had killed 40+ others along with him, which is unacceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;seeman-might-be-a-liar&quot;&gt;Seeman might be a liar&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way Seeman describes his encounters with Prabhakaran is kind of off place I feel. May be he could be using LTTE, the Tamil cause as a ladder to go up, just like DMK used Tamil cause to come up, but then just like DMK, Seeman could kick it off when he becomes powerful. Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;will-i-vote-for-them&quot;&gt;Will I vote for them?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes definitely. I don’t think they will be absolutely no evil in the party, but right  now they seem to be less evil among the top parties.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is your company an Indian or a slave company?</title><link href="/2024/03/29/is-your-company-an-indian-or-a-slave-company.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is your company an Indian or a slave company?" /><published>2024-03-29T20:53:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-03-29T20:53:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/03/29/is-your-company-an-indian-or-a-slave-company</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/03/29/is-your-company-an-indian-or-a-slave-company.html">&lt;p&gt;It’s been 75 years since we got our freedom, yet slavery mentality still persists in our country. Just look at the police force in Tamilnadu for example. They killed fellow people in Thutukudi and still the killers are out. The person who told to kill them Eddapaadi Palani Sami and Vedanta group are untouched. Even today while I was in Medavakkam I saw a car with government sticker and blue, red LED’s flashing, looks like a cop or some government employee wants to show off that he is above a normal citizen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Government people are untalented ones and don’t have any skills, their only skill is to exploit the nation and become wealthy. Because of that they want to feel superior and exploit us. That’s natural behavior of pea brained people, we can do nothing about it. Only if intelligent people come into the government offices things will change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike the government, one might think Info Tech companies are said to formed by intelligent and decent people, that’s not true, there are slave companies in I.T industry as well. Here is how to identify them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;indian-companies&quot;&gt;Indian Companies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/4/41/Flag_of_India.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indian companies are the ones that have pride in them. The pride I mean is not to say that they serve such a such client, but they pride their Indian workers. Pride I mean is not marketing pride, but financial pride. They pay Indians the same as western counterparts. Indian companies concentrate on quality of code than making one work hard, toil for long and deliver a lot of crap low quality cheap code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indian companies cultivate skills for their employees and make them valuable. They make their employees enjoy and live life. They bring more money into India by getting more salary for Indians, thus boosting the economy from its roots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;slave-companies&quot;&gt;Slave Companies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9e/IJzeren_voetring_voor_gevangenen_transparent_background.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slave companies are the ones that encourage you to work more and more. For them the colonial mentality is fixed, so the western client is always right. These companies are nothing more than slave brokers to the white man and the rich. They bow only to the clients money and pay no attention to your skill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slave companies say the company is great all the time, but during the time of appraisal the company will become so poor that it can’t give you a decent raise. These companies are only useful to propagate the colonial and slavery mentality in India, and are super dangerous cancer to our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;so&quot;&gt;So…..&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you work in an Indian company?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It’s been 75 years since we got our freedom, yet slavery mentality still persists in our country. Just look at the police force in Tamilnadu for example. They killed fellow people in Thutukudi and still the killers are out. The person who told to kill them Eddapaadi Palani Sami and Vedanta group are untouched. Even today while I was in Medavakkam I saw a car with government sticker and blue, red LED’s flashing, looks like a cop or some government employee wants to show off that he is above a normal citizen.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Getting things done</title><link href="/2024/03/07/getting-things-done.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Getting things done" /><published>2024-03-07T21:31:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-03-07T21:31:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/03/07/getting-things-done</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/03/07/getting-things-done.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;so-you-want-to-ace-stuff&quot;&gt;So you want to Ace stuff?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreianjzt2iguzubcj6wvy5k2ct4l2wpegxl76n3avo6gm4n34p2revy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you want to ace in stuff, you have ambitions, you want to get it all done efficiently. Well here is the truth, human desire is unlimited, so you can never get everything you want to do, done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At a given time you can never ace all stuff, even to ace in a single stuff is really tough. The best way to get things done is not to have expectation to do things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;it-worked-for-me&quot;&gt;It worked for me&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeihfhyeasj6gldf6b2tvdqydmbx4e4shec35nmcmioff7y5hz3zdt4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The things I write on this blog worked for me, I don’t know if it would work for you or not. This is my way of getting things done, or to precise this is my way of not getting many things done, and to be okay even when things are incomplete and imperfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Letting things go, and being happy with incompletion and not getting things done has given me mental peace. You might be a task master and want to really hurt yourself to achieve success for brag value, in that case this blog is not for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;expectations&quot;&gt;Expectations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreidkdbz6aqx2ilukpfhrrnkolk5ucjp533of3b46t72ch7bq3txymq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People might expect you to do something for them or for yourself. If you bow to others expectations, it does not work. It might not be possible for you to satisfy your own expectations, in that case how can you satisfy that of others?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s better for you not to expect others to do things for you, even if you expect so because of your desire, it’s better that you don’t feel hurt if those expectations are not met.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your tasks should be your first priority, only then comes the tasks expected of your from your loved one, and from your work and so on. Else you will burn up and feel void since none of your tasks were completed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So even though people around you blare at you with megaphones, do not give thought about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;todo-lists&quot;&gt;Todo lists&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeiaknorvvlbzxypq2sgfm6ohqdfkrrnsjnr5n3n2ct456iozvpwyaa&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todo lists don’t work. Maybe you can do a lot of planning, be meticulous as possible, but todo lists simply doesn’t work. May be if it gives you lot of joy to see long incomplete todo list, then fine, you can have a huge todo list and feel great that you have so much stuff undone, otherwise todo list is just a junk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;habit-forming&quot;&gt;Habit forming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreihhb4w7edtnftdio6vuhetfn2rf7seiti4nuob4s6qknsdrnsxlwq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Habit-forming never worked for me, you need to decide on a routine, and do it again and again periodically. You must force yourself against you. They say you have to win over yourself, but they don’t see the side of you that you want to defeat is a peaceful side of you which just wants a happy living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;multi-task&quot;&gt;Multi task&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreigjlas54k2ahznnpf5msjifsynqxdbeyktsfv7su33p7mawq46tge&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans are not for multitasking, all my attempts to multitask failed. I think even scientific research says we suck at multitasking. So try not to juggle many tasks, just try to do one task with concentration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hard-work&quot;&gt;Hard work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreiboje3fd7eszhtoei7yy3f3forobmaiq5z4kntkqyhtecq6csctnq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard work is act of stupidity according to me. You have to work less and less in your life, to such a point where you become like a king. If a society is shaped in such a way that you must work hard all the time, then it’s a failed, and unproductive society. If you want to be part of such a society, be happy with such a bleak future for humanity, yes do hard work, else stop doing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;forced-work&quot;&gt;Forced work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreiddqfjwfdipqf4oefd47a5b7os5jtvgjfogno6qbdmgbrlqxjdymq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some forced work you must do, these are great interruptions if you don’t like it. You might need to take break thrice a day to fill in your tummy, that’s a forced work if you don’t like it. You must work for your boss, your company so that you can earn money to live life, that’s a forced work. You must live your life in such a way that forced work gets reduced. Save and invest money so that you become less and less dependent on your salary and you can choose quality jobs. Choose a forced work that demands less of your time and freedom. Keep looking for ways to reduce forced work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;comparison-and-competition-sucks&quot;&gt;Comparison and competition sucks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeidkg236y5kbazoma5dkv5sfyyg3flvrjeo74mud6ofwyibc6in25a&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comparing yourself with others is a great waste of time. What matter’s is, are you comfortable with what you are. You should be comfortable with what you are, else there is a serious deficiency you need to fix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Competition sucks too, there is nothing really one achieves by winning or loosing. One has to realize we came from nothing and we will go back to nothing. Getting trapped in illusions of comparison and competition is super waste of time and energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;murphys-law&quot;&gt;Murphy’s law&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreigxvrtgw74dpzj4wjkehmhmljhc42sns3cbcy64xhdaqdk4tssqdm&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you getting things done, sometimes things go wrong, and in worst times all that could go wrong, goes wrong. There is nothing you can do about it. Accept it and try to have a cake and tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;it-doesnt-matter&quot;&gt;It doesn’t matter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c3/NGC_4414_%28NASA-med%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In grand scale of universe, it just doesn’t matter if you get things done or not. It doesn’t matter if you exist or not. It doesn’t matter if humanity poped into existence or not, it doesn’t even matter if solar system poped into existence or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In much grander scale, it doesn’t matter if this universe popped into existence or not. You are creating an illusion in your brain that something should get done, and you are suffering from that desire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Nothing is constant, everything is meaningless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;do-what-you-feel-like-doing&quot;&gt;Do what you feel like doing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeial6h5pxwdauscnp5cjv54igs7d7jaxvguj6yy4fjbql6k76c62qq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way of doing and possibly finishing stuff is to do what you like to do at the moment, and reflect upon how far have you come. You may not finish all in your todo’s, in fact for a good life you must not have todo’s, instead do what you feel like doing, do what gives you peace and satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;work-bursts&quot;&gt;Work bursts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreiga7ofybnxdth5d5l26duej6vva2a4b24jh4ggrg56h3w6ajkpksa&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always found that I achieve something in bursts of work. I get an intense energy to do something, I do that work, don’t bother if it really gives me any benefit in the future, or I am completing or achieving something. When the spirit is there, I do. These moments, I call it work bursts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One may say this is not the right way to work, you must form habit so things are consistent every day, I say ‘screw you’. Those habbit forming is just waste of time, and it doesn’t work for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;take-a-lot-of-rest&quot;&gt;Take a lot of rest&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreice6adqvxhf37henef7h23jbyv2pfchfqsscgj7aez4auzqd2vsay&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe before and after work bursts, I do take a lot of rest. Sometimes I do feel like I am wasting time while taking rests, I ignore it and take rests anyway. First I thought these rests are unproductive and should be avoided, but if I skip it, I get burned out. So I do take lot of rests and I strongly feel it helps in getting things done in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I found out was work done after taking rest gets finished or progresses better, somehow your brain seems to come up with new and efficient ways to do stuff after rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;completion-doesnt-matter&quot;&gt;Completion doesn’t matter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreibwxnpmyftwp3hhqpkt57aeegqjxklhbkzpx42wincndgyzrgryra&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t need to be complete, doing things is part of journey of life and even though you might have a goal to complete it, it shouldn’t bother you if you do not complete it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wabisabi&quot;&gt;Wabisabi&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreif54vfgbms7rljqlrvnutviwbusdc4hvs7zsdmaqfai7izvy3bcii&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your work isn’t perfect. Accept imperfections. We are humans, not robots. Imperfection is a part of us, accept it. Even if your work has imperfections, it’s okay. You may try to fix it, but it’s a big MAY. Not fixing imperfections adds beauty and character to your life. Even if there are imperfections, it’s okay, things makes things flavorful. Don’t be too strict on yourself to get things right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kaizen&quot;&gt;Kaizen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreiedww5xxrdimsuj4q5cva2nimg2cgsditupxxkhurhiesaz4qogzq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t matter if you are imperfect, you are not consistent, don’t get your tasks complete. All you need to do is to improve. Just keep improving each time a bit till you are satisfied. Don’t over work. If you have to move one step forward and many steps backward that’s okay too, but just improve. On the longer run that counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;satisfying-curiosity&quot;&gt;Satisfying curiosity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeicqii5bvy2mfkfanxz6zsuhpz2ekmbxcpkuo2f7ulrm4xih45ifee&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the time when you work on things you like to work, it’s not about getting things done. You have to get certain things done to get money and stuff, but I am talking about the work you love. Mostly work of love is not about getting things done, but it’s to satisfy your curiosity. Maybe the unknown unknown becomes known unknown, and a known unknown becomes known, and your curiosity is satisfied, and then you tend to cease to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when you have ceased to work on something, or if you are having a block, think, did you learn something new and understood some of the yearnings you had for learning? Maybe your brain made you start doing a thing because it needed to experiment and learn something, now it has learned it, it has stopped you from doing it. I feel this is an okayish behavior, and you must not resent it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;get-wiser&quot;&gt;Get wiser&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreie76gv5cacxrgbgzhyswuyxexoqqmmf6rugjzosltgif7bwrjt2fu&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, I think all we do is to get wiser, learn about the world so that we can be prepared and react better to what comes in the future. That’s what is getting done here. It’s not complete, it’s not perfect, but it’s improving at your own pace as long as it can improve, and it hopes for the best.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">So you want to Ace stuff?</summary></entry></feed>