<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-20T21:54:36+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">A very simple fix to low quality of Engineering</title><link href="/2020/05/20/a-very-simple-fix-to-low-quality-of-engineering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A very simple fix to low quality of Engineering" /><published>2020-05-20T21:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-20T21:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/05/20/a-very-simple-fix-to-low-quality-of-engineering</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/20/a-very-simple-fix-to-low-quality-of-engineering.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Indian-Engineer.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an Engineer, a Software Engineer, but I studied Electronics and Communication engineering in my college. When I came out of my college and even now, I don’t know how to solder a diode to a PCB, or to fabricate a PCB. My college Panimalar Engineering was a spoof. It did have good teachers, but some politics threw them out. One of the HOD even said to us, “here we need to be afraid of rowdys who are punes now, as they report about us to the management”. That is, it’s said that when Jeppiar was a hand of MGR and was a liquor kingpin, he had lot of rowdies under him, then after MGR’s death they started these colleges and these rodys were made as punes and they spied on staff and students. In fact we were literally living in North Korea. Naturally we got vexed and threw our brains into trash and just obeyed the management as zombies. Our 4 years which should be a sweet memory are years which we don’t want to think about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just because of these features, many colleges are technically incompetent. They are started by non engineer’s, people who have never practiced as engineer in the field and who doesn’t now what engineering is. Most are started by politicians who want easy money to run their parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These people naturally give headache to tech bosses like us, say we have a low budget project, we naturally tend to get the brightest and least experience person, we feel that new people out of college might be good after some training, but something happens in college that makes a person dumber than he was in his 8th std, college graduates come out really dumb, I don’t know why. It looks like even I managed to gain more knowledge under North Korean regime than these people who come out now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an engineer I was and am terribly upset, I had no solution or fix for it. But now I have found it out.  If the Tamilnadu government passes as a law it would be great, else colleges which say they provide quality education can take up on themselves and do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solution is this. Say you get a fees of 1.5 lakhs per year to train a student, then let’s say that you get fees of Rs 6 Lakhs in 4 years. Lets say that the student has finished the college, give the student 1% of the total fees collection every month as compensation till he gets the job, So a student who is out of job after finishing the college for 3 moths would have earned a minor compensation of Rs 6000/- per month, that is Rs 18000/- in total.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a student claims that he has got a job, then his degree certificate could be given to him, from that date on he can never claim any amount from the college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Tamilnadu government can force this upon colleges if it cares about it’s students rather than being a slave to rich barons. They possibly can even tell colleges to start an EPF kind of account called the non employment fund (NEF) to which colleges must pay it so that the student could draw it. India can even force online coaching websites to pay students compensation as well, or such sites could be marked fishy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel Engineering colleges that are truthful, and that have confidence in them and are serious about their quality will surely take up such idea.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A strategy to destroy religion</title><link href="/2020/05/16/a-strategy-to-destroy-religion.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A strategy to destroy religion" /><published>2020-05-16T09:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-16T09:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/05/16/a-strategy-to-destroy-religion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/16/a-strategy-to-destroy-religion.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/religion_is_poison.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is engulfed in blind faith, the time I write now, even during the time of dire crisis, there are more people who swear by the existence of gods, satan’s, spirits and other supernatural forces, than those who believe in free thought, exploration of ideas, finding out truth by experimentation. There is a group in India which claims that Corona is false, and your illness are not caused by viruses. It’s a bane on this society that such groups are protected by law too. I feel those people should be put as frontline workers in Corona treatment centers without any protection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During any crisis, blind faith surges, people think god is teaching us the lesson for our immorality and for badness in humanity, they never think why such a mighty force cannot create a uncorruptible humanity? But during this Corona crisis something has changed, data indicates that more people are following science, learning about virology and facts than calling their priests and spirits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are too many humans on this planet too, most of them only worth their dead meat, most humans are parasites too that are protected by law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to put a strategy to fellow rationalist around the world, a way to destroy religion. If our theory that religion makes humanity inefficient and makes it go in a wrong way is right, then religion is a self destructive force. We have proof for it, we have Brahmins in India who have made that country into their slaves and unproductive nation for at least 5000 years. Islam has banned the eating pork which would have fed millions in middle east thus ending hunger for many, the war between India and Pakistan is based on the notion that Islamic people and Hindu’s cannot live together. The list goes on and on. Billions around the world have been made miserable, inefficient and have even been slain by religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand people who have followed science have grown. Edison did not say oh god shed light so that I can see in the dark, he worked and found the light bulb, Samuel Morse did not sit and meditate so that his thoughts transmitted to brains on other side of the world, he seriously invented telegraph using kind of scientific methods. The result, we got a world that could work into night even when the god made the sun disappear, we got a closer humanity when god separated us by huge distances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel that we rationalist should ignore religious people, they are bound to get inefficient, bound to fail, and bound to follow science if they wished to survive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very good example can be found in India, where despite corona, a sect called Takrit-E-Jamat held Islamic meetings in Delhi, most of them got infected with virus, those people when faced with serious life and death situation did not run to their imams and pray to Allah for medicine to appear before them, they approached hospitals. Similarly a South Korean christian group almost surrendered after their meetings led to huge spread of Corona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today a mother carrying her dying child doesn’t run to temple, rings the bells and prays to god, she runs to a doctor who’s works are scientific. We have signals in junctions and proper education for the public to read and understand signals rather than a amman statue or vinayakar statue that in theory should keep a junction uncongested and smoothly running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As rationalism progresses, humans are giving up their wrong beliefs, these people are rationalist without them knowing it, it’s like people who drink milk calling themselves vegetarians, these people call themselves god and blind faith believers without knowing they truly trust science and rationalism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the way to defeat religion is progress, as a person following scientific way progresses, humans who are in blind faith and wants to improve will naturally shed his or her beliefs and would join us knowingly or unknowingly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vizag people won’t get Justice</title><link href="/india/capitalism/politics/corruption/andhra%20pradesh/vizag/2020/05/08/vizag-people-won-t-get-justice.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vizag people won't get Justice" /><published>2020-05-08T09:48:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-08T09:48:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/capitalism/politics/corruption/andhra%20pradesh/vizag/2020/05/08/vizag-people-won-t-get-justice</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/capitalism/politics/corruption/andhra%20pradesh/vizag/2020/05/08/vizag-people-won-t-get-justice.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://1000logos.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/LG-Logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am personally against India having so much population, I feel we must do all we can to reduce it, we humans are there everywhere like flies, but being a human it’s was hard to watch people falling down like dead flies in Vizag due  to chemical leak in L.G factory. It raises lot of doubts in me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is an establishment that has harmful substance in it, then why were residential buildings popped around it? Or how was the factory given permission to be established in residential area? Will the government officials be found out, their property be ceased and will they be hanged?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shouldn’t people of a place know about a factory that has harmful chemicals? Why the people never knew that there was a factory that had harmful chemicals? Why there was no education about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will L.G people be arrested and be hanged for mass murder? Or will the authorities will blame on Corona emergency to get off?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will people of India realize that they won’t get justice in Vizag mass murder as they haven’t got justice in Bhopal gas tragedy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will people of India realize that there is no difference between Congress and BJP. The only difference is one party demolishes mosques and kills Muslims and Christians?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a question I should ask myself: Why write blog, mostly my countrymen are utter fools to be corrected, when will I realize that?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A glimmer of hope for Alagiri</title><link href="/gossip/corruption/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/2020/05/02/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-alagiri.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A glimmer of hope for Alagiri" /><published>2020-05-02T14:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-02T14:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/gossip/corruption/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/2020/05/02/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-alagiri</id><content type="html" xml:base="/gossip/corruption/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/2020/05/02/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-alagiri.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2a/The_Union_Minister_of_Chemicals_and_Fertilizers%2C_Shri_M.K._Alagiri_briefing_the_media_on_%E2%80%98100_days_agenda%E2%80%99_of_the_Ministry%2C_in_New_Delhi_on_June_26%2C_2009.jpg/1200px-thumbnail.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I think a news circulated that Joy Alukkas owner died in middle east possibly due to Corona. The fact is some other guy called Joy Arakkal died there. Just imagine how happy Alagiri, a son of Karunadhi would have felt if he even heard this fake news, and thought it was true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story/gossip goes like this Joy Alukkas was about to open a branch in Madurai, before the day of opening, government officials there dug a trench before it claiming they have to do some corporation work there. It seems that Alagiri had asked bribe from them, they had refused to pay, so he decided to teach him a lesson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon it was said that top rowdy’s close to Alagiri came to know that an assassination team has been formed to finish off Alagiri, and it will take place before the opening of Joy Alukkas next day. The person who planned this was Dawood Ibrahim, a friend of Joy Alukkas, the gossip even goes that Dawood had invested in Joy. Confirmed the news was real Alagiri surrendered, the roads were mended, and Joy Alukkas opened as though nothing had happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also said that its because of this the DMK leadership was shaken and ultimatum was given to Alagiri by Dawood that he must not even dream of entering into any kind of politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just imagine who was Alagiri, the unshakable in Madurai, Stalin was nothing before him, we did not even know about Kanimozhi or something like that existed, and imagine how he fell almost because of no reason. Yes Alagiri’s men burned journalist in Dinakaran’s office which was part of DMK group, but I don’t think that would have contributed to his fall. I don’t think DMK or AIADMK value lives of people working in their party or in the businesses in which they have invested. A good threat by a terrorist would have shaken them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why I feel they don’t value life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine Stalin’s friend, he dies all of a sudden and people say it’s cyanide poisoning, looks like key witnesses in 2G case too have died in similar way by consuming cyanide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine Jayalaitha’s case, looks like some employees in Kodanadu died in mysterious accident. DMK and AIADMK are regimes which are no different from Noth Korea’s Kim dynasty, it’s we who people who think they are enemies and vote for one now and vote for other then. They are very clear in how to loot us and are super successful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why dont you avoid Joy Alukkas?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t buy gold. It’s because I believe gold has no value and is only worth to build toilets, but yes gold is a valuable element to scientist, it’s inert nature finds use in space science and in electronics because of its conductivity, but think whats the use of buying it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Economically as a storage Gold is good, but to convert currency into Gold and back to currency is a big process, plus they won’t give you the market value if you sell it back, I think you have to be a big trader for that. Better consider bitcoin which is mathematically secure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please research how people are treated in gold mines, and since there could be terrorist who are investors in these jewel shops, why fund them to kill us? Please think.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trivandrum</title><link href="/kerala/trivandrum/information%20technology/work/life/2020/04/26/trivandrum.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trivandrum" /><published>2020-04-26T14:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-26T14:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/kerala/trivandrum/information%20technology/work/life/2020/04/26/trivandrum</id><content type="html" xml:base="/kerala/trivandrum/information%20technology/work/life/2020/04/26/trivandrum.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/f/f0/Technopark_Trivandrum_Ariel_View_June_2014.jpg/1200px-Technopark_Trivandrum_Ariel_View_June_2014.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, I have thought to write this blog for some time, but now I think I have got some time for it, this is a guide for Tamils who want to work in Tech sector in Trivandrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trivandrum-is-not-cheap&quot;&gt;Trivandrum is not cheap&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first was about to goto Tribvandrum, my friends said that Trivandrum would be a cheap place. No it’s not. For example the P.G I stayed called Lotus PG, even to offer a 50sqft of space, they charged me Rs 5500/- per month, and guess what there is no hot water, the hall is empty without furniture, there are no plates in P.G to eat food got from Swiggy etc. The restaurants and food are not cheap too. They are as pricey or more costly than Tamilnadu. Maybe the guys over here have figured out that I.T people will pay any thing they ask for and hence are charging like hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food-is-not-of-good-quality&quot;&gt;Food is not of good quality&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The quality of food around technopark is not good enough. I had food poisoning twice in a month, almost all in my team had it. In fact people in my team were eating so called home cooked meals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-too-many-psychos&quot;&gt;Not too many psychos&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I have noted about Kerala is that there aren’t many psychos. For example in companies like Francium, Trumatics, Zanec, Kaaylabs etc there are psychopathic people. Mostly the boss or the second in command to him. But in Kerala I haven’t found it at least in the I.T industry. Somehow the company I consult for seems to have very nice HR’s to very nice Tech team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Keralites have a laid back life style, modest ambitions and know how to live life and not to fall into the rat race traps we have fallen into. Perhaps they don’t take loans, don’t do expensive spending like going to malls, buying gold, eating lavish food etc. The brains of Keralites seems to be good, far better than compared to Tamilians, or perhaps I am not in Kerala long enough to have noticed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;language&quot;&gt;Language&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Tamils have been spoiled by Banglore I think, every where you go in Banglore there is Tamil, we Tamil’s want Mangolians to speak Tamil if we goto Ulanbattar. I think Tamils went to Banglore and killed all the Kannda speakers (I think we really did that in Chola period), but Kerala is different, I did not understand a thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over here if some one calls you H.R it means not that they thought you are H.R of a company, but they had asked you if you need pickle for Briyani. If you say side dish, none knows a thing, you must say curry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kerala people speak like Tirunelveli people, words coming out rapidly, if you deconstruct them, some of it will be pure Tamil words which we do not speak now. They also remember some Tamil festivals like Aattukal Pongal which has got to do something with Kannagi, we Tamils have lost that festival though Kannagi is Tamil (possibly she lived before Tamil and Malayalam split).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like Tamil’s who feel inferior to people speaking good English, Kerala people feel so. I ask why? What’s wrong with Malayalam or any other language? They must feel proud of speaking Malayalam, they must use their time to grow their language and come out of this English subjugation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are some how okay with Hindi, we Tamils hate it. But imagine our stupidity, we said Hindi is not ours, but we have embraced English because we want to progress in Science and Tech and in Economics, but haven’t we Tamil’s let English rule us now? See the Germans, Japanese, Chinese, all these people speak their native and excel in these fields.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tamilian-food&quot;&gt;Tamilian Food&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be I’m a foodie and hence I am enjoying the taste of Kerala, but still it’s different. Once I thought potato with poori was bland, I fished out a green chili in the potato curry and bit to to give spice, and guess what? It was bland. I couldn’t believe it. Apart from few moments I enjoyed Kerala food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over here Briyani is not our Briyani, perhaps Kerala muslims are not Mughal muslims, they might have been descendants of Arbian people who traded with India’s western coast. Compared to ours I did not find Kerala briyani as exciting to put it mildly. And there is this thing called Kappa Briyani, when I ordered it, I thought it was a side dish, it looked like beef curry, I ordered parotta, fished out the beef and ate with it. Turns out that topica is a big crop in Kerala and it’s called Kappa and they make Briyani out of it, and according to us Briyani should have rice not kappa! My goodness, for the sake of heaven don’t order it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But other Tamils over here kinda hate the food here. They goto great lengths like employing cooks at their homes, going to Tamil Hotels that are far away etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is parota all the time, I love wheat products, but Tamils need rice, and that too the rice variety that originated from Tanjore, or a Tamil would not sleep that day if hadn’t had that rice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then for veggies, there is a brahmin in my PG who found it very difficult because in all hotels in Kerala you get beef. A Tamil Hindu will not go near it, Even Tamil Muslim and Christian would prefer mutton instead of beef. So if you are strict non beef eater it’s difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even the so called vegetarian Hotel Arya’s in VSSC road serves egg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ethnicity&quot;&gt;Ethnicity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps lot of Keralites in Tamilnadu may have white skin tone, but in Trivandrum, the people are like us. Walk in street, you would feel that these people are us. Not a bit different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you might know it’s Kerala if you see a woman wearing just blouse and lungi, that’s not common here in Tamilnadu, or perhaps the color veshti that’s worn in Kerala by men might give you a hint. But these people are just us, no different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;terrain&quot;&gt;Terrain&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No wonder we named them Malayalis, the people who are in the hilly region, almost every time you will be going up and down the hill. For a Chennai-ite like me, its very different, I realized I was livung in plains only after going to Trivandrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had lot’s of hills around Chennai too, but many have been mined off for gravel, in Kerala there are still hills and forests, looks like these people more respect their terrain and nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;size-of-it&quot;&gt;Size of I.T&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The size of I.T industry in Kerala is very tiny, people say entire Technopark even when doubled will fit into Mepz, Tambaram. And Mepz is just one small portion of Chennai’s I.T industry. Kerala is looking for slow and limited growth, not a mad rush toward globalization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are coming to Trivandrum in a hope of starting with a company and hoping to jump to neighboring building or next I.T park with a 30% hike, may be that won’t happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cheating-cab-and-auto-drivers&quot;&gt;Cheating cab and auto drivers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh damn, even if you order a cab from Uber the drivers ask for money over the metered rate. Over here too the auto meters don’t work and they demand 20 - 25 rupees a kilometer. So I better walk. If perhaps Corona did not interfere I would have got a bicycle to visit beach or library or for office commute every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My office is at a top of a hill, it’s good and bad. Good because it gives me exercise everyday, and bad because of the same reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;connectivity&quot;&gt;Connectivity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trivandrum is well connected to Kaniyakumari, Tirunelveli, but Chennai is really long, if you are okay with air travel, then Chennai is well connected too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually Chennai people are far different from rest of Tamil people, so if you try to find Chennai-ites in this city, you will be at a loss.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I am not an Atheist</title><link href="/2020/04/24/why-i-am-not-an-atheist.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I am not an Atheist" /><published>2020-04-24T16:43:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-24T16:43:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/04/24/why-i-am-not-an-atheist</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/24/why-i-am-not-an-atheist.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.britannica.com/75/177675-131-B7A64EA6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many have asked me why I am against Modi’s govt but not against many other governments that are religious. For example Pakistan is an Islamic state, so much Islamic that they only only recognize Sunni sect as Islamic and others like Boras, Ahmedias, Shias as not a part of Islam. The answer is simple, India is my country, I don’t really mind if Pakistan, Iran or Indonesia does not develop and fall to depths due to religion. I simply don’t care about those people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also oppose DMK and AIADMK having alliance with PMK and Muslim League, these are parties based on caste and religion, they are as poisonous as BJP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s come to thing why I am not an atheist. Imagine some one tells you take a plunge into a river and to swim against the current, you are with them on a dry land with no river in sight, you would think that person is mad. How can you go against anything that does not exist? Only a mad would imagine something exists and go against it. Calling some one atheist or anti God is similar. Where is God? What is God? Who created God?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly there are no theist too. Say that you are lying on a perfectly dry land, paddling your hand and feet and saying that you are swimming with the river current, as stupid as it sounds, that’s what theist do, they imagine something is there and they say that thing loves and protects them and by surrendering to the non existent God they feel they are blessed by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I would call myself is rationalist. We are the ones who don’t mind interacting with gods, satans, Ghosts, Sprits, Gobblins, Devils, Mickey mouse, Harry Potter, Poppye but where are they?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Are Tamils naturally foolhardy?</title><link href="/2020/04/20/are-tamils-naturally-foolhardy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Are Tamils naturally foolhardy?" /><published>2020-04-20T11:53:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-20T11:53:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/04/20/are-tamils-naturally-foolhardy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/20/are-tamils-naturally-foolhardy.html">&lt;p&gt;Iran cancels Ramzaan, a thing I wouldn’t expect to happen. A Nation that turned completely Islamic 40 years ago, now listens to its doctors and science. It was an excellent transformation! As a rationalist I am joyed to see it. But then few days back on April 14th, we Tamils celebrated our new year, people ventured out even in Corona intense places, they seem not to be concerned about the consequence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possibly going back a month or a month and a half ago, I was telling about Corona to my team back in Trivandrum, all were Kerala people and young, when I briefed them about corona their pupils dilated, their eyes became bigger, they had their desire to go home to their native. It was very different feeling I had, because in Tamilnadu, if I brief yong people about something, say like server crash or about some disaster, say warn about floods (which I did way back), they would take it into account, but would brush it off and go to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Kerala seems to have contained Corona, people over there are cautious about it, over here Corona is accelerating, and none seems to be bothered about it. Living in Kerala for a month, I feel Kerala people are gentle, and Tamils have some kid of rock in them, determined, they travel towards a goal or something not been bothered much about their feelings and fear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be something in people in Tamilnadu that I feel is making them more adventurous. Take for instance our sport Jallikattu, we want to match ourself with this big beast. It’s only now the sport which is done in a bit sane way, but before liquor was fed to the cow, chilly powder rubbed on its privates and it was made to face the youth to have a aggressive Jallikattu. We simply did not bother about been pierced and torn by it, we welcomed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not now, we have a saying ஆறிலும் சாவு, அறுபதிலும் சாவு (death at 6, death at 60), which means death comes at any age and don’t be bothered about it. The book of Pura-naanuuru hails of moms sending their young sons to battle, and feeling proud that they will die for the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even in war, at the battle field Tamils followed tactics that would make others feel that we are crazy. War elephants were made to drink and sent amok in the battle field, bringing in panic and killing friend and foe alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of all civilizations in India, it was the Tamils that ventured far into the oceans, as far as Newzeland. And for what purpose? We simply don’t know. Even places in Japan that are suitable for habitation are named kudil (குடில்), why so? We may not know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right at the place I live, in Sithalapakkam, I find foolhardiness of people, and it has got a philosophical base. It was after coming to this place I heard about Hans, Mawa and Supaari, these are drugs which people use, especially the youngsters over her. When asked why, and asked wont it bring early death? Their reply was ‘கோள் புடிக்கும் முன் சாவு நல்லது’, that is it’s better to die before I need a staff for my support. I was astounded by this philosophy of a drug addict who possibly did not attend his scool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s only after interacting with people of other states that I find there is something different in Tamil, a form of bravery, a form of foolhardiness, not being afraid of death, ignoring facts and Tamils feel comfortable being a stupid, perhaps unique to this region. Possibly it was this adventurous nature that made our language spread far and wide. Today our children call their parent’s mummy and daddy, whereas Korean kids call their parents Amma and Appa.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Iran cancels Ramzaan, a thing I wouldn’t expect to happen. A Nation that turned completely Islamic 40 years ago, now listens to its doctors and science. It was an excellent transformation! As a rationalist I am joyed to see it. But then few days back on April 14th, we Tamils celebrated our new year, people ventured out even in Corona intense places, they seem not to be concerned about the consequence.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Don’t write complex SQL queries</title><link href="/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/anti%20patterns/2020/04/17/don-t-write-complex-sql-queries.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Don't write complex SQL queries" /><published>2020-04-17T09:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-17T09:51:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/anti%20patterns/2020/04/17/don-t-write-complex-sql-queries</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/anti%20patterns/2020/04/17/don-t-write-complex-sql-queries.html">&lt;p&gt;Say that you want to be a musician, so you buy a nice violin, but you don’t know how to play it and don’t have the patience to learn how to play it, so to produce music you trash the violin on rock and call it music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the case I find with many teams using Rails. They pick up Rails because it’s fancy, a buzz word and they fail to stick with it’s best practices. Yesterday my team mate called me and asked me a doubt, there was a function that just had one line of ORM and it was easy to test, so I told him how. There was another in which a complex join was used, the function spanned 10 lines or so and mostly it was occupied by SQL query.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The function was badly written and it did not have any other documentation that said what it did. I simply couldn’t tell the poor fellow how to test it. It might have been an old code written before the dawn of humanity and it was crap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One reason I’d been told by the so called Rails people is that writing SQL is efficient than using ORM. The strength of Rails, well, most of it is in ActiveRecord, it’s ORM layer. If you don’t want it why on earth are you using Rails?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to Rails, it’s true that ORM is inefficient and firing lot of SQL slows down the DB. But haven’t you chosen the Rails and Ruby path because you are concerned with human productivity than with computer efficiency? Is your application so big that it spans more than 100 servers all scaled to max vertically that is making you to take such a drastic decision?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now what about making computers do lot of work so that humans are productive? Isn’t that progress? There are ways to scale Data Base, be it MySQL or Postgres. Postgres comes with very excellent scaling which you can use to make many servers act like one Posgres DB. For MySQL there are stuffs like ProxySQL that catches and make the DB run more cooler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making computer’s work hard makes economic sense too. An Engineer who is supposed to follow computing trends should know that computing costs are getting cheaper and human costs are getting higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder why people are bring up so much bane on themselves when there are so much boon that’s been given to us by the Free Software Community? One thing is due to ignorance. Managers push programmers so much and make them accountable for everything, that programmers become like narrow visioned horses which concentrate just on their destination than to think out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any technical house should trust it’s engineers, should give them enough resources to them to explore, when you are faced with a problem, the team should come up with 5 to 10 solutions which should be put to the test, out of that which is the most suitable for the team should be chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you like to bang things around and want to be a musician, choose to play drums rather than a violin.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Say that you want to be a musician, so you buy a nice violin, but you don’t know how to play it and don’t have the patience to learn how to play it, so to produce music you trash the violin on rock and call it music.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Don’t change constants in Ruby</title><link href="/programming/ruby/rubocop/anti%20pattern/2020/04/14/don-t-change-constants-in-ruby.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Don't change constants in Ruby" /><published>2020-04-14T20:42:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-14T20:42:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/ruby/rubocop/anti%20pattern/2020/04/14/don-t-change-constants-in-ruby</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/ruby/rubocop/anti%20pattern/2020/04/14/don-t-change-constants-in-ruby.html">&lt;p&gt;I am reviewing a lot of code now, kind of projects that have million plus lines of Ruby code that been (un)maintained for 13 years or so. That’s lot of code and lot of years. Still the project goes strong. I once encountered a thing that crashed our server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take this one&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for some reason, this hash constant changes, don’t ask me why, this changes, so the code is like this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:some_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:some_value&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually in the above code, ruby just warns and lets you a free run. I am kind of against that, but that’s how Ruby works. But now when I run rubocop auto correct against it, the above code get’s transformed to something like below&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{}.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;freeze&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:some_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:some_value&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH&lt;/code&gt; is frozen, and it cannot be changed. Rubocop is right, constant should not change, that’s why its a constant! Common!! That’s why rubocop froze it. So when it encounters this line &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;SOME_HASH[:some_key] = :some_value&lt;/code&gt;, what was set not to change, now changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i0.wp.com/theverybesttop10.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/Top-10-Best-Images-of-Surprised-Cats-2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Ruby throws an error and stops code execution. The basic thing is CONSTANT IS CONSTANT and don’t ever change it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I am reviewing a lot of code now, kind of projects that have million plus lines of Ruby code that been (un)maintained for 13 years or so. That’s lot of code and lot of years. Still the project goes strong. I once encountered a thing that crashed our server.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Will I.T companies realize the goodness of work from home?</title><link href="/2020/04/12/will-i-t-companies-realize-the-goodness-of-work-from-home.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Will I.T companies realize the goodness of work from home?" /><published>2020-04-12T15:06:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-12T15:06:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/04/12/will-i-t-companies-realize-the-goodness-of-work-from-home</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/12/will-i-t-companies-realize-the-goodness-of-work-from-home.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://fm.cnbc.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/img/editorial/2018/08/08/105384527-1533749153652manworkingonlaptopatdiningtable.1910x1000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I.T companies are simply marketing agents, they just sell your talent to those who seek it and they keep a huge amount of profit. Its just like a pipe that connects your water tank and sink and demands a chunk of money because its at the middle. In fact many of you who work in I.T would have known that I.T companies just forward the client emails to you and your emails back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before, say 30 years from now, working in I.T company made sense. Computers were so expensive that an individual cannot buy it. One needed salary and time to get trained in learning to write software. Training and training material were expensive. Computers were fragile and needed air-conditioning and static and dust free environment. All of these cannot be afforded by a single person and hence there were companies that did it and hired people. Today every one can buy a laptop and equipped with knowledge and internet connection can start a I.T business. Then why on Earth I.T companies sill exist and gobble off money that needs to go directly to workers and not those bosses that do almost nothing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I.T companies have become good at is to control their employees. Employees in I.T companies mostly believe that they need the company. It’s possibly because of our culture. We Indians were uneducated 4 generations ago, most of us were brought up with middle class thought that we must study hard get a job and work hard. So using this inferiority complex of ours, certain foxes are able to run their I.T business successfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s come to the point of working from home. Today many I.T companies let their employees work from home due to pressure from the government, and if not they would have asked their employees to come to office and wouldn’t have bothered a sliver if their employees die out of Corona. In fact I know certain I.T bosses who went up to the level of saying Corona is a fake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I.T companies and their bosses are always afraid that you, the tech guy / gal will know your potential and would start a parallel business. Even websites that say that it will connect you with potential clients are afraid  of you having contact directly with the client. Try creating your profile in Freelancer, Fiverr, or UpWork, you simply can’t list your phone number and email (but &lt;a href=&quot;http://nyoboo.com&quot;&gt;nyoboo&lt;/a&gt; allows you to do it).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work from home is also used to black mail you. In my previous company Francium, the bosses were psychos to put it mildly. There was an excellent devops guy, they did not realize his potential because of their limited knowledge and tunnel vision, all of a sudden work from home was cut for him. As it turns out that they wanted to fire him for some reason and hence they started to torture him. They couldn’t do it with me because I came to office anyway, so they told me to come to office at 11:00 AM every day, when I failed a spy would tell my arrival timing to the boss who will use it to make me feel bad. All were spied as far as I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I certainly believe freelancers will head the I.T industry of the future. It is good economics, why the middle man so called your boss or an I.T company get the lions share of money when it is just a pipe? Why can’t we develop automated tools that will market you depending on your activity and customer satisfaction?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can be done and that’s what we are doing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>