<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-06-14T16:50:17+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">What Stalin says about Senthil Balaji</title><link href="/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Stalin says about Senthil Balaji" /><published>2023-06-14T16:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-14T16:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeigc2rfxdghs6hycj5ord2qzo7kw3citwc7qzvmnwcbmi6n2rtengu &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tamils should search for right people to rule</title><link href="/2023/06/13/tamils-should-search-for-right-people-to-rule.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tamils should search for right people to rule" /><published>2023-06-13T20:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-13T20:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/13/tamils-should-search-for-right-people-to-rule</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/13/tamils-should-search-for-right-people-to-rule.html">&lt;p&gt;BJP is a shit party made up of shitty people, yet Amit Shah is able to hit at DMK’s dynastic politics, Annamalai is able to say that AIADMK’s passed away supremo Jayalalith is a criminal. Both the allegations are true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If people of DMK and AIADMK hear such damaging truth, and don’t have facts and reasons to counter it, they must commit suicide if they have a bit of self dignity left in them. Guess what none would.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we Tamils have elected this DMK or AIADMK again and again without shame, we must ask ourselves are we shameless people? Or do we have something left in us so that we can try to correct our politics? Do we know who we are voting to? What is his wealth? What are his revenue streams? What businesses he is associated with? What functions he attends? Who attended those functions? How many times the politician has knocked on your door and asked what should be improved? What are the last 10 good things he has done to Tamil Nadu, your district, your ward and to your street? What are the last 10 bad things he has done? Are you going to vote based on the facts you are learned about him? Or are you going to just vote?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even a garbage pickers children in Tamil Nadu are getting educated to have better lives, but we as voters have no plans to educate ourselves about the politicians in our voters list. We may never get political education, that’s what the corrupt want, and till the day most of us get educated, looting will be super high in Tamil Nadu, and we all will be just spectators.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">BJP is a shit party made up of shitty people, yet Amit Shah is able to hit at DMK’s dynastic politics, Annamalai is able to say that AIADMK’s passed away supremo Jayalalith is a criminal. Both the allegations are true.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">CGPA of Indian States</title><link href="/2023/05/27/cgpa-of-indian-states.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CGPA of Indian States" /><published>2023-05-27T23:38:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-27T23:38:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/27/cgpa-of-indian-states</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/27/cgpa-of-indian-states.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeidsgaq36fsdo3xtwup6eahfypatgdqjuu7tpian6oajmmmi7rhhpa&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why can’t Indian President Inaugurate The New Parliament?</title><link href="/2023/05/25/why-cant-indian-president-inaugurate-the-new-parliament.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why can&apos;t Indian President Inaugurate The New Parliament?" /><published>2023-05-25T21:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-25T21:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/25/why-cant-indian-president-inaugurate-the-new-parliament</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/25/why-cant-indian-president-inaugurate-the-new-parliament.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/Smt._Droupadi_Murmu_official_portrait_%281%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Draupathi Murmu&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s great that the opposition parties which almost don’t have the spine to appose Modi are going to boycott the inauguration of new parliament building, the reason they chose to boycott will anger all true Hindu’s in this nation, and it should.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opposition parties have a simple request, the leader of India Draupathi Murmu should inaugurate our parliament building, but why she is not invite and cannot inaugurate our parliament is hushed up, this speaks volumes about Hinduism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First our president is from lower caste, which Brahmin feet lickers won’t like, her caste people could be considered inauspicious beings by them. In fact, I think in ancient Hinduism our president’s caste could be a untouchable caste. According to hindu’s may be those caste people should do only tasks like disposing the dead, cleaning toilet’s, taking care of cattle, doing household chores etc. I think pure Hindu’s will even wash the things touched by lower caste people to purify it. So BJP and RSS might have been instructed by their Hind lords  not to invite a lower caste person to pollute our parliament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, she is a woman. India is a nation that still treats woman as slaves. Now we don’t publicly burn woman just because her husband is dead, but we do all other forms of mistreatment. Visit a house of an Aiyappan devotee and talk frank with the women in the home, and you will know, in fact one will be shocked to find out how women are still been treated as untouchables by their own dad’s, husbands and brothers even today during an Aiyappan season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Women are meant to be slaves who do not have access to Gods. Vedas are banned for them, in ancient homes Sanskrit was not thought to them so that they don’t have access to Gods. The only purpose of woman in post Aryan invaded India is to be slave of men in family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how can a woman who is impure according to the religion followed by BJP and RSS people can contaminate our pure Parliament? That too during it’s inauguration?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So according to a Hindu and Indian, people requesting that President should inaugurate parliament are anti-Indians and anti-national. I am proud to be one more anti-Indian during this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let them enjoy purifying parliament by spraying cow urine in it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Draupathi Murmu</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Which tech companies will make more money in future</title><link href="/2023/05/24/which-tech-companies-will-make-more-money-in-future.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Which tech companies will make more money in future" /><published>2023-05-24T19:27:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-24T19:27:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/24/which-tech-companies-will-make-more-money-in-future</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/24/which-tech-companies-will-make-more-money-in-future.html">&lt;p&gt;I.T has given India a lot, one’s father might be a daily wage laborer, but child in the family might be very interested in computers, all the child has is a cell phone, the child calls a right company expresses interest, they test for the curiosity, laptop arrives to their home, along with broadband, within 4 years the kid has a car, a home on loan which can be paid off in another 3 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recruiting the right and bright talent, and pouring money into them which would rival the salaries of CXO of other companies has been a winning strategy in the I.T industry. That too the kid in the I.T company if it’s in a tier 2 or tier 3 town, they an save a lot of money and settle for life soon, marry, and once that’s done, not even we can save it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now almost none of you in tech knows assembly language, soon no new hires might know programming languages. They will tell computers what to do, and the computer will spit the binary out. You need not worry about code craft, clean code and so on, just like you do not need to worry about garbage collection these days. Applications that took years to develop could be written in weeks, and they won’t have bugs, and they won’t have code quality issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies that can give the highest percapita A.I power to their employees will win. They will make money. Just like a company of 17 today is making more money than a company of untrained 350 programmers, a small company that has great minds and high percapita A.I power can make the money of a company that has 1000’s of people who are untrained in A.I and free thought.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I.T has given India a lot, one’s father might be a daily wage laborer, but child in the family might be very interested in computers, all the child has is a cell phone, the child calls a right company expresses interest, they test for the curiosity, laptop arrives to their home, along with broadband, within 4 years the kid has a car, a home on loan which can be paid off in another 3 years.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">An argument for the command line</title><link href="/2023/05/16/an-argument-for-the-command-line.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="An argument for the command line" /><published>2023-05-16T22:01:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-16T22:01:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/16/an-argument-for-the-command-line</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/16/an-argument-for-the-command-line.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeicligfwyuehx4vms7z5f6nbzpecm7q2td7sjtwpsv3pk4ahojwzp4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before there was GUI (Graphical User Interface), computers displayed text, they got input as text, and gave text as output. Certainly GUI appealed to a lot of people and made them to use computers, but business that are multimillion dollar worth ones used command line, that is text interface terminals for their computing needs, and they were happy with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we are in a wave where we need to make computers idiot-proof, even a baby should be able to use it, the intellectual person is the last customer who we aim for. We programmers seems to think the world is filled with non-intellectuals and we must never write nice informative command line systems for the intellect, and that’s where lot of software problems start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;command-line-is-tough-to-use&quot;&gt;Command line is tough to use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One misconception is command line is tough to use. To look at this months calendar this is the command I use on my computer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ cal
      May 2023
Su Mo Tu We Th Fr Sa
    1  2  3  4  5  6
 7  8  9 10 11 12 13
14 15 16 17 18 19 20
21 22 23 24 25 26 27
28 29 30 31
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now try to find on which day lies August 15&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; 1947, for me it took less than 5 seconds, what about you using an GUI?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ cal aug 1947
    August 1947
Su Mo Tu We Th Fr Sa
                1  2
 3  4  5  6  7  8  9
10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21 22 23
24 25 26 27 28 29 30
31
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, you need to memorize the word &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cal&lt;/code&gt; and read its documentation to use it, but my question is has the humanity got so stupid that shies away from reading things about tools it needs to use?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though there are GUI programs, I wish there was command lines tools that would be simple and fast to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;programmers-use-command-line&quot;&gt;Programmers use command line&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We programmers always use command line tools. The top programming languages are all text based languages and not visual one, though visual languages do exists, they are good for building apps fast initially, but they get bloated with complexity. The vast servers that run the internet run on GNU/Linux whose interface is the command line and do not have fancy Windows OS or Apple OS in it, those OSes are bloated with unneeded GUI. We programmers till to date trust text interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;very-fast-to-develop-command-line-applications&quot;&gt;Very fast to develop command line applications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Command line tools can be developed very fast, one need not worry a lot about display logic, fonts, colors and blah blah. It’s just information in and information out. Since we are limiting the options a lot without display logic and all the complexities and permutations the comes along with it, we can concentrate on solving the business problem and develop the app than worry about styling glitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;train-people&quot;&gt;Train people&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing with command line is, to use it, one has to train people, but once they are trained, they become super powerful, far powerful than people using GUI. To train people, you need to hire people who are ready to learn, and people who would like to understand your business and learn to use a tool to enhance it will definitely won’t be a stupid and would demand more money. May be businesses today want less paid large numbers of inefficient idiots, than productive intelligent high paid people. Maybe that’s what has killed command line business apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One question I would like to ask business people is, do you think business built relying on idiots will out last business built with people who would like to think and learn?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;information-matters&quot;&gt;Information matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately it’s information that matters for human development, tetris played on game boy is more exciting to me than tetris played on a touch screen phone. Gameboy just delivers information in monochrome and does not worry about the shininess of the app, does not worry about color of the blocks and the app animations are kept to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a logical situation its information and truth that matters than shininess, glitter and glamour. Command line apps gives you raw information without the need for the unnecessary stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-age-of-voice&quot;&gt;The age of voice&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The age of voice I think will usher in command line development, voice is just information in which gets converted to text, this text is fed into a program that mostly outputs a text, this gets converted to voice and sent back. Developing apps that take in information and transform it to another piece of information will be refreshing for developers than to concentrate on nasty GUI’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;books-are-still-there&quot;&gt;Books are still there&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though we have got movies, books are still there, they are easy to produce than movies, they deliver concise information to the reader. The story telling world seems to still cater the intellect though things can be done in much difficult visual way of movies, why not we app developers do the same?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case of app development, developers and businesses treat their users as not intellectuals who like to see right information on their screen, but they treat people as kids who like to see shiny things on screen. Common info tech world, serve the intellect than serving people who like glitter.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ghost encounters in office</title><link href="/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ghost encounters in office" /><published>2023-05-16T00:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-16T00:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office.html">&lt;p&gt;I had two ghost encounters in office till to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first one was in a company called Trumatics. I started it with my friend Umashankar who I met in another company called Zanec. We recruited a girl called Vadivikarasi. In that office I used to take walk in the terrace. Once while I was walking I saw Vadivikarasi leaving office, I thought she was leaving early for some reason. I was 40 feet up, and she was on road. I finished my walk and went downstairs to office and there she was Vadivukkarasi. I was shocked and asked her did she leave office and I said to her, I saw her leaving, she too got terrified. Not wanting to make her more afraid I stopped talking about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what ever left that gate had her dress, backpack like her, skin tone like her, the same hold of cell phone while she browses while she leaves our office. It could be a very strange coincidence that I saw someone else and mistook her, or may be my brain got screwed up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My second encounter was in a company Francium, there was a devops girl who seemed to know the trade, and we talked a lot. She drove an electric bike, at that time there were almost no electric bikes in India. She sat in my room because she is a one who cannot stay without super chill A/C. One day she left home, after some time a guy called Prasanna got introduced, or we were talking after acquitance after some time (may be few days). Suddenly he said my wife is devops here, before I could say I know and ask about the electric bike he said his wife Archana is inside coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My heart stopped, just moments ago I saw his wife leave the office, how can I say to him I saw a ghost which was his wife? This Vadivukkarasi incident popped into my mind. This guy Prasanna asked my why I looked tensed.  Dam hell how can I ever say I saw a ghost which just left office that looked like his wife. I did not react and went in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next day I got a doubt and asked others the name of the devops girl that sits in my room, it was Radha they said. Damn, God, dam, life came into me. I am not a peoples person and I get carried away speaking tech to people I don’t even bother asking about their names and stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I learned these girls names and memorized how they looked so that I don’t get confused. Radha soon quit office and hence from then on if it was devops girl it was Archana. So no more confusion. It was sad seeing a devops engineer who was talented go out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot about the work ethics of Prasanna and Archana, I think Archana left that office before I did, and I was thrown out all of a sudden, and Prasanna quit too. Now I don’t even know if Francium exists. I wonder if any company that let’s go off good talent due to carless planning ever comes up?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I had two ghost encounters in office till to date.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">India, a state intolerant to art and expression</title><link href="/2023/05/09/india-a-state-intolerant-to-art-and-expression.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="India, a state intolerant to art and expression" /><published>2023-05-09T21:36:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-09T21:36:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/09/india-a-state-intolerant-to-art-and-expression</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/09/india-a-state-intolerant-to-art-and-expression.html">&lt;p&gt;I was a bit surprised by negative reaction by Islamist towards Kerala Story. It’s a movie that’s been rated high in IMDB. I’m not sure if any Indian girl has been converted by ISIS into Islam and made to perform terror strikes, or serve as slaves to them, but even if they did, why would India expose it for the fear of embarrassment?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I first thought Kerala Story was a Malayalam movie, but it turns out it’s a Hindi one. I wish it could be translated to Tamil so that I can enjoy it full.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure some Islamist who do say The Kerala Story should be banned, surely said that BBC excellent documentary about Modi’s genocide in Gujarat should be screened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an atheist, I do get offended seeing people scammed by Temples, Mosques, Church, Guruduvaras which claim that God, Satan, Angels, Spirits and Supernatural stuff exists, but I certainly don’t oppose movies that are supernatural based (in fact they are really entertaining), even though I feel movies based on facts should be created rather than one preferring to create movies based on beliefs and myth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not the first time intolerance is seen in India. During Pakistan’s creation, Muslims and Hindus were intolerant to each other. Thousands of years ago before Islamists invaded India, one sect of Hindus were at war with others, but yes at that time there was no single Hinduism, there isn’t a single Hinduism now too. I would even claim what Christianity and Islam that is practiced in India is a part of Hinduism too. Maybe those God’s too will be part of Hindu’s collection of Gods hundreds of years from now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;M.F.Hussein died in Qatar and not in India. Taslima Nasreen is I think is living in France and not in India or Bangladesh which should be her motherland. Karuppar Kuutam youtube channel was banned by Hindu extremists who were pissed off when a group of youngsters thought the world the meaning of Hindu scriptures. Davinci Code did not screen well because the Christians wanted it to be banned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not just religious groups that are intolerant. Great cartoons against corruption emerged, like say one cartoon depicting mother India’s hand is held by politicians and bureaucrats, while corporate who have bribed them line up to rape her, I think it (the rape) was watched by the four lions of Ashoka with their tongue’s out. Politicians and bureaucrats got furious because it depicted India’s situation well, and they banned that cartoons against corruption website so that people don’t get educated about corruption in our nation. Very sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really wonder when Indian’s will learn to think rationally, respect art, thought, difference of opinion, freedom of ones belies, etc. Or maybe we will end up corrupting the world with our old thoughts (till humans exists), which even made California banning Indian caste system in its state.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was a bit surprised by negative reaction by Islamist towards Kerala Story. It’s a movie that’s been rated high in IMDB. I’m not sure if any Indian girl has been converted by ISIS into Islam and made to perform terror strikes, or serve as slaves to them, but even if they did, why would India expose it for the fear of embarrassment?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Miss Vairamuthu in Ponniyin Selvan</title><link href="/2023/04/30/miss-vairamuthu-in-ponniyin-selvan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Miss Vairamuthu in Ponniyin Selvan" /><published>2023-04-30T22:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-30T22:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/04/30/miss-vairamuthu-in-ponniyin-selvan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/04/30/miss-vairamuthu-in-ponniyin-selvan.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0d/Vairamuthu_alaigal_book_shop.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Photo By Gavaskar.tk - Own work, CC BY-SA 4.0, &lt;a href=&quot;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=39272896&quot;&gt;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=39272896&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maniratnam said that we are giving chance to new lyricist in Ponniyin Selvan, but I feel for a such a novel cherished by Tamils, which is been made into a movie, we must have gone for the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am well aware of the controversy surrounding Vairamuthu, there is even a gossip that says he has girls hotels in chennai supplying girls for him and his friends. If Vairamuthu has done anything against the law he should be punished. There is a very good chance that since Vairamuthu is been cherished by the Tamil people, and has deep political connections, no action is taken against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I feel is, even Vairamuthu is in jail, he must have been asked if he could write songs for Ponniyin Selvan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those who have read the book have got nothing good to say about the movie, it’s just running because of huge marketing effort. I am not sure if Lyca is just a money laundering company like Red Giant. In fact I am waiting for Viduthalai part 2 than Ponniyin Selvan 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly feel not having Vairamuthu in this movie is another slip for Maniratnam. I feel they should have boldly said that they are not bothered by Vairamuthu’s personal side, and they have recruited the poet in him to make this movie a good one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Photo By Gavaskar.tk - Own work, CC BY-SA 4.0, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=39272896</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why use ReactJS, Angular or Vue with Ruby on Rails?</title><link href="/2023/04/24/why-use-reactjs-angular-or-vue-with-ruby-on-rails.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why use ReactJS, Angular or Vue with Ruby on Rails?" /><published>2023-04-24T17:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-24T17:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/04/24/why-use-reactjs-angular-or-vue-with-ruby-on-rails</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/04/24/why-use-reactjs-angular-or-vue-with-ruby-on-rails.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiggzg4m2rnb44a5f6yucz3hlg27uvaaiabcfpgqsbiybz37w7r2ne.ipfs.dweb.link/1571754069Ruby on Rails Copyright Free Logo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s super mysterious to me why people choose to use ReactJS, Angular or Vue with Ruby on Rails and pay the price for low productivity. It’s like people are blind and pretend to know nothing about code. Or they go by Popularity Driven Development? That is, they choose stuff based on popularity without technical analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ruby programming language was created to be programmers best friend, and it is, until you reach say nears a million lines of code, at that stage OOP fails, you must switch to functional programming, but for medium-sized apps Ruby is best and Ruby o Rails tries to be Rubyish as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails emphasizes readability and productivity. JavaScript is a natural eye soar, hard to read, hard to debug. Right from Rails 2 I think there is a way to reduce JS code in Rails. First it was RJS, then you sent request using jQuery and got JS payload back which replaced part of page, then now you have this wonderful HotWire which does the same thus minimizing JavaScript hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout history Rails has provided better way to build webpages than any known JS framework. It’s a super mystery for me why anyone would choose a JS framework, increase code complexity, go for large team and ultimately be unproductive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why big tech created JS frameworks was because they have grown big and wants to manage front and back end teams separately. The front end guy might need to interact with designer, test UI in various devices, connect with the backend using API. The backend person designs API, checks the access capability of the user to a particular piece of data, and if some API is hit, triggers some business logic. Those two are different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;70% of the websites could just be static web pages. You don’t need a front end or backend frameworks for it, another 10% might need a simple scripting like PHP, another 18% might be okay with Rails, Laravel and so on, may be just 2% of the apps will be need to have separate front and back end teams, bureaucracy, planning, inefficiency and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a feeling that Indian companies want to bill the client more by adding more people to app development citing complexity, architecture, planning, project management and blah blah, rather than having a lean team, finishing stuff up, and increasing per-capita developer revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come into the present Info Tech firms!!! Common, you are embarrassing me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiaou7bgoe6pi4t5rhduszmfhilqf2twdye2koebxkjhsyjaxltf3a.ipfs.dweb.link/Facepalm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>