<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-11-20T19:05:29+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Elon Musk and my style of work</title><link href="/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elon Musk and my style of work" /><published>2022-11-20T19:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-20T19:05:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/34/Elon_Musk_Royal_Society_%28crop2%29.jpg/544px-Elon_Musk_Royal_Society_%28crop2%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Elon Musk - The evil boss you must avoid.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I push for 16 hour work week, with four-hour work days. I strongly feel that knowledge workers should have life, should spend time with their family and loved ones, think and reflect, should get new ideas. This I feel will cultivate a healthy brain and will ultimately increase productivity of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Elon Musk doing in Twitter looks very evil to me. For some reason even people of science and creativity, when they move to management, they become task masters without brains. They seem to forget where true productivity lies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are times when I finished coding for a sprint (2 weeks long one) in 2 hours, but yes all those other paper work does cost more time, but the core issue only takes two hours. There are times when even the sprint got over I haven’t started coding as the details were murky, or my understanding was not right. I understood a lot of things when I am away from keyboard, something works in your brains background while you enjoy life, all of a sudden most elegant solution pops up, and you implement it, and it works!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow management people never seems to understand it, their view of knowledge work is like viewing a repetitive work in a factory. Humans are like automated robots to them. If a robot can drive 1000 bolts in an hour, then it must drive 4000 in four hours. In my view a human or biological system is not like that. We get tired, we get energized, we sometimes find work rewarding, and sometimes boring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not worried about Twitters future, or its success or failure, I am long time user of Diaspora, I use Mastodon, and I have deleted my Facebook long ago. I am worried about the dangerous precedent Elon is setting in the I.T industry. With people like him, the industry will be populated by mindless ‘yes boss’ human bots who are there for a paycheck, than for the passion of coding.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Elon Musk - The evil boss you must avoid.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This woman is such a great stupid, BJP people would love to have her in their party</title><link href="/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This woman is such a great stupid, BJP people would love to have her in their party" /><published>2022-11-14T12:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-14T12:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeictysiokuwms63ywicar2wb5qe7stgf4edaalrwil4nnvzarcmlyi/redditsave.com_tamil_should_not_be_a_compulsory_language_in-dmws7qd2ioz91.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pragamin</title><link href="/2022/11/07/pragamin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pragamin" /><published>2022-11-07T20:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-07T20:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/07/pragamin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/07/pragamin.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeicikohkfb75id5ulkphzklqdhl6vlrlika2doguph2hqbsghurimq/pragamin.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bullshit Job</title><link href="/2022/11/06/bullshit-job.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bullshit Job" /><published>2022-11-06T21:44:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-06T21:44:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/06/bullshit-job</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/06/bullshit-job.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeibxqlrrhrtuiv3mk3hnaiwm4p5ioqu7x7ji4valbecsm5x5ck3hku/bullshit_job.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vadacurry in Hotel Archana Bhavan in Sithalapakkam is good</title><link href="/2022/11/06/vadacurry-in-hotel-archana-bhavan-in-sithalapakkam-is-good.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vadacurry in Hotel Archana Bhavan in Sithalapakkam is good" /><published>2022-11-06T08:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-06T08:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/06/vadacurry-in-hotel-archana-bhavan-in-sithalapakkam-is-good</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/06/vadacurry-in-hotel-archana-bhavan-in-sithalapakkam-is-good.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeig3ntb2jinitbxrihvgqkmf6ftehedzf3jpo4wc56dh426kg2vsce/dosai_vadacurry.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You turn left from the Sithalapakkam Panchayat office (the petrol bunk bend) and head towards Shankarapuram, you will see a hotel called Archana Bhavan. That hotel is not good for dining, it has got not fully closed space, you need to dine almost on platform. The ambience in front of the hotel is also not good. Dog and cow shit littered before the hotel and none bothers to keep it clean. I have seen dirty pigs grazing just meters away from the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no proper running water wash basin in the hotel, you will see a sink on the platform, near that a bucket containing dirty water with food particles floating in it and a tumbler near it, that’s the water they give you to wash hands. Once I went there to dine, and seeing this I returned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is good however is their vadacurry if you get parcel of it, it costs ₹20/-. It’s nice oily and tasty. I have tried their idyappams with their vadacurry, it’s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Slack is a distraction</title><link href="/2022/11/01/slack-is-a-distraction.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Slack is a distraction" /><published>2022-11-01T19:08:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-01T19:08:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/01/slack-is-a-distraction</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/01/slack-is-a-distraction.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://logos-world.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/Slack-Logo-2019-present.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I had to do a ticket in office today, I started it and within two hours I finished it. This work was estimated for a week or more. I couldn’t believe what had happened. I submitted a  pull request, deployed code to our testing server and only in mid day I realized I had never turned on Slack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Slack or any other messenger is turned on you are conscious about it. You expect someone to ping, this anticipation slows you down, drains some part of your cognition. When someone pings your attention moves, and rather than check the ping, you also check other channels and stuff. Then your brain stars to think in various pathways, your concentration is drawn out away from solving the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I turned on Slack, there was a pull request comment, though it was minor I think I took kind of 4 hours because I was looking at messages and interacting etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If one has to be productive, I strongly recommend turning off Slack, Zulip, Rocket Chat, Telegram, WhatsApp or any other messenger, finish your task and then check distraction stuff in your slack time. But yes this does not work for all, many of you are paid to respond to distractions you get professionally, but for those who can be productive, be productive.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Coimbatore blast, different perspectives</title><link href="/2022/10/29/coimbatore-blast-different-perspectives.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coimbatore blast, different perspectives" /><published>2022-10-29T23:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-10-29T23:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/10/29/coimbatore-blast-different-perspectives</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/10/29/coimbatore-blast-different-perspectives.html">&lt;p&gt;Few days ago there was a blast in Coimbatore. The case has been moved to NIA for investigation. In this journal I document what I think different people feel about this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;muslims&quot;&gt;Muslims&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muslim’s are nervous. This is the second time that city is being attacked by Islamic terror. They do fear being demonized as there are lots of terror activities in the name of Islam in India. BJP is one step closer to demonizing them, just like Hitler demonized and exterminated Jews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muslims as people are harmless, but as far as I know, I think Quoran says that one day Rome and India will be ruled by Islam. So they are caught in trap. Islam doesn’t allow Muslims to question it, at the same time they do not have the power to convert entire India to Islam right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dmk&quot;&gt;DMK&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first Islamic attack on Coimbatore was by Ul Uma, when Karunanidhi was in power. I think DMK never got foothold of the city after that attack, now DMK seems to make inroads into Coimbatore and this happens.  DMK needs Muslim vote banks and is a coward party to take action against them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK has always been soft on terror. Rajiv Gandhi was killed here in Tamil Nadu. A blast took place when L.K.Advani visited here. All wrong things happened in DMK rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking at DMK’s move, I feel they gave the case to NIA because the state was coward to investigate and was afraid that it would offend Muslim vote bank. This is not how a leader or leadership behaves. Leader is a one that stands by truth all times. If NIA arrests Muslims, DMK could project is as an anti-Islamic move by the BJP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bjp&quot;&gt;BJP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no doubt that BJP is a Hindu terror group. They are destined to bring shame to all Hindu’s around the world just like the Taliban and ISIS brought and are bringing shame to all Muslims on this planet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For BJP this blast is a good inroad for their effort to demonize Muslims, to put a perspective that Tamil Nadu is an unsafe place to live, and they are right, it looks Tamil Nadu is unsafe. BJP are already behaving like they are the opposition party, and they might want to rake up anti-Muslim sentiment to gain inroads here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;i&quot;&gt;I&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a rationalist I am thrilled. I have always advocated religion or any strong sentiment is a drug, and it makes you do crazy things. For me all religions must eliminated. Religion has costed lot to India, it has broken our country into 3 parts already and is doing damage every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a nationalist I am worried that ISIS is gaining foothold in Tamil Nadu, and all what DMK want’s to do is to loot for 5 years and go out of power, or bring Udhayanidhi to power if we are foolish enough. I also see that DMK is no longer a rationalist and atheistic party and has lost its meaning. All it wants to do is make few families rich.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also see this attack on Tamil Nadu as a victory to Arabic nations. Stalin visited Arabia recently, are his Arab friends telling him to ignore terror activities in Tamil Nadu in return to make his family rich? I am not sure. Tamil Nadu is one of the farthest states from Arabia and Pakistan, and they are able to strike us here at their will and ease. India is a coward nation, unlike Israel, India would watch its people suffer under Pakistan and Arabs killing than take concrete action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I hope people will wake up to religious terrorism and will become Atheists, think rationally, and become peaceful while at the same time eliminating invaders.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Few days ago there was a blast in Coimbatore. The case has been moved to NIA for investigation. In this journal I document what I think different people feel about this case.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why do people buy gold?</title><link href="/2022/09/29/why-do-people-buy-gold.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why do people buy gold?" /><published>2022-09-29T01:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-09-29T01:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/09/29/why-do-people-buy-gold</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/09/29/why-do-people-buy-gold.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s1.ibtimes.com/sites/www.ibtimes.com/files/styles/full/public/2018/11/21/gold-2959361920.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was and am still really confused by gold. Why do people buy it? It’s literally a useless metal unless you want to create an inert surface or if you want to wire circuits. Just like Lenin said, gold is good for building toilets, or it may not even be good for that as silver is more bacterial resistant than gold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my friend still lives in village and makes trips to Chennai every year, and gold is his purchase too. I asked him why he buys it regularly, and what he said baffled me. He said women think gold is beautiful. What? I couldn’t believe it. It’s such a negative investment, and people do it just because someone feels it’s beautiful? It defied all my senses, but he held to his point. He didn’t claim what he said was logical, but his claim was he is okay with the continuation of peace in his family despite the high financial burden that he had to endure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really felt sorry for him. For a person who thinks, I just have a question. There are plenty of ways to create more money from money. Let’s say you buy pure 24-carat gold, can you trade it the next year and buy even more gold? Think people think. Life is not about amassing stuff you want like crazy till you die. I feel life is, say if you have 200 hours of free time the last year, you must have at least 220 hours of quality free time this year. It should compound at the rate of 10 percent till one day you are so much financially interdependent that there is no need to work. You may work, but you do it because you want to, but not because you have to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are not achieving that goal, I truly feel one is a fool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;arguing-from-the-point-of-science&quot;&gt;Arguing from the point of science&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once people felt insulted in Napoleon’s dining table when their cutlery was not made with most expensive metal of that time. Today we call that metal Aluminum. Today it’s used to make utensils for prisoners because it’s so cheap. Gold is like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We humans at the max only mined down to a kilometer under the Earth. Gold is denser, as our tech improves, robots can go further down and bring us more gold. We will park asteroids in our orbit which contains more gold than mined ever by humanity. Engineered bacteria and nanobots will concentrate out gold from seawater.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s only a matter of decades or at max a century that gold becomes plentiful and worthless.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Don’t buy AGARO Regal Plus Upright Vacuum Cleaner</title><link href="/2022/09/05/don-t-buy-agaro-regal-plus-upright-vacuum-cleaner.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Don&apos;t buy AGARO Regal Plus Upright Vacuum Cleaner" /><published>2022-09-05T15:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-09-05T15:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/09/05/don-t-buy-agaro-regal-plus-upright-vacuum-cleaner</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/09/05/don-t-buy-agaro-regal-plus-upright-vacuum-cleaner.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeierwhc4dhxxxf5snurix2dwmsidh2oebp7djtol2iponfkywuu2ie.ipfs.dweb.link/Screen%20Recording%202022-09-05%20at%201.42.40%20PM.mov &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I wish I ran a tea and bonda shop</title><link href="/2022/09/01/i-wish-i-ran-a-tea-and-bonda-shop.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I wish I ran a tea and bonda shop" /><published>2022-09-01T13:12:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-09-01T13:12:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/09/01/i-wish-i-ran-a-tea-and-bonda-shop</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/09/01/i-wish-i-ran-a-tea-and-bonda-shop.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeifxsojhvny3hc4cidneaqei5knuu6vtxz3gxd4pcabujssbdzh3pm.ipfs.dweb.link/indian-street-foods-spicy-vegan-samosa-tea-fried-served-milk-masla-chai-exotic-recipes-155782777.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a professional coder. I think after long time I have found a right place to work. I feel like I am in a team manged by a person who knows to code, who had coded in the past and may be codes even today. I feel like I work under a person who understands programmers brain, and protects us. Yet sometimes I feel like I open up a tea and bonda shop and quit coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modern software is a complex system. We use Ruby in which we can accomplish a lot with few lines code, say compared to say C++ or Java, yet the systems I code have tens and thousands of lines. These days we believe that if we name our functions and variables right we can avoid comments altogether, and we still have a system where we need to deliver code in fixed time. These things though seen separately looks very innocent, but when combined breaks things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I had to code a feature, I was trying to read code and understand it, I was looking at deadline and I understood and gave a pull request, and I was confident. Turns out my understanding was wrong. Though variables were named and functions were named in a good way, when trying to read it in a given time it did not convey the entire information. I tapped into a API, but I should have tapped into deeper and low level API’s. I understood all these after a call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might ask why not discuss with others before coding a thing. It’s like this we coders do not disturb others unnecessarily. Thinking is costly and drains energy. If thought is disturbed, it takes time to bring it back in, it takes time to match it with trail of code you were following. So we don’t disturb others, and in that process we don’t want our trail of thought to be disturbed too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything is unique when you take up a new issue in programming, it’s like you are writing new poetry, or imagining a new picture to draw every time. That too you are doing it to match the thought of your customer, who apparently places time restriction to finish it. Errors do happen. Fortunately the place where I work, its seems to be tolerated more, but believe me, compared to this place, I have worked in places enriched with politics, corporatism, and places filled with people who do not know a thing about coding and control us. Its hell compared to my present client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But when deadline slips, no matter how tolerant your client is or not, it hurts. It’s then when I think of having a tea and bonda shop somewhere. The recipe for tea, bonda, samosa doesn’t change. Rather than a dozen comments for one pull request, maybe you will have one guy in a hundred complaining about your tea, bonda, samosa or vadai. If I own the shop, I am legally answerable to none. But ya I live in Tamilnadu, India where rowdies can rampage my shop, police could ask bribes and I won’t be able to say ‘no’, and must go to bed with some guilt after paying bribes. But at least every situation is not new, unique, that should be studied and understood and should be derived on tine estimate that none seems to get right in the history of programming.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>