<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-06T20:21:24+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Let’s de-grave marina</title><link href="/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Let&apos;s de-grave marina" /><published>2023-01-06T20:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-06T20:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3c/Chennai_Marina_beach_panorama1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am shocked by Stalin’s announcement of massive 80 crore waste to decorate Karunadhi’s grave with a massive statue of a pen on an artificial island. 80 crores is massive money. It could be given to 800 people to start very small business, even if 1% of them succeed, it will be good. But what good does it do decorating a grave?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I truly wonder what gives right to these dravidian parties to put their dead bodies in Marina? It’s a beach, it belongs to people, more than us, it belongs to all nature. We have converted it into a graveyard and have put artificial structures there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A leader might be needed for a society (of people who cannot think well, for a society that could think will be leader less), but I wonder what’s the big thing in having a rotting corpse below a huge concrete structure? It looks childish and silly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the thing that outrages me is that we have mausoleum for a proven criminal Jayalaitha in Marina, and almost none opposes it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly think a person should be remembered for what he had done. Today I know English and interact with the world, thanks to Annadurai. I am an atheist and think rationally, and don’t encourage building temples, mosques, churches and mausoleum, thanks to Periyaar. I don’t remember these people because I saw their graves, but the good things that they have done to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember Abdul Kalaam not because of his grave, but he protected me from invaders, helped our nation become a space power. I don’t even know where his grave is, though I do know they have built one for him. I remember Kamaraj for his honesty and, his ability not to build grave for his mom even though he was a powerful chief minister of Tamilnadu. I don’t know where Kamaraj is burried, I don’t even know if he was cremated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst thing is that the 80 crores that Stalin wants to spend on decorating his dad’s grave is our hard-earned money. It’s not from Red Giant’s or G-squares or some binaami’s loot. I really wonder what gives the right for these DMK and ADMK to waste our money on dead bodies like this? May be if they earned honestly they would know worth of money and spend it better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe we people are powerless, coward, and have too much to lose now by protesting against dravidian rule, but I feel ultimately we must de-grave Marina. All these bodies should be taken out, put somewhere else, beach should be given back to people to walk, turtles to reproduce, crabs to crawl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage the reader to talk about this loot going on in Tamilnadu. I encourage one to think about the good ways of using money than wasting it on dead matter. I wish you would would remeber this blog when you vote again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Think like a farmer</title><link href="/2023/01/06/think-like-a-farmer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Think like a farmer" /><published>2023-01-06T09:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-06T09:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/06/think-like-a-farmer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/06/think-like-a-farmer.html">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t shout at the crops.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t blame the crop for not growing fast enough.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t uproot crops before they’ve had a chance to grow.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choose the best plants for the soil.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Irrigate and fertilize.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove weeds.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remember you will have good seasons and bad seasons- you can’t control the weather only be prepared for it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Don’t shout at the crops. Don’t blame the crop for not growing fast enough. Don’t uproot crops before they’ve had a chance to grow. Choose the best plants for the soil. Irrigate and fertilize. Remove weeds. Remember you will have good seasons and bad seasons- you can’t control the weather only be prepared for it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Need freshers for a web tech company</title><link href="/2022/12/30/need-freshers-for-a-web-tech-company.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Need freshers for a web tech company" /><published>2022-12-30T10:30:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-30T10:30:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/30/need-freshers-for-a-web-tech-company</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/30/need-freshers-for-a-web-tech-company.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello All,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a web developer for more than 15 years, currently I am serving a client who seems not to treat his employees bad. This is very rare in tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The product we are working on need’s lot of people to maintain, upgrade and compete. So we are open for freshers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;qualification&quot;&gt;Qualification&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You must be an Indian citizen.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You need to love computers and enjoy working with them.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should have self belief.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should know any programming language. You must feel you are good at it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The job is fully remote, so if you are an office seeking person, sorry.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You must have a good internet connection.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;selection-process&quot;&gt;Selection Process&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I (Karthikeyan) will have a word with you, see if you are good. I will give you a small exercise which you need to complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once done, company name will be revealed, and you will be put in touch with my boss who will initiate the official process of trying to take you in with further rounds of interviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send your resume via Whatapp, Signal or Telegram (@mindaslab) to +91 8428050777. If you want to mail, mail it to mindaslab@protonmail.com, but I rarely check emails these days, so give me a ring after you send it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-the-job-be-like&quot;&gt;What The Job Be Like&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You will be given the necessary gear to start coding (I think it will just be a Mac Pro).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You will be thought to how to build web pages and turn them into enterprise apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t want to go into details as there are lot’s of things you will learn.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello All,</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">7 Japanese Philosophies</title><link href="/2022/12/28/7-japanese-philosophies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="7 Japanese Philosophies" /><published>2022-12-28T20:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-28T20:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/28/7-japanese-philosophies</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/28/7-japanese-philosophies.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-oubaitori&quot;&gt;1. OUBAITORI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never compare yourself.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone blossoms in their own time in different ways. Don’t judge yourself by someone else’s path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-kaizen&quot;&gt;2. KAIZEN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuously improve.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Constantly strive to improve across all areas of your life. Small changes accumulate and make all the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-wabi-sabi&quot;&gt;3. WABI-SABI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embrace Imperfection.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing lasts, nothing is complete. Accept your own flaws and those of others. Find beauty in imperfection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-gaman&quot;&gt;4. GAMAN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have dignity during duress.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard times need to b e met with emotional maturity and self-control. We need patience, perseverance, tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-ikigai&quot;&gt;5. IKIGAI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Know your reason for being.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Define the reason you get up in the morning. Make ti something you are good at passionate about, and that the world needs. THIS is meaning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-shikita-ga-nai&quot;&gt;6. SHIKITA GA NAI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accept and let go.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things simply aren’t within our control. Accept what you cannot change, and move on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-shu-ha-ri&quot;&gt;7. SHU-HA-RI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn, Experiment, Innovate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“When the student is ready the teacher will appear.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;When the student is truly ready… The teacher will Disappear”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Tao Te Ching&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a way of thinking about how to learn and master a technique. There
are 3 stages to acquiring knowledge:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shu:&lt;/strong&gt; Learn the basics by following the teaching of one master. Imitating the work of great masters also falls in this stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ha:&lt;/strong&gt; Start experimenting, learn from masters, and integrate the learning into the practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ri:&lt;/strong&gt; This stage focuses on innovation and adapting the learning to different
situations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">1. OUBAITORI</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dall-E generated mascot</title><link href="/2022/12/23/dall-e-generated-mascot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dall-E generated mascot" /><published>2022-12-23T12:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-23T12:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/23/dall-e-generated-mascot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/23/dall-e-generated-mascot.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreic6gajm63qaraepcvkoh4mb7tn3nrk7ppy72prr5binri2f54iuey.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Dall-E generated pig mascot.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designers do cost, sometimes even more than developers. Designing is a very creative process. Certainly web pages designed by me sucks, compared to one done by designer. Sometimes I need to shell out a lot if I am doing my personal open source project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to write a Personal Micro Blog application to learn Clojure which I named as pig. I have generated a &lt;a href=&quot;https://codeberg.org/pig&quot;&gt;codeberg project&lt;/a&gt; here. I wanted a cute baby pig as mascot. I asked designer and he gave me his budget, it was big. I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://openai.com/dall-e-2/&quot;&gt;Dall-E&lt;/a&gt; to generate the mascot. I used an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.upscale.media/&quot;&gt;A.I tool to upscale the image&lt;/a&gt;, and I used A.I to remove background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I gave the cute pig mascot to my designer to make it into a sticker which you can see in this blog above. I think I reduced designing cost by 70% this time, and I am very happy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Dall-E generated pig mascot.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">IQ of BJP vote bank</title><link href="/2022/12/10/iq-of-bjp-vote-bank.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IQ of BJP vote bank" /><published>2022-12-10T16:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-10T16:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/10/iq-of-bjp-vote-bank</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/10/iq-of-bjp-vote-bank.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeih3q2q22rkfn7fbvvuxwt6o6riuz7ktxw7z7jsagpjenoqvfnp74m.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dogs, bloody dogs</title><link href="/2022/12/10/dogs-bloody-dogs.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dogs, bloody dogs" /><published>2022-12-10T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-10T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/10/dogs-bloody-dogs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/10/dogs-bloody-dogs.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeihlk7byguxuhxxthfszgechhiv3l3mv6kg7jt5vma6zmexfrmmsfu.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I see a guy opposite to my home across the water logged empty ground feeding stray dogs. Frankly I would be very happy if he sees his children die before him and he one day vomits blood and die. He must be dead on the road, the same hungry dogs he fed must feast on his meat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday gone, I had to concentrate on work, but from morning 4AM, a stray dog was barking right outside my home at the top of its voice, I couldn’t sleep. Thankfully my client is very liberal, so I tried to have breakfast, did some minor work, had some lunch and tried to catch sleep, then my neighbor’s dogs started to bark. I cursed my neighbor’s too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bloody stray dog disturbed my sleep again on Monday night and even on Tuesday I was unable to do the work. I don’t know where I missed out due to lack of concentration, but I was thinking Thursday wad Wednesday and I missed out on a meeting. I felt so bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not against dogs, have them, feed them. But if they drop shit on road pick it up and take it home. Such an eyesore and disease spreading they are. You have to watch the dog shit or concentrate on traffic or pedestrian’s while traveling? Dog owners and lovers please answer this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you love dogs, have them in a sound-proof room where they can bark all the hell out, if you want to be in that room so that you can listen to the music you love that’s made by your dog, none objects, but letting it disturb your neighbor’s is barbaric and uncultured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreihkwj77nrjq7apxmiwkwqilnfnpjsiisgdnzs4ib623gvzu3na7si.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do not take dogs walks outside because it has no toilet sense, it shits out, and you won’t pick that treasure of yours up and take it to your home and lick it, instead you will leave it there. Your dog will urinate on lampposts and dustbins, and you won’t wash it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being such irresponsible human who just cares about you and your dog, what’s the use of your existence? Why you must have family and kids? If you have why should your kids survive with such a genetic defect you have? Why you shouldn’t watch your kids die thus feel bit better that the Earth is bit more purified? Why those indiscipline dogs you fed, feed on your carcass when you drop dead vomiting blood on street? Maybe some of those dogs might even urinate on your dead body proving their loyalty to you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What lack of sleep can do to you</title><link href="/2022/12/05/what-lack-of-sleep-can-do-to-you.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What lack of sleep can do to you" /><published>2022-12-05T17:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-05T17:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/05/what-lack-of-sleep-can-do-to-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/05/what-lack-of-sleep-can-do-to-you.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeidtza47heaiwrwzhioxy33vnupdycd2afmm4tyqw7lbsj662v3bku/lack_of_sleep.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Need for Tamil Professional Examination</title><link href="/2022/12/03/need-for-tamil-professional-examination.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Need for Tamil Professional Examination" /><published>2022-12-03T16:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-03T16:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/03/need-for-tamil-professional-examination</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/03/need-for-tamil-professional-examination.html">&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I went to hotel named Balaji Bhavan in Sithalapakkam, none except two were there in the hotel (excluding two customers who were sitting like zombies), some lady was doing some work and at the counter there was this guy. I asked for a kothu parotta parcel and he said “kothu parotta”, the way he said it confirmed he was from north India. I wanted to ask what’s there in their hotel’s menu, so I asked it, and he said “kothu parotta”. I asked him what all items / dishes he had, he said “kothu parotta”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got fed up and started walking out of the hotel and said cancel it, he said “kothu parotta ready”, I walked out any way wondering how kothu parotta could be ready within two minutes. It’s annoying with these people now days, though I know Hindi, I am a Tamil and my Hindi did not kick in, these northern people have an illusion that everywhere in India Hindi is spoken, they come here uneducated and irritate us. It’s great that Tamilnadu is providing work for these people and is contributing to the uplifting of North India, but at the same time our government should ensure these people are educated to serve us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plan is this, just like IELTS, we must have Tamil Professional Examination that every worker in Tamilnadu should take. Its syllabus should contain practical Tamil and must train people speak and write fluently. Imagine for example, how good it will be if doctors write medicine names in Tamil and medicine comes with Tamil labels in them? The syllabus should contain basic Tamil grammar and history, so that these workers who should take it by law to work in our land can speak fluently with us and serve us better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite dynastic politics and deep-rooted corruption that erode us, Tamils are hard workers, and we are developing. We are the most urbanized state in India, our economy too is diverse, we have plan to reach 1 trillion $ economy, and it’s high time we make our work force work smooth with us.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yesterday I went to hotel named Balaji Bhavan in Sithalapakkam, none except two were there in the hotel (excluding two customers who were sitting like zombies), some lady was doing some work and at the counter there was this guy. I asked for a kothu parotta parcel and he said “kothu parotta”, the way he said it confirmed he was from north India. I wanted to ask what’s there in their hotel’s menu, so I asked it, and he said “kothu parotta”. I asked him what all items / dishes he had, he said “kothu parotta”.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Does Coimbatore contain high number of psychopaths?</title><link href="/2022/11/28/does-coimbatore-contain-high-number-of-psychopaths.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Does Coimbatore contain high number of psychopaths?" /><published>2022-11-28T20:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-28T20:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/28/does-coimbatore-contain-high-number-of-psychopaths</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/28/does-coimbatore-contain-high-number-of-psychopaths.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/CHIL_SEZ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was taking a walk today when I remembered this phone conversation in which a Coimbatore guy was saying something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“My wife and her father had to take medicine to keep them mentally stable, this illness comes with high intelligence.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just then I was reminded how my life was tormented by people in Coimbatore belt. It was in a company called Z**ec where I was a project manager, another woman was also a project manager, she was from Coimbatore. She knew nothing about I.T and code, but lusted for power, she was like Nandhini in Ponniyin Selvan, I think life hurts her very much, possibly she did not like her marriage. She was highly sociable person, but she behaved like a psycho. I would give my team member a task, only to see that he had been seduced by her to complete her task. I was shocked and called her, and she threatened me to book me in harassing case. I was shocked a bit, but then I gained all my strength, told her to proceed, and I took it as my personal mission to work against her underground and looks like it paid off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that same company there was an old jalra guy to the management who was a true psychopath, who enjoyed putting grief into people, and he was this evil woman’s partner. This evil woman was from Coimbatore, I do suspect this evil guy was also from Coimbatore, but I am not sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that same company I met a great guy, who workers praised as a great manager, we ended up forming our own company, but guess what, think about one year of operation that guys started to shout at people like a mad dog. He shouted at me too for no reason. None of us could get it, he was from Salem, not Coimbatore. I don’t know Tamilnadu map, but I wouldn’t be surprised if Salem was near to Coimbatore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my girlfriend’s was near Coimbatore, and she behaved like she loved me and denied it, I wish she is happy now, but her dad’s sister was mentally unstable and did commit suicide. She herself did want to commit suicide once, and I have to talk to her for days to bring her out of it. I am happy I did not end up marrying her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As though I had committed a lot of sin, this second Coimbatore girlfriend loved me and wanted to marry me, but she was too afraid of her family and family pride, she got married to a guy which her family chose, later I heard that she believed if my love was true, she expected me to enter tha marriage hall, stopped that marriage and rescue her, since it did not happen she concluded our love was false 🤦🤦🤦🤦&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way at least someone thought I was like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ex36LeMLqas?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But ya, one has to be psychopath equating a tech guy with a rowdy. May be only Coimbatore girls can do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Coimbatore person known to me bought a home in Bangalore, he was close to me and asked me to visit for the house-warming, I refused because in those days getting a railway ticket was not easy, I am unsure what’s the status these days, I hated bus travel as I got almost no sleep in buses, and Aircraft when booked at last minute will be expensive. Even though I considered him as my brother, he seems to have taken my ‘No’ as something big. He knew a senior Coimbatore guy who could pressure me up, so the senior guy called me and told me to attend the function, I still said ‘No’, how can a new call change this universe? The senior guy stated behaving like a mad baby and was behaving in an unbelievable way. That senior guys sister was a mad person, she too committed suicide. I thought this guys was mad and so did not take him seriously, but these people worked to dislodge something’s in my life &amp;amp; economics which I will never forgive. I wish they rot in hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my software teams, I do find Coimbatore people behaving erratic many times. I don’t know if it’s my bias, or it’s the truth. I do know that Coimbatore contains lot’s of CEO’s and business leaders. Studies have shown that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/08/the-science-behind-why-so-many-successful-millionaires-are-psychopaths-and-why-it-doesnt-have-to-be-a-bad-thing.html&quot;&gt;high percentage of business leaders are psychopaths&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Tamilnadu we see that in Pollachi and Coimbatore, women are highly disregarded and disrespected. I think those are the rape capitals of our Tamilnadu if not India. Coimbatore is a place where BJP is strong and wins regularly. If you look at Tamilandu governor, H.Raja of BJP, Tamil Isai Sounderajan, Annamali, Modi, what names comes to your mind? Ho many internationally renowned intellectuals you have in Congress, how many are there in BJP?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you seen any sane leader ordering to shoot his own people? Or claiming he had no knowledge of massacare that happened in the land he rules, and only through news he knew it? We had a Chief minister from Edapaadi who did it, I think those who protested against Vedanta’s copper factory were shot. I think Edapaadi is in Pollachi belt. Once again I could be wrong, but I do consider EPS a mild psycho. He might not be as corrupt as the Karunanidhi family, but he might be a psychopath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would be very interested if any reader of this blog can come up with data, proving or disproving my hypothesis. I am really lazy to dig in and find out which kind of people are admitted in Mental hospitals and from which region they are from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason I find people of Madurai highly mentally stable, and they have ability to put long term plans. People who are born and brought up in Chennai are highly professionals. Once again I would like some on to prove it or disprove it with data. Till then this blog is just a rant. Maybe we might find the source of high psychopathic illness, and maybe we can do something to avoid and cure it, thus making Tamilnadu better.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>