<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-09-26T19:02:58+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Man with a woman</title><link href="/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Man with a woman" /><published>2019-09-26T19:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-26T19:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.wallpapers13.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/Sunset-romantic-couple-in-an-embrace-love-Wallpaper-HD-915x515.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have found this annoying trend, a man drives his car is okay, but when he is with his family and kids his driving is weird and confused, just like his life is. He goes slow even when the road is fast, brakes sudden, seems to have no aim and destination, just like a married man behaves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am beginning to wonder if a man with a woman is just like man with a liquor bottle. Being with a woman increases dopamine level just like being with liquor bottle. A man with them becomes aimless compared to the external world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more dangerous is, a man to get a bottle of liquor will do what ever he wants, even if it’s evil, similarly a man who wants to get a woman will do what ever he wants, even it means evil to the very woman he wants to have. Think about the Pollachi incident for women, think about many petty crimes that happen so that one can drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a man is with liquor or with a woman, will act strange too. Try disturbing a drunk. Look at all those people making illegal money via bribes and other stuff. Mostly they have a family story which to their mind gives them the right to break the law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of Karunanidhi, what he has done to us just because he wanted to fuck his wife’s! His son is leader of the party as though there is none else who could lead, his grandson is next in line so that Stalin can be with his wife. Though not proven its gossiped that their family is #1 in looting this country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So…. Have pity on these people. Evolution has created men to crave for women. Given a chance we all men will have as many women as we could, and as much liquor or any kind of dope we could. But we have a brain powerful enough to think, to put ourselves into the view of others. It’s as simple a person who does not want to eat by killing a conscious life just because he himself does not want to be cut up and knows the pain it causes. So think, even if you are a man with a woman or liquor, try acting like an evolved man, and not like an ape. Know that you are part of this huge universe and not just clam contained in a shell called family. It’s difficult to think broad for something that has evolved out of a baboon, but it’s possible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mistrust In Eastern Cultures</title><link href="/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mistrust In Eastern Cultures" /><published>2019-09-23T08:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-23T08:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures.html">&lt;p&gt;The Gulf War, though having one of the best armies in the middle east Iraq lost, and it lost badly. It did to USA the second time, and once again it lost very badly. The Arabs tried to conquer Israel, a tiny nation that had nothing and they lost, and they lost it bad. Long ago in Tamilnadu, despite being brave and having a disciplined military, the Maruthu bothers lost to the British. China lost to western powers during the Opium wars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question here is why? Why do people who are in the East loose to people who are in the West? One reason I can think of is that there is an element of mistrust in the east. Sadam does not trust his generals for the fear that he will be ousted by them. The Arab countries though they are all Islamic nations, they are deeply divided into Wahabi, Shia Islam and so on. During the Maruthu era in Tamilnadu, the Paalayam rulers were in a power struggle and deeply mistrusted each others. All this aided enemy victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did find it recently in the people I opposed, I expected a logical good fight, a debate of ideas, but the other side crumbled. They then I found out deeply mistrusted the people who in-fact came to their aid. They did not respect fellow humans. I, filled with western ideas had an open mind, and they could not deal with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We might think of Tamil villages a good place to live, may be it is, but people over there mistrust their neighbors and envy them. A neighbor will go into deep state of depression, hate and envy if one has converted a thatched roof house to one with tiles. He, the neighbor, will do all he can to spread a bad word about him, how that one earned in an illegal way and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just in Tamils, I find this deep sense of mistrust in Kerala people too. For a Keralite family is important. If a family is headed by a fool, then all the people in family are foolish too. Let’s say that a girl is a Hindu and she falls in love with a muslim, or say she is a feminist and wants to goto Aiyappan temple, that’s it, if the family head is offended, like goats almost all people in the family will be offended and mistrust the girl. Her life is finished. Or she must listen to the family head and mistrust a muslim boy proposing to her. This type of stupidity I find, makes Malayali’s deeply divided and unprogressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we in East must be open to ideas, listen to others and try starting to trust people. Yes some trust might fail, some might betray you, but unless one knows that you trust him and have given the full freedom to work, he or she cannot work for you 100% and be productive.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Gulf War, though having one of the best armies in the middle east Iraq lost, and it lost badly. It did to USA the second time, and once again it lost very badly. The Arabs tried to conquer Israel, a tiny nation that had nothing and they lost, and they lost it bad. Long ago in Tamilnadu, despite being brave and having a disciplined military, the Maruthu bothers lost to the British. China lost to western powers during the Opium wars.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Good Woman Driver</title><link href="/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Good Woman Driver" /><published>2019-09-14T08:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-14T08:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver.html">&lt;p&gt;Yesterday as usual around 8PM I think I was driving home from office. The roads I drive are quite dangerous, there are lots and lots of potholes, now someone has filled some of them with sand and seems to have compacted them a bit well,  plus you have got these people, Chennai people who do not give a damn about traffic rules. To add to that the street lighting would be awful, most of them would have their headlights turned high beam, sometimes against those  bright headlights it would be difficult to see the roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving in Chennai is not just looking at the road and driving. None follows rules here, some one would cut before you. Overtake you without warning, from the opposite side a scooter or a fast car would over take a tanker despite knowing that it would cause a lot of discomfort to you. You must look at the road, you must look at the eyes, hands, wheels of other vehicles too to determine their next move and drive by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add to the woes you have this Road Transport Officers who are perverts, they make it difficult for men to get license, so there are men who bribe them and get their license and being a pervert they grant license to woman just like that. Because of this people who go in car’s like me, when we spot a woman driver on bike we tend to keep distance. Their driving seems shit, their vehicle could change direction any time, sway from one side of the road to other, brake and so on. You need to get a man drunk to do that feat, woman do it just like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the matters worst, if you hit a woman, or a bike with a kid on it, or even a bike with a family driven by man, you will be blamed for it no matter who has made the mistake. Woman, kids and family are like cows in India, they can do what ever they want. Cows here shit and urinate on roads, drop their dung, stand on the road unmoving and obstructing traffic and none bothers about them or even complain. If you hit them or shoo away, our priminsters Hindu men, will come out drag you out and beat you, because you have abused the Hindu Goddess Lakshmi. These people of so found of cows, one of their favorite drink is cows urine, it like Coca-Cola here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay with all these in mind, yesterday I was driving behind a woman who was on a blue scooter. Definitely I thought she was a crap driver. She was wearing a red saree, black border with golden silk threads in the black woven into intricate pattern. If she did something stupid and I hit her, possibly she was having an auspicious occasion, and hence she was wearing a rich dress, the people would gather around and blame me like hell. I tried to over take and clear her off my mind, but the bad roads and opposing traffic did not permit that. I maintained my distance from her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After sometime I notices something strange. Unlike many woman on road, she did not make a mistake, she was driving perfect. She had a blue helmet too that matched her color of her bike. ‘Woman thinking about road safety? Wow!’ I thought. But I persisted, after nearly 5 minutes and 3 kilometers of this tense follow up I was able to over take her. Thank fucking God, I raced away, and no more woman scooterist I saw ahead of me from then on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roads filled with crap woman driver, I must clap for this one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yesterday as usual around 8PM I think I was driving home from office. The roads I drive are quite dangerous, there are lots and lots of potholes, now someone has filled some of them with sand and seems to have compacted them a bit well, plus you have got these people, Chennai people who do not give a damn about traffic rules. To add to that the street lighting would be awful, most of them would have their headlights turned high beam, sometimes against those bright headlights it would be difficult to see the roads.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Jesus won’t cut in, in India</title><link href="/christianity/religion/india/2019/09/02/why-jesus-won-t-cut-in-in-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Jesus won't cut in, in India" /><published>2019-09-02T20:41:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-02T20:41:00+05:30</updated><id>/christianity/religion/india/2019/09/02/why-jesus-won-t-cut-in-in-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/christianity/religion/india/2019/09/02/why-jesus-won-t-cut-in-in-india.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/f-qodKHzei4/maxresdefault.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story of Jesus, isn’t it so wonderful. God fucks Mary, and some innocent idiot marries her because God cannot take care of the women he fucks, and then their son is born and it endures pain to wipe out the sins of man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The theme of the story is self sacrifice, how the son of God sacrificed himself for others. And its the same story that’s told to Hindus and Indians. Were we moved? Mostly not. The ignorant believe in everything, we can do nothing about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why many religions in India won’t believe in Jesus is because many religions have many many messengers of God. Saadhu’s they are called. Over here you don’t be to be born to a whore fucked by God to reach God and make sacrifice for humanity. In fact many son’s and daughters of God have died doing bad stuff, and in vain due to their evil karma. Over here there are many ways to reach God. One is by doing good deeds, and other is by doing no deed at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saadhu’s do no deed. By the time I finished writing this blog may be 10 to 100 saadhu’s would have died all around India praying for the well being of not just the humanity, earth, the solar system, but praying for the well being of the universe / everything as a whole. Unlike the life of Jesus where he must be dragged on and then forced to make a sacrifice, these saadhu’s voluntarily sacrifice themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People here have seen many attain jeeva samadhi in a voluntary way every year, and a story of just one sacrificing himself for the humanity which is nothing but an insignificant spec in this vast universe will looks funny to Hindus and other religions here. Its only due to the existence of ignorant Hindus and mostly people who wish to switch sides for money, this so called Christianity which is a crap compared to religions here has penetrated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Rationalist Like Buddhism</title><link href="/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Rationalist Like Buddhism" /><published>2019-08-25T11:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-25T11:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_1.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One would see rationalist talk ill about almost all religions, but not much against Buddhism. It would look counter intuitive, rationalists are here to slam all religious practices, and why not they slam Buddhism so much? Buddhism was slammed, that too by a rationalist nation China. By the time it slammed Buddhism, this religion had become impure, and was well diverged from in initial teachings. Yes one has the right to be stupid and follow Tibetian Buddhism, but China thought its the duty of the state to teach rationalism to the people and bring them out of their stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buddhism has lot of belief that are untrue. They believe in previous and past life, they believe in Karma which is  a kind of accounting system that keeps track of ones good and bad deeds and assigns a score (very similar to loyalty score assigned by China to every citizen), Buddhist believe in spirits and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Buddhists have got many things wrong, they had invested a lot in psychological studies and had got one thing right. That is they figured out that ones happiness and sadness is not the function of external world, but lies within ones brain. Its very true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a man who has a corrosive family, none in his family respect him and they just abuse him. Just imagine Leo Tolstoy, the world knows how his family abused him. So imagine a man like him and he is very sad because of his family. Now imagine he goes to  a liquor shop and drinks. His wife, children and relatives are the same, but he finds his sadness disappears and he starts to feel a kind of forgetfulness and happiness. I wonder Tolstoy was a drunk, but writing gave him happiness despite everything around him was pulling him down. As you see from this example these people are able to ignore the sadness and are able to generate happiness. That’s what Buddhism says, it says you r feelings can be detached from the world around you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People believed that ones happiness and sadness was controlled by God, or some supernatural forces, but Buddhism said that one can manufacture these feelings in ones mind. A trained Buddhist can choose to become sad when he wants to, and can become happy when he wants to. He can observe and comment and debate about himself, a trait very very few in humanity have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ever God is knocked off, blind faith is shut down, we rationalist are happy and feel that humanity is one step closer to the truth, and hence we love Buddhism despite all its shortcomings.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The BJP has got more than an Economic Debacle</title><link href="/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The BJP has got more than an Economic Debacle" /><published>2019-08-17T19:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-17T19:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/A9VOMfY4bOo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BJP does this and that, but whats happening to the economy? Its sliding. What’s happening to the fuel prices? Its going high. Your saving looks like its dwindling. Businesses are closing down and top tycoons in India are coming out to speak against the government economic policies. Without strong economy a country is finished. I am quite sure Modi will loose all what Manmohan Singh has built up. When Modi one day goes, perhaps we will be beggars and can be happy that we were not ruled by a ruler controlled by Italy, but one controlled by the magical properties of cow dung and urine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay the econ is down, to fix it you need to have brains, not swearing, not ability to burn your midnight oil, not ultra nationalism, you need to have brains without anger, and that one Modi’s cabinet that doesn’t have. I am not worried about Modi making us poor, whats the use of worrying after giving a garland to a monkey, its going to make a mess of it, according to the monkey it did the right thing. I am worried about India becoming just another Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see once Pakistani earned more than an Indian. If Indian earned Rs 100, a Pakistani earned Rs 165, but now look what has happened to their country. They have to beg for $ 6 billion, which is actually nothing, and they are not getting it. The reason is their stupidity, obsession with something other than the economy. They were corrupt, fortunately right now we feel BJP is less corrupt than the Paki’s. Either they are un-corrupt or are good at hiding corruption. The next big mistake they made is to let religious people take over their country. When that happened, passion started to take over and development got a back seat, and down went Pakistan. Who can save them now? Not their Allah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its Allah in Pakistan and its Ram in India. That’s the only difference between Pakistan and Indian politics now. I do expect India to go down in economy quick and none should be able to do anything about it. Then what would happen? The people with relatively good economic minds, the Congress will come to power, improve economy and corruption, and then we can elect this religious fanatics once again to waste away our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And life goes on. But will that happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see when fanatics come to power, a nation goes a full transformation. When the liberal Shah was in power in Iran, a woman can wear a bikini in beach, what now? Think! Once upon a time in University of Peshawar students had bands, wore jeans, what happened now? Afghanistan was a thriving country, what happened after the Taliban rule?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Economic debacle is the first phase of transformation from civilized to religious rules. When economy goes down you can’t purchase things, you may not have a job, if you do you will not be paid well. You won’t have a good purchasing power. Life becomes harder. When life becomes harder where will you go for help? God men. And think what the BJP and RSS consists of. They have fanatic God men who think its their right to control our lives. I am very confident we are going there, and possibly no force is going to stop them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Dream of Islamic Caliphate</title><link href="/god/religion/islam/psychology/2019/08/17/the-dream-of-islamic-caliphate.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Dream of Islamic Caliphate" /><published>2019-08-17T13:39:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-17T13:39:00+05:30</updated><id>/god/religion/islam/psychology/2019/08/17/the-dream-of-islamic-caliphate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/god/religion/islam/psychology/2019/08/17/the-dream-of-islamic-caliphate.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IkYrhzhxSCQ?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some times your peace and well being is affected by some idiot thinking some thing. Have you have ever had a bad day just because your bosses brain has got crooked? Well that’s the fate of India too, and possibly the fate of Europe. There was this guy Muhammed in Arabia who thought the then Arabic religion sucked, so he came up with Islam. If some one today claimed that one had seen God or Angels, you would be put in a mental hospital, but in those day they believed in him because he was a honest tradesman. Even very honest people’s brain gets screwed up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now not being content with what he had, he said this Islam will spread to India, Rome etc. That is he just blabbered that Islam would spread to «all the countries that came up to his head», and that’s it, our fate was sealed. You see, Islam and all religions in this world are not religions of peace. We suspect Aryan’s invaded India, hence Hinduism cannot be considered a religion of peace. Buddhists masacare Tamils and Muslims in SriLanka and Burma. You have the crusades where Christians killed lot’s of Muslims. Similarly at that time Islam spread by war and conquest and not by people accepting it in a peaceful way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Islam was a peaceful religion, the original religion of Arabian’s would have peacefully coexisted with Islam, and today Kabba would have been worshiped not just by Muslims, but of the people of the old religion too. Islam just wiped them out, forced them to change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its set in Muslims brains that one has to conquer to spread Islam, now since they believe in Muhammad’s blabbers, it means that Islam must conquer India too, otherwise the God man is not really God man! Its that’s why they try to conquer India so hard.Though many Muslim nations have given up turning India into a Islamic nation, Pakistan for its strategic interest still tries to do so. It control’s Afghanistan and since it has got one of the best and most successful intelligence service, the ISI, it does have the capability and the desire to control India. We have to be terribly careful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s an Islamic Caliphate?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conquest of India by Islam is a part of the Islamic caliphate plan. Right after Muhammad’s death, Muslim’s were searching for a leader. They had the idea that there must be just one leader and under him the whole world should be ruled under the Kuran as its the book of God. So time and again some powerful Islamic ruler rises and tries to unite Muslims under him and tries to invade non Islamic territory to keep the dream of Muhammad alive. Till now they are bit successful. Islam now stretches from the gates of Russia to Indonesia. At the same time these leaders have failed too as they embraced violence and covert tactics to spread their religion, just like Muhammad has done during his life time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we must realize&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no fucking God. We all know it. We take our kids to a doctor when its ill rather than taking it to a temple alone thus avoiding science. If God with such greatness exists, it wouldn’t have freaked out just because some one has disobeyed it and ate a fruit. It could have fixed the brain of the disobeyed, perhaps reversed time and made the thing of eating the forbidden fruit never had happened. If God is sooo dumb, my God what to do about it? Its worth killing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People should realize that God is just a feeling, an illusion in one’s mind. One must come out of this trap and must embrace reason and common sense. Else we will see more bloodshed in the name of religion of peace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/B1YiDN8MT9w?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Great move on Kashmir</title><link href="/india/kashmir/2019/08/06/great-move-on-kashmir.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Great move on Kashmir" /><published>2019-08-06T20:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-06T20:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/kashmir/2019/08/06/great-move-on-kashmir</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/kashmir/2019/08/06/great-move-on-kashmir.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-bdViOY6_6zc/UIZ2hFrxZeI/AAAAAAAAAC8/I5BiOzf73yI/s1600/61809-pakistan-this-is-natural-beauty.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s really a great move on Kashmir I feel, its really a great one what the Modi government has taken. I hate Modi and the BJP and the RSS for destroying India with Hinduism and with their stupidity in general, but the move was great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kashmir is a part of India in every legal way. Pakistan with its misinformation and campaign tried to split Kashmir from India, and it tried to split Punjab from us. They failed. If you see, these states have the great rivers shared by India and Pakistan. Pakistan is terribly afraid about its water supply and don’t want these states been controlled by a power that it considers an enemy. Its a very natural feeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Right Timing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you see things happened at the right time. Now Pakistan is disrespected even by Saudi Arabia, a major money source for Pakistani terror. None knows who controls Pakistan, if its the terrorists, the elected government or the military. Plus Pakistan is failing financially time to time. Even the Chinese who want to encircle India by making Pakistan one of their hit man seems to be giving up. Imagine China pumps investment into Pakistan and its gone without right reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silent China&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China has its own Kashmir now, its called Hong Kong. China is trying to integrate Hong Kong into it and India is trying to integrate Kashmir into it. So China can’t speak a lot on this issue. The timing at which India executed this thing is great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a huge Islamic problem for China too. China has relatively peaceful Muslim population in its West, think what will happen if ISI is able to radicalize them like they did to Kashmir, Punjab and Afghanistan and ask money from China for their reduced involvement? If China doesn’t realize it and stop supporting Pakistan, then its a huge problem. So rather than supporting Pak’s, its better for China to keep silent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;India must not loose vigil&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Pakistan is weak, India must not loose vigil. A terror attack is very cheap. If you have a army, you must train people for years, they must have certain benefits, you must follow United Nations protocol and so on. For a terror attack, nothing needs to be followed. You can do it for few lakhs of rupees. Pakistan can do multiple attacks on India if India is not vigilant.
On a longer run these attacks would do nothing, but it might be enough to terrorize people and make them blame the government for taking a wrong move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must also look into funding of Islamic trusts, mosques in India, I suspect many could be receiving funding from ISI and other terror organization so that they can use them to brain wash people against India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have already let our territory to be used by LTTE and now by Islamic Tamil Terrorists to mount attacks on Srilanka, its a shame for India, technically India is terrorist state, no country has the guts now to call India a terror state, but that does not mean we are not one. We are a country who’s territory is been used to launch attacks on others. We are a terror state and we must curb it to get international respect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Economy in Doldrums&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No nation can be successful in stress and in war time if economy is down. Indian economy is down, our construction sector is gone, our automotive sector has slid, possibly irrecoverable now. SME’s are struggling and many are going down. If Modi hits at PAK and looses Indian economy, then he is a bloody fool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a feeling he will prove himself a great bloody fool.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">வருங்காலம் நல்காலம்</title><link href="/2019/07/13/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%99-%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%B2-%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="வருங்காலம் நல்காலம்" /><published>2019-07-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-07-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/07/13/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%99%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%B2%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/07/13/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%99-%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%B2-%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B2%E0%AE%AE.html">&lt;p&gt;ஊக்கம் உழைப்பு நற்சிந்தனை தெள்ளறிவு&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;வருங்காலத்தை நல்காலமாய் ஆக்கும்&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">ஊக்கம் உழைப்பு நற்சிந்தனை தெள்ளறிவு</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">History of Religion</title><link href="/2019/07/11/history-of-religion.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="History of Religion" /><published>2019-07-11T19:30:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-07-11T19:30:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/07/11/history-of-religion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/07/11/history-of-religion.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/religion_history.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>