<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-03-13T18:30:14+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">What has gradually disappeared over the last thirty years without people really noticing?</title><link href="/2025/03/13/what-has-gradually-disappeared-over-the-last-thirty-years-without-people-really-noticing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What has gradually disappeared over the last thirty years without people really noticing?" /><published>2025-03-13T18:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-03-13T18:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/03/13/what-has-gradually-disappeared-over-the-last-thirty-years-without-people-really-noticing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/03/13/what-has-gradually-disappeared-over-the-last-thirty-years-without-people-really-noticing.html">&lt;p&gt;I live in Chennai, and these have disappeared in the name of development:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gardens around the house.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of garden wildlife, from insects to mongoose to snakes etc.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Verandah.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Large Balconies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Socializing with neighbors.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Playgrounds.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Spacious parks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clean air.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Accessible and clean groundwater.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Free water (never thought water would be sold one day).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Giving free food.  (when I was young, anyone could knock our doors for food and they will get it)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Following traffic rules.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fast travel across city.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Slow paced lifestyle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not being greedy for money.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Functions taking place in home. No need for marriage halls.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Home cooked food. (I feel Kitchen should be eliminated to liberate women).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We buying our own groceries.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Going to office.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Library.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Teachers and principal having control of educational institutions. They being respected as Gods.  (Today, the money minded politicians and businessmen don’t respect teachers).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fountain pens &amp;amp; Writing. (I feel they are making a comeback)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not smoking, drinking in public.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Talking in tea shops.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Talking to people while sitting on culvet under a tree.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trees&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Walkable platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Financial Stability.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Telegram&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Writing Letters&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Long distant trunk calls (STD / ISD)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;FAX&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Computer Printers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Compact Disk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;USB (Almost Gone)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Floppy Disk.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Theaters and going to movies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Less populated cities.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Receiving and visiting relatives and friends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I live in Chennai, and these have disappeared in the name of development:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Heirs of corrupt should surrender 80% of their wealth in India</title><link href="/2025/03/08/heirs-of-corrupt-should-current-80-of-their-wealth-in-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Heirs of corrupt should surrender 80% of their wealth in India" /><published>2025-03-08T12:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-03-08T12:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/03/08/heirs-of-corrupt-should-current-80-of-their-wealth-in-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/03/08/heirs-of-corrupt-should-current-80-of-their-wealth-in-india.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3a/J_Jayalalithaa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Jayalalitha the Corrupt&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure if today is corrupt Jayalalith’s birthday, AIADMK people were celebrating with the corrupt women’s picture for something. My blood boiled. Will any person with dignity join a party that accept a declared criminal as their leader? Yet we have got tens of thousands of undignified people in Tamilnadu, electing undignified persons as our leader. Shame. Bloody shame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also thought what will happen if we had a dignified person as our Chief Minister? We have graves of Jayalalitha who is a corrupt leader, yet Stalin is not dignified enough to remove her grave from Marina, neither he is dignified enough to resign. Stalin knows very well that Karunanidhi, MGR, and Annadurai watched corruption and were mute. So these people graves should be removed too, and Marina should be kept clean. Yet those graves are there advertising the undignified politics we have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just because Annandurai, MGR, and Karunanidhi are not proven criminals, it cannot be said that they can never be proven criminals. What to do if they are proven criminals? Most people loot for their families to prosper generations, or the heirs of their wealth to prosper. So I feel India should enact a law that says when someone is proven criminal who has looted the state and is no more, then 80% of the wealth of their heirs should be confiscated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A audit of loot should be done, and 18% per annum compound interest should be calculated, if the surrendered wealth is not matching up, then their heirs should be arrested for treason. If the 80% is more than the looted amount and the compound interest, then their heirs can be let out to live as guilt free citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This should not just apply for politicians, it should apply for deceased bureaucrats, and normal citizens as well. The heirs of any deceased who has given and taken even 1 paisa as bribe, should loose 80% of their wealth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This strict measure will make people aware of what they inherit, and people will be more educated, and will know from where their finances come from. We won’t have lethargic bitches and bastards roaming around the nation like kings and queens, while a honest man works like hell and dies in poverty and vain.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Jayalalitha the Corrupt</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The consequence of India having idiot Modi as Prime Minister</title><link href="/2025/02/16/the-consequence-of-india-having-idiot-modi-as-prime-minister.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The consequence of India having idiot Modi as Prime Minister" /><published>2025-02-16T09:56:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-02-16T09:56:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/02/16/the-consequence-of-india-having-idiot-modi-as-prime-minister</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/02/16/the-consequence-of-india-having-idiot-modi-as-prime-minister.html">&lt;p&gt;India had great intellectuals like Nehru as Prime Minister, the one we have now, Modi  is a absolute idiot, only fit for drinking cow urine and feeding on cow dung. Let me explain what I mean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;maldives-criticizing-modi&quot;&gt;Maldives criticizing Modi&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime ago Maldives ministers criticized Modi, there was huge uproar in India. Though Modi was criticized, it was promoted by Godi media as thogh India had been criticized, and Modi went to Lakshadweep island and said that India should quit Maldives. Well, a critic on one person was projected by Godi media as a slap to India. In fact &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindu.com/news/international/maldives-govt-distances-itself-from-derogatory-remarks-against-pm-modi-by-minister/article67715983.ece&quot;&gt;Maldives did suspend three of its ministers&lt;/a&gt;. But a big buzz was created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;indians-treated-like-shit&quot;&gt;Indian’s treated like shit&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently USA deported about 100 Indians, they were illegal, yet they should be treated as human. They were handcuffed, their legs too were chained, and they were made to travel 40 hours, I have no clue what they did for nature calls. India raised no protest against this animal like treatment of Indians. The Godi media too never took it in a big way. May be for the Godi media, its criticizing Modi is criticizing India, whereas even though 100+ Indians were treated as animals, it meant nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trump-abusing-india&quot;&gt;Trump abusing India&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/PPrxCLMI1iI?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent India, US joint press brief, you can see trump abusing India right before Modi. Modi who claims he is super nationalistic and super patriot, just stood there. Either he was so dumb that he had no clue what was going on, or though he knew, he is an idiot and coward who cannot counter it. I wish he had at least a ball. Just one at least, a broken one would have done something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Godi media too was silent, I am not sure if they hailed his trip as a great triumph, but they just kept quiet when India was bashed like hell by Trump. In this blog I will tell you how Modi if he had some brains could have countered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;need-for-imbalanced-tariff&quot;&gt;Need for imbalanced tariff&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were long a slave nation to the Brits, and hence we are still a very weak nation today. We were abused by the west, and still proper retributions have’t been paid. In this blog I will explain how USA stalled India’s progress, and you decide if there should be a tariff imbalance or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;yale-university&quot;&gt;Yale University&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/36/Enoch_Seeman_the_younger_-_Portrait_of_Gov._Elihu_Yale_%281648-9%E2%80%931721%29_-_1789.1_-_Yale_University_Art_Gallery.jpg/500px-Enoch_Seeman_the_younger_-_Portrait_of_Gov._Elihu_Yale_%281648-9%E2%80%931721%29_-_1789.1_-_Yale_University_Art_Gallery.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elihu_Yale&quot;&gt;Elihu Yale, the looter of Chennai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s start with a History. The Yale university in USA was created with the wealth looted from my city Chennai, India. Yale amassed his wealth by not so genuine practices, and he took his loot to England. USA was a poor nation then, and when they wanted to build a university, Yale donated part of wealth he looted to the university, thus the university was named after him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact it was my city that is solely responsible for the existance of this university, and I don’t think USA acknowledges it and I don’t think its thankful for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think Modi is literate enough to know this, but at least he could have asked the “learned men” who accompanied him and told facts like this to correct USA, and to humble it. But he was dumb like the statue of Lord Ram erected in Ayodhya.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;global-warming&quot;&gt;Global Warming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USA is the largest emitter of green house gases, it’s the leading cause of Global warming, and we in India too are are experiencing the consequence. USA should be infact be paying trillions of dollars to all countries on this planet to cope with the damage it causes. Yet it’s foolish leader Trump want to drill for more oil and increase fossil fuel usage. Modi could have pointed this simple fact out to Trump. Yet he stayed dumb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1972-nuclear-threat&quot;&gt;1972 Nuclear Threat&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1972 war, USA sent its naval fleet and threatened India with a nuclear strike, it was hell bent on defeating India, Soviet Union saved us by sending its subs to our East Coast. Till today, USA hasn’t asked a sorry for it. This act of USA should have prolonged the war, costed more lives, it also put the independence of Bangladesh into jeopardy. USA never paid us any compensation for this cruel act. Modi could have pointed this out, yet he stayed dumb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;promoting-jihadist&quot;&gt;Promoting Jihadist&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uqZ-ToXjCz0?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch this video, Ronald Regan, another dumb leader, named a launch of space shuttle after Taliban. The bureaucrats of USA cannot think, they thought that snakes thrown at backyard of some one will never bite them, and here they are after loosing twin towers, and they lost the war in Afghanistan. They supported the terrorist nation of Pakistan which shielded Osama Bin Laden who was responsible for killing thousands of US citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even today, our soldiers are been killed by the Jihadist promoted by USA, and USA does not pay us single penny for damage it still causes to India. Modi stood there along with Trump as though he does not know this fact. Fucking ball less coward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sanctions&quot;&gt;Sanctions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India, or any other nation on this planet has the right to test nuclear weapons. But when we did it, USA slapped sanctions on us. Why? Because according to them we are an inferior species who are not worthwhile to have nukes. Such is the animalistic attitude of US people. Because of their sanctions, many of our programs like the space program, our fighter jet program, our nuclear program stalled. India lost billions of dollars due to sanctions, yet Modi did not have the courage to raise this issue on the podium with Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-killing-of-indian-scientists-and-lal-bahadur-sastri&quot;&gt;The killing of Indian Scientists and Lal Bahadur Sastri&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Homi_Jehangir_Bhabha_1960s.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Homi_Jehangir_Bhabha&quot;&gt;Homi Bhabha&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mysterious way in which Homi Baba died, if he had lived, our nuke programs could have been much faster. Who killed him? There is a strong suspicion that USA did it. Did USA open up its gates for Indian investigators? No. Why? Most probably because they killed Homi Baba. Till today USA has not said that it will let India to investigate people in USA, nor it had asked sorry. Such an evil nation it is. Any way how will a nation that kills millions every year be sorry for causing a plane crash? You need to be a human to feel sorry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/22/Lal_Bahadur_Shastri_%28from_stamp%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lal_Bahadur_Sastri&quot;&gt;Lal Bahadur Sastri&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One our excellent Prime Ministers Lal Bahadur Sastri mysteriously died in Tashkant. Hand of CIA is suspected. Yet USA did not throw open the gates for investigation, neither it admitted to its mistakes and asked sorry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vickram Sarabhai too died in mysterious circumstances. Was USA involved? We don’t know, did USA throw open its gates for investigation? Once again no. Modi could have brought up these issues, and could have said how much potentially USA costs us, and how it never paid us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;going-against-indias-nuclear-plans&quot;&gt;Going against India’s nuclear plans&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USA never wanted India to be a powerful nuclear state, it had done what ever it could to destabilize us. Sanctions, mysterious disappearance of scientists, causing brain drain and so on. It forced us to open up our reactors to USA’s dog IAEA. Modi could have easily pointed these out, yet he stood like dumb before the world press and Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nambhi-narayanan&quot;&gt;Nambhi Narayanan&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/0/0a/Nambi_Narayanan.jpg/672px-Nambi_Narayanan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nambi_Narayanan&quot;&gt;Nambi Narayanan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the case of Nambi Naryanan. He himself says USA could be behind he being falsely charged by Indian police on espionage case. ISRO is an open organization and they don’t hide their plans. But all of a sudden, Kerala police accused him of selling public domain ISRO data to other countries, its a laughable allegation. Till today who is behind it is not fully clear. If my memory is right A.K.Antony is one among the person who conducted this treason against India. Was his church any way controlled and / or connected with USA? Modi could have raises this issue too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;still-not-late&quot;&gt;Still not late&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay Modi is a coward and cannot speak on the podium with Trump. At least after the press meet Indian bureaucrats could have held another press meeting and have put forward these issues and have argued how much damage USA caused to India, and thus imbalanced tariffs are justifiable. They could have boldly said that just tarrifs are not enough, but USA owes tens of billions of dollars as retribution to India. Under a coward and unlearned priminster, how will they open their mouth? Even though Modi is back in India, I don’t think its late to point these out to brain dead Trump and his nation, but I am sure coward India will not do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish someone as knowledgeable as Sashi Tharoor is our priminster, some one who would  turn his back on Trump, or oppose him as soon as he abuses our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Indians should become intellectuals enough so that intellectuals become our leaders, not some school quitting religious fanatic who can’t even table facts and argue at the right time. Modi has costed a lot for India, and I am sure he will be expensive and cost us a lot more in times to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">India had great intellectuals like Nehru as Prime Minister, the one we have now, Modi is a absolute idiot, only fit for drinking cow urine and feeding on cow dung. Let me explain what I mean.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Perils of work from office</title><link href="/2025/01/29/perils-of-work-from-office.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Perils of work from office" /><published>2025-01-29T17:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-29T17:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/29/perils-of-work-from-office</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/29/perils-of-work-from-office.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;healthy-living&quot;&gt;Healthy Living&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing this blog with a throat and sinus infection. Just two weeks ago people in my office carried it, I had to go to office because it was the norm, the result, last week I took 3 days of leave and once I got better I went, and this week I am down again. Some virus is circulating. The COVID years were my healthiest, those who stayed clean were spared. I worked from home for a company that was efficient, (there were technical idiots in it mixing ReactJS Development with Rails, that’s another story,) but when it comes to work from home they got it spot on. So when it comes to healthy living, work from home wins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;traffic&quot;&gt;Traffic&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In work from home, I could think more. I could think in times I should worry about Chennai traffic, while people who are drunk drive freely, people get license not by passing driving exams, but by bribing the RTO (there is no other way). In my current office parking is crazy, and I have to go at odd times compromising my sleep. A person who is fully awake at 11AM, is forced to wake up at 5AM. Just to avoid traffic and parking issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am using an electric car, so I am a bit lucky on transport cost, else it would cost me Rs 300 every day to go to my office, thanks to Modi’s inflation. What I can say is even this can be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;money&quot;&gt;Money&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was once in an office where I was working, suddenly a boy jumped besides me asking for Rs 200/-, I asked for what, then he said “boss, that(fucking) …… has her birthday, we must buy cake and treats for her birthday.” Bloody damn. If prostitution was legal in a big way why would these people have to run behind girls dogs behind a bitch I thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to work from home, you can simply say congratz or a thumbs up on WhatsApp and that’s it. Who cares who has the dream of fucking who?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But ya in my previous office there was bloody inefficient team that did want work from office, thankfully it did not materialize. We had to attend in person ceremonies of our manager, because there was no way to avoid it. Fortunately I was in a team that was a bit efficient. I did attend those functions because my project manager was a good person and not because we saw each other every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in work from office you have to shed money for some fucking person just because the fucking person exists, and its no fault of you that one exists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;team-that-does-not-know-remote-work&quot;&gt;Team that does not know remote work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my present office, people went on Pongal leave, out of the 5 or so days they were out, only 2 days were supposed to be holidays, I tried contacting a team member, but to no avail. Teams in my present company are stuck if they are out of office. I wonder if they will survive if they need to work as independent freelancers, launch a product that challenges us and so on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;just-a-paying-club&quot;&gt;Just a paying club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though people put scene they work 10, 11 hours a day, in reality I don’t think one can work, or code more than 3 - 4 hours a day. I have worked just 1 hour a day and have completed stuff on time. But yes I did use highly productive languages like Python, Ruby, Clojure and so on, with a rock solid test suite. I would in fact encourage a programmer to restrict himself to just 4 hours of work a day (including mindless, depressing and unproductive meetings), to be productive and steady on the longer run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In software industry, if you claim more than 4 hours of work per day, then it means you do not know to use a computer that makes you highly productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In work from office it’s just a club you attend where your boss pays you for your socializing, that consumes the hours more than 4 that you claim to be working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;leaders-insisting-on-work-from-office&quot;&gt;Leaders insisting on work from office&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do leaders insist on work from office, even though software today is the transfer of data that can be done from anywhere? One simple reason. Control. Of course in companies where bosses are dumb, and I had to work from home, control was done by having no so transparent appraisal process, everyone in my previous office knew appraisal was a spoof, but in most office, the boss wants to be seen as a strong guy / gal, and it’s far easier to control you in an environment owned more by your boss than owned by you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;office-rent&quot;&gt;Office Rent&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In city like Chennai, damn the office rent! Damn the greedy and lazy real estate holders. Who will pay so much? Instead of paying rent, just convert small part of your home to office just for this stupid Indian government compliance purpose and make all things remote. I.T industry is literally loosing billions because ignorant people have risen to the top, and they want to put scene by having large offices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Healthy Living</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Understanding Quantum Computing</title><link href="/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Understanding Quantum Computing" /><published>2025-01-12T20:36:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-12T20:36:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/12/understanding-quantum-computing.html">&lt;p&gt;Richard Feynman said, if anyone says they understood Quantum Physics, it means they haven’t understood it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineering is more about practicality than about science. Fuzzy Logic was hated by mathematicians while we engineers are using it for a long time, similarly, we have looked at practical applications of stuff and used it, without having a full understanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently Google announced their willow processor. They claimed what was done by their computer in 5 minutes will take the best super computer today \(10^{25}\) years to complete. That’s a staggering claim. In this blog I would like to explain to you the reader how such feats are possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computers are here to solve problems, so here is one. Imagine you are in a room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%20%280%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are the green dot, and you want to reach the red X. So there are four pathways. One way to reach this path is like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%281%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, that’s one way, there are three ways left. You chose the path at your free will right? Well if you say yes, then you are absolutely wrong. The physics of this universe made you choose that path. In fact there are an uncountable number of universes with uncountable numbers of you, you just experience one of them, that to a short time interval of it. All that had happened is happening, and all that lies in the future has already happened, and there is no time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay lets keep it simple, now imagine there are four universes where it had made you choose four different paths as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%282%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subatomic particles communicate across multiple universes which our brain can’t comprehend, but even before you start a problem, all possible solutions and failures to solve it exists. In many universes you would (in truth that universe would have made you) have solved the problem with flying colors, in many universes you would have failed miserably, in many universes that problem simply would not exist. So say at quantum level if you know how you solved all problems in all universes, in our simple case it might look like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%283%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As indicated above, you would know all possible solutions of the problem you are solving in an instant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s say we have a problem where only 2 out of 4 paths lead you to the solution, a traditional you, or a computer should test each way to find a solution, but a quantum you, or a computer, since it communicates with parallel universes will know exactly which path leads you to red X, and in which paths you have banged yourself onto a wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902302.us.archive.org/33/items/understanding-quantum-computing.excalidraw/Understanding%20Quantum%20Computing%284%29.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Richard Feynman said, if anyone says they understood Quantum Physics, it means they haven’t understood it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Signs of a Highly Intelligent Employee</title><link href="/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Signs of a Highly Intelligent Employee" /><published>2025-01-07T20:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-07T20:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/07/signs-of-a-highly-intelligent-employee.html">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They cheat on their job with a side hustle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They treat everybody equal (including the cleaner).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They rebel against micromanagement and dictator leaders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They know when to say no to a meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They help others advance in their career.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They don’t respond to most emails.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They don’t attend meetings, but find efficient ways to communicate.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They stay away from gossip and corporate politics.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They create passive income so if they get fired it matters less.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They try entrepreneurship at least once to see what it feels like.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re fine to be the dumbest person in the room.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They ruthlessly protect their time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They focus on outcomes not KPIs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re wildly open to new ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They create stuff people want.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They learn without being told.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They’re humble.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">They cheat on their job with a side hustle. They treat everybody equal (including the cleaner). They rebel against micromanagement and dictator leaders. They know when to say no to a meeting. They help others advance in their career. They don’t respond to most emails. They don’t attend meetings, but find efficient ways to communicate. They stay away from gossip and corporate politics. They create passive income so if they get fired it matters less. They try entrepreneurship at least once to see what it feels like. They’re fine to be the dumbest person in the room. They ruthlessly protect their time. They focus on outcomes not KPIs. They’re wildly open to new ideas. They create stuff people want. They learn without being told. They’re humble.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DMK is incompetent and intoxicated</title><link href="/2025/01/01/dmk-is-incompetent-and-intoxicated.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DMK is incompetent and intoxicated" /><published>2025-01-01T11:44:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-01-01T11:44:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/01/01/dmk-is-incompetent-and-intoxicated</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/01/dmk-is-incompetent-and-intoxicated.html">&lt;p&gt;I feel DMK has become incompetent and intoxicated in its ruling years, I am sure the Stalin family cares about getting Inbhanidhi on stage during DMK’s meet, than solving our problems. In this blog I present case why I think DMK is intoxicated and incompetent, and why we Tamils need to choose alternatives. I am not sure though if alternatives are ready, but it would be foolish as a civilization if we are not looking for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;failure-to-select-a-right-leader&quot;&gt;Failure to select a right leader&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK failed even before Stalin became a CM. It’s a party that says it likes to be democratically represent us, but inside DMK, there is no democracy. Somehow Stalin, Udhayanidhi and Inbhanidhi have risen to the top. What qualification do they have? They just come from a single bloodline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even PTR comes from a blue blood, but he is intellectually sound. On the other hand Karunanidhis’s heirs looks like fools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stalin-is-a-fool&quot;&gt;Stalin is a fool&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stalin is a fool, or he thinks we Tamil’s are fools who will forget what he has done, here are my cases:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;senthil-balaji&quot;&gt;Senthil Balaji&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QUZ8X55WdUs?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw a video where Stalin slams Senthil Balaji, about his corruption, look what has happened now, Stalin kneels to Balaji, he is dependent on Balaji’s money so much so that when Balaji was arrested, Stalin and DMK came forefront to defend him. Such a……. God, what to say? What to say? To be descent, I would just put, such a shameless character now leads DMK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;campaign-against-drugs&quot;&gt;Campaign against drugs&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hb5BGb_vixU?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was funny when I watched this video. Here Stalin says a word &lt;em&gt;bothai&lt;/em&gt; which means intoxicated. He does not want Tamils to be intoxicated with drugs, but just from Medavakkam to Sithalapakkam, a 3Km stretch, there are 7 Liquor shops run by Tamil Nadu government. Don’t they give &lt;em&gt;bothai&lt;/em&gt; or intoxication? Does Stalin say it’s right to drink, but it’s wrong to take drugs? If yes how? Does he say that my neighborhood and I have not been affected by TASMAC (Tamilnadu Liqour Shops)? Does he claim no one sat on our street and drank? Does he claim drunk don’t roam our streets? Or does he claim a drunk does not come in the way when we drive and increases the potential of accidents?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stalin looks like an idiot when he intoxicates people, but says they must not get intoxicated by a competitive intoxicant like drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;covid-spreading-election-campaign&quot;&gt;Covid spreading election campaign&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must have looked at election campaigns in Tamilnadu, they took place in Covid era and none of protective measures were followed. Stalin and other leader’s grouped people and addressed them. They were mask-less, and no visible proof of hand sanitizers were present. Okay Stalin is a fool, no wonder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funny part is after coming to power, the same Stalin who helped to spread Covid, asked people to donate money to prevent the spread of Covid. I think he thinks we are absolute fools who do not watch him. I felt very bad that DMK came to power with such a stupid as leader. Or at least he thinks we will be stupid enough not to notice these things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-murder-near-court&quot;&gt;A Murder near court&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.indiatoday.in/india/tamil-nadu/story/tamil-nadu-tirunelveli-murder-man-hacked-district-combined-court-2653271-2024-12-21&quot;&gt;murder near court campus&lt;/a&gt;, okay, the issue is when reports asked the law minister, he almost disowned the murder as though it never happened in Tamil Nadu. He was proud that it happened out of the court campus than inside it, and it sounded like it was the triump of the DMK that enabled one be mudered outside court campus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shouldn’t a minister feel asamed when one is murdered in Tamil Nadu? Okay we know that politicians are scoundrels, but at least act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tungsten-mines-in-tamil-nadu&quot;&gt;Tungsten mines in Tamil Nadu&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindu.com/news/national/tamil-nadu/whats-the-row-over-tungsten-mining-near-madurai/article68959810.ece&quot;&gt;conterversy over tungsten mining in Tamil Nadu&lt;/a&gt;. The opposition leader EPS asked questions about it and the CM M.K.Stalin couldn’t answer it properly. When stalin came to power, what ever problems he faced, he blamed it on the previous leader EPS. This showed us that he likes to deflect off things than to think about solving it, once again in the tungsten issue, he blamed it on center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes the center wants to mine tungsten, and it might want to auction Tamilian lands, but you are a ruling party in Tamil Nadu. Have you protested against it? If not why all of a sudden you are blaming the center? Why were you sleeping till now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;blast-in-coimbatore&quot;&gt;Blast in Coimbatore&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindu.com/news/national/tamil-nadu/all-about-coimbatore-car-blast-case-2022-terror-probe-and-more/article66061346.ece&quot;&gt;bomb blast in Coimbatore carried out by Islamic terrorists&lt;/a&gt;, it was unprofessional and sloppy, probably made by a terror intern or trainee. It was bomb made from domestic gas cylinder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than acknowledging it was a terror attack, DMK people to get Islamic votes said that it was an accident, I couldn’t believe it. At that time a DMK guy came to my home to get trained in web development, and he swore that cylinder blast is an accident and not a terror attack. I was baffled. This shows to what length DMK people will go to keep their vote bank intact even though national security is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;arrest-of-savukku-shankar&quot;&gt;Arrest of Savukku Shankar&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.livemint.com/lm-img/img/2024/05/04/600x338/SavukkuShankar_1714814864098_1714814873937.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Savukku Shankar&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Savukku Shankar is a whistleblowing journalist in Tamil Nadu who is equated to Julian Assange. He somehow knows and accurately predicts what’s going to happen in politics. He also exposes corruption in such a way that infuriates the DMK. Rather than proving that Savukku is wrong, or placing an argument against him, DMK arrests him in false cases, so much so that Supreme Court of India has given stark warning to the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This proves that DMK does not like democracy, and does not like people questioning them and speaking against it. The reason why this happens is, DMK is intoxicated with power, and has become incompetent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-eliminating-cows-from-road&quot;&gt;Not eliminating cows from road&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/lT4pqto-140?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 6 months ago I think, an IAS office named Radhakrishnan told on TV that after the incidence shown in above video (it shows a little girl being attacked by a cow), cows in Chennai’s roads will be eliminated. I am sure even if I take a stroll now, I would be able to spot cows on road, cow dung all over roads, and worst, the cows affecting traffic, and causing a potential for accidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lies, lies, lies from Radhakrishnan. Absolute lies. The government, even it knows the truth, it hasn’t apologized for this guys lying, neither has announced how it will remove cows from roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-eliminating-dogs-from-road&quot;&gt;Not eliminating dogs from road&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An incident occurred in Chennai where a little kid was bitten by stray dog, when the mayor Priya was asked about it, she said the city will take census of dogs. What? Idiot, eliminate dogs idiot, eliminate it. Good or bad, dogs are like terrorists across border who still don’t attack us. Don’t be a fucking sitting coward like Modi, eliminate them. DMK doesn’t seem to have the guts to change such a mayor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I ask my friends why such an incompetent and inefficient person is a mayor, they say it’s because she is from a backward community. Okay you need a person from backward community for votes, but then why can’t you find an efficient one from backward community and make her or him mayor? If one is not performing, shouldn’t that one be eliminated?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is DMK a lazy party? Selecting a president because someone is a son of Karuna than someone who has the will to think about the people? Is the same laziness happening in Chennai mayor stuff too, though one is not performing, the party is reluctant to take her out and put new one in?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;flood-prevention-for-chennai-complete&quot;&gt;Flood prevention for Chennai complete?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent light rain, Valluvar Kottam was flooded, and I put it in my WhatsApp status, a DMK friend of mine replied that only 1800 of 4000 crores allocated for flood relief has been spent. What? I thought. Mayor Priya said within one rain Chennai will be flood proof, now Valluvar Kottam the work is still going on. I think in next light rain, or may be the next day, Moggapair was flooded. In how many places the anti-flood systems are still being implemented? In how many places it has been implemented and when it was last checked for maintenance? Who are the contractors who implemented it and how much money was given to them? Who are the people who worked for the project? How much money they got? From where the raw materials were procured, and what’s the supply chain? As a citizen why it’s hard for me to find this information online? What’s so secret about implementing a drainage system?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-ptr-is-not-coming-up&quot;&gt;Why PTR is not coming up?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b5/PTR.Thiagarajan.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Palanivel Thiagarajan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is an excellent leader called Palinivel Thiyaga Rajan in DMK. Of course, he is a leader in party because his family is close to that of Stalin’s, but he is not a tainted man, and he is an intellectual who does his job right. An audio leaked where PTR exposes 30,000 crores looted by Udhayanidhi, PTR claims that’s a fake audio, but after that, PTR who was finance minister declined. Now I think he is I.T minister.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A man who speaks with statistics and hard facts, PTR should be chief minister I say, we need such a talented man, not some idiot nod head like Stalin who is only good for photo shoots and propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;murugan-festival&quot;&gt;Murugan festival&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK which is supposed to be an atheistic party, to the dismay of many atheists who supported it, it held a festival for &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/chennai/dmk-govt-to-hold-global-lord-murugan-fest-faces-bjp-flak/articleshow/108507745.cms&quot;&gt;lord Muruga&lt;/a&gt;. I have always maintained, Dravida Kazhagam is the atheistic party and DMK is an Aryan Brahminical party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay things have deteriorated to a level the members of DMK follow God. Even if we treat that as personal belief, as a party which is now governing Tamil Nadu, I expect DMK to free people from the shackles of religion and move the masses towards science rather than plunging into the darkness of blind faith. DMK is in-fact dead, the DK soul of it has long rotted and vanished, DMK is just a name now that means nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dmk-people-in-my-area&quot;&gt;DMK people in my area&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you seen how ruthlessly cars with DMK flags drive? First I wonder what’s the use of cars to identify themselves with a party when all humans are equal? Why can’t people be normal and civil? Identifying oneself with a party sends a signal that that person is incompetent and needs a huge organization to support him to shield him from in societal misdeeds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay let me tell about DMK people in my area. First on December 18th gone, I returned from office and there were speakers blasting about Aiyappan praises just one house from my home. Even if all doors and widows were closed, the sound penetrated our home, kids were crying. I was told that some DMK guy is going to lord Aiyappan temple and wants the world know about it. I got a headache, and this speaker blasting went till 10PM. None dared to asked them to shut up because we know DMK people are bone head rowdies. Police won’t be of help too. Things ended at 10PM, next day I was unwell because I couldn’t take rest and did not go to my office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a second incident happened in EPS rule. There were rains and floodwaters in our street rose rapidly, this should not happen, Sithalapakkam is no flood zone where people have been living for more than 1400 years. The flood was because a DMK guy at the end of our street had built a bund so that his car can roll down from his property onto the road, this bund was blocking the draining of water to Perumbakkam lake. This DMK guy was asked to remove the bund did not relent. He said if it broke, the flood water will reach the slums.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He doesn’t seem to know we bought our properties legally, his bund construction that obstructed water and caused flooding is illegal, and the slums are illegal settlements too. As the waters rose, amazingly middle class people started amass and booked a JCB and the bund was broken. This is one simple example, if people wake up, DMK or no other party can stand before them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A party is built from ground up, and if people without simple civic sense constitue a party? Why should we vote for it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dmk-is-a-brahmin-party&quot;&gt;DMK is a brahmin party&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/af/Gandhi_Rajagopalachari.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Seen with Gandhi, at the right, Rajagopalachari&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK is a brahmin party, consisting of God believers. Whereas we Tamils want administration be separated from one’s beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/lhjNR66YGTg?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact DMK came to power by licking the feet of Rajagopalachari (Rjaji), a corrosive man who want to implement Vedic and Aryan traditions in our land subjugating our people. Periyaar supported Kamaraj who implemented his schemes, Rajaji unable to stand the march of rationalism in our land supported DMK, so that Periyaar and Kamaraj could be defeated. By this way Aryans could get their wishes implemented in Tamil Nadu in the name of Dravidian politics and cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;karunanidhi-shouldnt-have-become-dmk-president&quot;&gt;Karunanidhi shouldn’t have become DMK president&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think Karunanidhi should have become the president of DMK in the first place. I feel more honest, and more atheist Neduncherian should have been its president. Somehow politics do not favor gentlemen and uncorrupted and honest people, after the death of Annadurai, Karuna became CM and Tamil Nadu was scotched by the rising sun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes lack of education, foresight and thought might have been prevalent in uneducated masses then, there must have been a lot of people who can’t think well in DMK then, but what now? Haven’t your parents sent to school? Haven’t you learned to think? If not, why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-new-party-a-new-rule&quot;&gt;A new party, a new rule&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not saying to put back EPS in power, far worst will be BJP who are hell-bent on destroying our culture and language. What I am saying is look at alternative parties. Vijay has formed one, Vijayakanth has formed one, Seeman has formed one, there is Pazha Karupaiah who I really respect, he has a party, there are the communists (but yes they have become DMK feet licker’s now), and so on. Vote for different people, let us use this election and show that we need a change from this duopoly of DMK and ADMK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I feel DMK has become incompetent and intoxicated in its ruling years, I am sure the Stalin family cares about getting Inbhanidhi on stage during DMK’s meet, than solving our problems. In this blog I present case why I think DMK is intoxicated and incompetent, and why we Tamils need to choose alternatives. I am not sure though if alternatives are ready, but it would be foolish as a civilization if we are not looking for it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My thoughts on HAL AMCA</title><link href="/2024/12/20/my-thoughts-on-hal-amca.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My thoughts on HAL AMCA" /><published>2024-12-20T11:08:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-12-20T11:08:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/12/20/my-thoughts-on-hal-amca</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/12/20/my-thoughts-on-hal-amca.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/25/AMCA_model_displayed_during_Aero_India_2021.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am happy that India has taken up the challenge of 5&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; generation aircraft. I am very skeptical about its success, I do think India has the talent to develop it, but I am not sure to what pressures we will succumb to and make this aircraft a failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example HAL Marut failed because we did not have the right engine. The same case with LCA, it’s underperforming, but at least we can say it’s a partial success, at least it’s deployed into the armed forces with a foreign engine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The engine is the problem for us. For some reason we boast we are a superpower, but just outside my room, water logs as puddles when it rains, there is garbage strewn on the street, and stray dogs roam around. In such a nation, where simple problems cannot be solved, I am not surprised we don’t have our own jet engine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kaaviri&quot;&gt;Kaaviri&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Kaaviri engine, dream child of Kalam hasn’t materialized yet. It’s a government project, so there is no surprise it has failed, you may call it a success if it had made someone in` the creamy layer rich. I strongly feel we should have our own engine, and not rely on others. So, how do we go about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;publicly-funded-private-engine-company&quot;&gt;Publicly funded, private engine company&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need to remove government and bureaucracy out of engine manufacture. I feel we the citizens of India should crowd fund a private company that can develop a fighter jet engine. This company’s goal should be only to develop a fighter jet engine in India, and to sell it to who ever wants to buy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By keeping government and corruption out, I think there is a better chance of success. But yes corrupt politicians, having nexus with foreigners will try to ruin it. I am not sure how to defend against them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ai-in-lca-and-amca&quot;&gt;A.I in LCA and AMCA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want A.I navigation for LCA and AMCA. I want these planes to go autonomous. This will save tens of human lives during war. Pakistan has become a radical Islamic nation, so is Bangladesh approaching it quick, we may have two pronged war. Though China has eliminated Islam from its land, its supporting Islamic Jihadist in Bangladesh and Pakistan, so may be three-pronged war is also possible. In that case we need lots of autonomous fighter drones defending our ariel borders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nuke-missiles-missiles-missiles&quot;&gt;Nuke missiles, missiles, missiles&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If nuclear missiles are cheaper to make, let’s stockpile it. When ever someone enters our territory, thousands of them should be launched on the aggressors important cities, along with lots of decoys to confuse them. We should ensure war ends in minutes rather than months or years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am certain that AMCA will be a failure because we won’t be able to make our engine, so mass nuking of aggressor might be the only solution.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why they didn’t teach this in college?</title><link href="/2024/12/11/why-they-didnt-teach-this-in-college.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why they didn&apos;t teach this in college?" /><published>2024-12-11T18:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-12-11T18:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/12/11/why-they-didnt-teach-this-in-college</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/12/11/why-they-didnt-teach-this-in-college.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/soldering_202412/1%20Post%20LinkedIn-01.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I studied in Panimalar Engineering College, Chennai. It’s a super waste college, I am an electronics engineer (on paper) and have soldered nothing. I saw the video above on the internet and my heart broke. A Chinese video it is, and it shows how one can solder. But here I am a electronic’s engineer, and cannot solder a thing. Shame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineering in my state, Tamil Nadu is a bogus thing. The colleges that teach it does not understand that engineering is a technical thing and one needs hands on with it. Almost every thing I read was from books, and nothing was practical. I remember how few labs we had, we can’t stay late in labs, our access to it was controlled. We could enter college only by college bus and leave only by college bus, this severely restricted our movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our college chairman became bald at a young age, and he had a very ugly wife, because of that he did not want any of us to have girlfriends, so boy and girls were forbidden to speak with each other. I know people in west would be laughing reading about this rule, I swear it’s true. I am not gay to be happy about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The theoretical examination conducted by our state government is bogus, you can pass it with ease. There are practical exams, but colleges bribe the external examiners that visit and makes students pass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you ask my friends, they will praise my college. Yes these types of colleges are okay for people who want a paper that says they are engineers, even though they are not, but for me, a person who truly wanted to become a engineer and build things it’s a loot of my money.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tata Motors is a Buffalo and you can do nothing about it</title><link href="/2024/11/10/tata-motors-is-a-buffalo-and-you-can-do-nothing-about-it.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tata Motors is a Buffalo and you can do nothing about it" /><published>2024-11-10T19:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-11-10T19:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/11/10/tata-motors-is-a-buffalo-and-you-can-do-nothing-about-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/11/10/tata-motors-is-a-buffalo-and-you-can-do-nothing-about-it.html">&lt;p&gt;Here I am recording one of the least traumatic experience with Tata Motors. A month or two back, when water was poured into the car for wiper, it just drained out. I was not sure what happened and almost at the same time a person called Viji from FPL Tata Motors called. I booked an appointment and went to their Guindy service centre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I told the problem, a person sat us down and prepared a huge list of things that needs to be done with my car. I said ‘no’, all I wanted was this leaking problem to be fixed. That guy felt dismayed, but agreed he will fix it. I booked a cab and came home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think on the next day I got a call that the wiper tank had broken, and it needs 3 days to replace as they have no spare parts. I told them that I need the car as I have work, I went to FPL using call taxi, and took posession of my car. When I saw my car I was dismayed, it was covered in dust, nose to boot, and the person responsible seems to show no sign of shame. There were so many mosquitoes in my car. Even at that time I asked, will you call me when you get the wiper water tank, that person said ‘sure’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it’s a moth or two now, I don’t remember exactly when, now the Viji of FPL Tata Motors who has amnesia calls me again, and asked if I need my car to be serviced (I should not blame here, she could be just a pawn in the chess game of Tata Motors to squeeze out money from our pockets for their cheap quality of service). I said ‘no’. She asked me why, I said to here Tata Motors is like a buffalo, it stands at the middle of the road, if you honk it will move, and the same buffalo will stand again the next day at the middle of the road. There is no use one complaining, or there is no use in Tata Motors service people acting as though they care about their customers. The buffalo on the next day will be at the middle of the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, all the service centres in Tata Motors are buffalos, and you can do nothing about it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Here I am recording one of the least traumatic experience with Tata Motors. A month or two back, when water was poured into the car for wiper, it just drained out. I was not sure what happened and almost at the same time a person called Viji from FPL Tata Motors called. I booked an appointment and went to their Guindy service centre.</summary></entry></feed>