<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-12-02T09:29:43+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Kerala Muslims should stop spitting on food</title><link href="/india/food/kerala/islam/halal/2021/12/02/kerala-muslims-should-stop-spitting-on-food.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kerala Muslims should stop spitting on food" /><published>2021-12-02T09:28:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-12-02T09:28:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/food/kerala/islam/halal/2021/12/02/kerala-muslims-should-stop-spitting-on-food</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/food/kerala/islam/halal/2021/12/02/kerala-muslims-should-stop-spitting-on-food.html">&lt;p&gt;A month back I think I saw this video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeidweomi3ue2lgloeq6eoilc3wvoc7wc3nmtq5cfb7q4hg4jfnw2gy.ipfs.dweb.link/redditsave.com_is_it_true_kerala_people_spit_into_food_before-ttcdrtjhucy71.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It shows a man either spitting or blowing on food. I had been to this state Kerala where I did eat and enjoy the food there, but after seeing this video I almost threw up. It is said that certain kind of Muslims in Kerala spit on their food to purify it and they also run large number of hotels. Yak. Yukeee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later it was revealed in some investigation that it was true that Muslims there consider spitting on food makes it Halal (that is Arabic for edible), and so they do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This sent a media storm and finally now it looks like netizens in Kerala want to compile or are compiling a list of hotel’s where they don’t spit on food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeidiwubqfy7uiczktnapfxax6s6hjd7qtyqzr2i74wdlr6ildkoupi.ipfs.dweb.link/redditsave.com_india_today_tries_to_cover_up_the_halal_food-fbp3nbnu4x281.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, I think the damage has already been done. I don’t think I will ever go to Kerala again. I wonder if its God’s country or spitters country. I wonder what worst practices they still hide and that are not known to the outside world for centuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is facing the worst because of religion. Our country is divided into three, Pakistan, India and Bangladesh solely because of religion. We have a religious government called the BJP, headed by a fanatic Narendra Modi, who is controlled by a terror outfit called the RSS which is hell bent on making India into just another Hindu Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While China has given up religion and has emerged top of the world, Bangladesh has shed its Islamic identity and has raced ahead of India in per-capita GDP, we are following religion and are going back to the stone ages. It’s really stupid and sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Islam should refine, Quoran is 1000 years old may be, and what was okay then may not be okay now. I am sure all my Muslim won’t eat food that’s spit on it. Who ever these people are, even if they had to go to hell after death if they don’t spit, then they must say to their God: “so be it, I am not afraid of your hell and pain and suffering you will give to me”, and they must stop spitting on food. It’s disgusting.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A month back I think I saw this video:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">தீதும் நன்றும் பிறர் தர வாரா</title><link href="/2021/11/28/%E0%AE%A4%E0%AF%80%E0%AE%A4%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%A9%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%B1%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%AA%E0%AE%BF%E0%AE%B1%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%A4%E0%AE%B0-%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B0%E0%AE%BE.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="தீதும் நன்றும் பிறர் தர வாரா" /><published>2021-11-28T11:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-11-28T11:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/11/28/%E0%AE%A4%E0%AF%80%E0%AE%A4%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%A9%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%B1%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%AA%E0%AE%BF%E0%AE%B1%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%A4%E0%AE%B0-%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B0%E0%AE%BE</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/11/28/%E0%AE%A4%E0%AF%80%E0%AE%A4%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%A8%E0%AE%A9%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%B1%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%AA%E0%AE%BF%E0%AE%B1%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%A4%E0%AE%B0-%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B0%E0%AE%BE.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;subtle-tone&quot;&gt;Subtle Tone&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeig45mzqcucbvavzu3z2xy4wpjr36xyovunz7etwrg5nhstzlvi5aq.ipfs.dweb.link/buddha_6.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bafybeidhaxf2s57wyncsnrta7altwwssbjvodyaxhji65rf4twsrfsklkm.ipfs.dweb.link/buddha_6.png&quot;&gt;png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bafybeig45mzqcucbvavzu3z2xy4wpjr36xyovunz7etwrg5nhstzlvi5aq.ipfs.dweb.link/buddha_6.svg&quot;&gt;svg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;rich-tone&quot;&gt;Rich Tone&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeidcp27s436s4zwg3s5cub4k7wa4fjgqwpd6y2wcyplonir676nrfe.ipfs.dweb.link/buddha_7.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bafybeib4o4gzhfqwxbfjksktrpei2sbdqi2nvv4fzqc5v66quvvk3soppm.ipfs.dweb.link/buddha_7.png&quot;&gt;png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bafybeidcp27s436s4zwg3s5cub4k7wa4fjgqwpd6y2wcyplonir676nrfe.ipfs.dweb.link/buddha_7.svg&quot;&gt;svg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Subtle Tone</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TransferKit.io the miracle file transfer website</title><link href="/internet/file%20sharing/freedom/2021/11/23/transferkit-io-the-miracle-file-transfer-website.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TransferKit.io the miracle file transfer website" /><published>2021-11-23T21:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-11-23T21:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/internet/file%20sharing/freedom/2021/11/23/transferkit-io-the-miracle-file-transfer-website</id><content type="html" xml:base="/internet/file%20sharing/freedom/2021/11/23/transferkit-io-the-miracle-file-transfer-website.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeidfkbq5bo6xhz4qxq4qepehfwn6p6foz5ojmn7q32bmm4hba4epgm.ipfs.dweb.link/Masala-Aloo-Potatoes.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Potato Masala&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture above is of potato masala, it’s tasty, but you can’t eat it just like that. You need to wrap in on dough and make it as samosa as shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiffyct4idr4spb3juwjgulzst46gybso35zq345rv5uhsi4fjjihe.ipfs.dweb.link/Indian_Samosa_by_clumsy_home_chef.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Samosa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it becomes more edible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The below video is that of a parotta shop in Tamilnadu, India, it weighs 150MB, very good quality and it won’t break my website if you see it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeidwf57vxo3ft5ammqbqtptcofo57l5diati6jqpr4dpbaruvcwwbu.ipfs.dweb.link/redditsave.com_idhu_endha_oor_kadai-v8p2ejtx4k081.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, let me come to the first part.
Potato masala is tasty, but you can’t eat it just like that. You need a good interface like an oil roasted dough covering which converts it into samosa to make it palatable to the masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ipfs&quot;&gt;IPFS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s consider storing files. Long time back I came across this excellent technology called Inter Planetary File System (IPFS), I even used it to construct a block chain for one of my client’s project. I was in a company called Trumatics then. Then my partner got mad at me so frequent, I had to drop out. But the potential of IPFS was visible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me tell it to you in brief. First imagine a website like YouTube. It simply isn’t scalable, they have scaled it, but to keep it afloat they need to put lot of annoying ads in it. That’s because of it’s architecture. You have a single end point &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtube.com&quot;&gt;https://youtube.com&lt;/a&gt; into which you post a file and get it back, in this case a video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine an architecture where I watch a video from the internet, it’s so good that I tell you, and you start watching it, now the video get streamed to you from not only the original source, but from me too, or which ever source is nearby to you. That is rather than relying on centralized storage and distribution, this technology is like Torrent or the one implemented by Napster, Emule etc. In these technologies, as the client base grows, clients become host of the file too. IPFS is just like that. Plus if you put a file in IPFS it never get’s deleted if there are enough storage locations hosting it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;file-coin&quot;&gt;File Coin&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say a actress uploads her video, it get’s watched and stored by many in IPFS and would not get deleted for ages, but say you find a break trough stuff in science and upload a paper, not may would read it, and only your IPFS node would have it, if your computer get’s destroyed or disconnected, the video is lost!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine what if some one can mine coins just by storing your files, then they are getting incentivized, that’s the logic behind file coin. If you put a file in file coin network, you are kind of guaranteed that it will be there for ever, till say the internet is destroyed almost completely. File coin operates on IPFS by slapping a block chain on top of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tansferkit&quot;&gt;TansferKit&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://diasp.org/camo/9a2d089e90ed9cee07647047dae41213168287cb/68747470733a2f2f626166796265696873716f6266656d70376c7475357064627032756367787176766169346c7a326a6b797a717969376935716772696335673769792e697066732e647765622e6c696e6b2f53637265656e73686f74253230323032312d31312d3232253230617425323032312d30332d31362532305472616e736665724b69742532302d253230446563656e7472616c697a656425323046696c652532305472616e736665722e706e67&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;TransferKit&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://TransferKit.io&quot;&gt;TransferKit&lt;/a&gt; provides a neat interface over file coin network. It’s hard to set up a a file coin rig by a normal person, so TransferKit gives you a we UI which you can use to upload files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now if IPFS is like potato, Fie Coin is like cooked potato masala, TransferKit is the dough that wraps around it and roasted into samosa so that you can enjoy! That’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do visit it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://transferkit.io&quot;&gt;https://transferkit.io&lt;/a&gt;, use it to share your files with your friends without restrictions. Always support decentralized internet than pledging your data to evil centralized networks and corporations like Microsoft, Facebook, Google, Apple etc which have to make money because of their design and survival strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the files in this blog were uploaded to TransferKit and used here, and it does not track you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Potato Masala</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Backing up Heroku Postgres database, restoring it locally</title><link href="/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/postgres/heroku/2021/11/21/backing-up-heroku-postgres-database-restoring-it-locally.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Backing up Heroku Postgres database, restoring it locally" /><published>2021-11-21T10:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-11-21T10:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/postgres/heroku/2021/11/21/backing-up-heroku-postgres-database-restoring-it-locally</id><content type="html" xml:base="/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/postgres/heroku/2021/11/21/backing-up-heroku-postgres-database-restoring-it-locally.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.quest.com/community/cfs-filesystemfile/__key/communityserver-components-secureimagefileviewer/communityserver-blogs-components-weblogfiles-00-00-00-00-39/Slide2.JPG_2D00_1100x500x2.jpg?_=637219525519183603&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ever you are doing a complex ticket and want to be really sure it works in production, it’s better to  take a copy of production db and test your changes locally. We mainly use Heroku for our Ruby on Rails deployments and this is to show how we do the production backup stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First we must tell heroku to capture your production data base at current time. For that in your app folder type this command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ heroku pg:backups:capture
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could get the information about the running backup using the following command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ heroku pg:backups:info
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your DB is large, it will take some time, once the backup is completed, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;heroku pg:backups:info&lt;/code&gt; might throw out an output as shown:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;=== Backup b001
Database:         DATABASE
Started at:       2021-11-20 14:13:16 +0000
Finished at:      2021-11-20 14:21:34 +0000
Status:           Completed
Type:             Manual
Original DB Size: 904.40MB
Backup Size:      8.65MB (91% compression)

=== Backup Logs
2021-11-20 14:13:16 +0000 pg_dump: last built-in OID is 16383
2021-11-20 14:13:16 +0000 pg_dump: reading extensions
2021-11-20 14:13:16 +0000 pg_dump: identifying extension members
2021-11-20 14:13:16 +0000 pg_dump: reading schemas
2021-11-20 14:13:16 +0000 pg_dump: reading user-defined tables
2021-11-20 14:13:21 +0000 pg_dump: reading user-defined functions
2021-11-20 14:13:23 +0000 pg_dump: reading user-defined types
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to give your data to a Data Analyst who is not added to your heroku project, you can get a downloadable URL of your backup using this command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ heroku pg:backups:url
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can get a dump of your backup using the following command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ heroku pg:backups:download
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will create a file called &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;latest.dump&lt;/code&gt; in your project folder, to restore it you can use this command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ pg_restore --verbose --clean --no-acl --no-owner -h localhost -d local_db
_name latest.dump
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Linkedin is an anti-social network</title><link href="/work/networking/social%20network/linkedin/2021/11/11/linkedin-is-an-anti-social-network.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Linkedin is an anti-social network" /><published>2021-11-11T19:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-11-11T19:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/work/networking/social%20network/linkedin/2021/11/11/linkedin-is-an-anti-social-network</id><content type="html" xml:base="/work/networking/social%20network/linkedin/2021/11/11/linkedin-is-an-anti-social-network.html">&lt;p&gt;I was on Linkedin and suddenly I received this notification&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/linkedin_2021-11-09 at 09-39-00.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What? I thought. Previously I was interacting with lot of Data Scientists on Linkedin, I was telling them about my &lt;a href=&quot;https://datascience-book.gitlab.io/&quot;&gt;Introduction To Data Science Book&lt;/a&gt;, encouraging them to read it and tell their opinions about it. As Linkedin correctly found out, I was looking into lot of profiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One question I have for Linkedin is this. If Linkedin claims to be a social network, isn’t it a social behavior to meet and tell people about you and to know about them? Why is Linkedin is so pissed off by it and is blocking me from being social? I find it stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft people usually don’t have brains. You can see it from how crappy their operating system is, how complex their Azure service is compared to Linode. They buy companies, inject their greed and management practices into it and let it get devoid of its soul. Such a sad thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish some network like &lt;a href=&quot;https://diasporafoundation.org/&quot;&gt;Diaspora&lt;/a&gt; has a way to ask people their education and company details. Once asked it can connect people accordingly. That’s it, we have Linkedin competitor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linkedin does not generate its own data, people list data there so that they can be found, but Linkedin is doing the exact opposite of a social network. It’s obstructing people from contacting people who would like to be contacted. In other words its antisocial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diaspora and many free software social networks are distributed and open, they can develop an API where if the user is willing, any one can access their information and use it to contact them. This means by moving away from Linkedin, people will be truly linked in!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was on Linkedin and suddenly I received this notification</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DMK ministers are making fool of themselves</title><link href="/india/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/chennai/flood/corruption/2021/11/09/dmk-ministers-are-making-fool-of-themselves.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DMK ministers are making fool of themselves" /><published>2021-11-09T07:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-11-09T07:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/chennai/flood/corruption/2021/11/09/dmk-ministers-are-making-fool-of-themselves</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/chennai/flood/corruption/2021/11/09/dmk-ministers-are-making-fool-of-themselves.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7b/Ex.mayor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Ma. Subramanian (DMK Minister)&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was telling to my friends that sooner or later DMK ministers will start blaming AIAMK for Chennai floods and it happened. I switched on the T.V and in it was Ma. Subramanian. Exactly as I was saying he said the flooding in Chennai was caused by AIADMK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, there is simple question, if you promised good life in manifesto, you must deliver it. Since ADMK ruled Tamilnadu before and hence never can Tamil’s have a good life even if DMK comes to power, then it must be specified in manifesto as well. Has DMK manifesto said that they can’t provide us with good life during rains because ADMK ruled before? If not why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://image.nakkheeran.in/cdn/farfuture/UjIHjGoUOsiaKB5XAhmXenLVd7HaTUE2CSqWZOHG5Bk/1544698206/sites/default/files/inline-images/senthil%20balaji%2055.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Senthil Balaji (Power Minister)&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, this power minister Senthil Balaji who before blamed squirrels for power cuts. He said people should be careful with power infrastructure during rains. My simple question is why? Why should we be careful? If infrastructure in Tamilnadu is not good enough to transmit power safely during rains, then don’t transmit power. Say that’s the state of power infrastructure. Why put this rule and that rule upon people all of a sudden? Say that Varuna Bhagavan doesn’t like Tamilnadu to have electricity, and let’s go back to the age where we had wooden and cow dung fires for energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short why can’t DMK admit they are party who cannot give us good life if AIADMK ruled before them. That’s what they are saying indirectly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Ma. Subramanian (DMK Minister)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Every Indian Should Watch Jai Bhim</title><link href="/india/tamilnadu/law%20and%20order/police/murder/2021/11/03/why-every-indian-should-watch-jai-bhim.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Every Indian Should Watch Jai Bhim" /><published>2021-11-03T13:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-11-03T13:05:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/tamilnadu/law%20and%20order/police/murder/2021/11/03/why-every-indian-should-watch-jai-bhim</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/tamilnadu/law%20and%20order/police/murder/2021/11/03/why-every-indian-should-watch-jai-bhim.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://1847884116.rsc.cdn77.org/telugu/home/jai-bhim-teaser-151021.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I follow some journalists on twitter, and one of them from THE HINDU tweeted a lot about Jai Bhim, I think even before the movie launched he tweeted how good it was. I thought he and THE HINDU were bribed by the producers of this movie. There was a reson, I think years before THE HINDU wrote lot of articles praising TATA motors, and TATA motors ads would appear in the paper. I bought a TATA nano and it was worst to say the least. So I have always doubted THE HINDU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But any way since they were promoting the movie, I decided to watch hoping that it would be just another waste of time, but at least I can relax at that time and build more bad opinions about THE HINDU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boy oh boy, I was absolutely wrong! Wrong wrong wrong! The story is about a layer named Chandru or something, this guy helped oppressed people like workers, kuravars and many many more to get their rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know that Tamilnadu police treats us very badly. In the theft takes place, a cop does not know how to solve it (I think he was aiding the thief), so he arrests a suspected kuruvan who was there in that house for catching snake earlier. That kuravan had never committed the crime, the police torture him to death and plays a dram that accused escaped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The police were super cunning and planted false evidences and witnesses to make people believe these people really made out of the prison. It took the brilliant work of Chandru to bring things to light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;possibly-the-greatest-terrorist-organization&quot;&gt;Possibly the greatest terrorist organization&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jai Bhim is brilliant movie, it exposes possibly the greatest terrorist organization that’s there in this nation. If a terrorist kills, he admits he killed some one, and may be if we want to hang that terrorist, he won’t be afraid to be a martyr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Tamilnadu Police is far far more cunning, they want to inflict terror upon people, yet they wish not to die or get hurt by it. It’s a coward way of living, but that’s how Tamilnadu police is says this movie. It’s a slap on their face. but the police won’t bothe, I’m sure, they are far far evil to be shaken by a movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt bad, I go around telling my fiends to install solar cells on their roofs, urge them to buy electric vehicles so that we import less oil. Our oil spending is used by Islamic nations to fund terrorist activities against us just because some guy called Muhammad, who at that time starved in caves and illusion-ed that he met God’s angels told that Islam would spread to India. So bad! So these idiots now want to convert entire India into an Islamic nation. It’s a stupid thought, but that’s what they want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But greater than them we have a great terror organization amongst us which we cannot reform or be destroy or change in any way. That’s the movies point. I feel it’s a good thing to bring evil to light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look no further, we have this Thuthukudi massacre which Edapaadi Palanisamy (EPS) did, he hasn’t been hanged yet (this proves that there is no difference between ADMK and DMK, and they have some form of nexus), a terrorist murdered people for EPS so possibly he can et lot from Vendata.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.tollykata.com/media_images_files/large/jayaraj_1312.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Felix &amp;amp; Jayaraj. Father Son Duo who was murdered by Tamilnadu police for fun.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next we have this Felix and Jayaraj who were murdered for fun by the police, and we all know those murderers will escape and we can do nothing about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;disrespecting-the-true-indians&quot;&gt;Disrespecting the true Indians&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/1/165/352752649_01bd238ea9_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;A Kuravan selling beads necklace&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jai Bhim also tells about the Kuravar community. It’s possible they were in India even before Dravidian civilization took shape in Africa, and reached India via Mesopotamia and Iran.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/8a/7c/40/8a7c40aae9ef6d5a4e225e8cb0af0494.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Valli the Kurathi, new wife of Muruga welcomed by his first wife Devaiyani&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were the guardians of the forrest, fortune tellers, they brought us the wealth of nature without destroying it. It’s said Lod Muruga fell in love with a Kurathi and married her. But look now how we treat them? Agriculture has destroyed our forrest, and industries are destroying our agriculture. The Kuravars are left helpless, our system has shut out the true people of our land in favor of invading Dravidians and Aryans. that’s very sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;movies-should-be-like-this&quot;&gt;Movies should be like this&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually Tamil movie is nothing but a love affair between hero and heroine, and before they can fuck each other, they have to do 4 dances, and the hero had to do 4 fights to impress the girl. That’s it. This movie is totally different. They want to make a movie this time and not a circus and call it a movie. That’s refreshing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie looks so believable (though I believe the murderers were never hanged and managed to escape), and this is how movies should be. But I have no hopes for future Tamil movies, they just want to make money and will return back to cheap quality soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;you-must-watch&quot;&gt;You must watch&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only if we know evils in our society, at least we will start taking about let, let alone destroying it. No Indian has the balls to challenge these evils. At least know what these evils are and pretend to act like a man.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When Trix Image / Attachment does not upload to Amazon S3</title><link href="/web%20development/ruby%20on%20rails/trix/aws/s3/2021/11/01/when-trix-image-attachment-does-not-upload-to-amazon-s3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When Trix Image / Attachment does not upload to Amazon S3" /><published>2021-11-01T08:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-11-01T08:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/web%20development/ruby%20on%20rails/trix/aws/s3/2021/11/01/when-trix-image-attachment-does-not-upload-to-amazon-s3</id><content type="html" xml:base="/web%20development/ruby%20on%20rails/trix/aws/s3/2021/11/01/when-trix-image-attachment-does-not-upload-to-amazon-s3.html">&lt;p&gt;An app was all set and done and I had to test it, we had a commenting system and a rich text commenting was needed and hence we went for Trix editor which integrates well with Ruby on Rails. A problem arose, when we used local storage the image uploads worked, but when we used Amazon S3 it did not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out that Trix uploads images directly to storage, and let’s say if you are uploading from say &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:3000&quot;&gt;http://localhost:3000&lt;/a&gt;, you must whitelist it in Amzon S3 bucket. So we did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So go to your S3 console, you will have a tab call &lt;strong&gt;Permission&lt;/strong&gt;,  click it and scroll down, and this thing called &lt;strong&gt;Cross-origin resource sharing (CORS) would&lt;/strong&gt; appear&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/s3_cors.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add the text below in it and save.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;[
    {
        &quot;AllowedHeaders&quot;: [
            &quot;*&quot;
        ],
        &quot;AllowedMethods&quot;: [
            &quot;PUT&quot;,
            &quot;POST&quot;,
            &quot;DELETE&quot;
        ],
        &quot;AllowedOrigins&quot;: [
            &quot;http://localhost:3000&quot;
        ],
        &quot;ExposeHeaders&quot;: []
    }
]
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are using some other domain like &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;https://abc.ocm&lt;/code&gt;, then it should be added instead of &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;http://localhost:3000&lt;/code&gt;. Now add your image in Trix, it should sit upload to S3 bucket like charm.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">An app was all set and done and I had to test it, we had a commenting system and a rich text commenting was needed and hence we went for Trix editor which integrates well with Ruby on Rails. A problem arose, when we used local storage the image uploads worked, but when we used Amazon S3 it did not.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Businesses are Afraid of Kerala</title><link href="/india/kerala/business/2021/10/29/why-businesses-are-afraid-of-kerala.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Businesses are Afraid of Kerala" /><published>2021-10-29T12:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-10-29T12:05:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/kerala/business/2021/10/29/why-businesses-are-afraid-of-kerala</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/kerala/business/2021/10/29/why-businesses-are-afraid-of-kerala.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.steppestravel.com/app/uploads/2019/06/village-boat-view-backwaters-kerala-india.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I  was consulting for a company named Guidehouse in Trivandrum, Kerala. All was going good, none said anything bad about me or doubted my performance. Then there was a meeting all of a sudden, in it three of the people there, the H.R Shyam, Suresh Vasudev (Associate Director), and a person called Jeff who is some one senior in it tech ranking was there. They opened 4 page document saying that in my 9 months of work there, these were all the mistakes I did. When I questioned them they said I was behaving like a junior developer than a tech architect. I was shocked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a mistake was found about me, why not tell it then so that I can correct it and be productive and contribute to the organization? Why wait for 6 or 7 months thus degrading the organizations productivity?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To tell the truth, most of the accusations in the document about me were false and bogus. They demanded me to do three projects in a month which was impossible to complete and some could not be stated because I do not have right access to systems, getting access would take weeks, I have to complete those tasks in 28 days. Clearly it was an impossible thing to do. I frankly told them if they want to fire me I was ready to go out and I have no regret, but they insisted this is not firing procedure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They gave me the tasks, I refused to do, and they forced me out of the company so it looked like I left. I was devastated and shocked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My neighbor’s relative who himself an Keralite told me that that’s how Malyalis behave, they are full of politics he said. My point is your upbringing could be anything, but running a business, that too a tech company is near science and you have to be honest and practical to the hilt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why I am writing this now? Well, yesterday I saw in news that some one in Kerala had filed a petition against Tamilnadu government to limit the water level of Mullai Periyar dam to 132 feet, kinda 10 feet less than the maximum. This is done even though its established that the dam is safe in its full capacity. Its a pure case of a sadist who wants to bully Tamil’s. The sad thing is Kerala government supports that person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On one hand you agree to some thing, and all of a sudden since you are a sadist
you make a U-turn and hurt others for unnecessary reason. It was very same for me too, they way they welcomed me to Guidehouse was great, I left other offers to go there, the way they insulted me and sent me out was very cheap, and I am proud not to work in Kerala any more. I would never work there unless for very compelling reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just me and state of Tamilnadu, but imagine how many companies, professionals and businesses in Kerala would have been harassed by people with such mentality. How many life’s would have been degraded, tossed to the bin without a reason just because a bunch of people who’s upbringing involves nurturing sadistic thought in them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always wondered why Kerala has such a massive debt, why it was such underdeveloped that too when it borders Tamilnadu? I wonder why so many of its own people could not find work there and had to go abroad? Perhaps now I know why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be Kerala till now is like this, I call upon the youth of Kerala to reform, come into the modern world, form agreement with other people and stick to the agreement and make yourself valuable asset than an doubtful object. You had come into this world with nothing, even if you loose everything being honest, or if you become rich by plundering others wealth by cheating, you will still die with nothing. The choice of life’s path is yours.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Using Bootstrap Icons in Ruby on Rails</title><link href="/programming/web%20development/ruby%20on%20rails/2021/10/18/using-bootstrap-icons-in-ruby-on-rails.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Using Bootstrap Icons in Ruby on Rails" /><published>2021-10-18T10:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-10-18T10:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/web%20development/ruby%20on%20rails/2021/10/18/using-bootstrap-icons-in-ruby-on-rails</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/web%20development/ruby%20on%20rails/2021/10/18/using-bootstrap-icons-in-ruby-on-rails.html">&lt;p&gt;This seems to be the right way that bootstrap icons should be added to Ruby on Rails, I have tried many other ways, some work in local and fail in production, others work in normal production boxes but fail in Heroku, this one seems to work every where.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First you need to add bootstrap-icons to your project using yarn like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ yarn add bootstrap-icons
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next at the end of &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;app/assets/stylesheets/application.scss&lt;/code&gt; add this code:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-css highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;@import&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&quot;bootstrap-icons/font/bootstrap-icons&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;@font-face&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;font-family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&quot;bootstrap-icons&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;src&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;font-url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&quot;bootstrap-icons/font/fonts/bootstrap-icons.woff2&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;format&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&quot;woff2&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;font-url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&quot;bootstrap-icons/font/fonts/bootstrap-icons.woff&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;format&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&quot;woff&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can start using bootstrap icons like this now:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-erb highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;This is the icon for pencil &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;i&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;class=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;bi bi-pencil&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yo could write a helper, in &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;app/helpers/bootstrap_icon_helper.rb&lt;/code&gt; add htis:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;module&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;BootstrapIconHelper&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;sx&quot;&gt;%Q{
      &amp;lt;i class=&quot;bi bi-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sx&quot;&gt;&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt;
    }&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now in your application views, you can use icon like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-erb highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;This is the icon for pencil &lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;%=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;pencil&apos;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;%&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are working under a psycho boss who says there must be brackets for Ruby method calls, you can code like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-erb highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;This is the icon for pencil &lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;%=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;pencil&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;%&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This seems to be the right way that bootstrap icons should be added to Ruby on Rails, I have tried many other ways, some work in local and fail in production, others work in normal production boxes but fail in Heroku, this one seems to work every where.</summary></entry></feed>