<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-08-16T20:14:57+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Looking for sponsors for my Ruby Book</title><link href="/2017/08/16/looking-for-sponsors-for-my-ruby-book.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Looking for sponsors for my Ruby Book" /><published>2017-08-16T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-16T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/08/16/looking-for-sponsors-for-my-ruby-book</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/08/16/looking-for-sponsors-for-my-ruby-book.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://b2aeaa58a57a200320db-8b65b95250e902c437b256b5abf3eac7.ssl.cf5.rackcdn.com/media_entries/4819/front_cover.medium.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just told on the Internet that my ruby book has a permanent webpage here &lt;a href=&quot;https://mindaslab.github.io/I-Love-Ruby/&quot;&gt;https://mindaslab.github.io/I-Love-Ruby/&lt;/a&gt; and to my suprise I had more than 550 visitors less than 2 days. Thats a lot for programming book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/600_views.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes the book is a good one, you will know when you visit “What people say” section. Many people have given good reviews about it. I did have bad reviews from people, but soon found out they were bogus except for one or two who pointed out some grammatical mistakes. I was affected by lot of prejudice too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I am happy, a language thats made me food, given me shelter and clothing for some time is made easy to understand by me. I wanted to say how my book smashed things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Its free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My book is free 100%. Free in material, as you can download it free from Github.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its also free by soul. Its been copyrighted under GNU free documentation license (GFDL) so that all humanity can use it without restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not restricted by publisher&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I went to a publisher, I would have had lot of restrictions. People would have told this and that and I would have given up. Without publisher, I had no deadline. The first books of I Love Ruby had very less content, but then editions started to appear, sometimes even more than one edition per day. Today this has got a term now, they call rolling release. This lack of management and the ability to write when I want to write may have brought out the best in me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;looking-for-sponsors&quot;&gt;Looking for sponsors&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am looking for Ruby related companies to sponsor my work. If you like to please contact me. I am wishing to spend my time writing books so that people can understand technology better, become a better technician and earn with a smile. Sponsoring won’t be easy as I am not willing to give up my sovereignty for money. But if you think Ruby has made your life better for you and your office you might consider to sponsor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">No to buying property yet in Chennai</title><link href="/2017/08/14/no-to-buying-property-yet-in-chennai.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="No to buying property yet in Chennai" /><published>2017-08-14T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-14T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/08/14/no-to-buying-property-yet%20in-chennai</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/08/14/no-to-buying-property-yet-in-chennai.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chennaibeachhouse.files.wordpress.com/2010/05/dsc06392.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So should I buy a property now? The answer is no. Definitely not in Chennai. Yes the property prices have fallen, that does not mean that the property has a fair price. Just imagine, can you own the property fully in 5-years, of course after taking care of other expenses? If not why? Think why the prices are so high?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The basic reason for astronomical prices of property is greed. People did not buy seeing what will be the buying potential of people in future, but they bought home and lands so that magically they will become rich. This also made sure that lot of people with black money invested in thus driving up prices further. Now none can buy a property at a sane price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5 years of ones life is more than 5% of your life. Imagine should you waste so much for a house? Even if you buy a flat or an independent house in a colony, you need to pay  maintainance fees. In cities like Chennai it would easily be Rs 3000/- or higher. Thats Rs 100 a day. If you can cook, 100 rupees will be enough for you to make a decent food a day (of course it will be vegetarian). Plus there will be all these restrictions you must abide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The greed must vanish, people must look at what people can really purchase and they must lower the price. Rather than some company or individual deciding the prices of flats and land, the market should determine it. Though there are ready made homes now, none are buying it. When the prices were high didn’t the Realtors made us to wait for years even before lifting the foundation? Why they were so evil then and why they appear to advertise they are so good now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think people, think. We have bowed to marketing weather by corporates or by politicians and we have made our lives difficult. So think a lot before taking a life changing decision.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Accidents around Sithalapakkam</title><link href="/2017/08/12/accidents-around-sithalapakkam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Accidents around Sithalapakkam" /><published>2017-08-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/08/12/accidents-around-sithalapakkam</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/08/12/accidents-around-sithalapakkam.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/85/Sunrise_in_Sithalapakkam.JPG/1920px-Sunrise_in_Sithalapakkam.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last Thursday, on 10th, I took my car out for my office, right at Sithapakkam junction @ Mambakkam road / checkpost, I saw the concrete diver was smashed into pieces. Something from Ponmaar was going towards Medavakkam when it seems to have smashed into the divider. I later learned that a water tanker smashed. It was said that as the tanker crashed, it climbed up the divider, I was able to notice the ascent in the divider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also heard that a Ritz car driven by some college guys traveling from Medvakkam towards Sithalapakkam smashed head on at the divider before Gold winner oil company. I also heard that couples, old people apparently, Standing in Amman Kovil or Valluvar nagar bus stop in Sithalapakkam were hit by an yellow board vehicle and they both died, the vehicle ran away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All these things have happened literally just few stone throws away from my home, it makes me wonder what the local councilor, traffic police, the transport minister and Tamilnadu government is doing? I also admire at the efficiency of the bureaucracy, all these things have not appeared in main stream news channels. How these incidents have been efficiently hushed up? Or is media in Tamilnadu is just sleeping? I have no idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While driving back home from office at about 7:30 PM on the same 10th, the traffic was badly blocked, a van had hit the divider in front of Ramarao body works. I had witnessed evidence of an accident and another fresh accident happened just minutes before on the same day. The driver in the van hadn’t got out, the crumple zone before him was crumpled and his side of windshield bore a crack. The van was going towards Medavakkam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The politicians go door to door distributing money, bags of free rice and other goodies during election time, but they fail to put lamps on Medavakkam to Mambakkam road. Its really dark, we locals know which roads turns where, new one won’t as the roads badly turn at wrong places. There are speed breakers and numerous potholes here and there which new people won’t know. They could stick enough reflective stickers on those concrete dividers rather than erecting posters bearing their ugly looking faces on corner here and there. Around Medavakkam to Mambakkam road, there are three liquor shops, wonder if these are contributing to accidents? The police seem to stop goods lorries, water tankers and other merchant vehicles for inspection, but never I have seen in my neighborhood any one been stopped for drunk driving even though with an very untrained eye I have seen many people drive erratically around my neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish Sithalapakkam people were not stupid either, till today they seemed to have succumbed to the fores of bribes from politicians. I wish people think before they vote so that the neighborhood would become a better place.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Openmailbox restricts free users</title><link href="/2017/08/08/openmailbox-restricts-free-users.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Openmailbox restricts free users" /><published>2017-08-08T21:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-08T21:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/08/08/openmailbox-restricts-free-users</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/08/08/openmailbox-restricts-free-users.html">&lt;p&gt;Gmail and most of commercial emails track us in a shameless way. They have no
regard for our privacy. They scan our mails, sell us to advertisers, treat us as
a commodity. As a perk we get to use their email service as free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After NSA, Julian Assange and all those stuff, people have started to think.
Rather than having all emails in one large Gmail who has the possibility to know
about all, people who were conscious of these evils migrated to other services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One possible minnow email hosting provider was openmailbox. Though it was small
it seemed to have a big heart. It gave away a gigabyte of space for free. It also
ran own cloud for you so you could host your files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Owncloud is morally superior to Google Drive and Dropbox and works better than them.
I hosted my books on Openmailbox cloud instances so that people could download
them for free. All things went well until recently their Owncloud offering seems to have
collapsed, and my Thunderbird reported that it can no longer fetch email from Openmailbox
servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hope and Betrayal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked open mailbox on twitter weather my Owncloud will work, for which this was
their reply&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Any WebDAV based client will work in a few days&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Openmailbox (@openmailbox_org) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/openmailbox_org/status/893746011553878016&quot;&gt;August 5, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe them 100%, they never indicated that only paid service will work, and
now in their website I see this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/openmailbox_becomes_paid.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, its not wrong to make service paid, these were the mistakes done by open
mail box&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Free users were never told that they can access all service if and only they
become paid&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No warning was given to backup and migrate data and email&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to add to fuel to flame Openmailbox claims most people love this move&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The vast majority of people are currently very happy about the changes!&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Openmailbox (@openmailbox_org) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/openmailbox_org/status/894631423474376705&quot;&gt;August 7, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thats bloody bullshit. People must have been given sufficient warning so that
they can move out. Just making some good service go off doesn’t make them
worthwhile for the trust we have on them and the propaganda we made for them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Gmail and most of commercial emails track us in a shameless way. They have no regard for our privacy. They scan our mails, sell us to advertisers, treat us as a commodity. As a perk we get to use their email service as free.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Axis bank lets me down</title><link href="/2017/08/08/axis-bank-lets-me-down.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Axis bank lets me down" /><published>2017-08-08T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-08T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/08/08/axis-bank-lets-me-down</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/08/08/axis-bank-lets-me-down.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mercantile.in/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Axis-bank-logo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have been in times where you have to transfer money or make a payment at a crucial 
time? A situation like that happened to me yesterday and I had to use Axis bank
payment method. I entered the amount that has to be paid and I waited for OTP (
one time password). I waited and waited it never arrived. I hit the “RESEND OTP” button
and it was still the same. I waited. Then I hit the “On Call OTP” button and
still nothing happened even though I was promised to receive a call within a
minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then after 20 - 30 minutes or so I got the OTP (definetly an expired on by now).
Thinking that their systems have became normal I tried paying once again and it 
was the same. No new OTP came and I never got a call that would spell out an OTP
for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went for lunch, nearly 90 minutes later I got series of calls from Axis bank,
a robot called me and chatted out OTP to me. Grrr, I was in hotel, and even if I
had stayed on web page and continued, my session would have expired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Axis bank is third largest Bank in India and its technology is so weak. I am an
 engineer and as web engineer we deal with problem like these. What should happen
 if your server is over loaded? What should happen if there is an earthquake where
 your servers are located? Believe me, without leaving the comfort of your couch
 you can Google for answers and implement it. No kidding. Its difficult to think
 such a large institution would have neglected to think in that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the least they could have sent or shown me a message saying that their system
 queue is overloaded and its not advisable to do a transaction online. This problem
 I think still persists at this moment, I made a payment via check finally. I wonder
 why these banks boast of digital banking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope bitcoin catches up in India.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Invitation, Coimbatore Style</title><link href="/2017/08/03/invitation-coimbatore-style.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Invitation, Coimbatore Style" /><published>2017-08-03T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-03T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/08/03/invitation-coimbatore-style</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/08/03/invitation-coimbatore-style.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://im0.indiarailinfo.com/0/NEXT/NEXT/NEXT/NEXT/1659387/0/picsart1448295529880613480.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently a bunch of people from Coimbatore became acquittance with me and they
became important people in my life. I have had many problems with people from that region
in my past. I am a Agile project manager and very open and jovial. Living
in Tamilnadu, a place where there are lot of Coimbatore people, I had to manage
them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have found that its those people who fall off from my team often. They are dull,
don’t speak much and I feel their life is non-colorful and they have no taste and
passion for Computer technology. It would look like they have learned
computer science in a dream to get rich rather than for the love of it. Its very
similar like two people in thirties getting married because they are getting
aged quickly rather than they have really felt one another’s love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When this Coimbatore bunch became known to me, I had forgotten the lesson what
I had learned from them, possibly ignored it for my convenience and things struck
one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was an invitation to a function in Banglore that they wanted to attend with me.
I was certain I will not be able to find tickets on a train and since bus travel
will be tiring and aircraft ridiculously expensive when booked short I said no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time passed. One person in that gang, I still don’t know what happened to him,
possibly he was drunk, God knows, called me one day,  just a few days before the function was about
to happen. He said that he will not attend the function if I do not attend it. I
was confused. That guy kept repeating the same thing again and again despite me
refusing it repeatedly. In a haste to end the conversation I said I will attend.
I honestly thought that’s the end of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This first thing made me wonder. Lets say that I am in a hotel with a friend of
mine, I order poori and friend orders rava dosai. Even though that person is a
friend of mine, will it be okay if I insist that I will eat poori only if my
friend orders it too? Shouldn’t one respect others privacy and choice? Here is the
second one…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then that guy (, possibly more pegs must have gone in by now) said I must make sure
another senior person too must attend the function. I said tickets are not
available on train and it was verified by some travel agent who made a living by
booking train tickets. But that guy went on. ‘There are four trains available, you
must get tickets’. Like a tape recorder he repeated this too despite me telling
him again and again the facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I seriously had no idea what happened to that person and began to worry. His opinion
about me counts. I really thought something happened to him, the drunk theory did
not cross my mind then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I told a person very close to them, and asked if they had influenced this guy to
speak like this. For some reason it became a serious issue and this Coimbatore gang
thinks bad of me. All I was really doing at that time was ending my day, wishing
for good sleep and thinking about my company and felling grateful to what I had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its strange what rules people have. I was invited for a Hindu function. Hindus
in India can have very strange beliefs and rules and you can see here in
&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/21/strange-hindu-rules.html&quot;&gt;Strange Hindu Rules&lt;/a&gt;. Some how other
Coimbatore people don’t find that person crazy, but they don’t wish to speak
about this incident any more. People even say that this is showing respect in Coimbatore style.
Well, then this is the strangest piece of thing I have ever encountered in my
life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">University of Sandiego uses my work</title><link href="/2017/07/26/university-of-sandiego-uses-my-work.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="University of Sandiego uses my work" /><published>2017-07-26T20:08:52+05:30</published><updated>2017-07-26T20:08:52+05:30</updated><id>/2017/07/26/university-of-sandiego-uses-my-work</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/07/26/university-of-sandiego-uses-my-work.html">&lt;p&gt;I  was taking a &lt;a href=&quot;https://courses.edx.org/courses/course-v1:UCSanDiegoX+DSE200x+2T2017/course/&quot;&gt;Python Datascience course&lt;/a&gt;
on Edx, when in one of the video tutorials I  saw this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ucs_uses_my_work.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I  was stunned. Why? Because you see a car in there? It was created by me. You can
find it in Openclipart here &lt;a href=&quot;https://openclipart.org/detail/173850/race-car&quot;&gt;https://openclipart.org/detail/173850/race-car&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was very pleasing to see my work been used in one of the course I am taking.
This is how freedom progresses, you do a work and give it away for free, then
some one uses it as a building block in his or her work and uses it for something
and give it off for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The course I am taking comes in two version, one is free and another costs $350.
Unfortunately my image is available in paid version too and not even a dollar
will be given me out of the $350 charged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well thats how the world works.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was taking a Python Datascience course on Edx, when in one of the video tutorials I saw this:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Strange Hindu Rules</title><link href="/2017/07/21/strange-hindu-rules.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Strange Hindu Rules" /><published>2017-07-21T21:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-07-21T21:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/07/21/strange-hindu-rules</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/07/21/strange-hindu-rules.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-l--sUQAVskw/To0hdbaqLDI/AAAAAAAAEck/SzrbYIRCLEs/s1600/hindu-god-ganesha-pillayar-vinayagar-picture.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today @ office, a lady from below came to give some money to me, it was some adjustments for our office complex maintenance.  I opened the wooden door and through the grill gate stretched my hand to receive it. To my surprise she told me to open the grill gate, I wondered why when a bank note would just slip through the grills? Any way she looked far older than me and I did not want to  disappoint her, so I opened the grill and showed my hand. To my surprise, she asked me step out of the office door. I was utterly confused, but coming out of Hindu family I understood this was just another blind faith. When I stepped out she handed me the cash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In office there was a guy who is a regular Hindu, he told that there is rule in Hinduism which prevents such money transfer. Damn humans!!! What that lady is going to do next? Perform &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sati_(practice)&quot;&gt;Sati&lt;/a&gt; when her husband dies? Why? Why? WHY people are so stupid?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not just Hindus. Its all religions i feel are crack. Pork tastes so good and Muslims won’t eat it. Beef is plentiful and Hindus won’t eat it. I also came across a group called Jehovah Witness which says Christians are crack, but they believe none is dead. In short a group that consists of crack people says Christian religion is crack. Wonder how they figured it out?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it not high time for Human race to throw blind faith out and embrace science?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I bet on Ruby on Rails</title><link href="/2017/07/21/why-i-bet-on-ruby-on-rails.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I bet on Ruby on Rails" /><published>2017-07-21T13:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-07-21T13:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/07/21/why-i-bet-on-ruby-on-rails</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/07/21/why-i-bet-on-ruby-on-rails.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.vizteams.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/ruby-on-rails.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long long ago I was working in a kind of company that was corporate but called itself a startup to please itself.  There I was introduced to a management tool that was excellent and it captured the mindset of todays developers. The client then terminated his project and I approached the I.T department of the company about th product and they did not understand its significance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time went by many startups began to use the tool and now its a thriving business. I have my own company now and wanted to use the tool badly, but it was prohibitively expensive. My company is a small one and cannot afford it, but I did not want to loose productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our free time we started to  clone the tools features and within a month using Ruby on Rails we have our own tool now. Mine is a pure service company and because of a hobby we have a product now. Now we can use the productivity tool for 1/5th of its original cost. Its an enormous saving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can offer it cheap so that many Indian companies can now use it too.  Still we haven’t rolled it in our office, but others are stunned what Ruby on Rails team has done. Most of the credit goes to awesome Ruby as well as the Rails community. We were able to look at the behavior of the tool and we were able to come up with our own. We took the good features and dropped off the boring features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite many javascript frameworks bragging about their stuff, we used none, none more than jQuery. It was a good exercise we had done, it would surely benefit us, and possibly benefit the world if we move the tool in right direction.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Foul Smelling Velacherry</title><link href="/india/chennai/velacherry/2017/07/10/foul-smelling-velacherry.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Foul Smelling Velacherry" /><published>2017-07-10T19:10:52+05:30</published><updated>2017-07-10T19:10:52+05:30</updated><id>/india/chennai/velacherry/2017/07/10/foul-smelling-velacherry</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/chennai/velacherry/2017/07/10/foul-smelling-velacherry.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://farm1.staticflickr.com/115/258335544_26fdbaf151_z.jpg?zz=1&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took  a walk on the roof top of my office, and noticed something, it was smelling
foul due to something rotting. My office is in Velacherry which is supposed to
be a prime area. An area where the rich, tax evaders, law breakers exists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Velacherry always smells foul for some reason. When you approach it, near
Pallikaranai it smells foul, today garbage is dumped in Perungudi which includes
garbage from many first world nations. Winds blowing across it ends up in Velacherry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a very uncomfortable walk and had to end it prematurely. Its sad that being
such a filthy area, Velacherry is regarded as very premium Real Estate spot in Chennai.
Many fools believed it and had got their properties there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not just Velacherry, even Medavakkam has a huge problem with air. There is
some garbage dump in Medavakkam in which fire is lit every evening. Most times
when I drive through the air is filled with the smell of burning plastic which
is a carcinogenic substance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder why rulers of Tamilnadu were and are such a waste. They are unable to
keep their capital clean. And I wonder why people are idiotic to reside in such
a ill-healthy city like Chennai.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>