<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-12-03T19:21:01+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Need for Tamil Professional Examination</title><link href="/2022/12/03/need-for-tamil-professional-examination.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Need for Tamil Professional Examination" /><published>2022-12-03T16:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-03T16:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/03/need-for-tamil-professional-examination</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/03/need-for-tamil-professional-examination.html">&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I went to hotel named Balaji Bhavan in Sithalapakkam, none except two were there in the hotel (excluding two customers who were sitting like zombies), some lady was doing some work and at the counter there was this guy. I asked for a kothu parotta parcel and he said “kothu parotta”, the way he said it confirmed he was from north India. I wanted to ask what’s there in their hotel’s menu, so I asked it, and he said “kothu parotta”. I asked him what all items / dishes he had, he said “kothu parotta”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got fed up and started walking out of the hotel and said cancel it, he said “kothu parotta ready”, I walked out any way wondering how kothu parotta could be ready within two minutes. It’s annoying with these people now days, though I know Hindi, I am a Tamil and my Hindi did not kick in, these northern people have an illusion that everywhere in India Hindi is spoken, they come here uneducated and irritate us. It’s great that Tamilnadu is providing work for these people and is contributing to the uplifting of North India, but at the same time our government should ensure these people are educated to serve us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plan is this, just like IELTS, we must have Tamil Professional Examination that every worker in Tamilnadu should take. Its syllabus should contain practical Tamil and must train people speak and write fluently. Imagine for example, how good it will be if doctors write medicine names in Tamil and medicine comes with Tamil labels in them? The syllabus should contain basic Tamil grammar and history, so that these workers who should take it by law to work in our land can speak fluently with us and serve us better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite dynastic politics and deep-rooted corruption that erode us, Tamils are hard workers, and we are developing. We are the most urbanized state in India, our economy too is diverse, we have plan to reach 1 trillion $ economy, and it’s high time we make our work force work smooth with us.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yesterday I went to hotel named Balaji Bhavan in Sithalapakkam, none except two were there in the hotel (excluding two customers who were sitting like zombies), some lady was doing some work and at the counter there was this guy. I asked for a kothu parotta parcel and he said “kothu parotta”, the way he said it confirmed he was from north India. I wanted to ask what’s there in their hotel’s menu, so I asked it, and he said “kothu parotta”. I asked him what all items / dishes he had, he said “kothu parotta”.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Does Coimbatore contain high number of psychopaths?</title><link href="/2022/11/28/does-coimbatore-contain-high-number-of-psychopaths.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Does Coimbatore contain high number of psychopaths?" /><published>2022-11-28T20:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-28T20:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/28/does-coimbatore-contain-high-number-of-psychopaths</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/28/does-coimbatore-contain-high-number-of-psychopaths.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/CHIL_SEZ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was taking a walk today when I remembered this phone conversation in which a Coimbatore guy was saying something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“My wife and her father had to take medicine to keep them mentally stable, this illness comes with high intelligence.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just then I was reminded how my life was tormented by people in Coimbatore belt. It was in a company called Z**ec where I was a project manager, another woman was also a project manager, she was from Coimbatore. She knew nothing about I.T and code, but lusted for power, she was like Nandhini in Ponniyin Selvan, I think life hurts her very much, possibly she did not like her marriage. She was highly sociable person, but she behaved like a psycho. I would give my team member a task, only to see that he had been seduced by her to complete her task. I was shocked and called her, and she threatened me to book me in harassing case. I was shocked a bit, but then I gained all my strength, told her to proceed, and I took it as my personal mission to work against her underground and looks like it paid off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that same company there was an old jalra guy to the management who was a true psychopath, who enjoyed putting grief into people, and he was this evil woman’s partner. This evil woman was from Coimbatore, I do suspect this evil guy was also from Coimbatore, but I am not sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that same company I met a great guy, who workers praised as a great manager, we ended up forming our own company, but guess what, think about one year of operation that guys started to shout at people like a mad dog. He shouted at me too for no reason. None of us could get it, he was from Salem, not Coimbatore. I don’t know Tamilnadu map, but I wouldn’t be surprised if Salem was near to Coimbatore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my girlfriend’s was near Coimbatore, and she behaved like she loved me and denied it, I wish she is happy now, but her dad’s sister was mentally unstable and did commit suicide. She herself did want to commit suicide once, and I have to talk to her for days to bring her out of it. I am happy I did not end up marrying her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As though I had committed a lot of sin, this second Coimbatore girlfriend loved me and wanted to marry me, but she was too afraid of her family and family pride, she got married to a guy which her family chose, later I heard that she believed if my love was true, she expected me to enter tha marriage hall, stopped that marriage and rescue her, since it did not happen she concluded our love was false 🤦🤦🤦🤦&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way at least someone thought I was like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ex36LeMLqas?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But ya, one has to be psychopath equating a tech guy with a rowdy. May be only Coimbatore girls can do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Coimbatore person known to me bought a home in Bangalore, he was close to me and asked me to visit for the house-warming, I refused because in those days getting a railway ticket was not easy, I am unsure what’s the status these days, I hated bus travel as I got almost no sleep in buses, and Aircraft when booked at last minute will be expensive. Even though I considered him as my brother, he seems to have taken my ‘No’ as something big. He knew a senior Coimbatore guy who could pressure me up, so the senior guy called me and told me to attend the function, I still said ‘No’, how can a new call change this universe? The senior guy stated behaving like a mad baby and was behaving in an unbelievable way. That senior guys sister was a mad person, she too committed suicide. I thought this guys was mad and so did not take him seriously, but these people worked to dislodge something’s in my life &amp;amp; economics which I will never forgive. I wish they rot in hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my software teams, I do find Coimbatore people behaving erratic many times. I don’t know if it’s my bias, or it’s the truth. I do know that Coimbatore contains lot’s of CEO’s and business leaders. Studies have shown that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/08/the-science-behind-why-so-many-successful-millionaires-are-psychopaths-and-why-it-doesnt-have-to-be-a-bad-thing.html&quot;&gt;high percentage of business leaders are psychopaths&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Tamilnadu we see that in Pollachi and Coimbatore, women are highly disregarded and disrespected. I think those are the rape capitals of our Tamilnadu if not India. Coimbatore is a place where BJP is strong and wins regularly. If you look at Tamilandu governor, H.Raja of BJP, Tamil Isai Sounderajan, Annamali, Modi, what names comes to your mind? Ho many internationally renowned intellectuals you have in Congress, how many are there in BJP?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you seen any sane leader ordering to shoot his own people? Or claiming he had no knowledge of massacare that happened in the land he rules, and only through news he knew it? We had a Chief minister from Edapaadi who did it, I think those who protested against Vedanta’s copper factory were shot. I think Edapaadi is in Pollachi belt. Once again I could be wrong, but I do consider EPS a mild psycho. He might not be as corrupt as the Karunanidhi family, but he might be a psychopath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would be very interested if any reader of this blog can come up with data, proving or disproving my hypothesis. I am really lazy to dig in and find out which kind of people are admitted in Mental hospitals and from which region they are from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason I find people of Madurai highly mentally stable, and they have ability to put long term plans. People who are born and brought up in Chennai are highly professionals. Once again I would like some on to prove it or disprove it with data. Till then this blog is just a rant. Maybe we might find the source of high psychopathic illness, and maybe we can do something to avoid and cure it, thus making Tamilnadu better.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why India must promote lab grown meat</title><link href="/2022/11/27/why-india-must-promote-lab-grown-meat.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why India must promote lab grown meat" /><published>2022-11-27T03:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-27T03:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/27/why-india-must-promote-lab-grown-meat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/27/why-india-must-promote-lab-grown-meat.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/53/Tandoori_chicken_laccha_piyaz1_%2836886283595%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few days ago I read in an article that FDA had approved lab grown meat for human consumption. Soon Americans will be able to eat their food without killing animals. This will start small, but will become the primary source of very cheap non-vegetarian food soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Say you want to at goats liver, say that’s the part that is in demand in your region, for that you must raise an entire goat, to access the liver you must kill it. In western world animals are killed by carbon dioxide poisoning, so they feel like they go to sleep, and they die slowly without them knowing it, but here in India we still kill animals by cutting them up, it causes pain. We as a conscious living thing want to live, but we do evil to animals even though as a human we know they experience pain when they are culled. So ethically we must not kill, but we do it, but today science has given us tool to obtain meat without killing a thing, and we must make full use of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All religions that originated in India, Jainism, Buddhism, and Sikhism, advocate not to kill animals, but for nutritional needs we kill them. Even Aryanism which first favored eating of animals like horse and cow, after entering India became a bunch of cults called Hinduism today. Most branch of Hinduism today advocates not to eat meat. Somehow this land passivized avid non-vegetarians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike Arabia and Europe, where agriculture is not as easy, Indians had mastered taming of water long ago, and we produced surplus of grain, so we were able to be empathetic towards animals and get away by drinking milk. Religions evolved here have always advocated being kind to animals and to see them as our own. Even today in many household’s rice flour is used for kolams, so that ants could feed off it and be not hungry. So our land due to is nature advocates not to kill animals and be kind to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is an environmental benefit too, say just to get say kidney of goat, you must raise the entire goat by using current practices, this requires lot of energy and time, with selective cloning, we can just grow the kidney of goat in vats with far less energy and time involved. Meat industry is one of the worst polluters and emits a lot of carbon dioxide and methane, this new technique of growing animal parts in vats will make it supremely efficient thus reducing global warming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meat that does not grow in animals which gets disease, emotional, tired, and that can grow faster in vats and in much more energy efficient way will cost less. Indians need to eat a lot of meat, we are under nourished, and we have a lot of carbs. An average Indian eats 2.2Kg of meat a year, an average American eats 140Kg of meat a year. An average Indian looks really frail compared to a guy from USA, we need to improve our nutrition. One way to do is to drastically reduce price of meat by artificially producing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeiddxklcr5ykr45fhew7hho2qzic3y36a5qvrdu5yq7vgdaqwfb2wi/Baked-bug-kabob.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Bug Kebab in Cambodia.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eating of insects too is far more efficient and more economical than eating meat. It’s naturally healthier, I with HRD ministry in India promotes insect diet too, but once again insects are conscious, have emotions, and may not want to die. But I do feel we must promote insect protein for healthier India. All over in eastern Asian countries people eat insects, why not us?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might say that Muslim community in India might eat only slaughtered meat. Let them continue with slaughter, but 75% percent of India still can enjoy ethical lab grown meat and not have the guilt of enjoying food by causing death and pain. I don’t think many Islamists in India follow strict Islam. I have seen none pray 5 times a day, my friends drink, some of them abroad eat bread (even bread in west contains lard), pork is a delicacy for them. People will change, imagine a guy watching his neighbors buy meat for ₹50/- and he need to shell out ₹400/-, definitely common sense will kick in. So I strongly feel India must promote lab grown ethical meat for all good it has in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OWRwrQI3XOY?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/M-weFARkGi4?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is this what Quran tells about women?</title><link href="/2022/11/26/is-this-what-quran-tells-about-women.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is this what Quran tells about women?" /><published>2022-11-26T17:15:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-26T17:15:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/26/is-this-what-quran-tells-about-women</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/26/is-this-what-quran-tells-about-women.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeiemfn6f2ztnxoutpbu2fjoyopn2vgt2b43qrax2g5appyg3vpipcq/is_this_what_quora_teels_about_women.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Some strange scam on Linkedin</title><link href="/2022/11/23/some-strange-scam-on-linkedin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Some strange scam on Linkedin" /><published>2022-11-23T09:01:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-23T09:01:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/23/some-strange-scam-on-linkedin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/23/some-strange-scam-on-linkedin.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeidyyiaccku4dj7w6sgp5bqgcu7x6mjrhkwcrx6uuop7lh54x64uia/Screenshot%202022-11-22%20at%201.51.28%20PM.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be some scam going on Linkedin which targets founders and investors in companies. This group seems to be tempting us with something. I received the above message which are very identical from two linked in accounts, one from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/shubham-ravindra-9360a91b7/&quot;&gt;Subham Ravindra&lt;/a&gt;, and another from a girl called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/papiya-d-3a25081b8/&quot;&gt;Papiya&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After this happened Papiya’s account seems to have disappeared. I don’t respond to these messages anyway. This blog is just to warn my fellow founders.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This man should be our Prime Minister</title><link href="/2022/11/23/this-man-should-be-our-prime-minister.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This man should be our Prime Minister" /><published>2022-11-23T07:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-23T07:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/23/this-man-should-be-our-prime-minister</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/23/this-man-should-be-our-prime-minister.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeihlqjyb6nnkdov6sowsd252zyidzz6daqihjwtthyhzbgxwpq4qli/redditsave.com_the_truth_hindustanis_want_to_say_out_loud_well-lnhd19k2ph1a1.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Not satisfied with Sithalapakkam’s Jai Biriyani</title><link href="/2022/11/20/not-satisfied-with-sithalapakkam-s-jai-biriyani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Not satisfied with Sithalapakkam&apos;s Jai Biriyani" /><published>2022-11-20T19:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-20T19:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/20/not-satisfied-with-sithalapakkam-s-jai-biriyani</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/20/not-satisfied-with-sithalapakkam-s-jai-biriyani.html">&lt;p&gt;When you take the petrol bunk left turn while you cross Sithalapakkam’s panchayat office, you will see Jai Biriyani. Biriyani there is cheap, I think it costs ₹110/-. It tastes moderate, the first time I bought the chicken was bit rubbery, possibly not cooked fully? I am not sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the second time I bought kushka and chicken 65, it cost ₹170/-, there was a small piece in kushka which excited me, the chicken 65 was deep fried, came with few pieces of sliced onion and one eighth piece of lemon. It was more enjoyable than biriyani as this time there was no rubbery chicken, but that day I had a mild stomach upset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope Jai Biriyani improves. But I don’t think I will be buying from them again. The staff over there are all Tamil, so you won’t have language difficulty, they are respectful. I hope they improve quality.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">When you take the petrol bunk left turn while you cross Sithalapakkam’s panchayat office, you will see Jai Biriyani. Biriyani there is cheap, I think it costs ₹110/-. It tastes moderate, the first time I bought the chicken was bit rubbery, possibly not cooked fully? I am not sure.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Elon Musk and my style of work</title><link href="/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elon Musk and my style of work" /><published>2022-11-20T19:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-20T19:05:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/34/Elon_Musk_Royal_Society_%28crop2%29.jpg/544px-Elon_Musk_Royal_Society_%28crop2%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Elon Musk - The evil boss you must avoid.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I push for 16 hour work week, with four-hour work days. I strongly feel that knowledge workers should have life, should spend time with their family and loved ones, think and reflect, should get new ideas. This I feel will cultivate a healthy brain and will ultimately increase productivity of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Elon Musk doing in Twitter looks very evil to me. For some reason even people of science and creativity, when they move to management, they become task masters without brains. They seem to forget where true productivity lies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are times when I finished coding for a sprint (2 weeks long one) in 2 hours, but yes all those other paper work does cost more time, but the core issue only takes two hours. There are times when even the sprint got over I haven’t started coding as the details were murky, or my understanding was not right. I understood a lot of things when I am away from keyboard, something works in your brains background while you enjoy life, all of a sudden most elegant solution pops up, and you implement it, and it works!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow management people never seems to understand it, their view of knowledge work is like viewing a repetitive work in a factory. Humans are like automated robots to them. If a robot can drive 1000 bolts in an hour, then it must drive 4000 in four hours. In my view a human or biological system is not like that. We get tired, we get energized, we sometimes find work rewarding, and sometimes boring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not worried about Twitters future, or its success or failure, I am long time user of Diaspora, I use Mastodon, and I have deleted my Facebook long ago. I am worried about the dangerous precedent Elon is setting in the I.T industry. With people like him, the industry will be populated by mindless ‘yes boss’ human bots who are there for a paycheck, than for the passion of coding.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Elon Musk - The evil boss you must avoid.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This woman is such a great stupid, BJP people would love to have her in their party</title><link href="/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This woman is such a great stupid, BJP people would love to have her in their party" /><published>2022-11-14T12:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-14T12:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeictysiokuwms63ywicar2wb5qe7stgf4edaalrwil4nnvzarcmlyi/redditsave.com_tamil_should_not_be_a_compulsory_language_in-dmws7qd2ioz91.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pragamin</title><link href="/2022/11/07/pragamin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pragamin" /><published>2022-11-07T20:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-07T20:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/07/pragamin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/07/pragamin.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeicikohkfb75id5ulkphzklqdhl6vlrlika2doguph2hqbsghurimq/pragamin.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry></feed>