<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-02-13T14:29:57+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Rajinikanth in Free Software</title><link href="/free%20software/ruby/apple/mac%20m1/tamil/japan/culture/2021/02/11/rajinikanth-in-free-software.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rajinikanth in Free Software" /><published>2021-02-11T16:03:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-02-11T16:03:00+05:30</updated><id>/free%20software/ruby/apple/mac%20m1/tamil/japan/culture/2021/02/11/rajinikanth-in-free-software</id><content type="html" xml:base="/free%20software/ruby/apple/mac%20m1/tamil/japan/culture/2021/02/11/rajinikanth-in-free-software.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/49/%E0%AE%9A%E0%AF%82%E0%AE%AA%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%AA%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%B8%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%9F%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%8D_%E0%AE%B0%E0%AE%9C%E0%AE%BF%E0%AE%A9%E0%AE%BF%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%A8%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%A4%E0%AF%8D_-_Actor_Rajinikanth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rajinikanth is an hero here in Tamilnadu, India. He is a hero in Japan too. He has done nothing useful but to act, but his funny and comical way of acting has attracted fans like Tom and Jerry would attract fans and his movies are great to watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ruby’s creator Matz is Japanese, so as an Tamil I was asking him to view Rajikanth’s movie and he did :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/karthik_ak?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@karthik_ak&lt;/a&gt; I watched &amp;#39;The Robot|Enthiran&amp;#39;. It was marvelous.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Yukihiro Matsumoto (@yukihiro_matz) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/yukihiro_matz/status/720808569365397504?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;April 15, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and that’s okay because Rajini is super famous in Japan. His film Muthu grossed more than Titanic in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I wanted to manage Ruby versions on my machine and hence tried rbenv, and it did not work. I was using Mac M1 and its a bit pain to get Ruby on it. So after lot of DuckDuckGoing pain I found this tool called asdf here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.driftingruby.com/episodes/a-rubyist-s-apple-m1-review&quot;&gt;https://www.driftingruby.com/episodes/a-rubyist-s-apple-m1-review&lt;/a&gt;. It looked simple and it should work. But ya, we are installing Ruby 3 on rosetta instead of M1, hmmmm….. not okay, but okay. I managed to get Ruby installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then this happened:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;% asdf | tail
                                        environment used for command shim execution.
asdf info                               Print OS, Shell and ASDF debug information.
asdf reshim &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;            Recreate shims for version of a package
asdf shim-versions &amp;lt;command&amp;gt;            List the plugins and versions that
                                        provide a command
asdf update                             Update asdf to the latest stable release
asdf update --head                      Update asdf to the latest on the master branch

&quot;Late but latest&quot;
-- Rajinikanth
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the version of asdf I am currently using :o&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;% asdf --version
v0.8.0
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I checked the faces on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/asdf-vm/asdf&quot;&gt;asdf&lt;/a&gt; and found this guy &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/HashNuke&quot;&gt;Akash Manohar&lt;/a&gt;, an Indian, possibly a Tamil if not Japanese :D living in Banglore.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why India should absorb Pakistan and Bangladesh?</title><link href="/geography/india/2020/10/17/why-india-should-absorb-pakistan-and-bangladesh.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why India should absorb Pakistan and Bangladesh?" /><published>2020-10-17T15:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-17T15:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/geography/india/2020/10/17/why-india-should-absorb-pakistan-and-bangladesh</id><content type="html" xml:base="/geography/india/2020/10/17/why-india-should-absorb-pakistan-and-bangladesh.html">&lt;p&gt;Why did we elect Modi as our priminister? We did not like Manmohan Singh (even though he’s a genius,) to listen to a woman of Italian origin. We have just got freedom from Brits who don’t even wash their bottoms yet, and now we have to listen to a lady who is from a similar culture. We were fed up with 2G, and other scams that plagued our nation. For people like me, if Modi came to power he would not hesitate to kill Pakistanis and integrate that state with us. He is a person who watched genocide of Muslims in his own state and feels unrepentant, I thought he would not hesitate to put an end to Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;History needs Hitler like and devils. If it’s not for Winston Churchill who killed millions in India by shipping grains to Europe, England would have not won the second world war. If India needs a bloody war with Pakistan to wipe them off so that our territorial integrity is maintained, and so be it. Congress won’t do it, so we put a Satan in power. But this Satan is killing our own people who are Muslims and other lower castes in Hinduism, than killing Pakistanis and thus bringing relief to Iran, Afghanistan and us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I saw this map of India:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/indian_subcontinent.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look how well our territory is defined by mountains in North, East and West, and ocean at the bottom. And why we can’t rule this tiny land fully? Because some fucker 10,000 years ago said a God called Shiva exists? Because another fucker 1000 years ago said a God called Allah exist? Science says both are untrue! If we listen to some word of mouth things without verifying the facts how stupid we are? We must think about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even today I think Persians and Afghanistan’s refer Pakistanis as Hindu’s. We are the people of Indus, the mighty river that fed and watered our forefathers before all this Muhammad and this Saffron saints existed. We had an really efficient cities, drains, brick making and industrial skills. Still the iron pillars erected by Ashoka  hasn’t rusted, Qutub Minar needs regular tending to keep it upright. That was the level of sophistication we had achieved eons ago. A might civilization was spread from Boluchistan to Tamilnadu. In fact Dravidian Civilization was spread from Iran to Srilanka eons before Ashoka ruled. We are one people, and we have lost it all because few idiots point out to few texts and say that we are different people. What a bullshit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the United Kingdom, European Union and United States, we must form a united India that consists of Pakistan, Bangladesh, India, Srilanka and Burma We may have different parliaments, governments and cultures but we can have common things like defense, space program, scientific endeavor. There will be no borders among these states, people could travel freely without restrictions, a common currency would mean a better commerce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But ya, dream is a dream, foolish humans are foolish humans.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Why did we elect Modi as our priminister? We did not like Manmohan Singh (even though he’s a genius,) to listen to a woman of Italian origin. We have just got freedom from Brits who don’t even wash their bottoms yet, and now we have to listen to a lady who is from a similar culture. We were fed up with 2G, and other scams that plagued our nation. For people like me, if Modi came to power he would not hesitate to kill Pakistanis and integrate that state with us. He is a person who watched genocide of Muslims in his own state and feels unrepentant, I thought he would not hesitate to put an end to Pakistan.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to understand non Chennai Tamils emotions?</title><link href="/2020/10/10/how-to-understand-non-chennai-tamils-emotions.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to understand non Chennai Tamils emotions?" /><published>2020-10-10T10:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-10T10:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/10/10/how-to-understand-non-chennai-tamils-emotions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/10/10/how-to-understand-non-chennai-tamils-emotions.html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t know why I remembered this incident now, but anyway, a kind of funny thing happened long long ago. Opposite to the Medavakkam share auto stand there was and I think there is still a briyani shop, not hi-fi, but a very local one. Briyani over there was relatively cheap, and of good quality? I don’t remember the quality. Anyway….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I had a friend Senthil (he is a big shot in AIADMK), some how my busyness has left me without touch with him recently, he had a friend called Naveen, I think from Thankaasi, they both worked in Zoho. We 3, after just another meting where we planned for a Trillion dollar world conquering company, we thought of having nice treat. Who wouldn’t have briyani after planning about a Trillion dollar enterprise? We would!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we went to the shop we ordered chicken, something with lot of bones so that my friends felt good to hold and eat(, I always favor lot of meat chunk, more value for money you see). The chicken came, I think I forgot about the existence of this universe and started to focus on this chicken. After sometime Naveen started to breathe heavy, when I saw him he was looking at the chicken with great attention had bitten a piece and started to breathe heavy, okay, I started to dig into my pieces when Senthil said ‘let’s goto another shop, this place is not good’. I did not understand a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We turned the corner and went into another shop, there we ordered the same Chicken lollipop, I think it came from the same local shop where we were eating, but since the ambiance was good this guy Naveen was okay. Senthil asked Navaeen, ‘you did not like the ambiance right?’ and Naveen noded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am BBC (born and brought up in Chennai), I really wonder how and why village people thought and communicated like that and I really don’t know how to read their fucking emotions. How could heavy breathing mean this thing and blah blah, but not ‘wow I love this spicy chicken!’. I really don’t get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In another case I had a friend called Umashankar who I met in Zanec. All people said very good things about him and I landed up forming a company with him called Trumatics, it was in Velacherry. Ideally it should not have all the evils Zanec had and it was supposed to take off great. But after sometime Umashankar used to abuse my work, he used to say very ill things and used to say Skikit-Learn, Facebook Prophet are totally wrong, which stunned me. Slowly I started to prove he was wrong and till that time he used to sit with us, he shifted to another room. Though he abused me before others, he pulled me up and said not to prove him wrong before others because that hurt his image.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day when I went to file for tax, my auditors asked about the company, they rang up Uma, they knew I was super passionate. When I left, without my knowledge they rang my home up and seems to have expressed doubts in Uma, and said if Karthik is in right path he will be out of the company before next tax filing. I wonder how they got it in just 2 minutes conversation?! When I came out of Trumatics, then when people in my home revealed this to me, I was stunned by my auditors professionalism. May be Uma wanted me out all the time. Who knows? May be he set up something bogus company, who knows? I never ran my companies like Uma. I focus on how tech could help people and not how I could make money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uma is also from a place called Salem, a deep south city, may be he was communicating with me non verbally. But how to understand it? I have no clue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We BBC’s have one motive in life, that is to be happy, from our young age we had everything and if we wanted something we asked for it. But looks like the rest of Tamilnadu, the rural India somehow seems to have this non verbal communication, possibly they were trashed by their parents for speaking out and revolting. Some how for them breathing heavy means we need to switch hotels, shouting like mad at very proven machine learning libraries in office means get out of my business and something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non Chennai people succeed, there is a psychological basis for it, for us being born itself is success, all our parents want is to watch us being happy and hence we have relatively no pressure. In rural India you have this family pride, your car should change from Swift to Mercedes in 5 years or the fellow villagers won’t respect you or something, so these non Chennai people if they don’t achieve something they fall into depression of failure, for us, ya we feel depressed when we fail, but a peg, a tandoori, a mutton briyani would fix it and none would bother about us, and we would bother about none.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why I am writing this blog is, lot of Chennai people are in I.T offices which are dominated by south Tamilnadu fools who have these fucking old tradition thing and stuff. So when they behave mad at you, its their way. For us spitting, urinating, defecating in public is not right, for them even their best people do it. They are totally different. The solution for this, I have no fucking clue! :D&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I don’t know why I remembered this incident now, but anyway, a kind of funny thing happened long long ago. Opposite to the Medavakkam share auto stand there was and I think there is still a briyani shop, not hi-fi, but a very local one. Briyani over there was relatively cheap, and of good quality? I don’t remember the quality. Anyway….</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Moral void of youtubers during pandemic</title><link href="/2020/10/06/moral-void-of-youtubers-during-pandemic.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moral void of youtubers during pandemic" /><published>2020-10-06T12:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-06T12:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/10/06/moral-void-of-youtubers-during-pandemic</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/10/06/moral-void-of-youtubers-during-pandemic.html">&lt;p&gt;I’m a foodie and absolutely love food video’s and review. I want to go on an full India tour just to eat, I feel food and good taste are very essential and I feel no one should never go hungry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a pandemic time. Usually during times of stress and in times when society needs to come together it’s the media people who pick up the task of educating people and they advise the right thing, but look at this video&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9zYoahr6n0g?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This guy looks well educated, may be he won’t get bankrupt if he does not do these video’s, drives a nice car, looks polished, but he still hops from place t place during pandemic which encourages people too to visit these places. I can’t imaging what is happening to peoples brain? This guy may be a fool, but not enough opposition arises against him or other youtubers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, mostly this guy won’t die of Corona, but imagine he has it, shows no symptoms, he might transmit it to some one old, and that person could loose their life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is puzzling is this, if I get Rs 10 from some one for an emergency I keep thinking all night why I did not plan properly and had to borrow, next day morning I give them money back. In fact even if I need change, I give a person Rs 100, get Rs 10 back so that I need not be in debt. In India we have such culture where we should not owe an debt or cause an evil to someone. These guys are Indians too, rather than advising people to stay inside, eat simple food, avoid travel and contact, they encourage it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is not this guy I am angry about, its all these youtubers who want to generate few bucks are behaving in such an irresponsible way. If they die it’s okay, its their wish, but they could harm someone putting videos now, I feel very difficult to digest that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’m a foodie and absolutely love food video’s and review. I want to go on an full India tour just to eat, I feel food and good taste are very essential and I feel no one should never go hungry.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Using Bootstrap Icons in Rails 6 with Webpacker</title><link href="/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/design/bootstrap/2020/10/04/using-bootstrap-icons-in-rails-6-with-webpacker.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Using Bootstrap Icons in Rails 6 with Webpacker" /><published>2020-10-04T20:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-04T20:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/design/bootstrap/2020/10/04/using-bootstrap-icons-in-rails-6-with-webpacker</id><content type="html" xml:base="/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/design/bootstrap/2020/10/04/using-bootstrap-icons-in-rails-6-with-webpacker.html">&lt;p&gt;Font awesome is good and font awesome rails gem neatly integrates with Rails framework, but I think it uses Sprockets which is going out of fashion :(. As a community we are embracing webpacker, I wish we embraced Opal and ditched Javascript completely, but it’s not happening. Anyway…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Font awesome is okay, but their premium icons hide behind paywall and they are not as committed to free software as Booststrap guys I think. Font awesome needs money, they are into that model. The law of software development says that if you are offering a service, there is always a person to outsmart you. Welcome Bootstraop icons &lt;a href=&quot;https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&quot;&gt;https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now how to use it? First add the necessary dependencies using yarn&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ yarn add bootstrap-icon
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now create a file called &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;app/helpers/bootstrap_icons_helper.rb&lt;/code&gt;, in it add this code&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;module&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;BootstrapIconsHelper&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# refer https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;options&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{})&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;file&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;File&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;read&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;node_modules/bootstrap-icons/icons/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;.svg&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;doc&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Nokogiri&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;HTML&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;DocumentFragment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;parse&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;file&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;svg&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;doc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;at_css&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;svg&apos;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;present?&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;svg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;class&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;+=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot; &quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;+&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;doc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;to_html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;html_safe&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now in the app anywhere use this to add an icon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-erb highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;%=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;alert-circle&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;class: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;text-success&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;%&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To refer the names of icons goto &lt;a href=&quot;https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&quot;&gt;https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Font awesome is good and font awesome rails gem neatly integrates with Rails framework, but I think it uses Sprockets which is going out of fashion :(. As a community we are embracing webpacker, I wish we embraced Opal and ditched Javascript completely, but it’s not happening. Anyway…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wish people had astronaut level psychology</title><link href="/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wish people had astronaut level psychology" /><published>2020-10-04T18:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-04T18:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/91/Bruce_McCandless_II_during_EVA_in_1984.jpg/720px-Bruce_McCandless_II_during_EVA_in_1984.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any thing can kill you in space within minutes, even in times of stress you need to be calm. There was a knock at our gate today, our ex-driver it was. He seems to have had a safari near our home and dropped by, one of us engaged him outside the gate and rushed to the bathroom to have a bath, the conversation lasted 15 minutes I think. The people, and even families who worked with us seems to love us and seem to have extreme loyalties crossing generations, but does that warrant foolishness?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chanakya said its not enough to be wise and intelligent, one must also avoid staying around fools. If one is around fools, their intelligence would be wasted. Think of what is happening here, the Church is open, stupid parents drag their kids to it, parents are taking kids to Tirupathi, I haven’t noticed mosques, but just today morning I saw a family of jam packed Muslims (our neighbors) in a car traveling from somewhere to our area. Pathetic. Not even in nightmares I have encountered a situation where I sould be in a place where I would be sourrounded by fools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are in a midst of an pandemic, I wish people reading this have the knowledge to look about it in the dictionary. People know it’s a pandemic and they invent reasons to travel, to mingle! I can’t imagine how stupid we are as a society. If those people who are idiots die I am okay, but if they spread virus around knowing or unknowing, that’s a bloody crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish schools one day start training people about psychology, about logical thinking, about staying calm during situations like these, possibly staying calm during one’s death too. I wish we had astronaut level of psychology training so that we don’t invent reasons to be a fool.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How I Make My Curses Work?</title><link href="/2020/09/30/how-i-make-my-curses-work.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I Make My Curses Work?" /><published>2020-09-30T23:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-09-30T23:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/09/30/how-i-make-my-curses-work</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/09/30/how-i-make-my-curses-work.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/5b/Statue_of_Kannagi.jpg/665px-Statue_of_Kannagi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my friend won’t buy a music player, he will listen to his music from his mobile or laptop, the reason? He is afraid that if he buys it he will die in a month because I gave the curse to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very long ago, one of my friend called and told me a business move that was selfish and annoyed me, I cursed him that since I can’t have my breakfast in peace, he won’t be able to have his breakfast today. Few minutes after that while he was boiling his tea a lizard jumped into it. Seeing the boiling lizard he said he wasn’t able to eat properly for a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My in-laws did very bad stuff to me, they boasted I was alone and they had 25 people in their family trained against me, kind of Mahabharat ratio 1:25, I cursed them for their wrong doing, as far as I know 2 people dies within 4 - 6 months and they were visibly shaken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my former boss did not treat me well, she amassed his wealth for her children and threw me out of job with framed reason, now none of her children are alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have got a reputation of getting my curses work. And how I do it? I am a rationalist and don’t believe in curses, but I do curse people which automatically comes out of my mouth. The reason they work is as good as Mohammad Azrudding winning most of his tosses, just pure luck. What else could it be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I do do is when something wrong happens to a person I had cursed, I contact them and tell them its because of the negative Karma they earned against me had got them into this trouble. This fixes in their mind, it’s a small world and word gets around that this guys wrath and word happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes it could be the case where just because I curse some one when they are really bad, and they know about their ill doings, their subconscious works to punish them. Like deaths in family. Say some one in your family is dying, you must do all you can to stop it, but your subconscious mind says you have done a bad thing and hence you must endure a loss rather than do all it takes to save the life, perhaps the you rather than to put in work and thought freeze thus loosing a person. Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But once I curse I forget about it. That’s it. That person is my friend again and I have almost nothing against him, I just wish things would go right, but seems that the word runs in their mind and they associate it with evil things that happens in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Experience/Advice from a 10+ year data scientist</title><link href="/2020/09/09/experience-advice-from-a-10-year-data-scientist.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Experience/Advice from a 10+ year data scientist" /><published>2020-09-09T09:36:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-09-09T09:36:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/09/09/experience-advice-from-a-10-year-data-scientist</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/09/09/experience-advice-from-a-10-year-data-scientist.html">&lt;p&gt;For context, I was in most people’s shoes here so this is why I want to give back some advice and inspiration. There’s a bit of misinformation in this subreddit so I’ll consolidate my thinking. DM me if you need specific advice&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Been working in quant/data science for 10-11 years now. Didn’t know where to go because this field didn’t exist when I was in school.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Self-taught. This is where my imposter syndrome appears but little did anyone know this. Learned SQL through sqlzoo, learned R as a hobby to day-trade (yahoo-finance api, zoo package, etc.), Python through codeschool(?) or codeacademy(?) in 2012 (it was free back then), Math through OCW/torrented whitepapers &amp;amp; textbooks, ML through whitepapers &amp;amp; textbooks (coursera did not exist yet)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Interviewed around a lot and got rejected a lot (100+). When I first began, this was not a field, but the interview process &amp;amp; rejections gave me grit and understand what to study. I interviewed for a lot of exciting startups (now public companies) before they were even big. A small hedge fund gave me a chance as a quant trader, and our group got shut down in a year. I got a second chance somewhere else and the company went public (data science was central to their strategy)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Data Science is exciting. This field has brought me around the world. Worked at a hedge fund, electricity markets, global consulting, somehow ended up doing A.I work, and now in a leadership strategy role. I don’t oversee data scientists anymore, they mostly report to my business function now but previously managed 20+ data scientists. Worked all over the globe and across many, many states.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advice:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Study and code everyday. Make it a habit. Blog posts, whitepapers, textbooks. I’ve lost this habit and I regret it – getting back into it. You should love learning, otherwise you’re in the wrong field.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Build up your foundations. Python/R, Probability/Stats/Calculus/LinAlg/DiffEq, Algorithms. This will help you understand a lot . Do take an algorithms &amp;amp; design course. Most problems are solved through a design approach / framework rather than a model.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Stay in touch with whats going on. hackernews/datatau/rweekly &amp;amp; understanding new Data Engineering trends, Tech Engineering Blogs. Example, when I read some company blog about their implementation of spark in 2014, I immediately started playing around with it with my models.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Always be humble &amp;amp; prepare to get humbled but remain self-confident and determined. Don’t be afraid.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Find a subject you like to get started. Loving data &amp;amp; modeling is one thing, but find an area that really interests you. For me, I started with time series (not for the faint of heart). This introduced me to a lot of difficult concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Find a product/field. For me it was Energy &amp;amp; Finance. It can be marketing, sales, finance, pure ML, pure optimization work, supply chain, etc. Being a general hobbyist will only get you so far.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, Data science is not all SQL. It depends on how close you are to the revenue generating side. If you’re making a quarterly report on demand, that isn’t data science. If you’re building growth models to accelerate users on your platform that tie to scale and revenue. SQL will get your dad but still have to come up with model&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taken from:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/iorbjg/experienceadvice_from_a_10_year_data_scientist/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/iorbjg/experienceadvice_from_a_10_year_data_scientist/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">For context, I was in most people’s shoes here so this is why I want to give back some advice and inspiration. There’s a bit of misinformation in this subreddit so I’ll consolidate my thinking. DM me if you need specific advice</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Life Of An Indian</title><link href="/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life Of An Indian" /><published>2020-08-27T08:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-27T08:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/life_of_an_indian.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I don’t bet on gold?</title><link href="/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I don&apos;t bet on gold?" /><published>2020-08-18T21:12:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-18T21:12:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://dailytimes.com.pk/assets/uploads/2018/04/29/today-gold-prices-in-pakistan-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of my friend, Indians of course are stumped by why I don’t bet on Gold. There are two simple reasons for that, first I still expect to live another 50 years, and I still plan to have a family and leave my values and wealth behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the exact reason why you buy gold isn’t it? It will have a exchange value even 50 years from now? The answer is no. Gold will be as cheap as iron and other materials will become throw away cheap. Why? See this video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/y8XvQNt26KI?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speed at which SpaceX is going ahead with starship, the innovative ideas that other startups are coming up like 3D printed rockets like Relativity Space, it’s going to get very easy to reach orbit and back to earth. From orbit we have ion propulsion powered by solar in inner solar system and technology like powerball nuclear reactors in external system from Mars onwards. This will make enable us to bring and park asteroids near Earth and mine it’s resources and make even gold dirt cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.teslarati.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/BFR-2018-spaceship-and-booster-sep-SpaceX-2-crop.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup with the speed of human innovation, I think this will happen sooner than later. So let’s see. So definitely saving your wealth in the form of gold for your grand kids won’t work. In Napoleon’s table cutlery was made of very precious metal called Aluminum which was much costlier than gold, we now use it to make plates and pots for jail inmates because it’s so cheap now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;References&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.spacex.com/vehicles/starship/&quot;&gt;Starship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.relativityspace.com/&quot;&gt;Relativity Space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ion_thruster&quot;&gt;Ion Thruster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/nuclear-power-balls-triso-fuel/&quot;&gt;Powerball&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://x-energy.com/reactors/xe-100&quot;&gt;Xenergy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>