<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-02-23T11:57:18+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why I Think Modi Economics is Stupid</title><link href="/2021/02/23/why-i-think-modi-economics-is-stupid.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I Think Modi Economics is Stupid" /><published>2021-02-23T11:53:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-02-23T11:53:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/02/23/why-i-think-modi-economics-is-stupid</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/23/why-i-think-modi-economics-is-stupid.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.assettype.com/freepressjournal%2F2019-06%2F963c2b44-928d-41c5-a9db-7bd9df06c2d9%2Fmodi_yoga_video.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a firm believer that people who have very strong opinion that are not based on facts are ultra stupid who can never be changed. In fact a good mind should mind his or her business and get ahead in life than even thinking of changing them. This blog, or the opinion of countless thinkers definitely won’t change the BJP, but the government will have a hard fall due to its illogical economic practice of taxing the middle class for the benefit of its rich friends. When that happens then I feel if a good government that is not controlled by the corporates emerge, then possibly a very similar policy written in this blog might follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-poori-idli-story&quot;&gt;The Poori Idli Story&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.awesomecuisine.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/poori-masala-kizhangu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A hotelier in a town was selling Poori and Potato as a breakfast food, and it was popular. The person who supplied oil to make poori wanted to conquer the hotel, so using the oil money he earned from the sale of oil to the hotelier, he hired some rowdies to harass and attack the hotel. The hotel guy had no choice. Poori was his great sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://images2.thestatesman.com/uploads/images/2017/02/04/1486189244-idli-517.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day the hotelier heard a dish named idli. It does not need to be fried in oil, hence when made it will weaken the oil seller who wants to take control of the hotel. Next idli is a dish that is far healthier than poori, but how to introduce it in the town?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Production of idli costs, it requires investment into steamers. You just can’t take dough and roll it to become idli, you need knowledge of fermentation and art to make it. So initially idli would cost more. So to make people eat idli, the hotelier doubled and tripled poori price. People avoided his hotel and new guy was able to buy the hotel for a cheap rate because of its tumbling profits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hotel is India. The poori is carbon emitting fossil fuel vehicles. The idlis are electric vehicles. The oil seller is Arab who always dreams that the whole world should be controlled by him because some book said so. The change of hands of hotel is nothing but the fall of BJP to possibly a better economically minded government that might care more for the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-should-be-done&quot;&gt;What Should Be Done&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what should be done? How to make people eat more and fill their stomach, but still oil is avoided and we have healthy idlis. I am sorry if I had misled the reader, the idli here is electric transport. This section will tell  my opinion and ideas how to make India’s transport electric.
ß&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;reduce-petroleum-price&quot;&gt;Reduce Petroleum Price&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.theweek.in/content/dam/week/news/india/images/2021/2/16/petrol-price.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First reduce petroleum cost. This will stimulate the economy, put more money into peoples pocket, people will have the urge to travel more. The more people want to travel the more commerce and more vehicle sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next increase the cost of production of fossil fuel vehicles. Put a good tax on it. So you are shifting the burden from people to industry which should have a sufficient money base. So though people can travel with vehicles with cheaper petrol price, only the people who can afford a lot can purchase a vehicle that emits carbon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reduce-pollution&quot;&gt;Reduce Pollution&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mygaragestory.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Emission-Test-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As carbon tax, have very strict pollution control methods. So people must maintain carbon vehicles and that would cost, that means more money flow into the economy, into mechanical shops, into small industries that make parts for carbon emitting vehicles. Ofcourse you are robbing the people here, but possibly offsetting it in hospital bills which are caused due to pollution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next have green zones in many important parts of nation where you can get in with carbon vehicles only after paying a hefty fee. These green zones could be highly posh real estate area, hospital and school regions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So by now you have got people who can travel but they have to be very responsible. I wish all these stuff are done slowly than in a hasty way which is typical of Modi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reduce-electricity-cost&quot;&gt;Reduce Electricity Cost&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*oE_1iCFDAW8i7fr1ViOSSw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the above points are going on, this is the time time to reduce the cost of electricity. You see you have slashed the car sales, made petroleum cheap so that goods prices don’t get affected, now its time to reduce the electricity cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the easiest way to reduce electricity cost is to fund transmission grid so that losses will be reduced. Try making it smart. Still people come to my home and take electrical reading, make it automatic so that its taken away from my credit card. See how you can reduce the cost of generating electricity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another big thing is electrical storage. You might be tempted to build big storage solutions if renewables come in, but wait, can’t storage be distributed? Reduce cost of home installation solar power. Make people generate and sell excess solar electricity so that it adds some earning to them. Make batteries cheaper so that each home can store tiny amount of electricity, thus a million homes might add up to some storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you encourage domestic solar power production than relying on big companies that are your friends, you will cultivate lot of MSME’s that offer solar solutions. They will have the independence and autonomy and they will create numerous localised jobs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea is if people can create electricity at a mere throw away price, or can earn from generation of it, then if they can buy electric vehicles and charge it, its as equivalent as putting petrol into cars for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;encourage-electric-cars&quot;&gt;Encourage Electric Cars&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://sm.mashable.com/mashable_in/seo/default/tata-launches-compact-suv-nexon-ev-in-india_y5q4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now is the time to reduce the cost of idli than raising the price of poori. Its time to get in electric mobility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The government should first walk the talk. It can start to purchase electric vehicles and stop using carbon vehicles for its staff. Say the postal service, equip most postmen in the nation with electric scooters. Put a solar powered charging station in every post office if possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talk with people who could make electric vehicle. Give them a waiver of import duty. If an local industry is manufacturing part for electric vehicle maker, make the transaction tax free. Make electric vehicle zero tax. Electric vehicles already has no road tax I think, so thats good. So if one has electric vehicle, a solar roof, he almost has no running cost to bear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try increasing automation in EV manufacturing factories so that labor problems could be avoided and cost could be further reduced. If small companies can convert existing gasoline vehicles to electric, encourage them so that they will add more employment and slowly carbon vehicles are reduced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If one is buying a EV for commercial use, give that person 15 year car loan. It’s not just farmers are the only people in this land. Drivers are humans too. Remove toll 100% for EV’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put up charging stations all over the nation. Involve MSME’s for this so that labor intensive task it becomes. Make power available for EV’s at dirt pricing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By doing the above stuff and along with some other things, cost of owning a EV’s will drop below that of carbon vehicles and people will start to switch. Now that’s how you sell more idlis than poori. Not by increasing the cost of eating poori.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Running PHP on Mac M1</title><link href="/2021/02/18/running-php-on-mac-m1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Running PHP on Mac M1" /><published>2021-02-18T14:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-02-18T14:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/02/18/running-php-on-mac-m1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/18/running-php-on-mac-m1.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.codigofonte.com.br/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/php-elephant.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mac is stupid for development. I got a assignment from a friend for writing his PHP site. He had contracted a PHP programmer for cheap, and just like any cheap programmer the code of the site was bad, non reusable, inconsistent UI and UX were there and changes made added to complexity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The code was full of inconsistencies and trailing white spaces. I use Ruby for creation of websites, but my friend had bought a cheap hosting provider and was unwilling to change, that hosting provider gave only PHP on his servers for dirt pricing. So I had to do with PHP on Mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trying-out-xamp&quot;&gt;Trying out XAMP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XAMP is a wonderful tool to run AMP stack (Apache, Maria DB, PHP) on any OS. I first installed on it on my laptop and tried. To my horror for some reason PHP files got downloaded rather than it being executed on server and HTML sent back. Mac sucks in development, the support was bad it took very long time to figure it out. You see it may be due to XAMP using PHP 8 and I later found out that my Mac had inbuilt PHP 7 which could be the cause of the issue. These mismatches means some how XAMP PHP won’t work on Mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this kind of problem occurred on Ubuntu GNU/Linux, then it would be going to a forum and a 20 minute fix, because this happened in mac, it took nearly a day to find the solution. Pheeew!! Mac sucks for development, its a closed box and good enough developers should not use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now knowing that XAMP won’t work properly, I switched to Mac’s internal installation. thankfully XAMP had an uninstall script which I triggered to remove it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;using-macs-apache-and-php&quot;&gt;Using Mac’s Apache and PHP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, Mac has inbuilt Apache and PHP. Why a company which builds opaque OS and Processors that does not disclose about it to developers includes these software? I don’t know. So start Apache like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ apachectl start
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Launch &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;localhost&lt;/code&gt; in your browser and you should see this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/php_mac_m1/apache_works.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now edit this file:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo vi /etc/apache2/httpd.conf
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that find this one&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;LoadModule php7_module libexec/apache2/libphp7.so
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and uncomment it if its commented, if you can’t find it add it at last. Now in finder locate &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/Library/WebServer/Documents/&lt;/code&gt; and right click on it and click Get Info, it must show something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/php_mac_m1/changing_folder_permissions.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that I have added myself and given me Read and Write permissions. Now restart Apache like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ apachectl restart
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Place your PHP files in &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/Library/WebServer/Documents/&lt;/code&gt; and access it in your browser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you  are a Mac user, my only advise is don’t be a stupid, switch to GNU/Linux.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why you must not buy Apple M1</title><link href="/2021/02/14/why-you-must-not-buy-apple-m1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why you must not buy Apple M1" /><published>2021-02-14T20:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-02-14T20:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/02/14/why-you-must-not-buy-apple-m1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/14/why-you-must-not-buy-apple-m1.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.apple.com/newsroom/images/product/mac/standard/Apple_new-m1-chip-graphic_11102020_big.jpg.large.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who know me know that I am against Apple. Apple is just another black box, possibly a spying machine that sits right in your home. Who knows right now a NSA agent might be looking at me on camera, ya its Feb 14th today, so if its a woman she would be hopelessly in love with me. But I got a M1, why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I was in a situation, my personal Ubuntu GNU/Linux Lenovo machine started giving me problems, its screen went kaput and it took 6K to replace it and it was a poor work. Due to sloppy workmanship by S.S. Computer, Sithalapakkam, just a month after repair, its keyboard started failing. I was in a situation where I had no real projects and commitments at that time, but I was bugged by my friend to finish a Data Science project. My Lenovo got busted when it was analysing 60,000 images for a machine learning problem, its ENTER key won’t work at last. The Data Science experiment in it s i3 hardware was slow, waitful and painful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friends office uses Mac. He and his employees are idiots. He is definitely an idiot, and he would give salary to his employees only if they behave like idiot too. So to be with their ecosystem he asked me to use Mac. M1 is a well architected processor and is very bold in its innovations, I respect that, so I said yes. So an expensive an laptop landed on my desk. I couldn’t get System 76, or other really awesome GNU/Linux machines because they do not serve India. I can’t let him wait for long, so if he pays the money its okay for me. That’s how I ended up having a Mac. The shipment was slow, that wait for nearly a month. A person who codes every day, a month without coding was an unimaginable stuff, but I endured it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let me say how mac sucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-for-true-developers&quot;&gt;Not for true developers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First I can’t have GNOME, KDE, XFCE on it as Apple won’t let them run it. So I am stuck with the crappy UI Apple offers. Can you imagine my friend who is an computer engineer himself, I am not kidding, he really is and he really is chooses Apple to develop? In apple you don’t even have a decent terminal, you have to use a thing called &lt;a href=&quot;https://iterm2.com/&quot;&gt;iTerm&lt;/a&gt;. It’s for babies this computer was designed for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wifi-issues--dumb-users&quot;&gt;Wifi Issues &amp;amp; Dumb Users&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WiFi sucks. Suddenly it gets disconnected and even if I tell it to connect the connection keeps dropping. There is no solution for it. Unlike GNU/Linux where there is so much support, for Mac, no. Even if you chat for support they (the Apple folks) answer you like idiots. When you talk to a person who uses GNU/Linux you can see that he understands you because he understands computers, but Apple people look dumb all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sloppy-ux&quot;&gt;Sloppy UX&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I have used Mac OS now and then for 6 years I think. Each time forced by some one who wants to pay me. Unlike GNU/Linux where the UI has many iterations and changes and is refined constantly, here just look when I drag and drop a picture, it just stay in the folder just like that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/sloppy_ux.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The icons never rearrange. God. What’s wrong with Apple? Why are they so dumb and yet so rich? Why is Javascript the worst programming language and yet so popular? I simply don’t understand humanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;large-program-size&quot;&gt;Large Program Size&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/large_program_size.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look at the image above. Mac wants to update Keynote, its presentation software and it costs 340MB+. Almost any software you install is 100MB+ and you start wondering what the heck. Yes even in Ubuntu GNU/Linux, after this stupid snaps and flatpacks, the size has increased too, So this can’t be said as unique Apple problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;battery-drains-when-screen-is-bright&quot;&gt;Battery drains when screen is bright&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battery drains fast when the screen is bright. Or else the longevity of the battery is awesome, it drains only 60% in 9 hours of use. Thats good. Even when I played a near 1 hour game of 0AD, it drained only 11%, that too this happened in a laptop which was quiet and fan less! Now that’s a miracle. But the battery soon starts to drain a percent per minute as soon as you work in sunny conditions where screen must be bright. So it sucks if you don’t live in Moscow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;crappy-software&quot;&gt;Crappy Software&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traditionally Apple’s software sucks compared to that of GNU/Linux, but there are programs like Apple Books which are supposed to open and Ebook and they won’t do so. You can only view that that program has detected your Ebook, but you can’t open it. Once again if you ask Apple people they will respond its a good program. They simply don’t have the intelligence to listen to you like GNU/Linux guys. Worst, you can’t uninstall this shit program!! I don’t know why? there isn’t a decent Chess program like &lt;a href=&quot;https://pychess.github.io/&quot;&gt;PyChess&lt;/a&gt; on Apple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-good-stuff&quot;&gt;Some Good Stuff&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;M1 is fast, &lt;a href=&quot;/free%20software/ruby/apple/mac%20m1/tamil/japan/culture/2021/02/11/rajinikanth-in-free-software.html&quot;&gt;I installed Ruby&lt;/a&gt;, actually Ruby 3.0.0, in my old systems it took 20+ seconds to generate my &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; blog, here its 3. In the above text you would have found how M1 handles 0.A.D in a cool way when other laptops fan would be screaming. As always Apple looks good, the build is solid which other makers do not offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-thought&quot;&gt;Final Thought&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple sucks, no doubt about it. I am just waiting for AMD and Intel to crush M1. Will that happen or will Apple kill them at their own game is yet to be seen. I haven’t restarted my friends project yet, I am still evaluating stuff, once done will blog about Data Science on M1. I feel M1 is okay for computer pioneers, for others who can lay hands on &lt;a href=&quot;https://system76.com&quot;&gt;System 76&lt;/a&gt;, better do so.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Stunning possibility in Data Science</title><link href="/2021/02/13/stunning-possibility-in-data-science.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stunning possibility in Data Science" /><published>2021-02-13T14:36:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-02-13T14:36:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/02/13/stunning-possibility-in-data-science</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/13/stunning-possibility-in-data-science.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.arizonafoothillsmagazine.com/valleygirlblog/wp-content/uploads/Marilyn-Monroe-Pictures.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Merlin Monroe&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was 2005 I think, web development professionals were demanding US$ 10 per hour, I saw an opportunity, out of college and wounded by corporate HCL, a guy who had no idea on how to code in HTML approached real estate companies and said that their websites would be done at very cheap price. My idea was to train myself and do the code for US $ 10 per day, it worked, I had to get more people to satisfy orders. Works like people who thought like me has made websites dirt cheap today. Today I can get your website in a day, with just for $100 where most of it is my profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I see a similar chance Data Science. It’s just like web tech then. Then HTML, Ajax, Server, Domain were the terms that were cool, and people would shove money into your face if you tell these terms. Today its Data Science, Machine Learning, Big Data, Tensor flow and so on. Why they are cool? I don’t know. once upon a time Merlin Monroe was hot, people paid hug amount for anything that had that buzz word, but today? No. Today it might be Kim Kardashian, tomorrow? who knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/koko.ng/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Kim-Kardashian-Sexy-Swimsuit-Kanye-West-KOKO-TV-Nigeria.jpg?resize=626%2C681&amp;amp;ssl=1&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kim Kardashian&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans seem to have this peculiar tendency to rate hight fo certain words at certain time. I don’‘t know the exact psychology why so, but it is so. My business model is this. I see not so much good Data Science professional say in a big company demanding salary of Rs 45 Lakhs per annum. why can’t I train people so cheap that they will challenge this guys, offer better quality code for just Rs 15 Lakhs per annum?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving down tech cost is very important. Today I type this on a machine that has no fan but has possibly 1000X the processing power of computers in 1980’s. the result, this blog will be read by 1000’s of people at dirt cheap prices. I will get more Data Science and Cloud business without relying on expensive marketing people, which in turn will translate to lower and more affordable services for 100’s of others, and so it goes. One day it would be affordable enough to own an entire star system!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Merlin Monroe</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rajinikanth in Free Software</title><link href="/free%20software/ruby/apple/mac%20m1/tamil/japan/culture/2021/02/11/rajinikanth-in-free-software.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rajinikanth in Free Software" /><published>2021-02-11T16:03:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-02-11T16:03:00+05:30</updated><id>/free%20software/ruby/apple/mac%20m1/tamil/japan/culture/2021/02/11/rajinikanth-in-free-software</id><content type="html" xml:base="/free%20software/ruby/apple/mac%20m1/tamil/japan/culture/2021/02/11/rajinikanth-in-free-software.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/49/%E0%AE%9A%E0%AF%82%E0%AE%AA%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%AA%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%B8%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%9F%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%8D_%E0%AE%B0%E0%AE%9C%E0%AE%BF%E0%AE%A9%E0%AE%BF%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%A8%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%A4%E0%AF%8D_-_Actor_Rajinikanth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rajinikanth is an hero here in Tamilnadu, India. He is a hero in Japan too. He has done nothing useful but to act, but his funny and comical way of acting has attracted fans like Tom and Jerry would attract fans and his movies are great to watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ruby’s creator Matz is Japanese, so as an Tamil I was asking him to view Rajikanth’s movie and he did :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/karthik_ak?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@karthik_ak&lt;/a&gt; I watched &amp;#39;The Robot|Enthiran&amp;#39;. It was marvelous.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Yukihiro Matsumoto (@yukihiro_matz) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/yukihiro_matz/status/720808569365397504?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;April 15, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and that’s okay because Rajini is super famous in Japan. His film Muthu grossed more than Titanic in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I wanted to manage Ruby versions on my machine and hence tried rbenv, and it did not work. I was using Mac M1 and its a bit pain to get Ruby on it. So after lot of DuckDuckGoing pain I found this tool called asdf here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.driftingruby.com/episodes/a-rubyist-s-apple-m1-review&quot;&gt;https://www.driftingruby.com/episodes/a-rubyist-s-apple-m1-review&lt;/a&gt;. It looked simple and it should work. But ya, we are installing Ruby 3 on rosetta instead of M1, hmmmm….. not okay, but okay. I managed to get Ruby installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then this happened:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;% asdf | tail
                                        environment used for command shim execution.
asdf info                               Print OS, Shell and ASDF debug information.
asdf reshim &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;            Recreate shims for version of a package
asdf shim-versions &amp;lt;command&amp;gt;            List the plugins and versions that
                                        provide a command
asdf update                             Update asdf to the latest stable release
asdf update --head                      Update asdf to the latest on the master branch

&quot;Late but latest&quot;
-- Rajinikanth
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the version of asdf I am currently using :o&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;% asdf --version
v0.8.0
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I checked the faces on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/asdf-vm/asdf&quot;&gt;asdf&lt;/a&gt; and found this guy &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/HashNuke&quot;&gt;Akash Manohar&lt;/a&gt;, an Indian, possibly a Tamil if not Japanese :D living in Banglore.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why India should absorb Pakistan and Bangladesh?</title><link href="/geography/india/2020/10/17/why-india-should-absorb-pakistan-and-bangladesh.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why India should absorb Pakistan and Bangladesh?" /><published>2020-10-17T15:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-17T15:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/geography/india/2020/10/17/why-india-should-absorb-pakistan-and-bangladesh</id><content type="html" xml:base="/geography/india/2020/10/17/why-india-should-absorb-pakistan-and-bangladesh.html">&lt;p&gt;Why did we elect Modi as our priminister? We did not like Manmohan Singh (even though he’s a genius,) to listen to a woman of Italian origin. We have just got freedom from Brits who don’t even wash their bottoms yet, and now we have to listen to a lady who is from a similar culture. We were fed up with 2G, and other scams that plagued our nation. For people like me, if Modi came to power he would not hesitate to kill Pakistanis and integrate that state with us. He is a person who watched genocide of Muslims in his own state and feels unrepentant, I thought he would not hesitate to put an end to Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;History needs Hitler like and devils. If it’s not for Winston Churchill who killed millions in India by shipping grains to Europe, England would have not won the second world war. If India needs a bloody war with Pakistan to wipe them off so that our territorial integrity is maintained, and so be it. Congress won’t do it, so we put a Satan in power. But this Satan is killing our own people who are Muslims and other lower castes in Hinduism, than killing Pakistanis and thus bringing relief to Iran, Afghanistan and us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I saw this map of India:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/indian_subcontinent.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look how well our territory is defined by mountains in North, East and West, and ocean at the bottom. And why we can’t rule this tiny land fully? Because some fucker 10,000 years ago said a God called Shiva exists? Because another fucker 1000 years ago said a God called Allah exist? Science says both are untrue! If we listen to some word of mouth things without verifying the facts how stupid we are? We must think about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even today I think Persians and Afghanistan’s refer Pakistanis as Hindu’s. We are the people of Indus, the mighty river that fed and watered our forefathers before all this Muhammad and this Saffron saints existed. We had an really efficient cities, drains, brick making and industrial skills. Still the iron pillars erected by Ashoka  hasn’t rusted, Qutub Minar needs regular tending to keep it upright. That was the level of sophistication we had achieved eons ago. A might civilization was spread from Boluchistan to Tamilnadu. In fact Dravidian Civilization was spread from Iran to Srilanka eons before Ashoka ruled. We are one people, and we have lost it all because few idiots point out to few texts and say that we are different people. What a bullshit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the United Kingdom, European Union and United States, we must form a united India that consists of Pakistan, Bangladesh, India, Srilanka and Burma We may have different parliaments, governments and cultures but we can have common things like defense, space program, scientific endeavor. There will be no borders among these states, people could travel freely without restrictions, a common currency would mean a better commerce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But ya, dream is a dream, foolish humans are foolish humans.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Why did we elect Modi as our priminister? We did not like Manmohan Singh (even though he’s a genius,) to listen to a woman of Italian origin. We have just got freedom from Brits who don’t even wash their bottoms yet, and now we have to listen to a lady who is from a similar culture. We were fed up with 2G, and other scams that plagued our nation. For people like me, if Modi came to power he would not hesitate to kill Pakistanis and integrate that state with us. He is a person who watched genocide of Muslims in his own state and feels unrepentant, I thought he would not hesitate to put an end to Pakistan.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to understand non Chennai Tamils emotions?</title><link href="/2020/10/10/how-to-understand-non-chennai-tamils-emotions.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to understand non Chennai Tamils emotions?" /><published>2020-10-10T10:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-10T10:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/10/10/how-to-understand-non-chennai-tamils-emotions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/10/10/how-to-understand-non-chennai-tamils-emotions.html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t know why I remembered this incident now, but anyway, a kind of funny thing happened long long ago. Opposite to the Medavakkam share auto stand there was and I think there is still a briyani shop, not hi-fi, but a very local one. Briyani over there was relatively cheap, and of good quality? I don’t remember the quality. Anyway….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I had a friend Senthil (he is a big shot in AIADMK), some how my busyness has left me without touch with him recently, he had a friend called Naveen, I think from Thankaasi, they both worked in Zoho. We 3, after just another meting where we planned for a Trillion dollar world conquering company, we thought of having nice treat. Who wouldn’t have briyani after planning about a Trillion dollar enterprise? We would!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we went to the shop we ordered chicken, something with lot of bones so that my friends felt good to hold and eat(, I always favor lot of meat chunk, more value for money you see). The chicken came, I think I forgot about the existence of this universe and started to focus on this chicken. After sometime Naveen started to breathe heavy, when I saw him he was looking at the chicken with great attention had bitten a piece and started to breathe heavy, okay, I started to dig into my pieces when Senthil said ‘let’s goto another shop, this place is not good’. I did not understand a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We turned the corner and went into another shop, there we ordered the same Chicken lollipop, I think it came from the same local shop where we were eating, but since the ambiance was good this guy Naveen was okay. Senthil asked Navaeen, ‘you did not like the ambiance right?’ and Naveen noded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am BBC (born and brought up in Chennai), I really wonder how and why village people thought and communicated like that and I really don’t know how to read their fucking emotions. How could heavy breathing mean this thing and blah blah, but not ‘wow I love this spicy chicken!’. I really don’t get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In another case I had a friend called Umashankar who I met in Zanec. All people said very good things about him and I landed up forming a company with him called Trumatics, it was in Velacherry. Ideally it should not have all the evils Zanec had and it was supposed to take off great. But after sometime Umashankar used to abuse my work, he used to say very ill things and used to say Skikit-Learn, Facebook Prophet are totally wrong, which stunned me. Slowly I started to prove he was wrong and till that time he used to sit with us, he shifted to another room. Though he abused me before others, he pulled me up and said not to prove him wrong before others because that hurt his image.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day when I went to file for tax, my auditors asked about the company, they rang up Uma, they knew I was super passionate. When I left, without my knowledge they rang my home up and seems to have expressed doubts in Uma, and said if Karthik is in right path he will be out of the company before next tax filing. I wonder how they got it in just 2 minutes conversation?! When I came out of Trumatics, then when people in my home revealed this to me, I was stunned by my auditors professionalism. May be Uma wanted me out all the time. Who knows? May be he set up something bogus company, who knows? I never ran my companies like Uma. I focus on how tech could help people and not how I could make money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uma is also from a place called Salem, a deep south city, may be he was communicating with me non verbally. But how to understand it? I have no clue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We BBC’s have one motive in life, that is to be happy, from our young age we had everything and if we wanted something we asked for it. But looks like the rest of Tamilnadu, the rural India somehow seems to have this non verbal communication, possibly they were trashed by their parents for speaking out and revolting. Some how for them breathing heavy means we need to switch hotels, shouting like mad at very proven machine learning libraries in office means get out of my business and something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non Chennai people succeed, there is a psychological basis for it, for us being born itself is success, all our parents want is to watch us being happy and hence we have relatively no pressure. In rural India you have this family pride, your car should change from Swift to Mercedes in 5 years or the fellow villagers won’t respect you or something, so these non Chennai people if they don’t achieve something they fall into depression of failure, for us, ya we feel depressed when we fail, but a peg, a tandoori, a mutton briyani would fix it and none would bother about us, and we would bother about none.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why I am writing this blog is, lot of Chennai people are in I.T offices which are dominated by south Tamilnadu fools who have these fucking old tradition thing and stuff. So when they behave mad at you, its their way. For us spitting, urinating, defecating in public is not right, for them even their best people do it. They are totally different. The solution for this, I have no fucking clue! :D&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I don’t know why I remembered this incident now, but anyway, a kind of funny thing happened long long ago. Opposite to the Medavakkam share auto stand there was and I think there is still a briyani shop, not hi-fi, but a very local one. Briyani over there was relatively cheap, and of good quality? I don’t remember the quality. Anyway….</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Moral void of youtubers during pandemic</title><link href="/2020/10/06/moral-void-of-youtubers-during-pandemic.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moral void of youtubers during pandemic" /><published>2020-10-06T12:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-06T12:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/10/06/moral-void-of-youtubers-during-pandemic</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/10/06/moral-void-of-youtubers-during-pandemic.html">&lt;p&gt;I’m a foodie and absolutely love food video’s and review. I want to go on an full India tour just to eat, I feel food and good taste are very essential and I feel no one should never go hungry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a pandemic time. Usually during times of stress and in times when society needs to come together it’s the media people who pick up the task of educating people and they advise the right thing, but look at this video&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9zYoahr6n0g?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This guy looks well educated, may be he won’t get bankrupt if he does not do these video’s, drives a nice car, looks polished, but he still hops from place t place during pandemic which encourages people too to visit these places. I can’t imaging what is happening to peoples brain? This guy may be a fool, but not enough opposition arises against him or other youtubers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, mostly this guy won’t die of Corona, but imagine he has it, shows no symptoms, he might transmit it to some one old, and that person could loose their life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is puzzling is this, if I get Rs 10 from some one for an emergency I keep thinking all night why I did not plan properly and had to borrow, next day morning I give them money back. In fact even if I need change, I give a person Rs 100, get Rs 10 back so that I need not be in debt. In India we have such culture where we should not owe an debt or cause an evil to someone. These guys are Indians too, rather than advising people to stay inside, eat simple food, avoid travel and contact, they encourage it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is not this guy I am angry about, its all these youtubers who want to generate few bucks are behaving in such an irresponsible way. If they die it’s okay, its their wish, but they could harm someone putting videos now, I feel very difficult to digest that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’m a foodie and absolutely love food video’s and review. I want to go on an full India tour just to eat, I feel food and good taste are very essential and I feel no one should never go hungry.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Using Bootstrap Icons in Rails 6 with Webpacker</title><link href="/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/design/bootstrap/2020/10/04/using-bootstrap-icons-in-rails-6-with-webpacker.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Using Bootstrap Icons in Rails 6 with Webpacker" /><published>2020-10-04T20:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-04T20:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/design/bootstrap/2020/10/04/using-bootstrap-icons-in-rails-6-with-webpacker</id><content type="html" xml:base="/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/design/bootstrap/2020/10/04/using-bootstrap-icons-in-rails-6-with-webpacker.html">&lt;p&gt;Font awesome is good and font awesome rails gem neatly integrates with Rails framework, but I think it uses Sprockets which is going out of fashion :(. As a community we are embracing webpacker, I wish we embraced Opal and ditched Javascript completely, but it’s not happening. Anyway…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Font awesome is okay, but their premium icons hide behind paywall and they are not as committed to free software as Booststrap guys I think. Font awesome needs money, they are into that model. The law of software development says that if you are offering a service, there is always a person to outsmart you. Welcome Bootstraop icons &lt;a href=&quot;https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&quot;&gt;https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now how to use it? First add the necessary dependencies using yarn&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ yarn add bootstrap-icon
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now create a file called &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;app/helpers/bootstrap_icons_helper.rb&lt;/code&gt;, in it add this code&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;module&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;BootstrapIconsHelper&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# refer https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;options&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{})&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;file&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;File&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;read&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;node_modules/bootstrap-icons/icons/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;.svg&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;doc&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Nokogiri&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;HTML&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;DocumentFragment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;parse&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;file&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;svg&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;doc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;at_css&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;svg&apos;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;present?&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;svg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;class&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;+=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot; &quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;+&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;doc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;to_html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;html_safe&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now in the app anywhere use this to add an icon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-erb highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;%=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;icon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;alert-circle&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;class: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;text-success&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;%&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To refer the names of icons goto &lt;a href=&quot;https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&quot;&gt;https://icons.getbootstrap.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Font awesome is good and font awesome rails gem neatly integrates with Rails framework, but I think it uses Sprockets which is going out of fashion :(. As a community we are embracing webpacker, I wish we embraced Opal and ditched Javascript completely, but it’s not happening. Anyway…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wish people had astronaut level psychology</title><link href="/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wish people had astronaut level psychology" /><published>2020-10-04T18:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-04T18:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/91/Bruce_McCandless_II_during_EVA_in_1984.jpg/720px-Bruce_McCandless_II_during_EVA_in_1984.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any thing can kill you in space within minutes, even in times of stress you need to be calm. There was a knock at our gate today, our ex-driver it was. He seems to have had a safari near our home and dropped by, one of us engaged him outside the gate and rushed to the bathroom to have a bath, the conversation lasted 15 minutes I think. The people, and even families who worked with us seems to love us and seem to have extreme loyalties crossing generations, but does that warrant foolishness?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chanakya said its not enough to be wise and intelligent, one must also avoid staying around fools. If one is around fools, their intelligence would be wasted. Think of what is happening here, the Church is open, stupid parents drag their kids to it, parents are taking kids to Tirupathi, I haven’t noticed mosques, but just today morning I saw a family of jam packed Muslims (our neighbors) in a car traveling from somewhere to our area. Pathetic. Not even in nightmares I have encountered a situation where I sould be in a place where I would be sourrounded by fools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are in a midst of an pandemic, I wish people reading this have the knowledge to look about it in the dictionary. People know it’s a pandemic and they invent reasons to travel, to mingle! I can’t imagine how stupid we are as a society. If those people who are idiots die I am okay, but if they spread virus around knowing or unknowing, that’s a bloody crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish schools one day start training people about psychology, about logical thinking, about staying calm during situations like these, possibly staying calm during one’s death too. I wish we had astronaut level of psychology training so that we don’t invent reasons to be a fool.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>