<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-05-16T00:57:46+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Ghost encounters in office</title><link href="/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ghost encounters in office" /><published>2023-05-16T00:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-16T00:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office.html">&lt;p&gt;I had two ghost encounters in office till to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first one was in a company called Trumatics. I started it with my friend Umashankar who I met in another company called Zanec. We recruited a girl called Vadivikarasi. In that office I used to take walk in the terrace. Once while I was walking I saw Vadivikarasi leaving office, I thought she was leaving early for some reason. I was 40 feet up, and she was on road. I finished my walk and went downstairs to office and there she was Vadivukkarasi. I was shocked and asked her did she leave office and I said to her, I saw her leaving, she too got terrified. Not wanting to make her more afraid I stopped talking about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what ever left that gate had her dress, backpack like her, skin tone like her, the same hold of cell phone while she browses while she leaves our office. It could be a very strange coincidence that I saw someone else and mistook her, or may be my brain got screwed up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My second encounter was in a company Francium, there was a devops girl who seemed to know the trade, and we talked a lot. She drove an electric bike, at that time there were almost no electric bikes in India. She sat in my room because she is a one who cannot stay without super chill A/C. One day she left home, after some time a guy called Prasanna got introduced, or we were talking after acquitance after some time (may be few days). Suddenly he said my wife is devops here, before I could say I know and ask about the electric bike he said his wife Archana is inside coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My heart stopped, just moments ago I saw his wife leave the office, how can I say to him I saw a ghost which was his wife? This Vadivukkarasi incident popped into my mind. This guy Prasanna asked my why I looked tensed.  Dam hell how can I ever say I saw a ghost which just left office that looked like his wife. I did not react and went in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next day I got a doubt and asked others the name of the devops girl that sits in my room, it was Radha they said. Damn, God, dam, life came into me. I am not a peoples person and I get carried away speaking tech to people I don’t even bother asking about their names and stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I learned these girls names and memorized how they looked so that I don’t get confused. Radha soon quit office and hence from then on if it was devops girl it was Archana. So no more confusion. It was sad seeing a devops engineer who was talented go out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot about the work ethics of Prasanna and Archana, I think Archana left that office before I did, and I was thrown out all of a sudden, and Prasanna quit too. Now I don’t even know if Francium exists. I wonder if any company that let’s go off good talent due to carless planning ever comes up?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I had two ghost encounters in office till to date.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">India, a state intolerant to art and expression</title><link href="/2023/05/09/india-a-state-intolerant-to-art-and-expression.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="India, a state intolerant to art and expression" /><published>2023-05-09T21:36:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-09T21:36:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/09/india-a-state-intolerant-to-art-and-expression</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/09/india-a-state-intolerant-to-art-and-expression.html">&lt;p&gt;I was a bit surprised by negative reaction by Islamist towards Kerala Story. It’s a movie that’s been rated high in IMDB. I’m not sure if any Indian girl has been converted by ISIS into Islam and made to perform terror strikes, or serve as slaves to them, but even if they did, why would India expose it for the fear of embarrassment?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I first thought Kerala Story was a Malayalam movie, but it turns out it’s a Hindi one. I wish it could be translated to Tamil so that I can enjoy it full.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure some Islamist who do say The Kerala Story should be banned, surely said that BBC excellent documentary about Modi’s genocide in Gujarat should be screened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an atheist, I do get offended seeing people scammed by Temples, Mosques, Church, Guruduvaras which claim that God, Satan, Angels, Spirits and Supernatural stuff exists, but I certainly don’t oppose movies that are supernatural based (in fact they are really entertaining), even though I feel movies based on facts should be created rather than one preferring to create movies based on beliefs and myth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not the first time intolerance is seen in India. During Pakistan’s creation, Muslims and Hindus were intolerant to each other. Thousands of years ago before Islamists invaded India, one sect of Hindus were at war with others, but yes at that time there was no single Hinduism, there isn’t a single Hinduism now too. I would even claim what Christianity and Islam that is practiced in India is a part of Hinduism too. Maybe those God’s too will be part of Hindu’s collection of Gods hundreds of years from now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;M.F.Hussein died in Qatar and not in India. Taslima Nasreen is I think is living in France and not in India or Bangladesh which should be her motherland. Karuppar Kuutam youtube channel was banned by Hindu extremists who were pissed off when a group of youngsters thought the world the meaning of Hindu scriptures. Davinci Code did not screen well because the Christians wanted it to be banned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not just religious groups that are intolerant. Great cartoons against corruption emerged, like say one cartoon depicting mother India’s hand is held by politicians and bureaucrats, while corporate who have bribed them line up to rape her, I think it (the rape) was watched by the four lions of Ashoka with their tongue’s out. Politicians and bureaucrats got furious because it depicted India’s situation well, and they banned that cartoons against corruption website so that people don’t get educated about corruption in our nation. Very sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really wonder when Indian’s will learn to think rationally, respect art, thought, difference of opinion, freedom of ones belies, etc. Or maybe we will end up corrupting the world with our old thoughts (till humans exists), which even made California banning Indian caste system in its state.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was a bit surprised by negative reaction by Islamist towards Kerala Story. It’s a movie that’s been rated high in IMDB. I’m not sure if any Indian girl has been converted by ISIS into Islam and made to perform terror strikes, or serve as slaves to them, but even if they did, why would India expose it for the fear of embarrassment?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Miss Vairamuthu in Ponniyin Selvan</title><link href="/2023/04/30/miss-vairamuthu-in-ponniyin-selvan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Miss Vairamuthu in Ponniyin Selvan" /><published>2023-04-30T22:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-30T22:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/04/30/miss-vairamuthu-in-ponniyin-selvan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/04/30/miss-vairamuthu-in-ponniyin-selvan.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0d/Vairamuthu_alaigal_book_shop.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Photo By Gavaskar.tk - Own work, CC BY-SA 4.0, &lt;a href=&quot;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=39272896&quot;&gt;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=39272896&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maniratnam said that we are giving chance to new lyricist in Ponniyin Selvan, but I feel for a such a novel cherished by Tamils, which is been made into a movie, we must have gone for the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am well aware of the controversy surrounding Vairamuthu, there is even a gossip that says he has girls hotels in chennai supplying girls for him and his friends. If Vairamuthu has done anything against the law he should be punished. There is a very good chance that since Vairamuthu is been cherished by the Tamil people, and has deep political connections, no action is taken against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I feel is, even Vairamuthu is in jail, he must have been asked if he could write songs for Ponniyin Selvan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those who have read the book have got nothing good to say about the movie, it’s just running because of huge marketing effort. I am not sure if Lyca is just a money laundering company like Red Giant. In fact I am waiting for Viduthalai part 2 than Ponniyin Selvan 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly feel not having Vairamuthu in this movie is another slip for Maniratnam. I feel they should have boldly said that they are not bothered by Vairamuthu’s personal side, and they have recruited the poet in him to make this movie a good one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Photo By Gavaskar.tk - Own work, CC BY-SA 4.0, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=39272896</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why use ReactJS, Angular or Vue with Ruby on Rails?</title><link href="/2023/04/24/why-use-reactjs-angular-or-vue-with-ruby-on-rails.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why use ReactJS, Angular or Vue with Ruby on Rails?" /><published>2023-04-24T17:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-24T17:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/04/24/why-use-reactjs-angular-or-vue-with-ruby-on-rails</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/04/24/why-use-reactjs-angular-or-vue-with-ruby-on-rails.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiggzg4m2rnb44a5f6yucz3hlg27uvaaiabcfpgqsbiybz37w7r2ne.ipfs.dweb.link/1571754069Ruby on Rails Copyright Free Logo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s super mysterious to me why people choose to use ReactJS, Angular or Vue with Ruby on Rails and pay the price for low productivity. It’s like people are blind and pretend to know nothing about code. Or they go by Popularity Driven Development? That is, they choose stuff based on popularity without technical analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ruby programming language was created to be programmers best friend, and it is, until you reach say nears a million lines of code, at that stage OOP fails, you must switch to functional programming, but for medium-sized apps Ruby is best and Ruby o Rails tries to be Rubyish as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails emphasizes readability and productivity. JavaScript is a natural eye soar, hard to read, hard to debug. Right from Rails 2 I think there is a way to reduce JS code in Rails. First it was RJS, then you sent request using jQuery and got JS payload back which replaced part of page, then now you have this wonderful HotWire which does the same thus minimizing JavaScript hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout history Rails has provided better way to build webpages than any known JS framework. It’s a super mystery for me why anyone would choose a JS framework, increase code complexity, go for large team and ultimately be unproductive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why big tech created JS frameworks was because they have grown big and wants to manage front and back end teams separately. The front end guy might need to interact with designer, test UI in various devices, connect with the backend using API. The backend person designs API, checks the access capability of the user to a particular piece of data, and if some API is hit, triggers some business logic. Those two are different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;70% of the websites could just be static web pages. You don’t need a front end or backend frameworks for it, another 10% might need a simple scripting like PHP, another 18% might be okay with Rails, Laravel and so on, may be just 2% of the apps will be need to have separate front and back end teams, bureaucracy, planning, inefficiency and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a feeling that Indian companies want to bill the client more by adding more people to app development citing complexity, architecture, planning, project management and blah blah, rather than having a lean team, finishing stuff up, and increasing per-capita developer revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come into the present Info Tech firms!!! Common, you are embarrassing me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiaou7bgoe6pi4t5rhduszmfhilqf2twdye2koebxkjhsyjaxltf3a.ipfs.dweb.link/Facepalm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A BJP car gives me a laugh</title><link href="/2023/04/09/a-bjp-car-gives-me-a-laugh.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A BJP car gives me a laugh" /><published>2023-04-09T22:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-09T22:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/04/09/a-bjp-car-gives-me-a-laugh</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/04/09/a-bjp-car-gives-me-a-laugh.html">&lt;p&gt;Think of H.Raja, Tamil Isai Sounderajan, R.N.Ravi, Modi, Annamalai and so on, they are good for nothing comedians who rose to top because the nation is full of idiots. I have always wondered why there are so many idiots in BJP, I don’t know the answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I encountered a BJP car, I was driving from my friends home to a restaurant may be. The layout in Sithalapakkamis such that there was dead end and there was only one narrow road out, it’s behind JFA furniture’s. At the mouth of the narrow road was parked a car with a BJP flag in the car’s dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not good with identifying cars, so don’t remember what car it is, but it was big. Usually when you park the car in such a hindering way, the driver will be there in case you need to move it if you are causing trouble, here the driver too was not found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to drive my car very carefully, in fear that I would scratch that BJP car parked in most stupid way possible. Just feet away was the main road where there are ample spaces to park, but being a stupid that person got into BJP and somehow his lack of IQ made him park in worst spot possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if your intelligence is zero, and even if you park randomly, I wonder if one could park like that, I wonder how these BJP people generate such negative intelligence? That skill of theirs is baffling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While crossing that huge car I saw scratch marks, indicating this guy has been fool for a long, I started to laugh. Any way with idiots like this rising to the top, we are well on our way to become like Afghanistan under Taliban.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Think of H.Raja, Tamil Isai Sounderajan, R.N.Ravi, Modi, Annamalai and so on, they are good for nothing comedians who rose to top because the nation is full of idiots. I have always wondered why there are so many idiots in BJP, I don’t know the answer.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Making Tamilnadu a I.T superpower</title><link href="/2023/04/08/making-tamilnadu-a-it-superpower.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Making Tamilnadu a I.T superpower" /><published>2023-04-08T12:07:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-08T12:07:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/04/08/making-tamilnadu-a-it-superpower</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/04/08/making-tamilnadu-a-it-superpower.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreia5lj3w2bzraczt3vpo7ydueqtkfz4x5vuihjggw54h7goxbvvjkm&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;River Noiyal is totally polluted, thanks to the industries in Tirupur. Similarly, all rivers in Tamilnadu are polluted, cancer rates are increasing due to urbanization. North India still has low productivity and is low in Industry, the ideal thing would be is to move some industries in Tamilnadu to the northern states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What would Tamilnadu do if industries are moved? Thankfully concentration on mass education means we can start info tech and knowledge based industries here, these industries gives job, and cause less pollution than say textile mills and so on. Stalin has rightly said he wants to make Tamilnadu I.T superpower (in India). No way India or Tamilnadu can become I.T superpower of the world, like California is today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish Stalin good luck. I am typing this blog and two phases in my 3 phase home power is not working. Today the third phase just had 4 power cuts so far. One of my office mate is in Wallajah, and he has minimum of 4 hours power cut a day. Today I drove to Chennai and the potholes in rods were numerous. Almost all of my cousins have escaped to the West fearing corruption and inefficiencies in India, college students now seem to be more dumb than I was when I came out of college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Stalin had said Tamilnadu would become #1 in drunkards, or if he had said government will start selling drugs and do prostitution business and become #1 in it, it’s believable. Info tech is a mind thing, you simply can’t say this guy is a member of Karunadhi family, he knows to loot 1000’s of crores, and so he has enough brains to make a state #1 in info tech. It doesn’t work like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to understand what thought is, what freedom is, what communication is, what’s rational thinking and problem-solving is to succeed in info tech industry. You need to know math really well too. You simply can’t send DMK rowdies to 100’s of companies bully them and assassinate them to force them to produce good software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So. Good luck Stalin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oops another power cut at 11:52 AM, this is the fifth one I think for today.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I think evil people face demise</title><link href="/2023/04/03/why-i-think-evil-people-face-demise.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I think evil people face demise" /><published>2023-04-03T21:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-03T21:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/04/03/why-i-think-evil-people-face-demise</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/04/03/why-i-think-evil-people-face-demise.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://yu7.in/reaper-pic&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friends say it chills their spine to think about what happened to people who did evil to me. For some reason people who did evil to me get destroyed. Most of them are dead, and for many others, their loved ones in their family is dead, thus crippling them to do anything against me. Their spirit of life is taken away, they walk dead never again dare to face me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being an atheist, this has baffled me. My friends, this they say that I must start believing in God’s and spirits that protect me. I strongly disagree. Everything is a chance, but very consistent destruction of evil people who come into my life seems baffling. I thought hard about it and here is my theory why they face demise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We say evil people face demise, but turn it around it’s head and say people who face demise do evil. It’s like Annaduari’s saying “விட்டு கொடுப்பவன் கெட்டு போவதில்ல, கெட்டுப்போபவன் விட்டு கொடுப்பதில்லை” (a person who gives up does not rot, a person who rots does not give up).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our brain is split, there is more straight forward conscious communication, but there is s subconscious communication between your body and mind. Say that a person has a disease and his subconscious mind realizes it (maybe the person is dying superfast), it feels the pain, it tries to communicate the pain to others in conscious way, and it does by doing evil. It’s the communication of pain of subconscious mind that knows its rotting and ending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel ones subconscious mind can even sense demise of family members and their loved ones at a very early stage and those minds too start doing evil to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, when a person dies or looses his or her loved ones, we say it’s because it’s because of the evil deeds they have done, but it could be because they sensed their or loved ones demise without consciously knowing and felt the pain, and so they actually started doing evil as a form of communicating this pain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are others that do evil and still thrive, that’s psychopaths, that’s of different dimension, but for those who have faced demise doing evil to me (some have even contacted me to seek forgiveness), this is the only explanation I could come up with.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Khalistan now?</title><link href="/2023/03/31/why-khalistan-now.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Khalistan now?" /><published>2023-03-31T00:22:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-31T00:22:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/03/31/why-khalistan-now</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/03/31/why-khalistan-now.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://yu7.in/T475WF &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video above shows people in queue, I saw this on Reddit, these people are standing to get flour. First I thought it was Afghanistan, but then it turned out to be Pakistan. While the elite there seem to have a good life, people are suffering. Pakistan never gave up its Jihad on India, it wants to destroy us entirely, but its economic situation is such that it cannot fund terrorists. Remember Pakistan is a country that values Jihad and Terrorism far higher than good life of its people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even strong Islamic countries like the UAE, Saudi Arabia don’t see the point anymore to sponsor their proxy wars against India, they are staying away from funding terrorism in Pakistan. After the solar cell and electric vehicle revolution, the age of oil is fast coming to an end, if these countries don’t reform, their economies would collapse. For good economics, one has to shake hands with atheistic China, and secular India. Pakistan did shake hands with China, but its still obsessed with destroying India. Looks like brains of ISI and its army is screwed and nothing can be done about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With funding for Islamic terror running out, Pakistan is looking for something cheap. Looks like its agents are talking with Sikh separatist who want a separate nation called Khalistan. Ideally Khalistan should be from Afghanistan, all the way into Punjab, into Kashmir and to Tibet. In today’s scenario that’s impossible, but for Pakistan, all it needs is to give trouble to India, and may be all you need as a Sikh separatist is a moral boost, so that reality could be ignored, and it looks like that moral support is provided by Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afghanistan followed Pakistan, Pakistan’s own people followed Pakistan, now we know their fate. I think this will be the same fate of Khalistan separatists who follow Pakistan very soon. Khalistan seekers will become deeply religious, highly intolerant, strict, unproductive and hence economically weak, but will have a mindset of war and violence. Maybe they too will starve to death one day.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Better prison than tyrant</title><link href="/2023/03/25/better-prison-than-tyrant.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Better prison than tyrant" /><published>2023-03-25T09:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-25T09:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/03/25/better-prison-than-tyrant</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/03/25/better-prison-than-tyrant.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/8c/David_-_The_Death_of_Socrates.jpg/1644px-David_-_The_Death_of_Socrates.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Socrates said what he said and faced death for it. Nehru said what he said and he faced prison. Maybe Rahul Gandhi is following the footsteps of his great-grandfather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every civilization faces dark ages, and this is a dark age for India. We are ruled by a dictator who cannot stand criticism and who cannot face journalists. In short Modi is incapable of being a democratic leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Rahul said is simply a democratic way of living. He said this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Why do all these thieves have Modi as their surname? Nirav Modi, Lalit Modi, Narendra Modi.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Rahul Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One can react to it in many ways, one is to accept it true and so get angry about it and try to eliminate such comments, another one is to ignore it, another way is, if one is getting an impression that people with name &lt;em&gt;Modi&lt;/em&gt; in it are corrupt, take a simple survey. Go to a place where lot of Modi’s live, find out how many of them were kept quiet when Muslims were massacred, find of out many of them have done jewelry and sports fraud. If say more than 30% of them have done it, maybe we are up to something, else you have got a statistics to show that what Rahul Gandhi said only applied to three Modi’s who are an exception, and most of them are normal people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreicc27xjje2nsdjbahg5edklydkf5ngwuuhb5wdu72st6tnp6r255e.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Using Rahul Gandhi controversy to make people forget Adani scam.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s sad to see Nation going down the drain in hands of BJP. Rather than going behind possible criminals like Adani, finding out how that group caused so much losses, publishing the truth and taking legal action, this dictatorial just want to banish people who question it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreiewfblq3tx7kg37vibeeeho2vafn3cmlq4soxvia732o2hu5j4vci&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What path Rahul Gandhi is taking seems to be the right one. It’s better goto prison and even get executed by the tyrant Modi than to live under his rule. I’m sure those who put salt in food and eat, and people who do experience shame will follow Rahul.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tamilnadu government school rocks</title><link href="/2023/03/17/tamilnadu-government-school-rocks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tamilnadu government school rocks" /><published>2023-03-17T23:34:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-17T23:34:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/03/17/tamilnadu-government-school-rocks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/03/17/tamilnadu-government-school-rocks.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeibk7xzmlyinnjsfrwcmwzepgo5aqix4767wbqt72ctxf2mdwvelxi &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine if in a private school kids could throw off their duppata since its their choice. I studied in a college called Panimalar, if any girl there would arrive to college without a duppata, she would be sent back home, her parent will be called the next day, they would be humiliated and made to cry, their family would be insulted by the management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am really proud of the DMK government in this case. Yes they are looters, yes people died in mysterious ways when 2G scam went on, yes they loot public money to construct remembrance structures for Karunanidhi, Stalin can’t even banish stray dogs that bark every day in my street spoiling my sleep, he cannot give a month long of power without interruption, DMK can’t even sports minister or chief minister outside Karunadnidhi’s family, it has no democracy, but they are making impoverished realize their power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The author in the video is said to have written book, possibly calling girls not to wear duppatas, the girls in this school seems to have read it and got fascinated by it, and they threw it off when the author visited their school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreiemvtgaybjsjotpf6geeqgkysxwn2oailoiulkfj2bougva3ooyxi&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We in India make fun of Iran, Saudi Arabia and Islam for forcing women to abide by dress code, but this author has clearly seems to have explained that India is almost no different from these religious fanatic nations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish parents in Tamilnadu who send kids to private schools visited government schools, make their kids join there, and donate the high amount of money they would pay to private school to the government school in which their kids study.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the kids in this school, we parents should get educated, and not fall on corrupt private schools feet since they charge a lot just to cheat us and ruin our kids life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry></feed>