<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-03T06:40:49+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Baba Ramdev a fraud?</title><link href="/2018/10/03/baba-ramdev-a-fraud.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baba Ramdev a fraud?" /><published>2018-10-03T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-03T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/10/03/baba-ramdev-a-fraud</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/03/baba-ramdev-a-fraud.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.indianexpress.com/2017/08/ramdev-baba-film-ye-hai-india-759.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Baba Ramdev&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a Yogi in India who is called as Ramdev. He is advocate of how things Indian are superior to those of the west. He portrays himself as the savior of Indians from western influence and products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He promotes yoga and has got a product line called Patanjali which produces FMCG products so that Indian’s don’t buy western brands. All good, but what happens when Ramdev falls sick? Even though he calls himself a Yogi and promotes Indian stuff, when there is a real  issue with his health, he runs abroad for treatment says gossip. What a shame on him!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not just him, late M.G.Ramachandran, an actor and ex-chief-minister of Tamilnadu had a famous song line in one of his movies that say “Whats not there in this divine nation (India), why should we stretch our hands to foreign nations?”. Yet when he had a major illness with his Kidney what did he do? He ran to USA to get a treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0CNplJ-qiN4?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can only pity the people of India, how stupid they are and how they start to believe people who are in lime light so easy, and how they forget and forgive what the famous say and give in to sentiments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/_SNvusPdNHDc/TTFdpbANlFI/AAAAAAAAAlI/eyRVaccPDp4/s1600/annadurai.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;C.N.Annadurai&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should also be noted that another leader in India, C.N.Annadurai was critical of Tamils ignorance. He never boasted about Indian superiority over the West, at the same time he never said the West are superior to us. He acknowledged reality that West was highly developed compared to us and advocated close partnership. He got treatment for his cancer from USA and that’s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Annadurai once said, when asked a Tamilian “whats the capital of USA?”, a Tamil would not know the answer, but when asked “whats the vehicle of Yamadharamn?”, “its buffalo” a Tamil would say without hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will the people of my nation become more intelligent?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Baba Ramdev</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Iyappan and Strange Hinduism</title><link href="/2018/10/02/iyappan-and-strange-hinduism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Iyappan and  Strange Hinduism" /><published>2018-10-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/10/02/iyappan-and-strange-hinduism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/02/iyappan-and-strange-hinduism.html">![](https://thishollowearth.files.wordpress.com/2011/01/ayyappa.jpg)

Its quiet strange what has been happening in Hinduism for centuries. Like many cultures around the world, here in India, women are deprived of many rights, though they are slowly getting it back. I am happy that the supreme court has given a verdict that women can go into Iyappan temple. For centuries women have been kept out.

For some reason the God Iyappa there seems not to like women who are menstruating for some reason. No wonder he was born in an era that was relatively unscientific compared to what it is today and possibly menstruation was considered a taboo. Today in the age of science we know that's not the case and its a natural process. So women are not less to men because they menstruate and hence they can be allowed in the temple says the court.

But still Hinduism seems strange to me. Pilliyar and Hanumaan are are both unmarried and symbolized bhramachariyam (the art of not getting intoxicated and seduced by women), yet its not bad for women to worship them, go to their temples, touch their pictures and idols. Its only in Iyappan temple we see all these fuss. That's strange.

Now that the court has given equal rights to women, I wonder what is going to happen next. We have the fanatic RSS which is supported by the ruling BJP, and many ordinary Hindus do not welcome this verdict. Will families send their women of age to Iyappan temple? None knows. Even if women of age do go to the temple, will they be safe? Wont the fanatics try to harass them, some cases insult and kill them? No one knows.

One day Indian public will be mature. They will look upon women been banned from going to Iyappan as idiotic as women been forced to commit sathi, but till the mentality changes anything tragic fueled by Hindu fanatics could happen. That too today these fanatics are immune to law and order. Lets see....</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why VIP’s need special treatment?</title><link href="/2018/08/30/why-vip-s-need-special-treatment.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why VIP's need special treatment?" /><published>2018-08-30T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-08-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/08/30/why-vip-s-need-special-treatment</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/30/why-vip-s-need-special-treatment.html">![](https://dc-cdn.s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/dc-Cover-20160113043000.original.jpeg)

There is a new law coming in India that says VIP's must need a separate passage way in toll passes. That is the people who are our servants want to rush ahead of us rather than waiting behind our ass, or in other words VIP's want us to sniff their ass and follow them. Fuck. How dare they?

If a country is equal, then why we need to have a divide of VIP's and non VIP's. Imagine thousands of vehicles standing in a jam, and one lane on either side of toll pass just been kept free for these shitty VIP's. I just can't digest it. I pay so much taxes and those bastards who live on my money want to have a better and special treatment which I am not entitled to. Fuck them.

What a country am I living in? People who loot me are able to enjoy better than me. People should think, think about what we have done to ourselves in the name of democracy. Here a ruling in High Court is passed in which we have a new caste system that's been developed in which the upper most caste is VVIP', VIP's, Rich, and then we are shudras, the working class who do all the work but are entitled to sniff their shit and nothing else.

Think people think.

**Reference**

1. [India This Hour](https://indiathishour.in/separate-toll-lanes-for-vips-including-sitting-judges-madras-hc/)</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">India wide energy and water network</title><link href="/2018/08/16/india-wide-energy-and-water-network.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="India wide energy and water network" /><published>2018-08-16T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-08-16T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/08/16/india-wide-energy-and-water-network</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/16/india-wide-energy-and-water-network.html">Its flood in Kerala, tens are dying in it, Karnataka too is receiving a huge rainfall. These were the states that denied water to my state Tamilnadu for political and other reasons, and politicians in my state too took advantage of it to  increase their propaganda and get attention. The truth is, though we cannot completely avoid floods, we can minimize it by distributing water surplus to throughout India with careful planning and engineering.

As floods ravage many parts of our nation, we still have huge deserts in the North which when irrigated could produce food and support lot of livestock. Imagine the price of meat today in or nation, it has sky rocketed leaving many poor to be vegetarians.

|![](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/92/Thar_desert_Rajasthan_India.jpg/1024px-Thar_desert_Rajasthan_India.jpg)|
|:-:|
| *Thar Desert India* |

In fact the Chinese are converting their deserts to green paradise and are shrinking desert size, this achievement has never been done by any country

{% youtube jkdxObsCVGY %}

This type of achievement is possible in India too, if we can distribute water throughout the nation with pipes and motors we can achieve this. Pumping water costs energy, how can we find energy in an energy starved nation like us? The answer is solar and wind, India is a sunlight surplus nation, we also lot of shoreline that means we can harness wind energy, now offshore wind is becoming big and its costs are dropping.

{% youtube PUlfvXaISvc %}

If we can let homes apply for 0% loans to install solar on their roof tops, connect it to national grid, then we can make electricity extremely cheap. When there is excess electricity we can use it for pumping water from one place to another thus leveling out floods and water surplus.

{% youtube pKHTmhOeyLg %}

Imagine a million kilometers of pipe with 2 meters in diameter, they can store 2 trillion liters of water, this mega pipeline that crisscrosses the nation will add a network storage effort. On such a large scale this grand Indian pipeline will become like the railways, it needs many managers, engineers , laborers to keep it working.

This freshwater network could also serve as a energy storage solution. When there is huge amount of fresh water we can use pumped hydro to store excess energy that's been generated by our electricity grid and salinity gradient to generate energy in coastal regions.

{% youtube CDlvjkfpX_o %}

{% youtube 5UxCUuk4CEs %}

More canals, dykes and dams would mean more aquaculture. We all know how much fish and sea food costs now, this project could bring it down.

Are all these possible in a corrupt and bureaucratic country like India? I don't know. Technically its possible, as an Engineer I can guarantee it. But there are water surplus states in India who would like to let their water waste to sea than to give it to their neighbors. They have been blocking such a scheme for long.</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Its flood in Kerala, tens are dying in it, Karnataka too is receiving a huge rainfall. These were the states that denied water to my state Tamilnadu for political and other reasons, and politicians in my state too took advantage of it to increase their propaganda and get attention. The truth is, though we cannot completely avoid floods, we can minimize it by distributing water surplus to throughout India with careful planning and engineering.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A possible mistake in Rails Active Storage documentation</title><link href="/2018/06/23/a-possible-mistake-in-rails-active-storage-documentation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A possible mistake in Rails Active Storage documentation" /><published>2018-06-23T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-06-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/06/23/a-possible-mistake-in-rails-active-storage-documentation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/06/23/a-possible-mistake-in-rails-active-storage-documentation.html">I was coding for a project where image needs to uploaded and resized. I used Rails 5.2 and hence active storage. I did refer its documentation and resized the image as stated in 
[http://edgeguides.rubyonrails.org/active_storage_overview.html#transforming-images](http://edgeguides.rubyonrails.org/active_storage_overview.html#transforming-images) , and to my dismay I got this error message:


{% highlight bash %}
MiniMagick::Error (`mogrify -resize-to-fit [100, 100] /tmp/mini_magick20180623-27536-w8k32h.jpg` failed with error:
mogrify-im6.q16: unrecognized option `-resize-to-fit' @ error/mogrify.c/MogrifyImageCommand/5885.
):
{% endhighlight %}

So reading the error I was able to figure out *resize_to_fit* was not the thing that must be used, so I checked on the internet and found that *resize* works, and one rather than giving:

{% highlight ruby %}
&lt;%= image_tag user.avatar.variant(resize_to_fit: [100, 100]) %&gt;
{% endhighlight %}

can get away by modifying it as 

{% highlight ruby %}
&lt;%= image_tag user.avatar.variant(resize: &quot;100 x100&quot;) %&gt;
{% endhighlight %}

Did any one of you face such an issue? Is there a mistake in Rails docs? I don't know. But it definitely did not work for me.</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was coding for a project where image needs to uploaded and resized. I used Rails 5.2 and hence active storage. I did refer its documentation and resized the image as stated in http://edgeguides.rubyonrails.org/active_storage_overview.html#transforming-images , and to my dismay I got this error message:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The dark side of Fantastic Jeyachandran</title><link href="/2018/05/30/the-dark-side-of-fantastic-jeyachandran.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The dark side of Fantastic Jeyachandran" /><published>2018-05-30T22:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-05-30T22:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/05/30/the-dark-side-of-fantastic-jeyachandran</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/05/30/the-dark-side-of-fantastic-jeyachandran.html">{% youtube n2z-8oLPOWY %}

Jeyachandran invests crores to put ads on T.V about its new showroom in Pallikaranai, and its a grand showroom. I drive past it every day and I drive back late at night everyday.

Though Jeyachandran looks good on the outside and invests a lot of money in marketing, there is a dark side of it. This company seems to have no social consciousness.

For this fantastic Jeyachandran, sales are booming, and at night crowds arrive in large numbers, and their vehicles cause a huge traffic jam. Jeyachandran could ease it but they are doing nothing about it.

There are two main ways Jeyachandran could do it. First, Jeyachandran has 100's of people working with it, just by putting 2 people to control traffic will make a difference, now the junction is chaotic and traffic queues upto a Kilometer and none does anything about it.

The second thing Jeyachandran could do is to clear off some of its bike parking at its space near the roads so that there will be more road width, thus easing up the traffic flow.

But this thing is going on for sometime and Jeyachandran seems not to care. My humble request to people, yes you might be drawn by the low price, but try avoiding Jeyachandran if its possible as they seem to have no society consciousness till now.</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My blog in Dat Protocol</title><link href="/2018/05/28/my-blog-in-dat-protocol.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My blog in Dat Protocol" /><published>2018-05-28T15:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-05-28T15:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/05/28/my-blog-in-dat-protocol</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/05/28/my-blog-in-dat-protocol.html">I'm happy to have discovered Beaker Browser and my website is in dat protocol. You can access it [here](dat://06f0a59a3425002325fedbc8baefec11ef552a901bdb5200ad3aab85d622d7e2/) . This blog is just to test how well my website is getting updated when I put a new post.</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’m happy to have discovered Beaker Browser and my website is in dat protocol. You can access it here . This blog is just to test how well my website is getting updated when I put a new post.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I think Yedurappa and BJP are stupid</title><link href="/2018/05/17/why-i-think-yedurappa-and-bjp-are-stupid.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I think Yedurappa and BJP are stupid" /><published>2018-05-17T12:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-05-17T12:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/05/17/why-i-think-yedurappa-and-bjp-are-stupid</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/05/17/why-i-think-yedurappa-and-bjp-are-stupid.html">![](http://leadtech.in/infoelection/images/politician%20images/yeddyurappa.jpg)

I can't stop laughing, our country is ruled b a party that doesn't know elementary mathematics or it has the potential to buy or rowdy its way to power.

A mark of a gentleman is that he sets out to do whats decently possible, certainly Yedurappa is not of that kind, a childish brain he has, looks like his brain is tell &quot;I wanna be Karnataka C.M one more time even if happens to be days&quot;. Clearly he has no majority.

A politician should think 'how to run an country efficiently?', 'how to better peoples lives?', rather than think about those things BJP is acting childish in a desperate effort to gain power. Possibly its a childish move, or is there more to it?

BJP might be sitting on large swaths of money, possibly the Reddy brothers are ready to pay the BJP to buy MLA's, possibly they have done something terribly wrong and want the BJP to come to power for certain days so that they can hide something in those first few days so that bringing them to justice becomes not so easy.

Whatever! None knows whats there, weather BJP is childish or they have something more sinister, only time will tell. But I hope we had mature politicians who are gentleman than people who cannot control themselves. People who cannot control themselves loot the nations and try to manipulate and subdue the population so that they can escape.</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Telephone Companies Loot You</title><link href="/2018/05/02/how-telephone-companies-loot-you.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Telephone Companies Loot You" /><published>2018-05-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-05-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/05/02/how-telephone-companies-loot-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/05/02/how-telephone-companies-loot-you.html">![](http://images.jagran.com/bsnl_logo_090614.jpg)

I had to surrender one of my BSNL number, I went to Velacherry BSNL office, and damn, those sight of government servants. Definitely that office was unhelpful, you don't know which counter is for what. I went to  a lady clerk, and she keyed in my number on her terminal and found out that my bills were pending, well I haven't used my phone for months. If I hadn't used it for 5 months, why can't they cut my line when I did not pay the bill for the first month? Duh!!!

Instead they were charging me for the phone as though i was using it. Damn. When I pulled out my purse that lady said she can't take money and close my account. What? Bloody hell I am in BSNL office and I can't pay BSNL bill!!!?

I have to pay the bill online, then go to a place to surrender my number, then I need to write a snail mail to their account department to refund the money I had paid as deposit. Damn.

All mobile companies charge you even if you stop paying a months bill. Vodafone is crap, my friend got number and he stopped paying because he did not want that number, he got another Vodafone number. Vodafone identified him with his aadhar card and stopped their service for other number too, thus forcing him to pay for the first one. Damn. Don't ever get a Vodafone service.

Can't there be a rule that if you stop paying for a month your number will be terminated, and that's it. Why its so easy to get a new connection and so difficult to terminate it? Have you ever thought of it? Because they want to loot you. Its as simple as that.

Do you really know its possible for people in cities to communicate without the need of mobile carriers, and it will be far far cheaper, and have you wondered why the government is not allowing that by law?

We are just a bunch of slaves, that's it, a bunch of slaves and fools that mobile companies and governments could loot.</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Another admission of defeat for Windows</title><link href="/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Another admission of defeat for Windows" /><published>2018-04-16T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows.html">![](https://cdn.wallpapersafari.com/38/59/PYHvQk.jpg)

Windows is slowly but surely giving way to GNU Linux. Linux's desktop share is just
above 2%, but on the Internet scale GNU Linux rules. All computers that power our
Internet are critical systems and they run Linux. Most mobile phones use Linux
as Android. Many people who use Amndroid never know they are Linux users and
they vocally oppose using Linux on their desktops!?

But Microsoft is not as foolish as the people who use its OS. Looks like many
engineers on the M$ know that defeat of Windows is imminent, and they are giving
their way slowly ao that it would not look like a humiliating defeat.

First is M$'s Azure. It offers Linux on its servers, and I bet there are more Azure 
instances that run Linux than Windows. Recently I had a problem with Windows.
In my office we use Python as we are a data science company, one of my coworker
had a problem in running a flask app. It worked perfectly on my system which was
and Ubuntu.

After a little bit investigation it was evident the way that the way Windows OS
functioned was a problem. I had an irrational resistance for installing GNU Linux on
her computer, but it was clear the resistance was irrational. There is a way to
combat irrationality, let the irrational people finish stuff. Work stopped and
fortunately for me, the person realized loss in productivity and it was the only
the way to go ahead, so I installed GNU Lubuntu.

I just wondered if Windows was such a crap system, why are developers using it?
Are CTO's around the world gone nuts? Haven't they seen such a problem? But then
to my amazement, I found that Windows 10 now allows Linux subsystem to be
installed in it! Its not as good as full GNU Linux at your disposal, but rather
than fighting the free software community, M$ has recognized Linux which once it
famously called as the toy OS.

Like a Spartan phalanx Linux is advancing, though M$ is doing all it can to stop
Linux, it seems not enough. As more and more developers pour in to develop Linux
during their free time, M$ simply does not have the budget to win such a war, and
they know it really well.

Many economic theorist will be confused to  know that a capitalistic organization
is bowing to a communal force thats not interested in making a buck. Well, we
don't know if the Universe is infinite, but we are sure that human stupidity is.

**Reference**

[Install the Windows Subsystem for Linux](https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/wsl/install-win10)</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>