<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-09-26T10:24:56+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Jim Mattis should not be allowed to fool India</title><link href="/2017/09/26/Jim-Mattis-should-not-be-allowed-to-fool-India.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jim Mattis should not be allowed to fool India" /><published>2017-09-26T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-26T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/26/Jim-Mattis-should-not%20be-allowed-to-fool-India</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/26/Jim-Mattis-should-not-be-allowed-to-fool-India.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.independent.co.ug/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/james-mattis.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing has happened because the Congress leadership is ultra stupid, we have
a government made up of stupids at he center (stupids have won over ultra
stupid ones). Since stupids have ruled us long, the USA is simply using us as
their Colony so that it citizens could be merry, just like the repeat 70 years
ago when the British exploited us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India should think about India and Indians. We must think about ways to make
ourselves better and place trust in Science, Technology, Philosophy, Reasoning
and Logic. No matter how hard that Jim Mattis (visiting US diplomat) pushes,
we must not intervene in Afganistan militarily. It would be destructive to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have already invested a lot in Afganistan and haven’t got anything in return
yet. Afganistan is failure of USA’s foreign policy. Any country that had
relation with United Kingdom and USA has some kind of problem, Afganistan is one
among them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Afgan’s or USA wishes to give us money in advance, what can India do is to
sell its weapons to the Afgan army, we can train their military as our military
is one of the best disciplined in the world. We can repair Afghan defense and
offense installations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not a great situation to see the Taliban occupying 47% of Afganistan, but
this is what you will get if you have religion preside over logic and
administration. Afgans will never realize it. They might fight hundreds of
battles to get foreigners out of their land, but they are too afraid to fight
a battle to keep religion out of state affairs. They are simply doomed if no
miracle happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our operations should be in Pakistan, we must weaken it by a million cuts.
India should not go behind the Pakistan’s military, ISIS and terrorists as they
are doing a good job of getting the county plunging into abyss, but India must
target liberation of Boluchistan. With war on western and Eastern front,
Pakistan will have difficult time to concentrate on pumping terrorist into
Kashmir.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All I am saying is this, its not the fate of Indian soldier to die on someone
else’s soil, lets use this situation to test our weapons, technology progress
and political theory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wonder how many Indian politicians are corrupt and will let USA treat us as
another colony? We must wait and see.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A murder of democracy in Tamilnadu</title><link href="/2017/09/24/a-muder-of-democracy-in-tamilnadu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A murder of democracy in Tamilnadu" /><published>2017-09-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/24/a-muder-of-democracy-in-tamilnadu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/24/a-muder-of-democracy-in-tamilnadu.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.nmtv.tv/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Vidyasagar-Rao.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its fascinating to see how much of our democratic process is undermined by our
state government and the BJP at the center. Clearly EPS government has lost
majority and it just maintains it on paper by dismissing MLA’s who would vote
against it. Every thing is watched by the governor who is just another jerk only
fit to wash the feet of BJP and RSS people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its fascinating to see how much the BJP and the RSS have moved away from the
great days of Atal Vajpyee who resigned from office of PM just because he was
short of one M.P vote. Now for the BJP its all about technically and staying in
power and showing a blind eye to moral responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP has become a force that would protect any one who falls to at feet. What
an shameful existence. We Tamilians are fools too. The youth who came out to the
streets to save our Jallikattu culture will not come out to restore democracy.
These very same youth will get money for their vote. Is there any proof they or
their family members are not morally inferior?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its a shameful time to live as Tamilian in India. Once again after the English
we are subjugated by the Hindi’s and none takes a note of it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unicultural society possible?</title><link href="/2017/09/23/unicultural-societypossible.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unicultural society possible?" /><published>2017-09-23T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/23/unicultural-societypossible</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/23/unicultural-societypossible.html"></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Indians should be ignorant</title><link href="/2017/09/14/indians-should-be-ignorant.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Indians should be ignorant" /><published>2017-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/14/indians-should-be-ignorant</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/14/indians-should-be-ignorant.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-QidAjbf28eo/USz7ifNi6AI/AAAAAAAAFG4/1VNv2BewvBQ/s1600/saraswati.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The government is afraid of people getting knowledge. Well thats what the signal
Indian government is sending out. Recently it had blocked &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/&quot;&gt;Archive org&lt;/a&gt;,
why? Well none knows why really why? But in India somehow government seems to get away violating
the constitution now and then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its strange that a country that calls itself a democracy is unwilling to let
its people experience the world via the internet 100%. India claims that its citizens
have the right to information and free speech, and right to have rights granted
by our constitution but its really good at hiding things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take for instance the article 49-O which we know now as NOTA or No To Anybody. This
means in each election apart from the list of candidates provided, the voters
should have a NOTA option. That is they should be able to tell that they like
to vote for none. For more than 60 years our politicians have stealthily kept
this right given to us by our constitution away from us. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why a ruler who really wants to respect constitution of India do such a thing?
The reason? Politicians if they can fool people at every opportunity thats
available to them, they will fool us for their gain. It doesn’t matter we are
ruled by Congress, BJP or some coalition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Panama papers have named lot of people who were indulged in looting their
nation and stashing money into Panama. Because of its leak the Pakistani
Priminister Nawaz Sharif had to step down, but why it hasn’t affected India?
Whole India gossips that a mere actress like Aishwariya Rai had evaded taxes and
stashed wealth in Panama, have you ever wondered why and how she is free? Infact
she is not even a drop in the vast ocean of India’s wealth thats looted and
stashed in other countries. Why are we more weaker in implementing justice than
Pakistan who we regard as barbaric tribesmen invading our land?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Internet helps people to distribute things like Panama papers, Wikileaks documents
and others in much easier fashion. These things can be easily hosted on &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/&quot;&gt;Archive org&lt;/a&gt;
or &lt;a href=&quot;https://thepiratebay.org/&quot;&gt;Pirate bay&lt;/a&gt; and so on for all Indians to see, and
it terrifies the Indian government, the oligarchy and the rich to know that people
have the way to know and find out about their corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact time and again Torrent sites gets banned in India all of a sudden and we
don’t know why. When an Islamic terrorist puts up a site say about how he plans
to destroy India, it will be banned here. We as citizens are not allowed to know
who threatens us, and most important we should never know why he is doing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is actively discouraging bitcoin too as it fears that people will find true
financial freedom and possibly big money banks won’t be able to fund political
parties. Having a good relationship between banks and politicians is important.
For example there is a guy called Vijay Mallaya who looted India of 9000 crores
and is happy in London. India is simply doing nothing because he might have nexus
with Subramaniya Swamy of the Ruling BJP. So since this guy has looted the bank
which is called SBI, to offset its loss it (SBI) starts to loot people. SBI says SMS
bank statement is charged, there is charge if you maintain a balance thats low, there is a charge
if you move money in and out of your account, there is charge if you breathe.
So it lost 9000 crores to a man connected with politicians and is now aiming to
loot Rs 900 from each of its 10 crore customers. With bitcoin that won’t be the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are an Indian, there is just one thing you must know. Your government says
you are a free citizen, and its say it is good . Then why the hell its blocking
us to use the internet in free way? Doesn’t things smell fishy here?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wy can’t students get away with one exam?</title><link href="/2017/09/12/why-cant-students-getaway-with-one-exam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wy can't students get away with one exam?" /><published>2017-09-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/12/why-cant-students-getaway-with-one-exam</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/12/why-cant-students-getaway-with-one-exam.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.youthvillage.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/Exams-Stress.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was finishing up 12th, but that was not just it. I took on computer science group,
I had the vision to become a electrical engineer. The funny thing is though I
studied hard for my 12th exam and got decent marks, it was not enough. I had
to take exams to get into Engineering course. I then wondered why can’t I take an exam
straight for engineering degree and avoid 12th or why can’t people be smart enough
do design exams in such a way that if you have passed 12th you are qualified to
get engineering?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If someone eyed for medicine or engineering, then they must take 3 exams. One for
12th, another for medicine entrance and other for engineering entrance. In this
modern world where people are getting stressed because so much is put on their
shoulders, I truly wonder why there must be so many exams?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel education system in India and possibly in most  of industrialized countries
are broken, and I feel the world looks qualified enough but is not educated enough
to realize that its mostly made up of stupid people and they are the ones who are
controlling us.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">More of a con guru than a Sadguru</title><link href="/2017/09/07/more-of-con-guru-than-satguru.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="More of a con guru than a Sadguru" /><published>2017-09-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/07/more-of-con-guru-than-satguru</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/07/more-of-con-guru-than-satguru.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxhst.co/avaxhome/9f/0e/003b0e9f.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadhguru Jaggi Vasudev either a fool or a con man. Recently he seemed to have launched a project to grow trees. Well isn’t that good? Ummmm, smells fishy as he is posing himself as some one who care about nature and environment. Why because of this…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Jaggi has a huge ashram in Coimbatore and it covers lot of hectares, but what land it was? It was a land that had lot of frees and was kinda forest people say. It was also a path which was used by elephants to cross.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well this is BJP rule, a blind Hindu government means its a good times for conman like Jaggi and he was able to acquire the land somehow and the environment ministry seems to have given a nod for his ashram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having bashed trees, and having disrupted the movements of elephants and as though he is super innocent now he is posing himself to launch a new project to plant trees. Wouldn’t it be better for him to close his ashram and let nature take over?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Map of mathematics</title><link href="/2017/08/29/map-of-mathematics.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Map of mathematics" /><published>2017-08-29T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/08/29/map-of-mathematics</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/08/29/map-of-mathematics.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OmJ-4B-mS-Y?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shaky BJP</title><link href="/india/politics/2017/08/28/shaky-bjp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shaky BJP" /><published>2017-08-28T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/politics/2017/08/28/shaky-bjp</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/politics/2017/08/28/shaky-bjp.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://d.ibtimes.co.uk/en/full/1500377/narendra-modi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the Modi wave that has put BJP in power. When things are right we can see face of Modi everywhere, but now Modi seems to hide away from news. Yes BJP is getting shaky and its inefficiencies are starting to show off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP seems to be a showoff government. It just wants to do many things for a show and propaganda without thinking weather it will really benefit people. They claim that the state has caught lot of money in demonetization and by implementing GST. In fact now fearing government whiplash, many businesses have started to maintain account books, tax revenue to the nation has increased. But where does the money go?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;price-of-petrol&quot;&gt;Price of petrol&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Petrol now costs Rs 72/-,  a month ago it just costs Rs 65/-. If state is getting money,then why not ease petrol prices? Infact in that Rs 72/- about Rs 50/- is nothing but taxes to the government. Even if it can lower the taxes to Rs 25/- we can get petrol for Rs 49/-. That would be great boost for the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lack-of-railway-safety&quot;&gt;Lack of Railway safety&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have been two Train derailments in U.P alone. This after BJP government has raised the ticket price and has put additional cess tax on passenger safety. Where that all those safety tax money go? If it was put to improve Railway safety why we have derailments and deaths?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;privacy-concerns&quot;&gt;Privacy Concerns&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is this stupid thing called Aadhar that BJP pushed so that every one will have unique identification. For that Aadhar private info like name, age, address, phone number, iris and fingerprint scans were obtained. Now in a recent Supreme court judgment by a bench of 9 judges has said that one has the right to privacy. Now shouldn’t the government run a campaign and let people delete their personal information if they wish so? Why isn’t such campaign being held?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus the Aadhar software is not a Free and Opensource Software. We do not know whats happening in it? What bugs are present in it? How our information is accessed and manipulated? The government claims its safe, that’s it. Nothing more is said about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;law-and-order-fails&quot;&gt;Law and order fails&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ramrahim is a swamiji in India who is accused of sexual assault on woman and was found guilty. He supports the BJP. When news of his guilt reached out, his supporters created a huge carnage in Harayana, Punjab, Delhi and other places. There is a wide gossip that it was allowed to happen because of his BJP support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it was known that his disciples are kind of paranoid, why was the security not beefed up. More than 30 people lost their life in these violence’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;still-no-money-recovery&quot;&gt;Still no money recovery&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vijay Mallaya is a happy man in London. He owes Indian banks Rs 9000 crore. Thanks to his friendship with Subramaniya Swami of BJP, he is still free. SBI bank that lend him money is now taxing middle class clients to stay profitable, now it has become one of the most hated banks in India. Its gossiped that people are moving out of it in droves. The government seems not to take much note of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi famously said he will recover black money from Swiss banks and put a sum of 15 lakhs in every Indians account, because so much black money is out there that’s looted from India. But more than 3 years of rule, not even single paise has been put into the account. Wonder whats going on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ban-on-beef&quot;&gt;Ban on beef&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BJP has indirectly banned beef in the country. It has made selling cattle really hard and hence very difficult it is now to procure and slaughter. Plus unofficial Hindu terror groups are raiding Muslim and Dalit homes, searching their bags for meat and if they think its that of a cow, they beat them up and the law just watches because BJP rules with a Hindu ideology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP has gone very low. Rather than putting laws for the good of society, its putting laws to modify peoples behavior. Its intervening in silly things like what people should eat. I can’t even believe a group of people with such a childish attitude can form a government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bullying-state-governments&quot;&gt;Bullying state governments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the congress BJP is bullying state governments. We can see how (governor) Kiranbedi bullies (chief minister) Rangasamy in Pudhucherry. Okay the BJP is trying to catch the flaws of Rangasamy, but then how come Adhityanath the chief minister of Uttar Pradesh able to get away with child deaths in hospital which were caused by lack of negligence? Nothing is said about him just because he is one among BJP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;black-money&quot;&gt;Black money&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi famously said that if he came to power he would recover black money from swiss banks. So much will be recovered he claimed that Rs 15 Lakhs will be put into every Indians account. Till now not a single paise has been deposited into any Indians account by recovering money from Swiss banks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are huge business Tycoons like Vijay Mallaya who has cheated banks upto Rs 9000 crore and are living happily in Londoan. India under Modi seems not to have a heart to convict him and recover money. The banks who lend him Tax the middle class saving accounts to lower their losses. The government is keen on getting taxes but not keen on refining banks and make them more friendly to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-word&quot;&gt;Final word&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP is shaky, not really good as I expected it to be. But still apart from Vijay Mallaya there seem to be no bigger corruption issues like the congress government, but who knows, there could be lot of corruption and we are unaware of it. There is still lot for the BJP to improve, it has to shake off RSS and outdated Hinduism to become a better party.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Intolerant Christians</title><link href="/religion/christianity/2017/08/21/intolerant-christians.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Intolerant Christians" /><published>2017-08-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/religion/christianity/2017/08/21/intolerant-christians</id><content type="html" xml:base="/religion/christianity/2017/08/21/intolerant-christians.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.mygodpictures.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/Face-Portrait-Of-Lored-Jesus-Christ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was in car with an owner of a Travels company, he said about a personal incident. In his private car was a Hindu driver, he (the driver) one day saw a sticker of Shiva which looked great, he bought it and stuck it in the car so that he can worship it. After a while a day when he was on a holiday, another Christian driver took charge of the car. It was just a one day job for him. When he saw the Shivas image he started to shiver, he said that these images should not be in  the car and removed it off. The travels owner being a Hindu himself, but recognizing the driver is kind of a psycho let the Christian proceed his way so that at least his job won’t be blocked on that day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have heard of government teacher say something similar. A poojai was done in his house, he took laddus as prasadam to his school. He gave laddu to fellow teachers, when he said that laddu was a prasadam, one of the teaches spit it out. She said she is not supposed to eat “Hindu food”. Then why she is eating food grown in India? All farmers offer their produce to Hindu Gods and only then sell them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I myself have witnessed an incident. I asked for change from my friend who was a christian, he gave me two five rupee coins, I returned one of them saying that I need only 5 rupees, the coin was nice brass golden color, on its heads was beautiful image of Durga devi, I showed it to him and said that its rare to find coins like these. He flipped the one he had and after seeing Durga, I don’t know what happened to him, he placed the coin on table and left it off. It looked as though he was really afraid.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Looking for sponsors for my Ruby Book</title><link href="/2017/08/16/looking-for-sponsors-for-my-ruby-book.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Looking for sponsors for my Ruby Book" /><published>2017-08-16T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-16T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/08/16/looking-for-sponsors-for-my-ruby-book</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/08/16/looking-for-sponsors-for-my-ruby-book.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://b2aeaa58a57a200320db-8b65b95250e902c437b256b5abf3eac7.ssl.cf5.rackcdn.com/media_entries/4819/front_cover.medium.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just told on the Internet that my ruby book has a permanent webpage here &lt;a href=&quot;https://mindaslab.github.io/I-Love-Ruby/&quot;&gt;https://mindaslab.github.io/I-Love-Ruby/&lt;/a&gt; and to my suprise I had more than 550 visitors less than 2 days. Thats a lot for programming book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/600_views.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes the book is a good one, you will know when you visit “What people say” section. Many people have given good reviews about it. I did have bad reviews from people, but soon found out they were bogus except for one or two who pointed out some grammatical mistakes. I was affected by lot of prejudice too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I am happy, a language thats made me food, given me shelter and clothing for some time is made easy to understand by me. I wanted to say how my book smashed things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Its free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My book is free 100%. Free in material, as you can download it free from Github.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its also free by soul. Its been copyrighted under GNU free documentation license (GFDL) so that all humanity can use it without restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not restricted by publisher&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I went to a publisher, I would have had lot of restrictions. People would have told this and that and I would have given up. Without publisher, I had no deadline. The first books of I Love Ruby had very less content, but then editions started to appear, sometimes even more than one edition per day. Today this has got a term now, they call rolling release. This lack of management and the ability to write when I want to write may have brought out the best in me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;looking-for-sponsors&quot;&gt;Looking for sponsors&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am looking for Ruby related companies to sponsor my work. If you like to please contact me. I am wishing to spend my time writing books so that people can understand technology better, become a better technician and earn with a smile. Sponsoring won’t be easy as I am not willing to give up my sovereignty for money. But if you think Ruby has made your life better for you and your office you might consider to sponsor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>