<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-07-23T22:35:14+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Ponniyin Selvan may not be historically accurate</title><link href="/2022/07/23/ponniyin-selvan-may-not-be-historically-accurate.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ponniyin Selvan may not be historically accurate" /><published>2022-07-23T22:35:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-07-23T22:35:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/07/23/ponniyin-selvan-may-not-be-historically-accurate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/07/23/ponniyin-selvan-may-not-be-historically-accurate.html">&lt;p&gt;I was watching this Ponniyin Selvan trailer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/KsH2LA8pCjo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I couldn’t help noticing is the number of white skinned people appearing in the movie. I think this story is set to take place kind of at least 1500 years ago, before India was discovered by Vascodagama, I wonder how there are so many white people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At that time we did have healthy trade with Europe, and mostly white skinned women were especially European entertainers and prostitutes. Except for Parthiban and others, most seems to have Aryan tone and goes as white as European ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be this film is not a historically accurate one. May be Ponniyin Selvan novel itself wasn’t thought out well. Or may be in ancient Chola courts they looked at skin color and banished dark toned Tamil people (especially women) and wanted to have only light toned entertainers from Europe and Aryans. Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was watching this Ponniyin Selvan trailer:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Madras Bhai Biriyani not so good</title><link href="/2022/07/19/madras-bhai-biriyani-not-so-good.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Madras Bhai Biriyani not so good" /><published>2022-07-19T00:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-07-19T00:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/07/19/madras-bhai-biriyani-not-so-good</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/07/19/madras-bhai-biriyani-not-so-good.html">&lt;p&gt;I had to meet a friend in Velacherry, I went there it was on a Saturday. For me food is everything, so we need to have biriyani. We ventured into a place called Madras Bhai Biriyani. When we enetered the smell was good, and there was a muslim serving biriyani. When queried he said there was hydrabadi biriyani and vaniyambadi biriyani. I went for hydrabadi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully this hydrabai was not like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/7Y80xABY9A0?clip=Ugkx3G-vKny6xFSxHEyK2n20U-6z9sx4Ut4l&amp;amp;clipt=EJVZGPbsAQ&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like hydrabadi’s like to get the feel of 5-star hotels while eating biriyani. In 5-star hotel if you order coffee, you get milk, decoction, sugar, and you must mix them and make your own coffee. Similarly when you order hydrabadi biriyani, you will get rice, masala and meat pieces which you must mix. It’s a kind of way we Tamils hate. I was expecting biiyani to be like that, but it was given to me well mixed in Tamil way. I was thankful for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The taste was okay, the brinjal gravy was excellent, actually without the gravy of brinjal the biriyani was not so good. One thing that irked me was, when you pressed the chicken piece, something watery came out. I am not here to make judgement or demonize that place, but there was a heavy feeling after eating the biriyani, apart from that I did not face any health condition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my verdict on Madras Bhai Biriyani is: not so good. If you are using old Chicken, please don’t do stuff like that. It’s bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;they-might-cheat&quot;&gt;They might cheat&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend and his wife are vegetarians. This Madras Bhai Biriyani and other shops share the eating spot, so they ordered vegetable fried rice, the server brought them egg fried rice, when they spotted the egg which was obvious and all over the rice, that guy said it was paneer. What? That’s a lie, lie lie liar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So biriyani is not so good, neighboring shop cheats. Not a good place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;butterscotch&quot;&gt;Butterscotch?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that same place there was an ice cream shop, I ordered butterscotch, what I got was something like vanilla mixed with some stuff, and it was given in a waffle whose dimension was like a small tea cup, and for that they charged Rs 100/- . i couldn’t believe it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-word&quot;&gt;Final word&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They might be using old products&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They are not accurate, do wrong things and tell lies so that it will be covered&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Their rates are high&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should you go there?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I had to meet a friend in Velacherry, I went there it was on a Saturday. For me food is everything, so we need to have biriyani. We ventured into a place called Madras Bhai Biriyani. When we enetered the smell was good, and there was a muslim serving biriyani. When queried he said there was hydrabadi biriyani and vaniyambadi biriyani. I went for hydrabadi.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Thoughts about Goddess Kaali should be tolerated in a democracy</title><link href="/2022/07/09/thoughts-about-goddess-kaali-should-be-tolerated-in-a-democracy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Thoughts about Goddess Kaali should be tolerated in a democracy" /><published>2022-07-09T17:31:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-07-09T17:31:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/07/09/thoughts-about-goddess-kaali-should-be-tolerated-in-a-democracy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/07/09/thoughts-about-goddess-kaali-should-be-tolerated-in-a-democracy.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeihljqzimgzugj5z7q3rh6qa55p2m2ajuew44px44yhg27tumgpxee.ipfs.dweb.link/kaali-poster.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An Indian girl seems to have done a movie, and for the poster she has put an image in which goddess Kaali smokes. It would be shocking for any Hindu, as I was a Hindu too and am still a Hindu in my birth certificate, but I feel strongly that as a people of democracy we must tolerate any thought about our Gods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Hinduism, we don’t depict God’s as good beings, take for example Indiran, the way Pillar got his mango, lord Raman killing Vaali, those were not good acts. Neither Hinduism claims Asuras are bad. Keralite worship Mahabali who is a good Asuran, there is reason why they say Raavanan is head of 10 good deeds and none can match him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet this same Gods who have done good and evil are worshiped. One may say Kaali smoking is bad, okay then can someone ask why? We here in south worship Karuppan and Muneeswaran, Gods that smoke and drink. just because they are male Gods smoking still makes them good power, but just being a woman a smoking Kaali becomes a bad thing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel very sorry for Indians, rather than giving a good rule for the people where people can afford fuel, cooking gas, vegetables, meat and real estate, Indian government people as though they have met goddess Kaali, and as though having got instructions from her to take down this poster, they have protested against Canada to ban this film or something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Common we are not stupid Arabs to take a myth serious enough to waste our diplomat’s time like this. India was a mature democracy, now all it can do is to boast ho great it is, say to the world it’s the protector of Hinduism, while the living standards of Indians goes down unnoticed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The problem of being a good Ruby on Rails developer</title><link href="/2022/07/06/the-problem-of-being-a-good-ruby-on-rails-developer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The problem of being a good Ruby on Rails developer" /><published>2022-07-06T00:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-07-06T00:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/07/06/the-problem-of-being-a-good-ruby-on-rails-developer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/07/06/the-problem-of-being-a-good-ruby-on-rails-developer.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/62/Ruby_On_Rails_Logo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason I listen to keynote speech of Matz, DHH, and Aaron Patterson. I feel what they talk makes sense to me, that too Matz future ideas about programming, and how computers should serve humans and not the other way around, DHH’s idea of making Ruby on Rails so powerful that individual persons can challenge a big corporate employing tens of people coding a web app. these are powerful ideas. Aaron Patterson’s work of making Ruby as well as Rails faster and better. These all makes sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also felt what decisions what were made to Rails were very sensible except these two:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Getting rid of Coffeescript.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Using Webpacker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still don’t get what webpacker is. Thanks to Rails 7 we have got rid of it. I am coding in Rails since it was 2.x and it has given me a excellent experience. Even today if I touch legacy code of my former teams, I can understand the code and make changes in an easy way. As far as I know, none who has inherited code from me has reported a problem to me. The reason for that is very simple, Rails follows a convention, and I follow it religiously. Rails is a philosophy which has many best practices, and I stick to it. This however does not mean that changing double quotes to single quotes because shitty Rubocop yells at you. Doing such things is stupid. But I have to admit in project dominated by fools, I did follow Rubocop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then what happens when you are a good, stick to the principle Ruby on Rails developer. For example what will happen if you are a honest India government servant? You won’t take bribes, and you will find t too difficult to fit in India. So what will happen to a Ruby on Rails developer when he is in a project that violates lot of rules laid by Ruby on Rails. It becomes difficult for you, making modifications to it becomes a pain. You start to wonder why people picked up Ruby on Rails if they don’t want to follow it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you get experienced, when you become Architect of tech, Principal Engineer just by your age (I have seen no intelligence increase in a architect compared to novice), people hire you not because they want you to maintain a good project or want to start a green field project, they hire you because they really screwed up with Rails and want some one with age and experience to solve it. It’s like telling a bank manager to work with thieves. Thieves knows crappy way of doing things, the bank manager however sees perfection in system, understands economics and don’t want to loot because he understands economics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; When I say bank, I don’t means real banks of today which loot us, I mean a ideal bank and ideal bank manager in a dream world. Today a thief admits he loots us, a bank does not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So being a person who does not mess up Rails framework because you are sane, you need to work with insane people who have truly messed it up. That’s a great problem for a Ruby on Rails purist.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Task which will fail 99.99% of Tamilnadu’s Electronic Engineers</title><link href="/2022/07/02/task-which-will-fail-99-percent-of-tamilnadus-electronic-engineers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Task which will fail 99.99% of Tamilnadu&apos;s Electronic Engineers" /><published>2022-07-02T09:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-07-02T09:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/07/02/task-which-will-fail-99-percent-of-tamilnadus-electronic-engineers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/07/02/task-which-will-fail-99-percent-of-tamilnadus-electronic-engineers.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task:&lt;/strong&gt; Implement RTL NAND on PCB that operates on 5V power supply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure the above task will fail 99.99% of Tamilnadu’s electronic engineers and at about 80% of India’s electronic engineers. It could be possible that 50% of all HOD’s in electronics department in Tamilnadu will fail in this task too, those who succeed would have accomplished with tremendous difficulty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, if you ask an electronics engineer to do this task as an interview exercise, the person will look at you like you are insane and mad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I say college education is sham, and it loots middle class parents because they are ignorant, I mean it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Task: Implement RTL NAND on PCB that operates on 5V power supply.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fundamentals of a Business</title><link href="/2022/06/18/fundamentals-of-a-business.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fundamentals of a Business" /><published>2022-06-18T15:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-06-18T15:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/06/18/fundamentals-of-a-business</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/06/18/fundamentals-of-a-business.html">&lt;p&gt;I was talking with my friend who wanted to have his own business. I soon found out that he wanted to have a business to get rich, to leave something for his kids, which means his business has failed even before it materialized. He never talked about the three main things which I think is essential for a business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog I want to write what qualities I think are fundamental for a business, what qualities I think that will make it successful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;value&quot;&gt;Value&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first fundamental thing is value. Some one wants to buy your product or service only if they think it’s valuable, or else they have to be a fool to invest money. No matter how ever less value it is, your business must add value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example I was consulting for a company called DataMaking, our team size grew a lot, we had to do something to keep meeting times low, so we developed a tool &lt;a href=&quot;https://doneit.in&quot;&gt;doneit&lt;/a&gt;. It reduced our meeting times. After it worked for us, we told our friends to try, gave them free trials and some of them became paid subscribers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was some value for a tool creation, we could identify it and so we created it. It later became a business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;honesty&quot;&gt;Honesty&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honesty is necessary for business. Say you have a bank backing you, they want to know how your business will go so that they can predict the future and make sure there is enough funds available to the creditors. If you are dishonest, they will not be able to help you in the long run and will loose trust in you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are not honest about the product or service you are selling to someone, people will loose trust in it. For example almost no startups use Oracle, no programmer uses Windows. People have lost trust in them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;equality&quot;&gt;Equality&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today SpaceX is doing real magic in space industry, but I don’t think it will be successful in the long run. Elon Musk treats people like shit, does not value dissent. Business is for people and by people. If one does not recognize the equality of people, a business is doomed to fail in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once a business crosses 3 workers, the owner of the business has no real control of it, he has to consult people to take next decision, it becomes more of a democratic process. If a worker in a business doesn’t like it, crack will appear, will widen, and the business will fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the responsibility of people who say that they can run a business to make sure all have equal stake in the business.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was talking with my friend who wanted to have his own business. I soon found out that he wanted to have a business to get rich, to leave something for his kids, which means his business has failed even before it materialized. He never talked about the three main things which I think is essential for a business.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Defeat the Islamic Empire</title><link href="/2022/06/08/how-to-defeat-the-islamic-empire.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Defeat the Islamic Empire" /><published>2022-06-08T21:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-06-08T21:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/06/08/how-to-defeat-the-islamic-empire</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/06/08/how-to-defeat-the-islamic-empire.html">&lt;p&gt;Religion is poison said Chairman Mao. It’s very true. A girl called Nupur Sharma from my country India told something wrong about the Prophet Muhammed, and immediately her party the BJP which is known for killing Muslims suspended her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeicvkmcuikgsg4ksrwgsnpfqwq663koxkydz75jqb5jtrepsyuhoty.ipfs.dweb.link/nupur-sharma.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Nupur Sharma&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am dead against BJP, their philosophy of intolerance. they must tolerate other religions than hinduism I feel, and they being the ruling party should defend the right of Indian to speak anything he wants rather than bowing to vote bank pressure and throwing out Nupur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This girl having said something about Muhammad now is facing death threats from hardline Islamists. The funny thing is none really knows if prophet Muhammad existed. We today know God is not there and it’s impossible for him to have spoken to Muhammad or Munnusamy. May be if Muhammad existed it would have been an illusion, just like the ones Nithyanadha get’s these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RqDY8Kbx3dE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These people may not even know they are fools, they think what they envision is true, and their belief makes us believe what they say. Unless scientific thinking pervades over all humanity, religion and people who are been cheated by it will exist. It’s very energy efficient for our brains to take in as truth what most say, rather than compute from basic facts and arrive to a conclusion whats is the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically humans have scientific and logic thought. Though many believe God is there, and he is answering us and is almighty, none, not even the true believer says “God I want a samosa to appear before me”, instead they goto a shop and buy it which is scientifically proven to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;india-is-not-arabia&quot;&gt;India is Not Arabia&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know why the Arabs don’t want to question Islam and reform in big way. I am also very sure almost no Arab is a true Muslim and has reformed in some way. They must know India is not Arabia. Here we question Gods, comment about it, scold God in prayer, rate it, fall in love with it, marry it, give it name, give it form, make it multiply, transform and make it compete against itself. It’s my God here, not a God defined by some one in some book. The theological philosophy and thinking in India goes far beyond, may be to the days when Arabia was evergreen forrest. It’s far mature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here talking about God even in negative terms is not bad, though hardline Hindus are trying to turn India into an Arab like state where their notion of religion is right and others is wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiacokmzjjaalccwpmu57hdbhixuksmnhnxaqtc4uvomfww4qompji.ipfs.dweb.link/story_647_091715100533.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;M.F.Hussein&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example hardline Hindus have forced M.F.Husein out of this nation just because he drew Goddess Saraswati naked. It’s his version of her and he is entitled to have it. Once again none knows if a girl called Saraswati existed and she played veena, and did so much good to society that she was worshiped as God. She could just be an imagination form a persons brain who was smoking a pot at that time! Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arabs should know that this is India where opinions are tolerated and not banished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example Arabs could not tolerate some one drawing prophet Muhammad, I don’t know why. When ever I imagine Muhmmad I see a man towing a camel with a beard, in white Arabic robe, I don’t see something like a light bulb or blof of light moving like an UFO around and saying Allah said this and that. That would scare people off. Even Europeans imagine Muhammad as a person and draw him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeielvruqa2yjk23jdfa2ullm72aoflvodkp3dmmhdr7yxk5fxmioxu.ipfs.dweb.link/muhmah1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Cartoon of Prophet Muhammad by Europeans&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They even have a day called Draw Muhammd day just to tell the Arabs that in Europe one has the right to imagine and visualize, and it’s not bad. For some reason which I cannot understand, Arabs do not like a visual representation of their own prophet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly Arabs must realize that India is much of a free nation than Arabia where people control what other should even think, eat, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;quran-spells-trouble-to-india&quot;&gt;Quran spells trouble to India&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though we don’t know if Muhammad exist or not, in Quran it’s said that Rome and India will be converted to Islam, and hard line Muslims still hold it true. They do all crazy things like sending terrorist from Pakistan, trying to take off Kashmir and Punjab away from India and all those nonsense. People never seem to realize that laws of Physics work, but human belief sometimes work and sometimes doesn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;defeating-the-islamic-empire&quot;&gt;Defeating the Islamic Empire&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently Saudi Arabia earns $1 billion a day, and part of it definitely used to create people to kill us. Like Gandhis Salt and Kadhi protest, if we change our consumer behavior we can mitigate some attacks on us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;electric-vehicles&quot;&gt;Electric Vehicles&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The money we spend for petroleum goes to Arabs, if you can switch your car or bike to electric, you are saving money in the long run, and coal power plants get coal mostly from Australia which won’t get mad if we talk something about Pope or Jesus or something, and Aussies won’t sponsor killing of Indians. That will put a dent in Arab revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;solar-cell-roof-tops&quot;&gt;Solar cell roof tops&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get solar cell roof tops, it will charge your electric vehicle and make your commute cost almost to zero. If we can generate electricity from Kashmir to Kaniyakumari and share it on grid, we can even eliminate diesel and crude oil power plants that take our money to Arabia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;solar-water-heaters--cooking&quot;&gt;Solar water heaters / cooking&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can’t afford costly solar cell roof tops, try to go with solar water heater, try using solar cooker. If you can save LPG by cooking with preheated water, or if you can cook with solar power, we are denying that revenue to Arabia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dont-travel-in-qatar-airlines&quot;&gt;Don’t travel in Qatar Airlines&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qatar Airways though awesome feeds money to Arabia. Try not to travel in it. If you have planned tours in Islamic countries cancel it. This will put a dent in their revenue from us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stop-working-for-arab-nations&quot;&gt;Stop working for Arab nations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are planning for job in Arab nation, reconsider. Consider Europe, Australia, Canada or even USA. Personally I don’t like USA as all it’s been able to do is genocide, but at least in theory they support free speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/c/c4/RUEDA_DE_PRENSA_CONJUNTA_ENTRE_CANCILLER_RICARDO_PATI%C3%91O_Y_JULIAN_ASSANGE_%28cropped%29.jpg/810px-RUEDA_DE_PRENSA_CONJUNTA_ENTRE_CANCILLER_RICARDO_PATI%C3%91O_Y_JULIAN_ASSANGE_%28cropped%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;USA? Free Speech?&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are working in Arab nations, try switching job to some other nation. I am sure Arabs see us as slaves than workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;educate-people-about-religion&quot;&gt;Educate people about religion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiciilsauxaxtcotxz3bzd76wlgnikdhvfjeaqkfwkwyr2d7kwjqna.ipfs.dweb.link/periyar.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Periyaar&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the most important thing. We in Tamilnadu had Periyaar to educate us about truth. Europeans had James Randi, they have Richard Dawkins etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a0/Richard_Dawkins_Cooper_Union_Shankbone.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Richard Dawkins&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But for the Islamic world? Are voices been suppressed believing a baseless millennium old book? When will Muslims improve? Know the truth? Shed their religion and embrace rational thought?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will the descendants of Muslims 100 years from now be a modern human, or some one who upholds cock and bull stories? We the rationalists must reach out. May be economically draining out Arabia is a temporary solution, but in long run we must empower them to embrace science and have a rational thought.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Religion is poison said Chairman Mao. It’s very true. A girl called Nupur Sharma from my country India told something wrong about the Prophet Muhammed, and immediately her party the BJP which is known for killing Muslims suspended her.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shameless DMK</title><link href="/2022/05/27/shameless-dmk.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shameless DMK" /><published>2022-05-27T12:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-27T12:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/05/27/shameless-dmk</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/05/27/shameless-dmk.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/f/fd/Hon_CM_Photo.jpg/864px-Hon_CM_Photo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;M.K.Stalin, leader of DMK&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is nothing new in this blog. DMK is known for it huge nation wide corruption, rowdy and murderous cadres, nepotism. One thing they stood by till the time Vajpyee became priminister was that they were bit anti religious, but were they?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK claims to be a non religious party and its UPA is non religious, but all these days they are in alliance with some muslim parties which even muslims don’t think it’s worth to exist. Many muslims either vote for DMK or ADMK, but DMK claims that they have non religious alliance having alliance with Islamic parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Tamil they will say that &lt;em&gt;to hide a full pumpkin in a plate of rice&lt;/em&gt;, by having alliance with religious party then telling they are non religious, is it believable? Any way as Tamils we all know DMK will do any thing to earn money and be in power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP is a shame to this nation. When Babri Masjid was demolished, Vajpyee said that a symbol of shame had been destroyed. Well, let’s say that ancient Islamic kings did demolish Tamples and built Mosques there, should we be intolerant to Muslims because of few scoundrels like them? May be they (kings of that time) did not have enough data, they were exposed only to Islam and might have been brought up been told that non Muslims are fit for nothing. Today we have science, we understand all humans are equal, and religion and ones spiritual belief is immaterial. In this age Vajpyee (who we considered an intellectual) saying such a thing is a shocker. I strongly feel existence of RSS and BJP is not needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi conducted Gujrath genocide killing lot of Muslims. He is a un-educated idiot filled with narcism, nothing can be done about it, we can hope that some miracle would happen and he would die, but he does keep his health top notch any way. Modi thinking wrong about minorities in India is one thing, but Vajpyee not forgiving mistakes done by the muslim invaders is worry-some. DMK having an alliance then with Vajpyee BJP was immoral and shame to Dravidian society as a whole. DMK is not a dravidian party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vajpyee led well, he did not pursue Hindutava because of aligning with DMK, but I felt a Dravidian party has fell down the ladder of morality by having alliance with a religious parties. Ideally DMK should not have alliance with any religious party if they utter the word of Periyaar and rationalism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An ideal DMK member should educate people that God does not exists, and what exists is real. A DMK guy should make one think, ask questions like how likely that a party is worth existing if Grandpa, Dad, and Son are the leaders without much contest. They must think, question, be brave and rational.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Edapaadi’s rule when Modi visited Chennai, DMK was loved by Tamils as it took to the slogan &lt;em&gt;Go Back Modi&lt;/em&gt;. But now? Just for it’s survival, for power, for Udhayanidhi to be next CM, and for the center to turn blind eye to corruption in Tamilnadu, Modi is welcomed here. This is a blow to DMK’s moral stand, and I don’t think a party and / or a leader who would switch morals to stay in power is worthy of existence.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">M.K.Stalin, leader of DMK</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Amit Shah started language war and Modi wants to end it?</title><link href="/2022/05/20/why-amit-shah-started-language-war-and-modi-wants-to-end-it.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Amit Shah started language war and Modi wants to end it?" /><published>2022-05-20T20:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-20T20:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/05/20/why-amit-shah-started-language-war-and-modi-wants-to-end-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/05/20/why-amit-shah-started-language-war-and-modi-wants-to-end-it.html">&lt;p&gt;Everything was not okay in India. Fuel prices have crossed Rs 100, gas cylinder prices crossed Rs 1000 which is higher than some family’s monthly earnings, inflation is touching double digit and Modi was claiming &lt;em&gt;ache din&lt;/em&gt; which means people are having a good day under his rule. There is an economic collapse in Srilanka, and people have woken up, in India people are still sleeping. This would give chill to any ruler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you take Romans, their problems were caused by the uncivilized barbarians raiding their territory. If you take Hitler’s Germany, it’s the Jews who caused problems. If you take USA, their problems were caused by the Red Indians, then Blacks, The Soviets, now Mexicans and Chinese. If you take Srilanks, their problems are caused by Tamils. If you take India, they say our problems are caused by Muslim and Christians, and now all of a sudden by Tamils says Modi without mentioning us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout History a pattern emerges, if the people place a ruler who cannot rule, definitely the nation would sink, for the incapable ruler to be in power he would like to have a scape goat to blame, the usual template is for the incapable ruler to associate himself with the majority and blame the minority or an enemy state. If the populace is kept uneducated they will fall to such propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the eyes of the Indian commoner life is becoming insanely tough, we have a clown ruling our nation who has no idea about economics and possibly won’t even listed to good economic advisors. So naturally the clown tells Amit Shah to say that Hindi should replace English in India as a ruling language, this they know would cause stir and would aid people forget the economic crisis. But for how long? In the long run it seems not to work, and never the center is able to answer the questions asked by people who are proud of their language and would resist Hindi imposition. So this could back fire. Some how the BJP has forgotten that Hindi imposition taken up by congress failed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amit Shan might have thought his words might fuel wide scale protest and some language speaking people could be announced as problem makers and Modi’s India could have blame them and turn the majority against them thus proving BJP as the guardian of the majority. It seems not to work. We are too diplomatic in dealing with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for some reason they want to end it and Modi is claiming that some one is starting language wars, I think Modi is now thinking that people have forgotten that Amit Shah has started it recently. Well may be BJP supporters will forget, but what about people who have brains and think? Will they fall into this trap?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Everything was not okay in India. Fuel prices have crossed Rs 100, gas cylinder prices crossed Rs 1000 which is higher than some family’s monthly earnings, inflation is touching double digit and Modi was claiming ache din which means people are having a good day under his rule. There is an economic collapse in Srilanka, and people have woken up, in India people are still sleeping. This would give chill to any ruler.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Strange Hinduism</title><link href="/2022/05/17/strange-hinduism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Strange Hinduism" /><published>2022-05-17T19:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-17T19:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/05/17/strange-hinduism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/05/17/strange-hinduism.html">&lt;p&gt;He fantasized such kind of stupids could exist:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DJjvxLiE_BA?clip=UgkxaiVgDbWovYTLhbknt6sJePGkRhJxJrFG&amp;amp;clipt=EM6GJRiu2yg&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now watch this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeihvkwfhb6gx5c3b43z6w6wysim6r7hu5uqdhax3is2gjdwrsw6nlm.ipfs.dweb.link/redditsave.com_i_dont_know_what_is_wrong_with_these_people-gvicl66vo0091.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder if Vivek watched this news clip and made his joke. ROFL.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">He fantasized such kind of stupids could exist:</summary></entry></feed>