<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-01-13T20:12:41+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why I think India is a super poor nation?</title><link href="/2024/01/13/why-i-think-india-is-a-super-poor-nation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I think India is a super poor nation?" /><published>2024-01-13T20:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-01-13T20:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/01/13/why-i-think-india-is-a-super-poor-nation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/01/13/why-i-think-india-is-a-super-poor-nation.html">&lt;p&gt;I take classes for Web development with Ruby on Rails, Data Science with Python, I have also started teaching Clojure. These are 1 to 1 classes via Jitsi. The courses are 3 - 4 months long and cost ₹1,50,000/-. If people ask for a discount, I tell them to pay after the course. Some people are okay to pay after the course. Then my only requirement is for them to have a good computing machine. One with a decent processor and Ubuntu so that things flow smoothly. Here comes the catch, most people I meet who want to gain this knowledge do not have computer. Somehow they have finished engineering without a machine, and they seem to have no idea to buy it. When I pressed many and asked how can they learn without a computer? The answer I got was they couldn’t afford it. It shocked me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there are lot a of EMI plans on Amazon and other platforms, but people are unable to afford that too. They are so poor, with a degree, they kind of know what to learn to get a job, but they can’t afford. India I find is a super poor nation contrary to what many people think. I completely understand why Jio is introducing a very basic phone in India targeting the super poor, because they simply can’t afford, and Ambani has the stats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why India is called a rich nation? I think it goes like this, say there is a nation X with just one person (just for easy math sake), and the one earns $50 per day there, now in India population 1000X as that of a rich nation and every one earns $1 a day. So India still on total earns $1000 because of its huge population and Indian leaders get to boast that India is richer than X as X just earns $50 as a nation whereas India earns $1000. This is not a lie our politician says, India as a whole is richer, but Indians are poor, super, super poor. Our politicians want us to think we are rich though we are super poor. It’s a deception with math they want to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To even things out in India, I think we need a very good economic expert as our leader. One who does serve people and not the oligarchs and corrupt. The leader should be capable enough to kill corruption (almost an impossibility in India), and should be able to spread money to all its people, than just few who fund the electoral victors. The leader should b brave enough to speak truth, and really brave should (s)he be as I assume truthful ones will be assassinated or brought down quickly from power. That person should not be mute, and be a slave to a foreigner (say an Italian). That person must connect with the people of India, and not live in ivory tower and just make policies listening to the intellect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short India will be a super poor for a long time, may be forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/85/PM_Modi_addressing_the_Matua_Dharma_Maha_Mela_2022%2C_at_Shreedham_Thakurnagar%2C_Thakurbari%2C_West_Bengal.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;A stupid who understands nothing about economics and human equality is a disaster&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/Mallikarjun_Kharge.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;A person who is slave of a foreigner should not be a leader&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I take classes for Web development with Ruby on Rails, Data Science with Python, I have also started teaching Clojure. These are 1 to 1 classes via Jitsi. The courses are 3 - 4 months long and cost ₹1,50,000/-. If people ask for a discount, I tell them to pay after the course. Some people are okay to pay after the course. Then my only requirement is for them to have a good computing machine. One with a decent processor and Ubuntu so that things flow smoothly. Here comes the catch, most people I meet who want to gain this knowledge do not have computer. Somehow they have finished engineering without a machine, and they seem to have no idea to buy it. When I pressed many and asked how can they learn without a computer? The answer I got was they couldn’t afford it. It shocked me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Deeply saddened by Stallman’s cancer</title><link href="/2024/01/07/deeply-saddened-by-stallmans-cancer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deeply saddened by Stallman&apos;s cancer" /><published>2024-01-07T10:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-01-07T10:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/01/07/deeply-saddened-by-stallmans-cancer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/01/07/deeply-saddened-by-stallmans-cancer.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeigdukpyroexsho3vp6chyiltw3g6l7jbb2vldfdzp2yclnzxipzea&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I was watching a free software video, I noticed Richard Stallman had no hair on his head and his beard is gone. First I thought he shaved it because he had gotten old and want to get rid of hair, but then I went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_Stallman&quot;&gt;his Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt; page and found that he had cancer. It shocked me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Bf7DaRmywUo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many of you know that your smart T.V takes screenshot of your entire screen every two seconds and sends it to a centralized server? How many of you know Xiaomi phones, Kindle and other devices you use spy on you? Are you able to stop it spying? Have you thought how to stop corporate’s spying and controlling your life using software in the devices you own?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is ruled by a leader who conducted genocide when he was a Chief Minister, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pegasus_Project_revelations_in_India&quot;&gt;he also spied and spying on fellow politicians using software in their phones&lt;/a&gt;. Many of us have Government utility software in our phone, how can we be sure the government is not spying on us? Those software products are made with our money, why aren’t we able to see how it works? It might have a bug that might be exploited by a foreign actor, why are our programmers not able to look at the code, and are unable to comment on code quality, fix code issues etc?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those software products that are closed, and has a potential to cause harm to you are called proprietary software. A software that you can see the source, understand its working, modify it, and redistribute possibly better version of it to your friends is called free software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stall man pioneered the &lt;a href=&quot;https://fsf.org&quot;&gt;Free Software Movement&lt;/a&gt;, which aims to educate and liberate us from proprietary software. His efforts shook evil empires like Microsoft, today even Microsoft (though no way less evil than before,) is run by free software. It simply can’t compete with GNU/Linux and lots of other free softwares out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stallman created the free software movement, gave us awareness about free software with his relentless campaigns, he is a fighter who never gives up, he is a leader who you would think should live forever, and he getting cancer is blow to our morale. He even replied to my emails. To Emacs user, he is God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world would be far worst without Stallman, we would have been shackled by software far far more than we are shackled now. I might have not had this program to &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; create this blog. I would have been blogging using some other software like Medium that shackles me and spies on my readers. We would have accepted being spied and shackled by software, we would have happily accepted it as the norm. Stallman challenged it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish Stallman recovers soon, comes back with more energy, and we have mechanism where no matter what happens, free software movement exists and becomes stronger and stronger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Free software still has immense potential, imaging what would happen if every human in this world realizes what free software is and demands that he would only use free software? Lot’s of digital evil will be gone. Your data won’t be sold left, right, and center to evil marketing people. Just imaging a world without spam on your phone. That’s just one side effect of having free software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine your government which is unable to spy on you and control you with information gathered about you, focuses instead winning the next election by providing the nation with good governance. The world will be far better if it switches to free software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a world where some tech guy in a big company unable to listen to your kid and watch it by turning camera on its devise. That’s the kind of world we want, not a world what it is now, where we are spied upon relentlessly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope people reading this blog understands what &lt;a href=&quot;https://fsf.org&quot;&gt;Free Software&lt;/a&gt; is and who is &lt;a href=&quot;https://stallman.org&quot;&gt;Stallman&lt;/a&gt;, and I wish you too take a step into the wonderful world of free software.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ayodhya Ram Temple is a slap on the face of Indian Democracy</title><link href="/2023/12/24/ayodhya-ram-temple-is-a-slap-on-the-face-of-indian-democracy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ayodhya Ram Temple is a slap on the face of Indian Democracy" /><published>2023-12-24T11:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-12-24T11:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/12/24/ayodhya-ram-temple-is-a-slap-on-the-face-of-indian-democracy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/12/24/ayodhya-ram-temple-is-a-slap-on-the-face-of-indian-democracy.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeiaumaq2ikafd4gz5y4r3pa6hforqdgpminu4cijx7loc5n7t3nzna&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s evident that some Islamic king did destroy an ancient temple and build mosque on Ayodhya, none disputes it. India has had a very bad history because of its ability to generate wealth, numerous invaders invaded us and still we have China and Pakistan which would like to invade us and loot us. Though we do not have external invaders ruling us now, we are being looted by our own politicians and oligarchs. That’s very sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When India got independence, we gave a pledge in our constitution that integrity of all religious sites will be respected as it was at the time of independence. It doesn’t matter if a religious site was built in a good way, or was it built by destroying other religious sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can understand the anger of Hindus, their temple was destroyed, and a Mosque was built, but India is a nation of tolerance, we have to tolerate, and we must not show barbarism, even though others have been barbaric to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t round up Brits living in India, send them to Janian Wallah Bagh and get them shot. We don’t amas army to invade Briton. We don’t trade Britons as slaves. We forgave them. It’s us being Indian. Similarly, we must forgive the Arabian and Persian people who have invaded us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a Dravidian, I am angry that my culture is polluted by Aryan’s, but I don’t seek to destroy them, drive them back to Europe where they belong, I accept history, and have forgiven them and have accepted them as a visitor who stays in my land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If religious sites should be returned to old state, then, a lot of Amman temples in Tamilnadu should be converted to Jain temples. Jains were persecuted by Hindus, of that time, many jain carvings were wrapped with sarees, worshipped as Amman even today. Jains don’t do tit for tat  because they are tolerant people, and that’s what defines and Indian. We must have a strong mind at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a nation that accepts invaders if they want to stay, and being a nation that gives equal rights to all people, and being a nation that has guaranteed them that their places of worship won’t be destroyed, the intolerant behavior of RSS and BJP is a slap on Indian democracy which we should all be ashamed of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People should be proactive, should discuss how Mod is killing democracy in India, people should spread the word, and people should use the upcoming election as tool  to dethrone him so that much more democratic government comes to power.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Execution tracing protocol for better developer experience</title><link href="/2023/12/03/execution-tracing-protocol-for-better-developer-experience.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Execution tracing protocol for better developer experience" /><published>2023-12-03T10:38:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-12-03T10:38:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/12/03/execution-tracing-protocol-for-better-developer-experience</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/12/03/execution-tracing-protocol-for-better-developer-experience.html">&lt;p&gt;Let’s say you are a developer, and you want to understand how a software works, so you run it. The software fetches some data from a table, which is packed by the DB engine, this passes through multiple layers of code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/execution-tracing/Execution%20Tracing/Execution%20Tracing%201.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now each piece of code transforms the data from one format to another, until a final format that humans can understand is derived. So even as a developer if I run the software, as you can see the diagram below, only the dark blue parallelogram arrives to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/execution-tracing/Execution%20Tracing/Execution%20Tracing%202.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the data is not the one I expected, I must trace the data path, and the algorithm path and understand what piece of algorithm receives what data it receives, and how it transforms it from its input to output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine there is a protocol built into all languages, data storage system and data delivery systems that delivers data to human, rather than delivering the final blue parallelogram, that is the final data packet, what if they delivered the paths in which the data traveled and information about the code through which the data traveled and how it got transformed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than the dark blue parallelogram, you get a huge data packet like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/execution-tracing/Execution%20Tracing/Execution%20Tracing%203.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now say I’m a web developer, just by inspecting a piece of data on my web page, due to this protocol, I get all the rich information that led to the outcome, it becomes very easy for me to inspect and trace things step by step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This I think will massively reduce development and debugging time required for any software engineer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the code is running in production mode, this feature could be turned off, and just the transformed data arrives to you, thus making the system more efficient but less intelligible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this protocol will be a boon for free software, as users of free software can turn the execution tracing on, they can know the data traversal path, they can report better bugs, may be possibly fix them. If this takes off it will be a golden age for developers and A.I systems that helps us to write software. This protocol can be implemented into neural networks, as it will aid us understanding them faster and better. This is like taking all log files, packing them up and sending to the developer so that he need not go here and there to see what’s happening.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Let’s say you are a developer, and you want to understand how a software works, so you run it. The software fetches some data from a table, which is packed by the DB engine, this passes through multiple layers of code.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">In defense of Mansoor Ali Khan</title><link href="/2023/11/22/in-defense-of-mansoor-ali-khan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="In defense of Mansoor Ali Khan" /><published>2023-11-22T20:39:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-11-22T20:39:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/11/22/in-defense-of-mansoor-ali-khan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/22/in-defense-of-mansoor-ali-khan.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeig6vi7okxgl5warl7zl5ve7wcsodskq2pb7rnqnlaaa6tl5uutopa.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t say Abdul Kalam and Sivathanu Pillai are killers and enemy of humanity if they want to design better lethal missiles, it’s their profession. We do not say if A.R.Rehmaan wants to do a better song than Wakka Wakka, that he wants to make a lot of Indian girls dance seminude, it’s his job to direct sensual and emotional songs. Only Hindu terrorists threatened M.F.Husain and drove him to Qatar, others saw his work as art, I don’t think Madhuri Dixit got offended when he said he wants to draw her nude. To think and produce work of art is his job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/pRpeEdMmmQ0?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I view Mansoor Ali Khan as a profession villain, it’s his job to do evil roles as possible, so movies look better with him, and hero gets the credit of slaying a very bad guy. No wonder he wants a rape scene with Trisha. He did not say I really want to rape Trisha, that’s bad, but making him look bad is his job, I find no wrong in his speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why I think things have gone bad? Here are the reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;genetic-angle&quot;&gt;Genetic Angle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genetically men are programmed to access many women as possible, that’s how our genes survive. This also means genetically if you block access to a known girl from a guy, then you are successful male. If you have loved a girl, you will know how her brother or dad behaves. Mansoor Ali Khan exhibits no characteristic as alpha male, so slaying him before Trisha will make males near her feel that they are more successful. It’s programmed in our genes, and we will obey it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;netflix-angle&quot;&gt;Netflix Angle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except for very few, Vijay produces crap movies. He is a good singer and dancer, but he cannot act. Delivering punch dialogs and bravado is not acting, if one needs to know about acting look at Nazaruddin Shah, Irfan Khan and guys like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leo is a movie that only absolutely waste would watch, and if there is a controversy around it, some non-waste people will watch it on OTT, and they might even subscribe to Netflix to see what did happen in the movie. Maybe Netflix sponsored Mansoor to speak like this, or he spoke as a professional, and they pumped money to Trisha to make it controversial, or both, or none of these theories are true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;women-rights-group-wrg-angle&quot;&gt;Women Rights Group (WRG) Angle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These WRG’s, I really don’t know if they help women who are in need, but if there is a beep song (which is perfectly okay in a democracy), or some sensual news, they jump in. Maybe they want to show that they are there and doing something, rather than gobbling up crores of rupees and watch Raki Savanth dance on their personal televisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;weaker-sex-angle&quot;&gt;Weaker Sex Angle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Definitely we are programmed to support the weaker sex, and we are programmed to support good-looking people, so it’s natural to support Trisha than thinking what could be true, so it’s not surprising much in society support her and villainies Mansoor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rails killed ReactJS, now its burning the corpse</title><link href="/2023/10/29/rails-killed-reactjs-now-its-burning-the-corpse.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rails killed ReactJS, now its burning the corpse" /><published>2023-10-29T14:04:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-10-29T14:04:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/10/29/rails-killed-reactjs-now-its-burning-the-corpse</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/29/rails-killed-reactjs-now-its-burning-the-corpse.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/62/Ruby_On_Rails_Logo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Rails, 20+ year old grandpa that still brings smile to developers, unlike ReactJS, which is arrogant unruly teenager, which is no good for humanity.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There are two ways to solve a problem.
One you solve it.
The other you create an impression of solving it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://d1d6azhz7lc2s3.cloudfront.net/hotwire-screencast.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video above explains the first way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-downfall-with-reactjs&quot;&gt;My downfall with ReactJS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am working with one of the best clients I ever had in my life. In India, technicians and programmers get treated like shit, in such a country I feel blessed to work in a team where politics seems to be void. It’s very weird, I can’t believe. When there was the job interview, in the job description it was said I must know basics of ReactJS. I thought ‘how hard could it be?’. ReactJS and other JavaScript frameworks were written to make life of jQuery programmers better right? I was wrong. Fucking wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought myself as a Rails programmer, but my company sees me as full stack programmer (wonder where the full stack ends, does it end in mining sand and making chips?). I didn’t like JavsScript and hence used jQuery, which wrapped JavaScript mess in a tolerable to use library. But in my job I found that ReactJS took JavaScript, added states to front end, made it worst. I found it was a huge framework designed to give a feeling that you are solving something, but gets you nowhere in limited amount of time and effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took up Ruby and Ruby on Rails because I am very lazy guy. Rails lets me develop stuff for my client without a sweat (human politics and stupidity apart, there is no cure for that), so I can enjoy my life rest of the time. ReactJS made stuff super complex, and now being branded full sack developer, I was pushed into this abyss, hell!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rails-killed-reactjs-in-rails-2x&quot;&gt;Rails killed ReactJS in Rails 2.X&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiaqsoerch34vafklzb3sbpyyrt4amnhxkdyy67gm5mitudj6cm7mq.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeiaqsoerch34vafklzb3sbpyyrt4amnhxkdyy67gm5mitudj6cm7mq/prototype.png&quot; alt=&quot;prototype.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiaqsoerch34vafklzb3sbpyyrt4amnhxkdyy67gm5mitudj6cm7mq.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeiaqsoerch34vafklzb3sbpyyrt4amnhxkdyy67gm5mitudj6cm7mq/Screenshot%202023-10-29%20at%2011-18-28%20script.aculo.us%20-%20web%202.0%20javascript.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot 2023-10-29 at 11-18-28 script.aculo.us - web 2.0 javascript.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Prototype&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Scriptaculous&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails killed ReactJS in Rails 2.X. We had Rails JavaScript or RJS. It neatly wrapped Ruby code over &lt;a href=&quot;http://prototypejs.org/&quot;&gt;Prototype&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://script.aculo.us/&quot;&gt;Scriptaculous&lt;/a&gt;, and gave us a way to partially update pages. It was awesome, then Rails fell into the trap of jQuery, which sucked, but was better than ReactJs, Angular etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right from the start Rails killed ReactJs. Yet people just took Rails as a buzzword, started to develop and muddle with it with JavaScript frameworks, made life worst for developers. &lt;a href=&quot;https://hotwired.dev/&quot;&gt;Hotwire&lt;/a&gt; is just a rebranding / reincarnation of RJS. If RJS continued, it would have been 5X times more productive than ReactJS, hotwire is 10X more productive ReactJS. That’s the main difference. Both just replace part of a webpage. Nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;people-have-no-idea-about-rails-front-end&quot;&gt;People have no idea about Rails front end&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without knowing that Rails is a full front end framework, I saw projects after project fall into a trap saying that Rails is great for backend, and some JavaScript framework is great for frontend. All the while I saw how &lt;a href=&quot;https://37signals.com/&quot;&gt;37Signals&lt;/a&gt; effectively used Rails and made huge progress, but half-baked Indians muddled stuff, did politics and made progress so difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who are at the top of tech must use a new tech, understand it thoroughly, see if it does good, then adopt it only if it makes any productivity increase. But most code houses in India don’t do this basic research. Tech heads seem to talk, rather than toil with keyboard. Their decision is based on blogs, vlogs and hype.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reasons-indian-companies-use-react-and-avoid-rails&quot;&gt;Reasons Indian companies use React and avoid Rails&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason why Indian companies use ReectJS, Angular, Vue etc. is because they are service companies. They need to give impression to their clients that they are working hard so that they can bill a lot and prolong the project. That’s another reason why people choose non-productive frameworks that will drag stuff months than finishing things in days by using Rails recommended front end techniques which are super productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hotwire-rebranding-the-old-killer&quot;&gt;Hotwire, rebranding the old killer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All RJS did was to take a request, replace part of a page with HTML content, that’s what Hotwire does, but now its more developer friendly and much easier to do. RJS, and jQuery lost the propaganda war with ReactJS, just like Oracle’s SQL won the Database language battle, though it sucked. Hotwire merely make developers look back into Rails front end techniques, and people say its an innovation, in reality its not. I have been replacing parts of webpage using &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;XMLHttpRequest()&lt;/code&gt; since the days I programmed internet explorer. But yes, Rails and Hotwire has made to do that stuff tremendously easier. That’s an innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;burning-reactjs-corpse-with-morphing&quot;&gt;Burning ReactJS corpse with Morphing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I said Rails killed ReactJS even before BackboneJS was born, now it wants to burn the corpse of ReactJS so that people don’t even know ReactJS exists. Watch this &lt;a href=&quot;https://piped.video/watch?v=m97UsXa6HFg&amp;amp;list=PLHFP2OPUpCeY9IX3Ht727dwu5ZJ2BBbZP&amp;amp;index=10&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;. If you like to be tracked by Google watch it here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/m97UsXa6HFg?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look at this pull request &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/hotwired/turbo/pull/1019&quot;&gt;https://github.com/hotwired/turbo/pull/1019&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With morphing, Rails is burning the corpses of ReactJS, Angular and Vue. All you need to do is to write server side code, Rails will look at the diff and applies it when the view is rendered. You get a single page application using Rails backend ways. I was blown away. This is what you need, I did have, and I am sure many of us would have had this idea, but now Rails people are bring it to reality. I thank them a lot for doing it. It’s still not innovation as they a have borrowed the idea, but they are committed to make developers happy. I respect that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also thankful to DHH to keep Rails as a powerful framework where single developer like me can use it to launch a full-fledged SaaS product. DHH is delaying my professional switch to Clojure, I hate him for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-escape-from-reactjs-and-other-javascript-frameworks&quot;&gt;How to escape from ReactJS and other JavaScript frameworks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are products based company and have given your project to some company that wants to bill you a lot, showing lot of work, you are screwed, I don’t know how your product will come out of evil peoples clutches. But if you have a team that obeys you, tell them yto ditch JavaScript framework and develop new features using Hotwire. This will make a quantum leap in productivity. Once the team has slack, tell them to port pages from ReactJS to Hotwire. Have a good tech person to audit their work so that no mishap happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreibsjisszcc5lgojyj4kddqierbti52mab3d74aapsb7b5gc7fgzm4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;htmx - liberating you from JavaScript hell&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are not in a Rails project, if you are using Django, there is &lt;a href=&quot;https://turbo-django.readthedocs.io/en/latest/&quot;&gt;Turbo Django&lt;/a&gt;, else you can use &lt;a href=&quot;https://htmx.org/&quot;&gt;HTMX&lt;/a&gt;, a library that I think was born out of frustration of using super low productive front end frameworks like ReactJS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;yoda&quot;&gt;Yoda&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Clojure_logo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Don’t forget the &lt;a href=&quot;https://clojure.org&quot;&gt;Yoda&lt;/a&gt; of programming that will bring bliss to development, its one of the latest incarnation of the force.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeifcn4v7paltgjvvpid5umpjvuuod6y73lcuuqhxoow2b6k6gs4egq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;May the force be with you.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/P2yr-3F6PQo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch the above video &lt;a href=&quot;https://piped.video/watch?v=P2yr-3F6PQo&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; if you want to move near to the force.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rails, 20+ year old grandpa that still brings smile to developers, unlike ReactJS, which is arrogant unruly teenager, which is no good for humanity.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tamilnadu’s Engineering colleges are super waste</title><link href="/2023/10/19/tamilnadus-engineering-colleges-are-super-waste.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tamilnadu&apos;s Engineering colleges are super waste" /><published>2023-10-19T18:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-10-19T18:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/10/19/tamilnadus-engineering-colleges-are-super-waste</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/19/tamilnadus-engineering-colleges-are-super-waste.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/3e/Mercedes-Benz_H247_IMG_3397.jpg/1190px-Mercedes-Benz_H247_IMG_3397.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was sitting in my hall one day when one of the person in my family remarked that less than 50% or somewhat around that mark of seats in Engineering colleges got filled up. I was a bit shocked. I know that Tamilnadu’s engineering colleges are super waste, but I also know that their marketing departments are perfect, and I also know that people in Tamilnadu are fools, they will never realize that learning knowledge for the sake of learning and curiosity will lead to real learning, and learning for money or fame or status in society will lead you no where. I expected engineering colleges to keep fooling people like politicians will do to us till our civilization ends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If by some way people are discovering that putting your kid in engineering means you are just funding a rich guy who wants to cheat you to have a luxurious lifestyle by riding on your hardship, then people are slowly opening their eyes I hope. Though I don’t think a revolution will take place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did not believe fools to become non fools. Try telling a God believer God doesn’t exist, he won’t believe you, try telling him you had breakfast with God today, he still won’t believe you. So how can Tamil people suddenly believe most engineering colleges are a spoof? I felt it as an impossibility. I did ask my college group in WhatsApp, and to my surprise my friend said it’s true, colleges are asking students to pay only 20-25% of original fees demanded, they are begging students to stay, and not leave for cheaper courses that would still get you same salary like B.Sc. Another friend who is H.O.D, said some departments in colleges are vacant, that kind of stunned me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staffs in colleges are also very poor in knowledge. Once a lecturer or professor was revered. I still remember how people in my parental generation talk highly of their professors, about the researches and books they have written, how their professors like knowledge and rose from ashes to upper echelons of the society. I did have very good teachers in my college Panimalar Engineering too, but they vanished. It looked like those who totally failed professionally and had nowhere to go, those who would be slave to management and never questioned it stayed. Still among those lambs that stayed, some were good, thought us well, but were they people who could turn humans to engineers? I really doubt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The management during the time I studied was headed by a guy who once sold liquor illegally (but he was trying to change, shed his past I think), he was a hit man of our former chief minister M.G.Ramachandran (MGR), it makes me wonder how people with impulsiveness, violence, anger and subjugation which are result of not having a strong mind can build institutions that claim to create strong minds. Though my college was run by son-in-law of MGR’s thug, I don’t think he was powerful enough to resist the ways of his in laws. I still remember my HOD saying in class that he was watched by thugs who reported his moves to the management, he also lamented that teachers were afraid of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineering is a practical subject, you need to experiment a lot, being an electronics engineer, and a first class pass out, and best outgoing student from my college, I still don’t know how to solder diode to a PCB. It might be astounding, but it’s the truth about Indian, and Tamilnadu’s educational system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This how our electronics lab worked, if you brown out a component, you have to fill on a notebook saying you browned it out, I am not sure if they charged you for the component. In short if you hit a little failure, you were subjected to some bitter process. In that case how do you think one will have the spirit of experimentation? How can one be practical guy? Is engineering a theoretical subject or a practical subject?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s assume that the college was so poor it could not let people brown out components in lab, then how come the grandsons of our college founders have expensive cars that cost’s the worth of possibly lakhs of IC’s? How come they have expensive lifestyles? How come we’re studying in colleges where the kids of management people drive in Mercedez, and possibly apply for Rolls Royce, but we can’t even afford to buy a Mercedez a year even today, after 20 years of our being a “professional”? Think people think!!! And they say colleges is like a ladder that lets you climb above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking that I am an engineer in 2004 and going into HCL as proud first class graduate, and finding that I can’t type fast enough on a computer is not a joke. I had to do that by traveling in Chennai’s buses that were crammed and leaked in rain, at least if I had traveled to HCL in Mercedes and discovered I was not an engineer, I might not have complained so much.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My views on Agile and Project Management</title><link href="/2023/10/16/my-views-on-agile-and-project-management.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My views on Agile and Project Management" /><published>2023-10-16T22:48:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-10-16T22:48:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/10/16/my-views-on-agile-and-project-management</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/16/my-views-on-agile-and-project-management.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreiddqfjwfdipqf4oefd47a5b7os5jtvgjfogno6qbdmgbrlqxjdymq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I am working with a very good team now, somehow there seems to be no politics as far as I know, or looks like politics is hidden from me for reason unknown. It’s very difficult for honest person and thinkers who are honest to survive in politics, and somehow I found a company where I could survive, it looks like an impossibility for me to come across such a good fate. At least my tech team is lead by a guy who knows to code, so maybe he knows what difficulties we face. Possibly that’s why he created an environment without politics, else if it were created by a management guy, we would have been roasted and many of us would have flown off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a great project manager too, and we use Agile, we use jira which is only worth bringing misery to people, its just designed to nag us log this and that and take our attention away from coding. For some reason across the I.T industry non coders like marketing people and the managers who know little of code seem to prefer giving us a lifestyle that lets us create a scene and show off that we are busy, rather than let us alone in deep thought and make something innovative. That’s how the world works, even in the best team I have found so far. I truly wish hell for the creators of Jira.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hVajuTFFqKA?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, let’s come to the project management and my views about project management in the I.T industry as of now. I feel project management is still the same. Maybe it’s the same across almost all I.T companies (may be 37 signals is an exception). Let’s say that you can create a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dosa_(food)&quot;&gt;dosai&lt;/a&gt; in 2 minutes, a project managed way of creating a dosai is a manager standing near you with his eyes closed, and asking every five seconds if a new dosai is ready. You have to answer that you are lifting the ladle, you have poured the batter on to the (tawa)[https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tava], now the dosai is getting cooked, now you will turn it around and so on. If you don’t say it, in today’s project management, you are a person with attitude, a person incapable of creating a dosai. Somehow for this attitude gravity will fail you, the batter won’t fall on tawa, and even it did the heat would not make it crisp. That’s how I still view project management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it will not change in my lifetime. Maybe someone will have brains enough to bring in A-players for project management and create a company with great value, thus nullyfying companies which have no clue about project management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coding standards in India has improved, developer’s pay is improving, but it’s still got lot to improve. The dumb boss earns more than coders with brain, this is a system that will fail when faced with real competition. But project management is still in its dark ages, and doesn’t even have a clue that sun also rises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zPT-DuG0UjU?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Oh fuck, not the bulb again!</title><link href="/2023/09/29/oh-fuck-not-the-bulb-again.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Oh fuck, not the bulb again!" /><published>2023-09-29T23:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-29T23:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/09/29/oh-fuck-not-the-bulb-again</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/29/oh-fuck-not-the-bulb-again.html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what’s happening in my life. The germ of Mind As Lab’s idea started in my mind may be when I was in 6&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, we have been able to place excellent minds into tech Industry since it started operation from 2005. I have worked in Mind As Lab, and have been its observer. Currently, I observe it more. I get consulted for big decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was this webpage tweaks recently, and I noticed this logo:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreiegwxqgtjvt32454bxnwjvdrz7xgg76u4vqpcsegmngxgsz47mmhu.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, damn I said to me, this was our previous logo, but since it’s a democratic company, the one above won the vote, the one which I saw getting designed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeibgy45edzopr3ncx56o74iowjtuh7cfo3czmxbhb2aqrv5q65vvla.ipfs.dweb.link/mind%20as%20lab%20logo%207.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;got thrown out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new logo resembles an electric bulb. What bothers me is I worked for two companies that were obsessed with this bulb thing on there webpage, technologically these companies were junk and were driven by emotions of their leadership and never a scientific process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first company was Zanec, look at their webpage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeiga4l2lpx6zf6qnipqvxg4cb3t63vy2tpedrm6s5ak5wa3umixdxe&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has a bloody bulb. The leadership of this company will never listen to tech and science and they are management kind of people, they need to be selling bottled water like John Sculley to be really successful and never tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next company was Trumatics:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeibrdcg7rphbjrdea3su7cedhcto42horqbwr7um7phca5gb5as7oy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was Trumatics director for a short period, thankfully I left, and we joke that people picked by Mind As Lab can make more money than Trumatics, and possibly 5 or 6 of them can match and outperform Zanec. But yes, success is never equals technical perfection. Technically perfect person in right environment has higher probability of success. I must also say that I don’t have revenue data of these companies, and I don’t have revenue data of Mind As Lab, it’s just a guess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working in these three companies, I can guarantee that a good and honest tech guy can never be successful in Trumatics and Zanec, his chances of success are more probable in Mind As Lab. But yes, since everything changes, I advise the people of Mind As Lab be vigilant and thoughtful so that C-players do not dominate it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their tech people are so deprived and mentally drained by the management, Mind As Lab wouldn’t even consider making a deal with them. But yes, I’m just an observer of Mind As Lab, I can only advise it to make deal with tech companies, and not tech bogus ones. If some management guy becomes leader of Mind As Lab, not even God can save it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing that irks me is, these tech bogus companies have bulb as logo, and so does Mind As Lab (for now), I wish the first company created by me never becomes tech bogus one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I don’t know what’s happening in my life. The germ of Mind As Lab’s idea started in my mind may be when I was in 6th, we have been able to place excellent minds into tech Industry since it started operation from 2005. I have worked in Mind As Lab, and have been its observer. Currently, I observe it more. I get consulted for big decisions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Richard Stallman interview goes wrong</title><link href="/2023/09/29/richard-stallman-interview-goes-wrong.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Richard Stallman interview goes wrong" /><published>2023-09-29T13:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-29T13:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/09/29/richard-stallman-interview-goes-wrong</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/29/richard-stallman-interview-goes-wrong.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeidngrikl33oygx4c5jcemhrr255bx3f3ujgvgddj5fbat44ji5gpy &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A person having no idea of what software freedom is talks with Stallman. LOL.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry></feed>