<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-02-25T21:28:29+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Nobody should code</title><link href="/2024/02/25/nobody-should-code.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nobody should code" /><published>2024-02-25T21:26:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-02-25T21:26:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/02/25/nobody-should-code</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/02/25/nobody-should-code.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeifuvr72gkq2xar7tf73nsupexxa26nlgjajaiwhovabj3lsxq6pc4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans are really shit at coding, our brains are totally different and is far less logical to be a programmer. Even the so-called star programmers are called so just for hype, so that others in the company will slave off to achieve the near unachievable elusive stardom. To make things complicated we have invented this thing called project management, where less intelligent people command swaths of intelligent people. This is an embarrassment to evolution and future sociology researchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Information technology companies treat coders like slave, they are not here for improvement of humanity, they are here as a middle agent, to squeeze out money from clients, and work from coder to maximize their profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way to deal with the mess info tech industry has created is to achieve a state where computers are our perfect slaves and totally understands us and codes for us. I completely agree with this talk.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BJP and Annamalai have got it totally wrong about DMK</title><link href="/2024/02/15/bjp-and-annamalai-have-got-it-totally-wrong-about-dmk.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BJP and Annamalai have got it totally wrong about DMK" /><published>2024-02-15T21:38:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-02-15T21:38:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/02/15/bjp-and-annamalai-have-got-it-totally-wrong-about-dmk</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/02/15/bjp-and-annamalai-have-got-it-totally-wrong-about-dmk.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeibnnv7nfpth3lgvjxaycynxrmn2i43fptxs6dvxourevxujap7tqa&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S.Ve.Sekar when speaking about Annamalai said that he is no more than a poop of an insect. Despite all the scenes he puts, that’s what Annamalai is, a nothing. Maybe he is leader of Tamilnadu BJP because he might be praising Modi a lot when he meets him. In this blog I will say why Annamalai and BJP has got it totally wrong when it comes to DMK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;failed-it-raids&quot;&gt;Failed I.T Raids&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senthil Balaji’s arrests and other things by the BJP, like raiding of DMK supporting businesses are not for quelling corruption I think, I think BJP want’s to talk with DMK to get some political mileage in Tamilnadu, and DMK isn’t talking with BJP. I feel DMK Sending message to BJP that its funding is not dented. The menu of youth wing DMK’s gathering recently where the family shamelessly fielded Inbha Nidhi says it, it was a rich menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I favor a corruption less DMK and I feel what BJP is doing to end DMK’s corruption is not enough. Even the recent dusting of 2G files I feel is not to punish Raja and Karunanidhi family and bring justice, I feel its just for political mileage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dmk-saved-hinduism&quot;&gt;DMK Saved Hinduism&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speech that triggered off this blog was made by Annamalai, he said DMK is a party against God. Sure DMK is a party who’s core philosophy should be atheism, but I feel it has lost it. Duraimurugan is a bakth of this fraud Puttabathi Sai Baba, lot’s of God believers are in DMK. In fact DMK is refining Hinduism and is saving it, rather than letting it get destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today in Tamilnadu poosaari’s are telling chants in Tamil rather than Sanskrit. We as Tamilians are able to understand it. We no longer feel that the God that can have rituals performed in our language as a foreign God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Hinduism, God is equal for all, anyone can do pooja for him / her, DMK has broken the myth that priests in Temples should only be brahmin. Anyone from any caste can become a priest. I would like DMK to amend a law where women and transgenders could become priests, I hope one day that will happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel Hinduism should go one step ahead and make people from any religion become priest of Hindu temples. Our Gods are there for everyone, so all have the right to access our gods and become priests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK is also freeing up temple properties which was dominated and used by few elite, and its been made as a part of temple trust and property of the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without knowing these, Annamalai saying that DMK is going against God is laughable. This shows how much Annamalai and BJP have studied the DMK. Looks like they have not done good work to go against the ruling party with facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;jallikattu&quot;&gt;Jallikattu&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jallikattu is a Tamil Hindu festival, while BJP was in power, and while ADMK (EPS) was in power in state, they tried to ban it, students protested it. DMK was not invited for the protest as it was pure citizen protest, but DMK supported it from outside. That sentiment must have had reverberations in Tamil heartland and DMK swept polls. BJP which does say it’s for Hinduism was hell bent on banning this Tamil and Hindu festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;animal-sacrifices&quot;&gt;Animal Sacrifices&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Jayalalitha (ADMK) was in power, I think while BJP ruling was in central, and while Karunanidhi was in active politics, Jaya banned slaughtering animals in Tamples. A direct attack on Hindu sentiments. I think DMK stood for peoples sentiments though its core philosophy is atheism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-religion-should-be-eliminated&quot;&gt;Why religion Should be eliminated?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Religion should be eliminated because we have better explanation of how things work than saying God created it that way. I personally feel Periyaar’s way must win for a society if that society wants to improve, but I don’t think Tamils are ready and knowledgeable enough for a massive change to atheism and science driven society. At the same time we can’t let society drench in religion and blind faith and become a heavy sponge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel DMK has understood that first religion (Hinduism) should be reformed to modern times, people who were oppressed by religion should be brought up, they must be told they are equal to all, they must be given education, women who are subjugated by religion should be freed, made to work, and slowly as they learn about the world, and get knowledge, they will rely on their brains than mythical God, Satan or what ever to better their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-it-should-be-eliminated&quot;&gt;How it should be eliminated?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way to eliminate religion is not the way China does, forcing thought into people:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WmId2ZP3h0c?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But its by educating people so that they can learn and make judgement better. First people should have confidence, to build it leaders like Periyaar despite their apprehensions towards religion they worked for all to be welcomed in Temples, this gives confidence to people and makes them come up in life which ultimately leads to questioning, thus paving the way of elimination of religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-dmk-will-fall&quot;&gt;How DMK will fall?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Annamalai cannot bring fall to DMK as of now. DMK I feel will destroy itself, it has rich and elite as leaders who are disconnected from people. These elite are only interested in serving the DMK family and support its dynastic politics. If there balloons a party which cares about people, then DMK is gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite we Tamils knowing that DMK and ADMK parties are  ultra corrupt, there are no credible challengers today. BJP being a collection of idiots are no match for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;who-should-you-vote&quot;&gt;Who should you vote?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a Tamil and are feeling helpless, there is not much you can do. Tamils are corrupt, and they will vote for money without having the idea what it does for the nation. But if you care something for this nation, then vote for Naam Tamizhar or Pazha Karuppiah’s party. I wish you vote for Karuppiah’s party since Naam Tamizhar hold up a terrorist as their icon. They could be radicals. If Karuppiah’s party is not standing this Parliament Election, better go for Naam Tamizhar.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I might be lucky to have good Christian as Project Manager</title><link href="/2024/02/07/i-might-be-lucky-to-have-good-christian-as-project-manager.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I might be lucky to have good Christian as Project Manager" /><published>2024-02-07T11:48:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-02-07T11:48:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/02/07/i-might-be-lucky-to-have-good-christian-as-project-manager</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/02/07/i-might-be-lucky-to-have-good-christian-as-project-manager.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeiac7cagg2y2il3sbnab6ut275vmor5rqvujrm2phexryeeiqatnme&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend and I were supposed to meet a guy at 11 Today, and my friend abruptly put a message yesterday that his manager wanted him to be at office today. He works in a corporate and has to deal with psychopaths regularly, he has cultivated the habit of acceptance, obedience, and nature of non-questioning, even if his boss does something idiotic. It’s like ADMK people bowing to Jayaalitha and licking her car’s tire to show their obedience or like the DMK people bowing to Karunadhi family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to wonder why I do not face psychopaths in my current job? Information Technology is relatively high paying field &amp;amp; hence people who are attracted to money even though they possibly don’t love tech, and people who don’t know how they can help the world by doing tech dominate this industry and ruin lives of everyone in it. There are very few pockets where true tech survive, in those places somehow listening leaders lead. Looks like i found a contract in such a tiny island amidst bloodthirsty sharks just by chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday we were having a meeting where some coding metrics did not reflect in spreadsheet. Our manager despite having a deadline to submit it, did not get wild, he did not stress out people, but he explained his problem, he said what he will face with his seniors. That’s clear communication. I was happy I found a good person in my office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what makes him such a gentleman in a field so rich with scoundrels. He is a devout Christian as far as I know, may be going to Church, may be reading the bible and disciplining himself had made him such person? I don’t know. He did behave well despite news leaking out that he too had fair share of problems, he never seems to dump this frustration on others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One other same type of guy I encountered was Mr. Joe Mathew, I encountered him while I worked in a company called Zanec. Zanec did have its fair share of Psychopaths, but Joe protected us. He was a Kerala Christian, based in Australia, having a company named Software Worx. After his project got over, life in Zanec became a bit of hell. I am no person to deal with politics, I am here for productivity and I quit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also another extremely disciplined guy named Vijay Vincent who I met in a company called Francium. He was a business development guy there. Francium consisted of lots of people who studied in BITS Pillani, and we all know people who come out of it have head weight, don’t respect humans and behave like Psychos. It was rumored one of its boss was raised in an Army family and had an abusive childhood, he too behaved psychopath, it was good to tlk to him about tech, but when it comes to dealing with problems, he would happily dump on others head rather than trying to solve it, it also looked like he couldn’t stand if someone smiled before him. Among those psychos, Vijay was a gentleman, a true Christian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish God really existed and rewards these good souls, but if God did exist, why would so many evil people would have been created in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Not a pinnacle of stupidity, India wants to ban imagination</title><link href="/2024/02/03/not-a-pinnacle-of-stupidity-india-wants-to-ban-imagination.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Not a pinnacle of stupidity, India wants to ban imagination" /><published>2024-02-03T18:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-02-03T18:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/02/03/not-a-pinnacle-of-stupidity-india-wants-to-ban-imagination</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/02/03/not-a-pinnacle-of-stupidity-india-wants-to-ban-imagination.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeigwpvsbpdhd7j5d6lqwmi3gm6si2hjwaqdawpfde4e3dqgox3lyv4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;No matter how much she shows, do you think Rashmika Mandana has got great juicy bouncy boobs?&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If evolution had consciousness, Modi, RSS, BJP, Indian bureaucrats would be a great embarrassment, evolution will commit suicide to have created people like these. I think it was in Modi’s rule, suddenly github was banned in India, in Modi’s rule bitcoin is facing serious problems just because Modi wants his friends but not the people of India to control money and economy. We still see people trying to convert Mosques to Temples, though we know such process of converting religious places is barbaric, and we know eye for an eye will surely make the world blind. Somehow psychopaths and people who cannot think and connect with our people have become our leaders, India is still in its dark ages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think Indian politicians are only fit to boast themselves off, being pea brained they have got no ability to think Information Technology is a product of human nature. Humans like to find out facts, imagine and share them with one another. Or maybe it looks like Modi wants an audience with Rashmika Mandana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OJvEta1rkyI?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some guy imagined how it would for Rashmika have a great boobs, found a nice body for her face and told his neural network to merge it, and it did a great job as you can see in the above video. Looks like Rashmika who is dumb enough to think that no one is supposed to imagine stuff above her expressed regret, and these stupid government officials sprung into action and arrested the poor guy who did this video. I wonder what part of the constitution says it’s wrong to imagine and share one’s imagination with others?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think India did threat social networking platforms not to allow deep fakes. What they did not say is how deep the neural network to be? I wonder if they really know what’s the meaning of deep fakes? Computers have gotten powerful enough to imagine stuff, today they are below human levels when it comes to imagining stuff, but very soon a Vijayakanth fan who is watching Gagnam Syle video can just talk to his T.V or phone and tell it to swap Psy with his favorite hero, and you will have Gagnam Style Vijaykanth video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An Ajith fan who does not like Vijay will just say to his T.V to remove Vijay and put Ajith into it, and it will happen. Me watching Romi Rain in deep action will ask my T.V how Shakila or Rashmika Mandhana would be in that position and my T.V will create a new movie, it will one day happen in real time as well. Even I would star opposite to them ;) Why not?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding out how brain works, putting those findings into a computer, telling it to imagine stuff, then sharing that imagination is not crime. We are here to imagine, dream, and it’s noway wrong if a machine helps us to imagine and create stuff better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People in government think that we have copyrights here, but is it followed? Why not? Can they really prevent Indians from using Bitcoin? The government thinks putting laws will curb human desire to share and trade stuff will somehow change humans not be a human, they have totally misunderstood about humans. We are here to share, trade, help each other and become greater. I don’t think these illegal and scary laws and action will stop us being a human.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-not-a-pinnacle-of-stupidity&quot;&gt;Why not a pinnacle of stupidity?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case if one is wondering why I don’t consider these acts by India as not a pinnacle of stupidity, here is the answer. Modi is one of the dumbest leaders India could ever have, I am expecting more super idiotic stuff from him. So this is definitely not a pinnacle of his stupidly, I am expecting more from him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">No matter how much she shows, do you think Rashmika Mandana has got great juicy bouncy boobs?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I think India is a super poor nation?</title><link href="/2024/01/13/why-i-think-india-is-a-super-poor-nation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I think India is a super poor nation?" /><published>2024-01-13T20:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-01-13T20:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/01/13/why-i-think-india-is-a-super-poor-nation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/01/13/why-i-think-india-is-a-super-poor-nation.html">&lt;p&gt;I take classes for Web development with Ruby on Rails, Data Science with Python, I have also started teaching Clojure. These are 1 to 1 classes via Jitsi. The courses are 3 - 4 months long and cost ₹1,50,000/-. If people ask for a discount, I tell them to pay after the course. Some people are okay to pay after the course. Then my only requirement is for them to have a good computing machine. One with a decent processor and Ubuntu so that things flow smoothly. Here comes the catch, most people I meet who want to gain this knowledge do not have computer. Somehow they have finished engineering without a machine, and they seem to have no idea to buy it. When I pressed many and asked how can they learn without a computer? The answer I got was they couldn’t afford it. It shocked me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there are lot a of EMI plans on Amazon and other platforms, but people are unable to afford that too. They are so poor, with a degree, they kind of know what to learn to get a job, but they can’t afford. India I find is a super poor nation contrary to what many people think. I completely understand why Jio is introducing a very basic phone in India targeting the super poor, because they simply can’t afford, and Ambani has the stats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why India is called a rich nation? I think it goes like this, say there is a nation X with just one person (just for easy math sake), and the one earns $50 per day there, now in India population 1000X as that of a rich nation and every one earns $1 a day. So India still on total earns $1000 because of its huge population and Indian leaders get to boast that India is richer than X as X just earns $50 as a nation whereas India earns $1000. This is not a lie our politician says, India as a whole is richer, but Indians are poor, super, super poor. Our politicians want us to think we are rich though we are super poor. It’s a deception with math they want to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To even things out in India, I think we need a very good economic expert as our leader. One who does serve people and not the oligarchs and corrupt. The leader should be capable enough to kill corruption (almost an impossibility in India), and should be able to spread money to all its people, than just few who fund the electoral victors. The leader should b brave enough to speak truth, and really brave should (s)he be as I assume truthful ones will be assassinated or brought down quickly from power. That person should not be mute, and be a slave to a foreigner (say an Italian). That person must connect with the people of India, and not live in ivory tower and just make policies listening to the intellect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short India will be a super poor for a long time, may be forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/85/PM_Modi_addressing_the_Matua_Dharma_Maha_Mela_2022%2C_at_Shreedham_Thakurnagar%2C_Thakurbari%2C_West_Bengal.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;A stupid who understands nothing about economics and human equality is a disaster&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/Mallikarjun_Kharge.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;A person who is slave of a foreigner should not be a leader&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I take classes for Web development with Ruby on Rails, Data Science with Python, I have also started teaching Clojure. These are 1 to 1 classes via Jitsi. The courses are 3 - 4 months long and cost ₹1,50,000/-. If people ask for a discount, I tell them to pay after the course. Some people are okay to pay after the course. Then my only requirement is for them to have a good computing machine. One with a decent processor and Ubuntu so that things flow smoothly. Here comes the catch, most people I meet who want to gain this knowledge do not have computer. Somehow they have finished engineering without a machine, and they seem to have no idea to buy it. When I pressed many and asked how can they learn without a computer? The answer I got was they couldn’t afford it. It shocked me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Deeply saddened by Stallman’s cancer</title><link href="/2024/01/07/deeply-saddened-by-stallmans-cancer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deeply saddened by Stallman&apos;s cancer" /><published>2024-01-07T10:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-01-07T10:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/01/07/deeply-saddened-by-stallmans-cancer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/01/07/deeply-saddened-by-stallmans-cancer.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeigdukpyroexsho3vp6chyiltw3g6l7jbb2vldfdzp2yclnzxipzea&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I was watching a free software video, I noticed Richard Stallman had no hair on his head and his beard is gone. First I thought he shaved it because he had gotten old and want to get rid of hair, but then I went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_Stallman&quot;&gt;his Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt; page and found that he had cancer. It shocked me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Bf7DaRmywUo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many of you know that your smart T.V takes screenshot of your entire screen every two seconds and sends it to a centralized server? How many of you know Xiaomi phones, Kindle and other devices you use spy on you? Are you able to stop it spying? Have you thought how to stop corporate’s spying and controlling your life using software in the devices you own?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is ruled by a leader who conducted genocide when he was a Chief Minister, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pegasus_Project_revelations_in_India&quot;&gt;he also spied and spying on fellow politicians using software in their phones&lt;/a&gt;. Many of us have Government utility software in our phone, how can we be sure the government is not spying on us? Those software products are made with our money, why aren’t we able to see how it works? It might have a bug that might be exploited by a foreign actor, why are our programmers not able to look at the code, and are unable to comment on code quality, fix code issues etc?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those software products that are closed, and has a potential to cause harm to you are called proprietary software. A software that you can see the source, understand its working, modify it, and redistribute possibly better version of it to your friends is called free software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stall man pioneered the &lt;a href=&quot;https://fsf.org&quot;&gt;Free Software Movement&lt;/a&gt;, which aims to educate and liberate us from proprietary software. His efforts shook evil empires like Microsoft, today even Microsoft (though no way less evil than before,) is run by free software. It simply can’t compete with GNU/Linux and lots of other free softwares out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stallman created the free software movement, gave us awareness about free software with his relentless campaigns, he is a fighter who never gives up, he is a leader who you would think should live forever, and he getting cancer is blow to our morale. He even replied to my emails. To Emacs user, he is God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world would be far worst without Stallman, we would have been shackled by software far far more than we are shackled now. I might have not had this program to &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; create this blog. I would have been blogging using some other software like Medium that shackles me and spies on my readers. We would have accepted being spied and shackled by software, we would have happily accepted it as the norm. Stallman challenged it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish Stallman recovers soon, comes back with more energy, and we have mechanism where no matter what happens, free software movement exists and becomes stronger and stronger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Free software still has immense potential, imaging what would happen if every human in this world realizes what free software is and demands that he would only use free software? Lot’s of digital evil will be gone. Your data won’t be sold left, right, and center to evil marketing people. Just imaging a world without spam on your phone. That’s just one side effect of having free software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine your government which is unable to spy on you and control you with information gathered about you, focuses instead winning the next election by providing the nation with good governance. The world will be far better if it switches to free software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a world where some tech guy in a big company unable to listen to your kid and watch it by turning camera on its devise. That’s the kind of world we want, not a world what it is now, where we are spied upon relentlessly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope people reading this blog understands what &lt;a href=&quot;https://fsf.org&quot;&gt;Free Software&lt;/a&gt; is and who is &lt;a href=&quot;https://stallman.org&quot;&gt;Stallman&lt;/a&gt;, and I wish you too take a step into the wonderful world of free software.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ayodhya Ram Temple is a slap on the face of Indian Democracy</title><link href="/2023/12/24/ayodhya-ram-temple-is-a-slap-on-the-face-of-indian-democracy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ayodhya Ram Temple is a slap on the face of Indian Democracy" /><published>2023-12-24T11:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-12-24T11:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/12/24/ayodhya-ram-temple-is-a-slap-on-the-face-of-indian-democracy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/12/24/ayodhya-ram-temple-is-a-slap-on-the-face-of-indian-democracy.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeiaumaq2ikafd4gz5y4r3pa6hforqdgpminu4cijx7loc5n7t3nzna&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s evident that some Islamic king did destroy an ancient temple and build mosque on Ayodhya, none disputes it. India has had a very bad history because of its ability to generate wealth, numerous invaders invaded us and still we have China and Pakistan which would like to invade us and loot us. Though we do not have external invaders ruling us now, we are being looted by our own politicians and oligarchs. That’s very sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When India got independence, we gave a pledge in our constitution that integrity of all religious sites will be respected as it was at the time of independence. It doesn’t matter if a religious site was built in a good way, or was it built by destroying other religious sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can understand the anger of Hindus, their temple was destroyed, and a Mosque was built, but India is a nation of tolerance, we have to tolerate, and we must not show barbarism, even though others have been barbaric to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t round up Brits living in India, send them to Janian Wallah Bagh and get them shot. We don’t amas army to invade Briton. We don’t trade Britons as slaves. We forgave them. It’s us being Indian. Similarly, we must forgive the Arabian and Persian people who have invaded us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a Dravidian, I am angry that my culture is polluted by Aryan’s, but I don’t seek to destroy them, drive them back to Europe where they belong, I accept history, and have forgiven them and have accepted them as a visitor who stays in my land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If religious sites should be returned to old state, then, a lot of Amman temples in Tamilnadu should be converted to Jain temples. Jains were persecuted by Hindus, of that time, many jain carvings were wrapped with sarees, worshipped as Amman even today. Jains don’t do tit for tat  because they are tolerant people, and that’s what defines and Indian. We must have a strong mind at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a nation that accepts invaders if they want to stay, and being a nation that gives equal rights to all people, and being a nation that has guaranteed them that their places of worship won’t be destroyed, the intolerant behavior of RSS and BJP is a slap on Indian democracy which we should all be ashamed of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People should be proactive, should discuss how Mod is killing democracy in India, people should spread the word, and people should use the upcoming election as tool  to dethrone him so that much more democratic government comes to power.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Execution tracing protocol for better developer experience</title><link href="/2023/12/03/execution-tracing-protocol-for-better-developer-experience.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Execution tracing protocol for better developer experience" /><published>2023-12-03T10:38:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-12-03T10:38:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/12/03/execution-tracing-protocol-for-better-developer-experience</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/12/03/execution-tracing-protocol-for-better-developer-experience.html">&lt;p&gt;Let’s say you are a developer, and you want to understand how a software works, so you run it. The software fetches some data from a table, which is packed by the DB engine, this passes through multiple layers of code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/execution-tracing/Execution%20Tracing/Execution%20Tracing%201.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now each piece of code transforms the data from one format to another, until a final format that humans can understand is derived. So even as a developer if I run the software, as you can see the diagram below, only the dark blue parallelogram arrives to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/execution-tracing/Execution%20Tracing/Execution%20Tracing%202.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the data is not the one I expected, I must trace the data path, and the algorithm path and understand what piece of algorithm receives what data it receives, and how it transforms it from its input to output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine there is a protocol built into all languages, data storage system and data delivery systems that delivers data to human, rather than delivering the final blue parallelogram, that is the final data packet, what if they delivered the paths in which the data traveled and information about the code through which the data traveled and how it got transformed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than the dark blue parallelogram, you get a huge data packet like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/execution-tracing/Execution%20Tracing/Execution%20Tracing%203.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now say I’m a web developer, just by inspecting a piece of data on my web page, due to this protocol, I get all the rich information that led to the outcome, it becomes very easy for me to inspect and trace things step by step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This I think will massively reduce development and debugging time required for any software engineer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the code is running in production mode, this feature could be turned off, and just the transformed data arrives to you, thus making the system more efficient but less intelligible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this protocol will be a boon for free software, as users of free software can turn the execution tracing on, they can know the data traversal path, they can report better bugs, may be possibly fix them. If this takes off it will be a golden age for developers and A.I systems that helps us to write software. This protocol can be implemented into neural networks, as it will aid us understanding them faster and better. This is like taking all log files, packing them up and sending to the developer so that he need not go here and there to see what’s happening.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Let’s say you are a developer, and you want to understand how a software works, so you run it. The software fetches some data from a table, which is packed by the DB engine, this passes through multiple layers of code.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">In defense of Mansoor Ali Khan</title><link href="/2023/11/22/in-defense-of-mansoor-ali-khan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="In defense of Mansoor Ali Khan" /><published>2023-11-22T20:39:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-11-22T20:39:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/11/22/in-defense-of-mansoor-ali-khan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/22/in-defense-of-mansoor-ali-khan.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeig6vi7okxgl5warl7zl5ve7wcsodskq2pb7rnqnlaaa6tl5uutopa.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t say Abdul Kalam and Sivathanu Pillai are killers and enemy of humanity if they want to design better lethal missiles, it’s their profession. We do not say if A.R.Rehmaan wants to do a better song than Wakka Wakka, that he wants to make a lot of Indian girls dance seminude, it’s his job to direct sensual and emotional songs. Only Hindu terrorists threatened M.F.Husain and drove him to Qatar, others saw his work as art, I don’t think Madhuri Dixit got offended when he said he wants to draw her nude. To think and produce work of art is his job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/pRpeEdMmmQ0?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I view Mansoor Ali Khan as a profession villain, it’s his job to do evil roles as possible, so movies look better with him, and hero gets the credit of slaying a very bad guy. No wonder he wants a rape scene with Trisha. He did not say I really want to rape Trisha, that’s bad, but making him look bad is his job, I find no wrong in his speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why I think things have gone bad? Here are the reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;genetic-angle&quot;&gt;Genetic Angle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genetically men are programmed to access many women as possible, that’s how our genes survive. This also means genetically if you block access to a known girl from a guy, then you are successful male. If you have loved a girl, you will know how her brother or dad behaves. Mansoor Ali Khan exhibits no characteristic as alpha male, so slaying him before Trisha will make males near her feel that they are more successful. It’s programmed in our genes, and we will obey it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;netflix-angle&quot;&gt;Netflix Angle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except for very few, Vijay produces crap movies. He is a good singer and dancer, but he cannot act. Delivering punch dialogs and bravado is not acting, if one needs to know about acting look at Nazaruddin Shah, Irfan Khan and guys like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leo is a movie that only absolutely waste would watch, and if there is a controversy around it, some non-waste people will watch it on OTT, and they might even subscribe to Netflix to see what did happen in the movie. Maybe Netflix sponsored Mansoor to speak like this, or he spoke as a professional, and they pumped money to Trisha to make it controversial, or both, or none of these theories are true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;women-rights-group-wrg-angle&quot;&gt;Women Rights Group (WRG) Angle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These WRG’s, I really don’t know if they help women who are in need, but if there is a beep song (which is perfectly okay in a democracy), or some sensual news, they jump in. Maybe they want to show that they are there and doing something, rather than gobbling up crores of rupees and watch Raki Savanth dance on their personal televisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;weaker-sex-angle&quot;&gt;Weaker Sex Angle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Definitely we are programmed to support the weaker sex, and we are programmed to support good-looking people, so it’s natural to support Trisha than thinking what could be true, so it’s not surprising much in society support her and villainies Mansoor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rails killed ReactJS, now its burning the corpse</title><link href="/2023/10/29/rails-killed-reactjs-now-its-burning-the-corpse.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rails killed ReactJS, now its burning the corpse" /><published>2023-10-29T14:04:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-10-29T14:04:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/10/29/rails-killed-reactjs-now-its-burning-the-corpse</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/29/rails-killed-reactjs-now-its-burning-the-corpse.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/62/Ruby_On_Rails_Logo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Rails, 20+ year old grandpa that still brings smile to developers, unlike ReactJS, which is arrogant unruly teenager, which is no good for humanity.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There are two ways to solve a problem.
One you solve it.
The other you create an impression of solving it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://d1d6azhz7lc2s3.cloudfront.net/hotwire-screencast.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video above explains the first way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-downfall-with-reactjs&quot;&gt;My downfall with ReactJS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am working with one of the best clients I ever had in my life. In India, technicians and programmers get treated like shit, in such a country I feel blessed to work in a team where politics seems to be void. It’s very weird, I can’t believe. When there was the job interview, in the job description it was said I must know basics of ReactJS. I thought ‘how hard could it be?’. ReactJS and other JavaScript frameworks were written to make life of jQuery programmers better right? I was wrong. Fucking wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought myself as a Rails programmer, but my company sees me as full stack programmer (wonder where the full stack ends, does it end in mining sand and making chips?). I didn’t like JavsScript and hence used jQuery, which wrapped JavaScript mess in a tolerable to use library. But in my job I found that ReactJS took JavaScript, added states to front end, made it worst. I found it was a huge framework designed to give a feeling that you are solving something, but gets you nowhere in limited amount of time and effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took up Ruby and Ruby on Rails because I am very lazy guy. Rails lets me develop stuff for my client without a sweat (human politics and stupidity apart, there is no cure for that), so I can enjoy my life rest of the time. ReactJS made stuff super complex, and now being branded full sack developer, I was pushed into this abyss, hell!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rails-killed-reactjs-in-rails-2x&quot;&gt;Rails killed ReactJS in Rails 2.X&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiaqsoerch34vafklzb3sbpyyrt4amnhxkdyy67gm5mitudj6cm7mq.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeiaqsoerch34vafklzb3sbpyyrt4amnhxkdyy67gm5mitudj6cm7mq/prototype.png&quot; alt=&quot;prototype.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeiaqsoerch34vafklzb3sbpyyrt4amnhxkdyy67gm5mitudj6cm7mq.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeiaqsoerch34vafklzb3sbpyyrt4amnhxkdyy67gm5mitudj6cm7mq/Screenshot%202023-10-29%20at%2011-18-28%20script.aculo.us%20-%20web%202.0%20javascript.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot 2023-10-29 at 11-18-28 script.aculo.us - web 2.0 javascript.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Prototype&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Scriptaculous&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails killed ReactJS in Rails 2.X. We had Rails JavaScript or RJS. It neatly wrapped Ruby code over &lt;a href=&quot;http://prototypejs.org/&quot;&gt;Prototype&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://script.aculo.us/&quot;&gt;Scriptaculous&lt;/a&gt;, and gave us a way to partially update pages. It was awesome, then Rails fell into the trap of jQuery, which sucked, but was better than ReactJs, Angular etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right from the start Rails killed ReactJs. Yet people just took Rails as a buzzword, started to develop and muddle with it with JavaScript frameworks, made life worst for developers. &lt;a href=&quot;https://hotwired.dev/&quot;&gt;Hotwire&lt;/a&gt; is just a rebranding / reincarnation of RJS. If RJS continued, it would have been 5X times more productive than ReactJS, hotwire is 10X more productive ReactJS. That’s the main difference. Both just replace part of a webpage. Nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;people-have-no-idea-about-rails-front-end&quot;&gt;People have no idea about Rails front end&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without knowing that Rails is a full front end framework, I saw projects after project fall into a trap saying that Rails is great for backend, and some JavaScript framework is great for frontend. All the while I saw how &lt;a href=&quot;https://37signals.com/&quot;&gt;37Signals&lt;/a&gt; effectively used Rails and made huge progress, but half-baked Indians muddled stuff, did politics and made progress so difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who are at the top of tech must use a new tech, understand it thoroughly, see if it does good, then adopt it only if it makes any productivity increase. But most code houses in India don’t do this basic research. Tech heads seem to talk, rather than toil with keyboard. Their decision is based on blogs, vlogs and hype.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reasons-indian-companies-use-react-and-avoid-rails&quot;&gt;Reasons Indian companies use React and avoid Rails&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason why Indian companies use ReectJS, Angular, Vue etc. is because they are service companies. They need to give impression to their clients that they are working hard so that they can bill a lot and prolong the project. That’s another reason why people choose non-productive frameworks that will drag stuff months than finishing things in days by using Rails recommended front end techniques which are super productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hotwire-rebranding-the-old-killer&quot;&gt;Hotwire, rebranding the old killer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All RJS did was to take a request, replace part of a page with HTML content, that’s what Hotwire does, but now its more developer friendly and much easier to do. RJS, and jQuery lost the propaganda war with ReactJS, just like Oracle’s SQL won the Database language battle, though it sucked. Hotwire merely make developers look back into Rails front end techniques, and people say its an innovation, in reality its not. I have been replacing parts of webpage using &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;XMLHttpRequest()&lt;/code&gt; since the days I programmed internet explorer. But yes, Rails and Hotwire has made to do that stuff tremendously easier. That’s an innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;burning-reactjs-corpse-with-morphing&quot;&gt;Burning ReactJS corpse with Morphing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I said Rails killed ReactJS even before BackboneJS was born, now it wants to burn the corpse of ReactJS so that people don’t even know ReactJS exists. Watch this &lt;a href=&quot;https://piped.video/watch?v=m97UsXa6HFg&amp;amp;list=PLHFP2OPUpCeY9IX3Ht727dwu5ZJ2BBbZP&amp;amp;index=10&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;. If you like to be tracked by Google watch it here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/m97UsXa6HFg?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look at this pull request &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/hotwired/turbo/pull/1019&quot;&gt;https://github.com/hotwired/turbo/pull/1019&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With morphing, Rails is burning the corpses of ReactJS, Angular and Vue. All you need to do is to write server side code, Rails will look at the diff and applies it when the view is rendered. You get a single page application using Rails backend ways. I was blown away. This is what you need, I did have, and I am sure many of us would have had this idea, but now Rails people are bring it to reality. I thank them a lot for doing it. It’s still not innovation as they a have borrowed the idea, but they are committed to make developers happy. I respect that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also thankful to DHH to keep Rails as a powerful framework where single developer like me can use it to launch a full-fledged SaaS product. DHH is delaying my professional switch to Clojure, I hate him for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-escape-from-reactjs-and-other-javascript-frameworks&quot;&gt;How to escape from ReactJS and other JavaScript frameworks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are products based company and have given your project to some company that wants to bill you a lot, showing lot of work, you are screwed, I don’t know how your product will come out of evil peoples clutches. But if you have a team that obeys you, tell them yto ditch JavaScript framework and develop new features using Hotwire. This will make a quantum leap in productivity. Once the team has slack, tell them to port pages from ReactJS to Hotwire. Have a good tech person to audit their work so that no mishap happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreibsjisszcc5lgojyj4kddqierbti52mab3d74aapsb7b5gc7fgzm4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;htmx - liberating you from JavaScript hell&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are not in a Rails project, if you are using Django, there is &lt;a href=&quot;https://turbo-django.readthedocs.io/en/latest/&quot;&gt;Turbo Django&lt;/a&gt;, else you can use &lt;a href=&quot;https://htmx.org/&quot;&gt;HTMX&lt;/a&gt;, a library that I think was born out of frustration of using super low productive front end frameworks like ReactJS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;yoda&quot;&gt;Yoda&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Clojure_logo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Don’t forget the &lt;a href=&quot;https://clojure.org&quot;&gt;Yoda&lt;/a&gt; of programming that will bring bliss to development, its one of the latest incarnation of the force.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeifcn4v7paltgjvvpid5umpjvuuod6y73lcuuqhxoow2b6k6gs4egq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;May the force be with you.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/P2yr-3F6PQo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch the above video &lt;a href=&quot;https://piped.video/watch?v=P2yr-3F6PQo&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; if you want to move near to the force.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rails, 20+ year old grandpa that still brings smile to developers, unlike ReactJS, which is arrogant unruly teenager, which is no good for humanity.</summary></entry></feed>