<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-06-21T15:28:40+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Resume Vs CV</title><link href="/2023/06/21/resume-vs-cv.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Resume Vs CV" /><published>2023-06-21T15:28:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-21T15:28:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/21/resume-vs-cv</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/21/resume-vs-cv.html">&lt;p&gt;One of my friends seems to have got a Ruby on Rails project, he kept calling me till I got annoyed and picked up, he was ready to pay me well if I sent him 2 Ruby on Rails people trained by me. It was not possible because even the last Rails guy trained by me seems to have an offer, any way I convinced the last guy to consider another job too depending on the nature of boss and payment and I sent his resume to my friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend called minutes later and said the resume lacked detail. I did not read the resume, and so I read it, it looked perfect to me, in further calls it looked like my friend was expecting a CV and not resume. It’s funny that people who are in tech industry for so long are not familiar with the difference between resume and CV. I wish HR’s are familiar what’s the difference, else it would be really laughable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One must also know what’s the purpose of resume and CV and why and when you must ask. I felt bad for putting a good tech guy’s fate in the hands of a person who claims to be an engineer but is unable to be clear, or at least he must admit he does not know something so that one can serve better and create economic value.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">One of my friends seems to have got a Ruby on Rails project, he kept calling me till I got annoyed and picked up, he was ready to pay me well if I sent him 2 Ruby on Rails people trained by me. It was not possible because even the last Rails guy trained by me seems to have an offer, any way I convinced the last guy to consider another job too depending on the nature of boss and payment and I sent his resume to my friend.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Facts are unmasking Kushboo and Chennai Mayor Priya</title><link href="/2023/06/19/facts-are-unmasking-kushboo-and-chennai-mayor-priya.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Facts are unmasking Kushboo and Chennai Mayor Priya" /><published>2023-06-19T08:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-19T08:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/19/facts-are-unmasking-kushboo-and-chennai-mayor-priya</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/19/facts-are-unmasking-kushboo-and-chennai-mayor-priya.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;kushboo-is-a-waste&quot;&gt;Kushboo is a waste&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeib4s4jaubxjbuo2eg2e454remwheahhqxkfy2f4egzwbky6c3dqt4.ipfs.nftstorage.link/kushboo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Actress and Politician Kushboo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I saw news that a DMK speaker was removed because he told some remark about Kushboo, and Kushboo gave a crying interview before the press saying how she felt hurt by the derogatory remark and how she wanted to slap the DMK worker with her slippers, but felt that her slipper will get morally dirty by slapping him. After this emotional interview DMK removed that stage speaker Sivaji Krishnamurthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now DMK has sent a message to BJP, if women’s rights are stepped upon, then DMK will act upon it. Or may be DMK people love cinema people and want to be associated with them, who knows? I am saying this because Udhayanidhi Stalin went on a hunger strike because Nayantara refused to act with him. May be her policy is to act with actors (that is people who can act), so unable to get associated with her, Udhayanidhi went to extreme measure. May be DMK still wants to please Kushboo. Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Kushboo is in a tight spot, if her rights are violated, then she puts up all scene, but if women wrestlers of India are molested by a BJP guy Brij Bhushan, Kushboo is almost mute. She won’t cry for them, she won’t call a press meet, she won’t put a sentimental show to get that guy out, her slippers will be under her feet, and she won’t feel like slapping him with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mayor-priya-deceived-us&quot;&gt;Mayor Priya deceived us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeib4s4jaubxjbuo2eg2e454remwheahhqxkfy2f4egzwbky6c3dqt4.ipfs.nftstorage.link/mayor_priya.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;DMK Politician Priya&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s raining in Chennai, I woke up to and found in News that Chennai is not flooded, it wwas a shock to me. Last year Mayor Priya told us to excuse the DMK, and this year there will be no floods, I couldn’t believe that DMK did what they promised. I was shell shocked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the truth set it, I was watching Sun TV a DMK channel. I switched to other channels and found that Santhome, lot of subways are flooded. I don’t think Chennai corporation has produced any official briefing that it’s better to avoid traveling in these routes and these routes are clear. Looks like the corporation still hasn’t woken up to the fact that Chennai is under rain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my place Sithalapakkam, the place where I live Skylab Avenue has no metalled roads, even on sunny days we get a bumpy ride, water gets puddled up here and there during rains. Governments that claim that they care about people, still seem not to recognize we are people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lets-wake-up&quot;&gt;Let’s wake up&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreiho5mapxmrr5xospm6xjpkdspazeqflusiwkpsnwychpr3dhv4tzi.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Learn before you vote&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheaters dominate the parties we vote for, there are more symbols and names to vote than people standing for DMK, ADMK, Congress, BJP etc. Learn about politics, learn about people who stand for elections and let’s try to create a corruption free and honest India.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Kushboo is a waste</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why bad things happen in batches?</title><link href="/2023/06/16/why-bad-things-happen-in-batches.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why bad things happen in batches?" /><published>2023-06-16T07:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-16T07:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/16/why-bad-things-happen-in-batches</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/16/why-bad-things-happen-in-batches.html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t believe in astrology, even if you believe, it’s just a set of words that could or could not happen. A great astrologer once told me that I will start believing in God by age 27, I’m 40 now and wonder how nonexistent God is going to pop out of nowhere and make me believe in it. When I do ask questions about astrology, my friends who believe it and even some astrologers get furious, I don’t get why. Just for sun, when friends come to me with problems, I do ask them what did the astrologers say, they get really serious and say something, and I laugh inside seeing their ignorance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish I knew psychology, sometime some incidents seems to happen in batches, and they seem totally unrelated to each other, it looks like you are destined to receive it. Here are two of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, one of my relative bought a house in Bangalore, so he told the elders in my family that I should attend the housewarming, I did not want to travel in bus, it robs my sleep and next day would be somewhat, I never got a train ticket, and flight would be prohibitively expensive, so I said no, and thought that was the end of matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like that jerk got really pissed off because I said no, and he started to pull string, and gave 
me unnecessary problems. I saw good people turn evil, the guy causing the problem was comfortably hiding behind them like a coward, unable to confront me. People behaved like psychopaths with me. I was baffled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dealing with those psychopaths, I thought what could go wrong? And it did. I was working in a company called Trumatics, and something happened to my co-director. He started to shout, he started to shout at me and every one like psychopath. I even saw him shout at my friend, because he was angry that he could not blame me that day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really started to wonder if fate had decided about me, (even though I had eliminated some psychopaths out of my life and was recovering,), if it wanted to be keep me encountering more psychos or something. In brief, I was wondering if there is some destiny or something?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next incident happened recently, I was traveling in car with few people, the person sitting next to instructed me on every thing, he said which lane I should drive, when to put the indicator, when to brake and blah blah, I was frustrated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A week after that his son was sitting next to me, and he told me when to switch on the wiper, he asked me to pick up speed in densely packed road that was almost dead still in traffic. I thought, okay this is a son of a psycho and no wonder. I brushed it off, maybe it’s genetics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The very next day I was with a another friend whose company I am investing in, historically he was not like the father son psychos, a well tuned mind he was, he started say do this and that while I was driving. These three driving incidents happened within a span of week and few days, and I was wondering why am I encountering such a strange behavior of people in my car. I started to think about destiny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though coincidence, very similar stuff happening at very short intervals looks spooky.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I don’t believe in astrology, even if you believe, it’s just a set of words that could or could not happen. A great astrologer once told me that I will start believing in God by age 27, I’m 40 now and wonder how nonexistent God is going to pop out of nowhere and make me believe in it. When I do ask questions about astrology, my friends who believe it and even some astrologers get furious, I don’t get why. Just for sun, when friends come to me with problems, I do ask them what did the astrologers say, they get really serious and say something, and I laugh inside seeing their ignorance.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Stalin says about Senthil Balaji</title><link href="/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Stalin says about Senthil Balaji" /><published>2023-06-14T16:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-14T16:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/14/what-stalin-says-about-senthil-balaji.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeigc2rfxdghs6hycj5ord2qzo7kw3citwc7qzvmnwcbmi6n2rtengu &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tamils should search for right people to rule</title><link href="/2023/06/13/tamils-should-search-for-right-people-to-rule.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tamils should search for right people to rule" /><published>2023-06-13T20:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-13T20:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/06/13/tamils-should-search-for-right-people-to-rule</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/06/13/tamils-should-search-for-right-people-to-rule.html">&lt;p&gt;BJP is a shit party made up of shitty people, yet Amit Shah is able to hit at DMK’s dynastic politics, Annamalai is able to say that AIADMK’s passed away supremo Jayalalith is a criminal. Both the allegations are true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If people of DMK and AIADMK hear such damaging truth, and don’t have facts and reasons to counter it, they must commit suicide if they have a bit of self dignity left in them. Guess what none would.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we Tamils have elected this DMK or AIADMK again and again without shame, we must ask ourselves are we shameless people? Or do we have something left in us so that we can try to correct our politics? Do we know who we are voting to? What is his wealth? What are his revenue streams? What businesses he is associated with? What functions he attends? Who attended those functions? How many times the politician has knocked on your door and asked what should be improved? What are the last 10 good things he has done to Tamil Nadu, your district, your ward and to your street? What are the last 10 bad things he has done? Are you going to vote based on the facts you are learned about him? Or are you going to just vote?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even a garbage pickers children in Tamil Nadu are getting educated to have better lives, but we as voters have no plans to educate ourselves about the politicians in our voters list. We may never get political education, that’s what the corrupt want, and till the day most of us get educated, looting will be super high in Tamil Nadu, and we all will be just spectators.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">BJP is a shit party made up of shitty people, yet Amit Shah is able to hit at DMK’s dynastic politics, Annamalai is able to say that AIADMK’s passed away supremo Jayalalith is a criminal. Both the allegations are true.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">CGPA of Indian States</title><link href="/2023/05/27/cgpa-of-indian-states.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CGPA of Indian States" /><published>2023-05-27T23:38:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-27T23:38:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/27/cgpa-of-indian-states</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/27/cgpa-of-indian-states.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeidsgaq36fsdo3xtwup6eahfypatgdqjuu7tpian6oajmmmi7rhhpa&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why can’t Indian President Inaugurate The New Parliament?</title><link href="/2023/05/25/why-cant-indian-president-inaugurate-the-new-parliament.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why can&apos;t Indian President Inaugurate The New Parliament?" /><published>2023-05-25T21:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-25T21:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/25/why-cant-indian-president-inaugurate-the-new-parliament</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/25/why-cant-indian-president-inaugurate-the-new-parliament.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/Smt._Droupadi_Murmu_official_portrait_%281%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Draupathi Murmu&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s great that the opposition parties which almost don’t have the spine to appose Modi are going to boycott the inauguration of new parliament building, the reason they chose to boycott will anger all true Hindu’s in this nation, and it should.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opposition parties have a simple request, the leader of India Draupathi Murmu should inaugurate our parliament building, but why she is not invite and cannot inaugurate our parliament is hushed up, this speaks volumes about Hinduism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First our president is from lower caste, which Brahmin feet lickers won’t like, her caste people could be considered inauspicious beings by them. In fact, I think in ancient Hinduism our president’s caste could be a untouchable caste. According to hindu’s may be those caste people should do only tasks like disposing the dead, cleaning toilet’s, taking care of cattle, doing household chores etc. I think pure Hindu’s will even wash the things touched by lower caste people to purify it. So BJP and RSS might have been instructed by their Hind lords  not to invite a lower caste person to pollute our parliament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, she is a woman. India is a nation that still treats woman as slaves. Now we don’t publicly burn woman just because her husband is dead, but we do all other forms of mistreatment. Visit a house of an Aiyappan devotee and talk frank with the women in the home, and you will know, in fact one will be shocked to find out how women are still been treated as untouchables by their own dad’s, husbands and brothers even today during an Aiyappan season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Women are meant to be slaves who do not have access to Gods. Vedas are banned for them, in ancient homes Sanskrit was not thought to them so that they don’t have access to Gods. The only purpose of woman in post Aryan invaded India is to be slave of men in family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how can a woman who is impure according to the religion followed by BJP and RSS people can contaminate our pure Parliament? That too during it’s inauguration?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So according to a Hindu and Indian, people requesting that President should inaugurate parliament are anti-Indians and anti-national. I am proud to be one more anti-Indian during this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let them enjoy purifying parliament by spraying cow urine in it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Draupathi Murmu</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Which tech companies will make more money in future</title><link href="/2023/05/24/which-tech-companies-will-make-more-money-in-future.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Which tech companies will make more money in future" /><published>2023-05-24T19:27:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-24T19:27:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/24/which-tech-companies-will-make-more-money-in-future</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/24/which-tech-companies-will-make-more-money-in-future.html">&lt;p&gt;I.T has given India a lot, one’s father might be a daily wage laborer, but child in the family might be very interested in computers, all the child has is a cell phone, the child calls a right company expresses interest, they test for the curiosity, laptop arrives to their home, along with broadband, within 4 years the kid has a car, a home on loan which can be paid off in another 3 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recruiting the right and bright talent, and pouring money into them which would rival the salaries of CXO of other companies has been a winning strategy in the I.T industry. That too the kid in the I.T company if it’s in a tier 2 or tier 3 town, they an save a lot of money and settle for life soon, marry, and once that’s done, not even we can save it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now almost none of you in tech knows assembly language, soon no new hires might know programming languages. They will tell computers what to do, and the computer will spit the binary out. You need not worry about code craft, clean code and so on, just like you do not need to worry about garbage collection these days. Applications that took years to develop could be written in weeks, and they won’t have bugs, and they won’t have code quality issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies that can give the highest percapita A.I power to their employees will win. They will make money. Just like a company of 17 today is making more money than a company of untrained 350 programmers, a small company that has great minds and high percapita A.I power can make the money of a company that has 1000’s of people who are untrained in A.I and free thought.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I.T has given India a lot, one’s father might be a daily wage laborer, but child in the family might be very interested in computers, all the child has is a cell phone, the child calls a right company expresses interest, they test for the curiosity, laptop arrives to their home, along with broadband, within 4 years the kid has a car, a home on loan which can be paid off in another 3 years.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">An argument for the command line</title><link href="/2023/05/16/an-argument-for-the-command-line.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="An argument for the command line" /><published>2023-05-16T22:01:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-16T22:01:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/16/an-argument-for-the-command-line</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/16/an-argument-for-the-command-line.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeicligfwyuehx4vms7z5f6nbzpecm7q2td7sjtwpsv3pk4ahojwzp4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before there was GUI (Graphical User Interface), computers displayed text, they got input as text, and gave text as output. Certainly GUI appealed to a lot of people and made them to use computers, but business that are multimillion dollar worth ones used command line, that is text interface terminals for their computing needs, and they were happy with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we are in a wave where we need to make computers idiot-proof, even a baby should be able to use it, the intellectual person is the last customer who we aim for. We programmers seems to think the world is filled with non-intellectuals and we must never write nice informative command line systems for the intellect, and that’s where lot of software problems start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;command-line-is-tough-to-use&quot;&gt;Command line is tough to use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One misconception is command line is tough to use. To look at this months calendar this is the command I use on my computer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ cal
      May 2023
Su Mo Tu We Th Fr Sa
    1  2  3  4  5  6
 7  8  9 10 11 12 13
14 15 16 17 18 19 20
21 22 23 24 25 26 27
28 29 30 31
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now try to find on which day lies August 15&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; 1947, for me it took less than 5 seconds, what about you using an GUI?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ cal aug 1947
    August 1947
Su Mo Tu We Th Fr Sa
                1  2
 3  4  5  6  7  8  9
10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21 22 23
24 25 26 27 28 29 30
31
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, you need to memorize the word &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cal&lt;/code&gt; and read its documentation to use it, but my question is has the humanity got so stupid that shies away from reading things about tools it needs to use?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though there are GUI programs, I wish there was command lines tools that would be simple and fast to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;programmers-use-command-line&quot;&gt;Programmers use command line&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We programmers always use command line tools. The top programming languages are all text based languages and not visual one, though visual languages do exists, they are good for building apps fast initially, but they get bloated with complexity. The vast servers that run the internet run on GNU/Linux whose interface is the command line and do not have fancy Windows OS or Apple OS in it, those OSes are bloated with unneeded GUI. We programmers till to date trust text interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;very-fast-to-develop-command-line-applications&quot;&gt;Very fast to develop command line applications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Command line tools can be developed very fast, one need not worry a lot about display logic, fonts, colors and blah blah. It’s just information in and information out. Since we are limiting the options a lot without display logic and all the complexities and permutations the comes along with it, we can concentrate on solving the business problem and develop the app than worry about styling glitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;train-people&quot;&gt;Train people&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing with command line is, to use it, one has to train people, but once they are trained, they become super powerful, far powerful than people using GUI. To train people, you need to hire people who are ready to learn, and people who would like to understand your business and learn to use a tool to enhance it will definitely won’t be a stupid and would demand more money. May be businesses today want less paid large numbers of inefficient idiots, than productive intelligent high paid people. Maybe that’s what has killed command line business apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One question I would like to ask business people is, do you think business built relying on idiots will out last business built with people who would like to think and learn?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;information-matters&quot;&gt;Information matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately it’s information that matters for human development, tetris played on game boy is more exciting to me than tetris played on a touch screen phone. Gameboy just delivers information in monochrome and does not worry about the shininess of the app, does not worry about color of the blocks and the app animations are kept to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a logical situation its information and truth that matters than shininess, glitter and glamour. Command line apps gives you raw information without the need for the unnecessary stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-age-of-voice&quot;&gt;The age of voice&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The age of voice I think will usher in command line development, voice is just information in which gets converted to text, this text is fed into a program that mostly outputs a text, this gets converted to voice and sent back. Developing apps that take in information and transform it to another piece of information will be refreshing for developers than to concentrate on nasty GUI’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;books-are-still-there&quot;&gt;Books are still there&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though we have got movies, books are still there, they are easy to produce than movies, they deliver concise information to the reader. The story telling world seems to still cater the intellect though things can be done in much difficult visual way of movies, why not we app developers do the same?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case of app development, developers and businesses treat their users as not intellectuals who like to see right information on their screen, but they treat people as kids who like to see shiny things on screen. Common info tech world, serve the intellect than serving people who like glitter.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ghost encounters in office</title><link href="/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ghost encounters in office" /><published>2023-05-16T00:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-16T00:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/05/16/ghost-encounters-in-office.html">&lt;p&gt;I had two ghost encounters in office till to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first one was in a company called Trumatics. I started it with my friend Umashankar who I met in another company called Zanec. We recruited a girl called Vadivikarasi. In that office I used to take walk in the terrace. Once while I was walking I saw Vadivikarasi leaving office, I thought she was leaving early for some reason. I was 40 feet up, and she was on road. I finished my walk and went downstairs to office and there she was Vadivukkarasi. I was shocked and asked her did she leave office and I said to her, I saw her leaving, she too got terrified. Not wanting to make her more afraid I stopped talking about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what ever left that gate had her dress, backpack like her, skin tone like her, the same hold of cell phone while she browses while she leaves our office. It could be a very strange coincidence that I saw someone else and mistook her, or may be my brain got screwed up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My second encounter was in a company Francium, there was a devops girl who seemed to know the trade, and we talked a lot. She drove an electric bike, at that time there were almost no electric bikes in India. She sat in my room because she is a one who cannot stay without super chill A/C. One day she left home, after some time a guy called Prasanna got introduced, or we were talking after acquitance after some time (may be few days). Suddenly he said my wife is devops here, before I could say I know and ask about the electric bike he said his wife Archana is inside coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My heart stopped, just moments ago I saw his wife leave the office, how can I say to him I saw a ghost which was his wife? This Vadivukkarasi incident popped into my mind. This guy Prasanna asked my why I looked tensed.  Dam hell how can I ever say I saw a ghost which just left office that looked like his wife. I did not react and went in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next day I got a doubt and asked others the name of the devops girl that sits in my room, it was Radha they said. Damn, God, dam, life came into me. I am not a peoples person and I get carried away speaking tech to people I don’t even bother asking about their names and stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I learned these girls names and memorized how they looked so that I don’t get confused. Radha soon quit office and hence from then on if it was devops girl it was Archana. So no more confusion. It was sad seeing a devops engineer who was talented go out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot about the work ethics of Prasanna and Archana, I think Archana left that office before I did, and I was thrown out all of a sudden, and Prasanna quit too. Now I don’t even know if Francium exists. I wonder if any company that let’s go off good talent due to carless planning ever comes up?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I had two ghost encounters in office till to date.</summary></entry></feed>