<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-09-21T20:29:56+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The missing feedback in corporates and companies</title><link href="/2024/09/21/the-missing-feedback-in-corporates-and-companies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The missing feedback in corporates and companies" /><published>2024-09-21T20:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-09-21T20:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/09/21/the-missing-feedback-in-corporates-and-companies</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/09/21/the-missing-feedback-in-corporates-and-companies.html">&lt;p&gt;Not long ago, I had a a call with my boss. It was about a ticket that got delayed. There was a bug in it, I explained that my server-side code was okay, and there is something wrong in the JavaScript library that’s causing this bug. My boss, as usual, was sure I was the culprit, he told me how to debug the Rails app, and I listened even though I had been coding in it more than 15 years. He explained it to me as though I were a kid. I just listened without protesting. No storm lasts forever. I am a mountain range, I weather millions and  billions of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, it turned out that the QA  was an inexperienced or sloppy one, she did not know how to distinguish between a new feature or as bug, and she conveniently called what should be a new feature as bug. Later, I would find out that if our APP was less buggy, the QA would be put on to the noose and asked why there were few bugs. So they frame a new feature as a bug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I coded the new feature, it took some time to understand D3js, but I finished it and was proud of it. The thing is, my boss was absolutely wrong, and he is still thinking he was absolutely right, and I created a bug. He was so sure that the data I sent to the front end was wrong and caused the bug. He never had the intelligence to question, ‘Why did the front-end developer who developed the code for this chart display not check the data integrity and raise it?’. In that case, if I had sent the data wrong, I would have had an instant feedback. Simple!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one of the Machine Learning companies where I was a Director, my co-director suddenly thought 100, with a margin of \(+-\) 20% error means the values ranged from 60 to 120. He wouldn’t budge. I assure you, he passed engineering, and I still wonder how he passed, and I wonder why I chose to work with him. He became s difficult to deal with, so I came out of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In every company, there is a way to give feedback from the more powerful to the less powerful ones, but there is no way for the less powerful ones to grade the more powerful one. That’s a fatal flaw. That’s not democratic. That’s not freedom. If one gives an open opinion in an Indian company, he will find himself boiling in a soup very soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel there must be an anonymous feedback system in every company where one can rate his or her boss, so that the real truth comes out. Otherwise, corporate lifestyles will dominate, and people will believe their destinies are like those of soulless machines and zombies. Fact-less thoughts will dominate brains, and less and less efficient bosses will be created, ruining humanity. We need a reverse feedback system.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Not long ago, I had a a call with my boss. It was about a ticket that got delayed. There was a bug in it, I explained that my server-side code was okay, and there is something wrong in the JavaScript library that’s causing this bug. My boss, as usual, was sure I was the culprit, he told me how to debug the Rails app, and I listened even though I had been coding in it more than 15 years. He explained it to me as though I were a kid. I just listened without protesting. No storm lasts forever. I am a mountain range, I weather millions and billions of them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">ChatGPT beats Youtube on many occasions</title><link href="/2024/08/28/chatgpt-beats-youtube-on-many-occasions.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ChatGPT beats Youtube on many occasions" /><published>2024-08-28T13:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-28T13:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/28/chatgpt-beats-youtube-on-many-occasions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/28/chatgpt-beats-youtube-on-many-occasions.html">&lt;p&gt;I was watching this video&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3_fcZApGq1I?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to know how much Gold is there in Earth. This video went on blah blah, and I was not able to find out the answer by skipping here and there. I asked ChatGPT this question and here is the answer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chatgpt.com/share/421d6287-bfae-414b-a26f-bb05f73d8a74&quot;&gt;Total Gold on Earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The total amount of gold on Earth is estimated to be around 244,000 metric tons. However, this estimate includes both the gold that has already been mined and the gold that remains in the ground. Here’s a breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mined Gold&lt;/strong&gt;: Approximately 201,296 metric tons of gold have been mined throughout human history.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unmined Gold Reserves&lt;/strong&gt;: The U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) estimates that about 53,000 metric tons of gold are still in the ground and economically viable to extract with current technology.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;These estimates only account for accessible gold. There is also a vast amount of gold deep within the Earth’s core, which is currently inaccessible to us. Some estimates suggest that there could be as much as 1.6 million metric tons of gold in the Earth’s crust and mantle, but this gold is distributed in such low concentrations that it’s not economically feasible to mine it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-severe-problem-with-youtube&quot;&gt;A severe problem with YouTube&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think YouTube forces one to create video’s of length so that it can fit in more ad’s. For a person like me who does not want to waste time and want to get precise and fast information, this is a severe problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to wait and wait in a video, and you don’t know where the answer to the question is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;use-chatgpt-more&quot;&gt;Use ChatGPT more&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel that ChatGPT is a competitor to YouTube as well. Suddenly video have become the least dense material to seek precise information, and that’s good. May be in the future, videos are there just for entertainment, and A.I. will be there for information and productivity stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;videogpt&quot;&gt;VideoGPT?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need an A.I. that can distill information in videos and answer us precisely. I wish OpenAI mines YouTube too so that we have super precise way to seek information than to look at boring videos.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was watching this video</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">POST should return status 201</title><link href="/2024/08/21/post-should-return-status-201.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="POST should return status 201" /><published>2024-08-21T19:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-21T19:51:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/21/post-should-return-status-201</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/21/post-should-return-status-201.html">&lt;p&gt;I have been coding webapp’s for more than 17 years, and I discovered just yesterday that a successful POST should return status 201.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my office, though I am a Ruby on Rails developer, they told me to code in ReactJS too. Things were hieroglyphs, I never understood it, but there I was staring at a ticket, I never finished it. I hated JavaScript, then after learning a bit of React, I started to hate it more. I still can’t believe humans with embarrassing low intelligence exist, that they can invent JavaScript and React.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any ways, to learn React, I need a backend, I can’t keep creating back end for this and that. I started to think if we can have instant backend for front end developers, and I came up with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://injee.codeberg.page/&quot;&gt;injee&lt;/a&gt; (in memory JSON store) project. It served me well, I was able to create frontend apps because I had a ready-made back end all the time. I am still working on injee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not an expert on HTTP protocol, since injee should provide highly standardized API’s my research suggested that a successful POST should return status 201, and not 200.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why I insist that developers should have a side project, or must contribute to open source projects. At work its work work work, you don’t give a thing about your learning, you trade your existence for money, you can’t expect life in it. If I did not have side project I would have never discovered it may be even in next 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason side project I find enhances my soul. May be because it’s not Agile, and I don’t have to touch this depressing JIRA to log my time, I don’t have tell to someone every day I worked. I don’t have to rush because I won’t lose out on my appraisal and slip into poverty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Injee has not been just refreshing to my soul, about 15+ front end developers have been freed from creating a backend. It’s ironic, because in my work I am unable to free myself from JavaScript and ReactJS even though I am a Ruby on Rails developer and never claimed myself as front end guy, but here, to learn front end tech, I was able to create a project that frees up frontend devs from their miseries of creating a back end server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/19199872/best-practice-for-restful-post-response&quot;&gt;‘Best’ practice for restful POST response&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vinaysahni.com/best-practices-for-a-pragmatic-restful-api&quot;&gt;Best Practices for Designing a Pragmatic RESTful API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I have been coding webapp’s for more than 17 years, and I discovered just yesterday that a successful POST should return status 201.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I missed these stuff in my college</title><link href="/2024/08/19/i-missed-these-stuff-in-my-college.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I missed these stuff in my college" /><published>2024-08-19T10:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-19T10:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/19/i-missed-these-stuff-in-my-college</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/19/i-missed-these-stuff-in-my-college.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/e/eb/12-inch_silicon_wafer.jpg/768px-12-inch_silicon_wafer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was young, I disassembled watches, clocks, those times (in 1980’s) it was all mechanical, I could understand how it worked. But when I opened a radio set, I was puzzled. No matter what I did, I could not find how it worked, it just puzzled me, the same stuff happened when I opened a quartz watch and hand held games, there was big black lump with wires from it, and it worked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took up Electronics and Communication Engineering in my college, theoretically I did learn how they worked, but though my degree says I am a first class engineer, I know I am not. I don’t know how to make a PCB, I can’t even solder a resistor to PCB, leave alone soldering a temperature sensitive Zener diode. Though I finished studying electronics engineering., I could not repair a single electronics device in my home. Shame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure none of the staff in my college Panimalar Engineering had a tie-up with engineering firms, they were out of sync with practicality. I am afraid any of them can implement &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/02/task-which-will-fail-99-percent-of-tamilnadus-electronic-engineers.html&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;. It’s not just a problem in my college, it’s a problem India faces, and is facing for decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is said that when my family was in Gandhinagar, Adyar, my granddad rented out apartments, in one of them there was IIT professor of electronics. A sony radio in my home got repaired, and my granddad took it to him, that guy did not say that he cannot repair, he just had the radio in his home for a long time, realizing that he was not an electronics engineer as he claimed, my granddad got the radio back from him and got it repaired from a local shop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder, if engineer is not useful to community, why you call that one a engineer? Why should that person exist in the first place? Won’t it be good if his body is cremated or buried so that he or she will serve as fertilizer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why am I writing this blog? I went into engineering thinking that I can at least repair a radio set, but I came out without even knowing to create a PCB, or to solder a resistor to a PCB. There was nothing seriously practical in my college. I was dismayed. Recently I was searching on the internet to buy a discarded silicon wafer, I did not work in chip manufacturing, I never will, no matter how much I desire, so I thought why can’t I buy a discarded silicon wafer, frame it and hang it on my wall. The miracle of silicon tech is earning me money, I want to honor it and remember it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I searched ebay, and I searched amazon India, and to my surprise they do sell blank silicon wafers, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.in/Ultranano-Silicon-Scientific-Laboratory-Research/dp/B09LV195B4&quot;&gt;here is a n-type one&lt;/a&gt;, they are so cheap, colleges can stockpile it and if they can build a small fab, can teach students how to create a small chips. It will be a excellent learning for electronics students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.in/99-99-Monocrystalline-Semiconductor-Material-Production/dp/B0C4ZQHSKV&quot;&gt;raw silicon been sold&lt;/a&gt;. For th humongous fees colleges demand today, these investments per student is nothing. They can buy it, and along with a induction furnace, graphite crucible and molds, try to cast their own wafers!!! It won’t be perfect, but they can try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be if a colleges does this, may be students now and in future may not feel void when they come out of engineering, they will feel they are engineers. They might be able to solve industrial problems, say when they are in their 3rd year of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skeptical&quot;&gt;Skeptical&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure all engineering colleges are here to extract money from rich parents, definitely they won’t be doing it. May be students should form groups, should pool in investment of say 1 to 5 lakhs, think of problems to solve using electronics, think of how they can build IC’s on wafers, wafers from silicon, buy or forge the instruments need to do it and execute it. Else even 100 years from now, Indian engineers will be waste.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Aryan BJP, Dravidian Kerala</title><link href="/2024/08/16/aryan-bjp-dravidian-kerala.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aryan BJP, Dravidian Kerala" /><published>2024-08-16T11:32:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-16T11:32:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/16/aryan-bjp-dravidian-kerala</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/16/aryan-bjp-dravidian-kerala.html">&lt;p&gt;It’s no wonder Modi did not announce Wayanad tragedy as a national disaster. BJP being a party submissive to Aryan culture does want to destroy India’s Dravidian past. It’s not now this has been happening, its been happening for thousands of years. As a Tamilian I can say that lot of Tamil works were destroyed, because Tamils listened to Aryans words. Shankaracharya, the betrayer of Tamils, said that Tamil is an eesha baasha, I think it translates the language of lower class people.  Aryans cannot tolerate Dravidians for some reason, Aryan literature depict us as Asuras, people with evil mind and desire. They even celebrate good Dravidians like Mahabali been killed by their God’s Vishnu who in his incarnations has committed many adharma and atrocities, shamelessly promoted caste and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than another Gujarat, where Brahmin feet lickers went from home to home of Muslims and slaughtered them, this time nature itself has slaughtered a lot of non-Aryans. This, BJP will think is a gift to them by their Gods. Now the BJP’s strategy would be to add to the misery as much as possible so that the communist government in Kerala gets bad name. Well that’s what the stupids in BJP think tank would think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayanad is a tragedy, the timing the disaster happened, they way it happened, the gory way it happened, all are tragic, its scale is very high. I am personally against Kerala, for all its hydrological problems, to cover its corruption, it’s government always blame the Mullai Periyaar dam to steer the public attention and anger onto Tamilnadu. This time it couldn’t do it, it would seem rubbish if it blamed Tamilnadu. Tamilnadu was smart, the next day this tragedy happened it announced Rs 5 crore relief for Kerala, thus stopping any anti-Tamil forces in Kerala making a move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally felt no Tamil should have helped Kerala. In an unjust way they blamed us many times to cover their corruption, and they should be left to suffer. But this blog is not about Tamilian’s feeling of been betrayed by Malayali’s, this is analysis of BJP’s reaction to Wayanad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel BJP has failed the nation by not announcing Wayanad as a national disaster. They have violated Raj dharama of looking at every citizen as equal. If Anatha Padma Sami Temple, or if Guruvaayur Temple got destroyed, will the BJP be so mute? Won’t they announce it as a national tragedy immediately to please the upper caste Hindus?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People of Kerala should not only reject BJP and RSS. They must reject Bharminism, Aryanism. If Sanskrit is spoken in their temples, a Malayali should feel ashamed of it and must strive so that Gods are prayed to in Malayalam. They must realize that Kerala is Dravidian state and Dravidians have got longer and richer history than Aryans who merely walked into our lands and are trying to destroy our culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least in politics Kerala people have got more brains, they have elected a communist government. Why don’t they realize that time for religion is over, and why don’t they reject religion and embrace science and race ahead?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It’s no wonder Modi did not announce Wayanad tragedy as a national disaster. BJP being a party submissive to Aryan culture does want to destroy India’s Dravidian past. It’s not now this has been happening, its been happening for thousands of years. As a Tamilian I can say that lot of Tamil works were destroyed, because Tamils listened to Aryans words. Shankaracharya, the betrayer of Tamils, said that Tamil is an eesha baasha, I think it translates the language of lower class people. Aryans cannot tolerate Dravidians for some reason, Aryan literature depict us as Asuras, people with evil mind and desire. They even celebrate good Dravidians like Mahabali been killed by their God’s Vishnu who in his incarnations has committed many adharma and atrocities, shamelessly promoted caste and so on.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Illegal India</title><link href="/2024/08/10/illegal-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Illegal India" /><published>2024-08-10T11:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-10T11:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/10/illegal-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/10/illegal-india.html">&lt;p&gt;I live in a place called Sithalapakkam, a place that is ill maintained by government. My house is on a gravel and dirt paved road, though this place is part of Chennai, the second metro on the planet earth, dust enters my home regularly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I take my car out, even the cement roads in part of Sithlapakkam are heavily cracked and cratered, making the drive worst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dogs roam the street and bark at night, denying one right to sleep. I heard in news the once a dog bit a child and when the Chennai Mayor Priya was asked about it, she said she will soon start counting the dogs? Is this a response a responsible leader should be giving? Imaging if she became a defense minister or Prime Minister, when asked `what are you going to do about the Islamist killing Indian soldiers?’ she might well reply, ‘we will count the dead bodies from now on’. Pathetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On streets of Sithalapakkam, no matter where you turn, you can see a piece of plastic. It flies here and there. Nothing is done about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few months back, my friend who had bought a house here, went to Panchayat office to pay house tax. To pay tax of ₹ 1000/-, he was forced to pay ₹ 6500/- as bribe. The leader of panchayat, I think he said his name was Ravi, was asking others to buy road light fixtures and give it to panchayat. Maybe he will write fake bills for it and pocket the money. The leader Ravi was pointing to staffs and saying that the government was not paying them properly, and claimed this sort of bribes keeps the panchayat going. He said people were negotiating bribe amount with the leader so that their housing tax will get accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is a problem with water lines in Sitalapakkam and if we ask panchayat people to fix it, one must buy materials and give them, plus one must pay bribe to them for them to do the work. Sithalapakkam panchayat doesn’t even know that if you have water lines, and it needs maintenance now and then. Due to the pea braind leaders they don’t even stock spares for repair. Or do they stock spares according to the books ;) and we are the one who the are fools who elected them and staying mum?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The guy who comes to pick up garbage, comes in electric vehicle. He says if the panchayat vehicle allotted for him gets punctured, then he must pay ₹ 100/- from his own pocket and get it fixed, the panchayaat never cares about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost no Sithapakkam roads have a platform, people can’t think of walking here safe without being bothered by traffic. I don’t think the panchat leaders know this is the case here. I haven’t seen any politician in Sithalapakkam in my life except for the time of elections where they go from house to house giving freebies. I imagine, they after winning, spend their time partying with oligarchs, transferring peoples money to the rich. Spending weeks touring the world and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-private-public-works-department&quot;&gt;A Private Public Works Department&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All these made me think, why can’t I start a non-profit for Sithalapakkam. Lot of people here are I.T guys, they like to see the neighborhood in a better shape than being dilapidated. I thought if we can form a non-profit body, collect tax-free donations from the people, then do the public works in less corrupt way, we can be a good competition to the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, one rather than paying his or her income tax to indian governemtn, waiting the center to give part of the money to Tamilnadu, then Tamilnadu governemnt giving part of it to Sithalapakkam panchayat, will see his money been donated to us, and we’re doing the public works for this place. This way we are cutting a lot of red tape and saving lot of time in putting money to action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The government will be forced to reform, else it will be totally uprooted by our public works. Others who like India will see flaws in us, start competing public works, thus increasing competitiveness, and make stuff efficient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;shot-down&quot;&gt;Shot Down&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I called my lawyer friend to explain about this idea, if he gets excited, maybe we can do something that fixes India a bit, but to my dismay he shot down the idea. He said that Indian government is very clear not to allow any competition to it, no matter how corrupt and rotten it is. The government will interpret this as illegal and will get me arrested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I asked about how my other friend is minting money in the name of feeding the poor, he said feeding the poor is a basic right, but road is a luxury. What? I thought. I am not sure if India considers a decent road and decent living as luxury, or it’s my friend’s interpretation of the constitution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;illegal-india&quot;&gt;Illegal india&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it’s true that, if government fails, India does not want it’s citizens to run a parallel government so that the country could be fixed, then I would say that India as a nation has failed. If the constitution prevents running a parallel government in India, then I would say this constitution is illegal and its against the people, hence its India that is illegal, not one who wants to run a parallel government to make life’s of people better.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I live in a place called Sithalapakkam, a place that is ill maintained by government. My house is on a gravel and dirt paved road, though this place is part of Chennai, the second metro on the planet earth, dust enters my home regularly.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When toilet papers disappeared</title><link href="/2024/08/06/when-toilet-papers-disappeared.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When toilet papers disappeared" /><published>2024-08-06T09:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-06T09:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/06/when-toilet-papers-disappeared</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/06/when-toilet-papers-disappeared.html">&lt;p&gt;Usually it’s assumed that the intelligent and capable will lead, but in reality it’s not. I can assure about that in the I.T industry. When ever I asked doubts to my higher up, they with confidence will say this is the path forward. I’m coding for 20+ years, if I ask doubt, it means that I have to log I have done something today, it’s mandatory in most companies to log something everyday, when I don’t want to work, I ask doubt. I don’t even listen to what shit people talk, I read the code and fix it. Code is truth for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing in the I.T industry that appears now and then is frugality. Recently it looks like my friends’ office is not giving free biriyani and pizzas during meetings. That’s bad, I.T companies never want us to be frugal with work, but for some reason they have the god given right to go frugal anytime they want. Yet the non-working top brass will fly here and there in biz class, stay in expensive hotels, goto bars, and even take their family to European trips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was in a company Zanec, things were going well, though the company had huge politics, my client Mr. Joe Mathew of Software Worx seem to be saving me now and then and kept me afloat, else Zanec was near shit. As shit as most software firms. It was not created because someone loved technology and wanted to make people’s life’s better, it was created because a management could make money by brokering work for people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company hit hard times, the company employed a very nasty guy called Varadharajan who would annoy people enough so that they would leave. This way the company saved 2 months of pay check which they need to give when they fired people. Actually such kind of frugal stuff is employed by most companies. When I worked in HCL technologies, I think from 2004 - 2006, it’s HR Mr. Nandhakumar talked to me and made me leave. Same stuff happened to me in Navigant, where my boss Suresh Vasudev and HR Shyam tortured me so that I left. Even Zanec employed a person called Anu Balaji who would annoy me, and finally make me leave. Over here I must appreciate the company Francium, they had hard times, they fire me, at least for me, they gave some compensation. But usually I.T companies are fraud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why I tell many people in west, if you are giving project to Indian companies, check how ethical they are. Else if the project goes well, ask the guy who is working in the company to directly work for you, so that the person has a chance to escape if he is in high politics environment, and by cutting out the middle man, one could save money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now lets comeback to Zanec. As the company was crumbling, we suddenly notice there was no toilet paper. There was no paper near the hand wash, and in the toilets. A person called Ravi, I think he is the director, would lecture us how we are going eco-friendly without the toilet papers. Damn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I did not endure this stupidity long, like Kaikeiyi poisoned by Manthara, poisoned by Varadharajan, Anu Balaji pitched in, gave me a hard time, I left and life did become better. Never be frugal in cultivating your skills, it’s only skill and truthfulness will save you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Usually it’s assumed that the intelligent and capable will lead, but in reality it’s not. I can assure about that in the I.T industry. When ever I asked doubts to my higher up, they with confidence will say this is the path forward. I’m coding for 20+ years, if I ask doubt, it means that I have to log I have done something today, it’s mandatory in most companies to log something everyday, when I don’t want to work, I ask doubt. I don’t even listen to what shit people talk, I read the code and fix it. Code is truth for me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why JavaScript is an Anti-Programmer’s language?</title><link href="/2024/07/28/why-javascript-is-an-anti-programmer-s-language.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why JavaScript is an Anti-Programmer&apos;s language?" /><published>2024-07-28T09:17:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-07-28T09:17:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/07/28/why-javascript-is-an-anti-programmer-s-language</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/07/28/why-javascript-is-an-anti-programmer-s-language.html">&lt;p&gt;If you came to this blog to find a solution to &lt;em&gt;Why JavaScript is an Anti-Programmer’s language?&lt;/em&gt;, then i am sorry. I don’t know why it is. But if you like to listen to a programmers rant, then this is the page for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work in a web development company for 2+ years. It’s kind of an achievement for me. I don’t know why apart from the company I started Mind As Lab, other employments have been jittery. One reason is I worked with Ruby on Rails (RoR), startups like it, and many startups closed, thus terminating my contract. But now very mature companies are using it, so RoR guys are finding a stable job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I sat in job interview for this company I work now, the JD said, you might know something of React, or knowing React was an advantage. I knew &lt;a href=&quot;https://jquery.com&quot;&gt;jQuery&lt;/a&gt;, it abstracted much of JavaScript nonsense away and was good. This jQuery when combined with &lt;a href=&quot;https://coffeescript.org&quot;&gt;CoffeeScript&lt;/a&gt; was kind of heaven compared to JavaScript. Well polished languages like Ruby and Perl bet jQuery + CoffeeScript hands down. So terrible was JavaScript then even wraped with syntactic sugar like CoffeeScript, it was bad enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also learned from other front end friends that JavaScript had improved, so when I sat in the interview I was confident, and I don’t fail interviews, may be because I have been developing web apps more than 50% of my life. My boss asked me questions in Ruby, and it was a no-brainer for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company was good, but then wait for it, all of a sudden I have to code in React. How hard could it be? I thought, and god when I opened the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.js&lt;/code&gt; file I was hit like hell and sank. Spaghetti, spaghetti, spaghetti, fucking spaghetti, as opposed to as apposed to elegance of Ruby. Though jQuery looked far worse than Ruby I was able to manage it, but here God, fucking God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to train my self on naked JavaScript and RectJS, and they sucked, they suck still. Imagine you are a rich guy who swim with beautiful models in a climate controlled pool day in and out, and you get paid for it, now imagine you are made to swim in sewage infested Indian rivers with buffaloes. That’s how it looked with React. If JavaScript is a sewage river, the buffaloes, the pigs and their dung droppings in it is React. Certainly they do enjoy life swimming in the sewage river, but damn I’m a human with feeling, one who appreciate elegance, I have taste, and can’t eat anything thrown tome like a pig!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Money, fucking money. My company doesn’t treat me as shit yet, but certainly they don’t listen to me. For the first point I did decide to continue at my job. But ReactJs makes thing so so so so so difficult compared to Rails. That too when compared to &lt;a href=&quot;https://hotwired.dev/&quot;&gt;HotWire&lt;/a&gt;. HotWire is sooo sexy, if you ask me to choose between HotWire and &lt;a href=&quot;https://xhamster.com/pornstars/romi-rain&quot;&gt;Romi Rain&lt;/a&gt;, I swear I will have a hard time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this made me think, &lt;em&gt;Why JavaScript is an Anti-Programmer’s language?&lt;/em&gt;. Maybe it was created in week, and the creator never cared about programming elegance, and people who were attracted to it from then on were anti-programmers, and they kept the anti-programmer thing alive because they bowed to time pressure and finished their work for money, than caring about great good of humanity. Maybe that Sith is carried on to ES6, and it super amplified now, and ReactJS is a nuclear bomb that is designed to destroy programmer happiness en masse. Maybe this theory could be right, or maybe it could be wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did learn some React, I got so fed up with it while learning, to keep my brain not burning off I created a tool called &lt;a href=&quot;https://injee.codeberg.page/&quot;&gt;Injee - The no configuration instant database for frontend developers&lt;/a&gt;, using &lt;a href=&quot;https://clojure.org/&quot;&gt;Clojure&lt;/a&gt;. That made me not to commit suicide. Clojure is so elegant than Ruby, it’s totally incomparable to JavaScript. It is unimaginable that members of human race which have such nice brains, and who could create a Lisp dialect called Clojure, could be so stupid enough to create JavaScript&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an optimist. Once it was told to me that you can’t become a web developer without knowing Adobe Flash, one glance of it and I knew it was junk, in fact I favored JavaScript over it then. Now I know JavaScript is junk. I am sure WebAssembly or something will end the dominance of JavaScript, which dominates the programming world not because it’s a good language, but for some reasons browser vendors will only support JavaScript. Till then, and if it happens, till the time the top of my company realizes ReactJs is a productivity drain, I think I have no choice but to dwell in hellhole and swim in the shit river along with praise singing JavaScript pigs and buffaloes, so that my plate has enough food. Or some miracle should happen for me to escape from it right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;I can do Perl, python , c, c++, I can do many flavors of SQL and it&amp;#39;s weird Java implementations (SOQl, databricks ) but you put that damn JavaScript in front of me and I just walk away&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; RationalAnarchist (@curtisschlepp) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/curtisschlepp/status/1816706150152499572?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;July 26, 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">If you came to this blog to find a solution to Why JavaScript is an Anti-Programmer’s language?, then i am sorry. I don’t know why it is. But if you like to listen to a programmers rant, then this is the page for you.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Quality of Education &amp;amp; Dogs</title><link href="/2024/07/24/quality-of-education-and-dogs.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quality of Education &amp; Dogs" /><published>2024-07-24T09:40:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-07-24T09:40:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/07/24/quality-of-education-and-dogs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/07/24/quality-of-education-and-dogs.html">&lt;p&gt;I was watching a program on DW TV or I think. It was about Iran, how that country has a problem with stray dogs. People in Iran like to feed and stray dogs, and some dogs get rabies and attack people, sometimes killing them, many times infecting them with diseases. I was interested in the program because in Skylab Avenue, Sithalapakkam, we have the same problem. I think there are about 50 dogs in Skylab Avenue alone and people feed them relentlessly. I don’t understand why bring up such a wretched species will do any good to society?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DW program gave me the answer, it was quality of education they said. People with low quality of education never realize feeding stray dogs is a health hazard. It completely fitted with Skylab Avenue. I don’t see thinkers here, I just see people, who just do things because they do it. They have no brains to connect feeding dogs and public health hazard. They are just limited by their emotional values and won’t raise to the level of thought, and cannot think what’s good for the society and what’s good for the future. They simply can’t. You can’t expect an ant to write ‘As you like it’, it’s like that, it’s brain is too incapable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have seen both my neighbors feed strays. One of my neighbors has a dog, which barks who know at what time. At all ungodly hours it barks. I am sure that my dog neighbor is educated, but not educated enough, so they take their dogs on to street so that it has the luxury of going toilets right in a public place. They don’t clean up their mess. I’m sure they won’t even know what they are doing even in their deathbed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One having a dog is his own right, but make it not defecate on street, it’s a health hazard. If it’s barking, do have a nice soundproof, air-conditioned room and raise the dog there so that it does not disturb others. Have a dog that does not disturb and pollute the society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than my neighbors, its stray dogs in Skylab Avenue, Sithalapakkam that make my life hell. I don’t like to have Air Conditioners, I like natural air than the one that circulates in the room. Having my windows open I sleep, only to be disturbed by the dogs, the barking dogs of Skylab Avenue, and they bark loud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in Sithalapakkam, don’t buy idiyappam from the local vendor here, he feeds the dogs, if you buy idiyappam, you are cursed by me, and your family will go into ruin soon. Plus the dogs surround the idiyappam guy before he goes out to sell, who know what licks, paws have touched his hands that deliver idiyappam to you. There is also a guy, may be in his mid 50’s who goes for walk in the morning, and while returning, he empties a Good Day biscuit packet right in front of my home. Did I say quality educated people won’t feed strays? After emptying the packet, he just throws it on the street. My locality is cursed with such low quality people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At a dead end in Skylab avenue, sharing border with Signature flats, there is a pink color home. Very strange thick glassed people live there. One woman there creases the dogs and I have seen her feed dogs with a cooker full of food! I don’t think she works, and she is definitely not educated I presume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;chennai-mayor-sucks&quot;&gt;Chennai Mayor Sucks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a girl called Priya, and she is the Chennai mayor. I appreciate DMK making some one from a backward community as a Mayor, but can’t they make someone intelligent from a backward community as a mayor? When asked about what she is going to do about dogs that mauled a school boy in Chennai, she responded that they are going to take survey of dogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was no mention of launching an investigation and terminating the dogs. There is no plan in Chennai to get rid of dogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;improved-quality-of-education-is-a-must&quot;&gt;Improved Quality of Education is a Must&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think Chennai people will stop feeding stray dogs any time soon. Ones brain and a whole city getting intelligent is tough. It’s very easy to slip into comfort and stupidity. As a city, as a state and as a nation, we must seek good quality of education so that people have the intelligence to think about the consequence of their action which stretches far beyond the instant emotional kick they get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I pity Iran though, to keep Islam (or any religion) alive, people have to be kept stupid, so the problem of stray dogs will be there forever. But we as Indians have the freedom to exploit science, becoming intelligent and become a better society by eliminating stray dogs by better educating us.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was watching a program on DW TV or I think. It was about Iran, how that country has a problem with stray dogs. People in Iran like to feed and stray dogs, and some dogs get rabies and attack people, sometimes killing them, many times infecting them with diseases. I was interested in the program because in Skylab Avenue, Sithalapakkam, we have the same problem. I think there are about 50 dogs in Skylab Avenue alone and people feed them relentlessly. I don’t understand why bring up such a wretched species will do any good to society?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Solving problems should be part of a programmers life</title><link href="/technology/programming/2024/07/16/solving-problems-should-be-part-of-a-programmers-life.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Solving problems should be part of a programmers life" /><published>2024-07-16T10:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-07-16T10:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/technology/programming/2024/07/16/solving-problems-should-be-part-of-a-programmers-life</id><content type="html" xml:base="/technology/programming/2024/07/16/solving-problems-should-be-part-of-a-programmers-life.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/736x/64/13/45/6413457e57000b55f22d73f484e4c634--personalized-puzzles-self-esteem.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two types of programmers who I encounter. The first one has an Indian middle class mentality, they are like yaa I was born, and I finished a degree, and so I &lt;strong&gt;must&lt;/strong&gt; have a job, an income more than enough to support my family, these form bulk of Information Technology work force here in India. They also have other traits, the moment they get a salary you can see a change in their lifestyle, a new mobile, new dress, new blah blah. Looks like they are here to show off their new stuff than to apply technology to the betterment of humanity. This blog is not for those people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is for the hard-line people, THE PROGRAMMERS. This blog is for people who want to improve their programming despite the salary and other gains because they feel programming is cool. There are many stuff and books written about how to become and keep being a great programmer, almost all those books are about design patterns, they say do this kind of technique over others. I have read those kinds of books and felt that its authors are dumb. For me for some reason the design patterns and architectures they advocate in their books somehow flows naturally. Possibly that’s why I am in this field with relative ease. But for many that may not be the case, you must seek that knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is not about seeking knowledge, but it’s about maintaining a healthy mind. As a programmer you must solve very different problems every day, the problems may vary, your brain must be flexible. To keep your brain flexible you need to solve problems in your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So where can you find problems? May be love and marry a girl, and keep the marriage afloat! Or if you want real problem try criticizing Modi or claim that you want to destroy Hinduism because it’s based on myths than facts. You will be arrested and possibly killed or at lease physically mentally abused in police station. Don’t these techniques give you problems enough? :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay so where can you seek problems which makes you not deal with those animals? Well I do it in the following ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mock-projects&quot;&gt;Mock Projects&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First is mock projects. Why does Iran make a mockup of American carrier and lets its fighters and army boats attack it? Why did Japanese pilots practiced hard and conducted mock raids on Pearl Harbor before the real attack. By doing mock projects you get some kind of familiarity, possibly mussel memory, and you will solve many problems in real projects withe ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In real environments things will be boring and repetitive. You may be having a lot of ideas about what you can do with the knowledge you have, but you must respond to your client or boss because they hold or control the money that flows to you, in such cases mock projects made me flex my neurons and see what I think can be made into practicality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can even team up with your friends for some project. I do not do that personally because I am not a people’s person. I have huge intolerance for illogical humans, whenever I teamed up with people I feel my ideas are diluted by the ones of idiots. But if you feel teaming up with people will enhance your problem-solving skills, please do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;thinking-solutions-to-problems&quot;&gt;Thinking Solutions to Problems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another way to keep your brain active and thinking is to think about solutions to real world problems. Satellites launches are costly, energy intensive and needs a lot of planning, so I am thinking of an alternative solution. Why think about such crazy ideas? Because I can. Plus it keeps my brain working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can think about solutions to very hard problems, like how to end corruption in India. It’s very difficult, you could be killed trying to do it, so how can you do it? Hard problems stimulate one’s brain. The problems can be from math and computer science domain as well, it could also be a problem in your office, for example your office can be bureaucratic and full of politics, if you want to continue in such environment, then how to do it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of solutions to problems to keep your brain healthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;puzzles&quot;&gt;Puzzles&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Puzzles are a great way to keep problem-solving mindset alive. There are a lot of puzzle books out there, there are puzzle websites and apps, so get them and start working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;math&quot;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Math and computer science are interrelated. In fact computer science is a direct extension of math and number theory. Computers can do math billions of times faster than us, that’s it, that gives them these amazing powers. I have personally found solving math problems with machines is fun, and I am able to relate it to parts of real world problems like machine learning, searching, big data and numerical analysis. You may try it too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;games&quot;&gt;Games&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computer games, aka video games are popular among developers. I think they are the most popular mentally stimulating puzzle solving experience. Lot of programmers play games, usually they are game fanatics, which includes me too. Usually when you play games your brain will be motivated to get the highest score using the least possible effort. This motivation will help you research the game plan and find a way out. Many great computer programmers are game players too, almost all of us have tried to create a computer game as our side project. So, if possible try playing games which will improve your problem-solving skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;take-it-easy&quot;&gt;Take it easy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to keeping your brain fit, some people seem to schedule it, now I am going to learn this, at this time I am going to solve a puzzle, and they overstretch. The aim of this article is to exercise your brain in a fun way. Unless you know something really perfectly you won’t be able to predict. Especially if you are stretching your self beyond your usual boundaries prediction and planning fails. So do not plan, go by the flow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just remember this, solving problems should be part of programmers life, that will keep your brain healthy and possibly make you ignore stupidity of humanity and this life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>