<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-19T18:46:52+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Tamilnadu’s Engineering colleges are super waste</title><link href="/2023/10/19/tamilnadus-engineering-colleges-are-super-waste.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tamilnadu&apos;s Engineering colleges are super waste" /><published>2023-10-19T18:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-10-19T18:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/10/19/tamilnadus-engineering-colleges-are-super-waste</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/19/tamilnadus-engineering-colleges-are-super-waste.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/3e/Mercedes-Benz_H247_IMG_3397.jpg/1190px-Mercedes-Benz_H247_IMG_3397.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was sitting in my hall one day when one of the person in my family remarked that less than 50% or somewhat around that mark of seats in Engineering colleges got filled up. I was a bit shocked. I know that Tamilnadu’s engineering colleges are super waste, but I also know that their marketing departments are perfect, and I also know that people in Tamilnadu are fools, they will never realize that learning knowledge for the sake of learning and curiosity will lead to real learning, and learning for money or fame or status in society will lead you no where. I expected engineering colleges to keep fooling people like politicians will do to us till our civilization ends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If by some way people are discovering that putting your kid in engineering means you are just funding a rich guy who wants to cheat you to have a luxurious lifestyle by riding on your hardship, then people are slowly opening their eyes I hope. Though I don’t think a revolution will take place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did not believe fools to become non fools. Try telling a God believer God doesn’t exist, he won’t believe you, try telling him you had breakfast with God today, he still won’t believe you. So how can Tamil people suddenly believe most engineering colleges are a spoof? I felt it as an impossibility. I did ask my college group in WhatsApp, and to my surprise my friend said it’s true, colleges are asking students to pay only 20-25% of original fees demanded, they are begging students to stay, and not leave for cheaper courses that would still get you same salary like B.Sc. Another friend who is H.O.D, said some departments in colleges are vacant, that kind of stunned me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staffs in colleges are also very poor in knowledge. Once a lecturer or professor was revered. I still remember how people in my parental generation talk highly of their professors, about the researches and books they have written, how their professors like knowledge and rose from ashes to upper echelons of the society. I did have very good teachers in my college Panimalar Engineering too, but they vanished. It looked like those who totally failed professionally and had nowhere to go, those who would be slave to management and never questioned it stayed. Still among those lambs that stayed, some were good, thought us well, but were they people who could turn humans to engineers? I really doubt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The management during the time I studied was headed by a guy who once sold liquor illegally (but he was trying to change, shed his past I think), he was a hit man of our former chief minister M.G.Ramachandran (MGR), it makes me wonder how people with impulsiveness, violence, anger and subjugation which are result of not having a strong mind can build institutions that claim to create strong minds. Though my college was run by son-in-law of MGR’s thug, I don’t think he was powerful enough to resist the ways of his in laws. I still remember my HOD saying in class that he was watched by thugs who reported his moves to the management, he also lamented that teachers were afraid of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineering is a practical subject, you need to experiment a lot, being an electronics engineer, and a first class pass out, and best outgoing student from my college, I still don’t know how to solder diode to a PCB. It might be astounding, but it’s the truth about Indian, and Tamilnadu’s educational system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This how our electronics lab worked, if you brown out a component, you have to fill on a notebook saying you browned it out, I am not sure if they charged you for the component. In short if you hit a little failure, you were subjected to some bitter process. In that case how do you think one will have the spirit of experimentation? How can one be practical guy? Is engineering a theoretical subject or a practical subject?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s assume that the college was so poor it could not let people brown out components in lab, then how come the grandsons of our college founders have expensive cars that cost’s the worth of possibly lakhs of IC’s? How come they have expensive lifestyles? How come we’re studying in colleges where the kids of management people drive in Mercedez, and possibly apply for Rolls Royce, but we can’t even afford to buy a Mercedez a year even today, after 20 years of our being a “professional”? Think people think!!! And they say colleges is like a ladder that lets you climb above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking that I am an engineer in 2004 and going into HCL as proud first class graduate, and finding that I can’t type fast enough on a computer is not a joke. I had to do that by traveling in Chennai’s buses that were crammed and leaked in rain, at least if I had traveled to HCL in Mercedes and discovered I was not an engineer, I might not have complained so much.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My views on Agile and Project Management</title><link href="/2023/10/16/my-views-on-agile-and-project-management.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My views on Agile and Project Management" /><published>2023-10-16T22:48:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-10-16T22:48:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/10/16/my-views-on-agile-and-project-management</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/16/my-views-on-agile-and-project-management.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafkreiddqfjwfdipqf4oefd47a5b7os5jtvgjfogno6qbdmgbrlqxjdymq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I am working with a very good team now, somehow there seems to be no politics as far as I know, or looks like politics is hidden from me for reason unknown. It’s very difficult for honest person and thinkers who are honest to survive in politics, and somehow I found a company where I could survive, it looks like an impossibility for me to come across such a good fate. At least my tech team is lead by a guy who knows to code, so maybe he knows what difficulties we face. Possibly that’s why he created an environment without politics, else if it were created by a management guy, we would have been roasted and many of us would have flown off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a great project manager too, and we use Agile, we use jira which is only worth bringing misery to people, its just designed to nag us log this and that and take our attention away from coding. For some reason across the I.T industry non coders like marketing people and the managers who know little of code seem to prefer giving us a lifestyle that lets us create a scene and show off that we are busy, rather than let us alone in deep thought and make something innovative. That’s how the world works, even in the best team I have found so far. I truly wish hell for the creators of Jira.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hVajuTFFqKA?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, let’s come to the project management and my views about project management in the I.T industry as of now. I feel project management is still the same. Maybe it’s the same across almost all I.T companies (may be 37 signals is an exception). Let’s say that you can create a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dosa_(food)&quot;&gt;dosai&lt;/a&gt; in 2 minutes, a project managed way of creating a dosai is a manager standing near you with his eyes closed, and asking every five seconds if a new dosai is ready. You have to answer that you are lifting the ladle, you have poured the batter on to the (tawa)[https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tava], now the dosai is getting cooked, now you will turn it around and so on. If you don’t say it, in today’s project management, you are a person with attitude, a person incapable of creating a dosai. Somehow for this attitude gravity will fail you, the batter won’t fall on tawa, and even it did the heat would not make it crisp. That’s how I still view project management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it will not change in my lifetime. Maybe someone will have brains enough to bring in A-players for project management and create a company with great value, thus nullyfying companies which have no clue about project management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coding standards in India has improved, developer’s pay is improving, but it’s still got lot to improve. The dumb boss earns more than coders with brain, this is a system that will fail when faced with real competition. But project management is still in its dark ages, and doesn’t even have a clue that sun also rises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zPT-DuG0UjU?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Oh fuck, not the bulb again!</title><link href="/2023/09/29/oh-fuck-not-the-bulb-again.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Oh fuck, not the bulb again!" /><published>2023-09-29T23:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-29T23:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/09/29/oh-fuck-not-the-bulb-again</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/29/oh-fuck-not-the-bulb-again.html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what’s happening in my life. The germ of Mind As Lab’s idea started in my mind may be when I was in 6&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, we have been able to place excellent minds into tech Industry since it started operation from 2005. I have worked in Mind As Lab, and have been its observer. Currently, I observe it more. I get consulted for big decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was this webpage tweaks recently, and I noticed this logo:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreiegwxqgtjvt32454bxnwjvdrz7xgg76u4vqpcsegmngxgsz47mmhu.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, damn I said to me, this was our previous logo, but since it’s a democratic company, the one above won the vote, the one which I saw getting designed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeibgy45edzopr3ncx56o74iowjtuh7cfo3czmxbhb2aqrv5q65vvla.ipfs.dweb.link/mind%20as%20lab%20logo%207.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;got thrown out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new logo resembles an electric bulb. What bothers me is I worked for two companies that were obsessed with this bulb thing on there webpage, technologically these companies were junk and were driven by emotions of their leadership and never a scientific process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first company was Zanec, look at their webpage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeiga4l2lpx6zf6qnipqvxg4cb3t63vy2tpedrm6s5ak5wa3umixdxe&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has a bloody bulb. The leadership of this company will never listen to tech and science and they are management kind of people, they need to be selling bottled water like John Sculley to be really successful and never tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next company was Trumatics:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeibrdcg7rphbjrdea3su7cedhcto42horqbwr7um7phca5gb5as7oy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was Trumatics director for a short period, thankfully I left, and we joke that people picked by Mind As Lab can make more money than Trumatics, and possibly 5 or 6 of them can match and outperform Zanec. But yes, success is never equals technical perfection. Technically perfect person in right environment has higher probability of success. I must also say that I don’t have revenue data of these companies, and I don’t have revenue data of Mind As Lab, it’s just a guess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working in these three companies, I can guarantee that a good and honest tech guy can never be successful in Trumatics and Zanec, his chances of success are more probable in Mind As Lab. But yes, since everything changes, I advise the people of Mind As Lab be vigilant and thoughtful so that C-players do not dominate it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their tech people are so deprived and mentally drained by the management, Mind As Lab wouldn’t even consider making a deal with them. But yes, I’m just an observer of Mind As Lab, I can only advise it to make deal with tech companies, and not tech bogus ones. If some management guy becomes leader of Mind As Lab, not even God can save it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing that irks me is, these tech bogus companies have bulb as logo, and so does Mind As Lab (for now), I wish the first company created by me never becomes tech bogus one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I don’t know what’s happening in my life. The germ of Mind As Lab’s idea started in my mind may be when I was in 6th, we have been able to place excellent minds into tech Industry since it started operation from 2005. I have worked in Mind As Lab, and have been its observer. Currently, I observe it more. I get consulted for big decisions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Richard Stallman interview goes wrong</title><link href="/2023/09/29/richard-stallman-interview-goes-wrong.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Richard Stallman interview goes wrong" /><published>2023-09-29T13:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-29T13:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/09/29/richard-stallman-interview-goes-wrong</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/29/richard-stallman-interview-goes-wrong.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeidngrikl33oygx4c5jcemhrr255bx3f3ujgvgddj5fbat44ji5gpy &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A person having no idea of what software freedom is talks with Stallman. LOL.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Perfection &amp;amp; Survival</title><link href="/2023/09/13/perfection-and-survival.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Perfection &amp; Survival" /><published>2023-09-13T21:34:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-13T21:34:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/09/13/perfection-and-survival</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/13/perfection-and-survival.html">&lt;p&gt;‘You don’t care about family, you know nothing about people who have family’ was the kind of words I heard from a guy whose company I was a director of, I was shocked. Nothing wrong had been done technically but here is guy losing his mind. The company did not have enough revenue, or he was trying to cut me out of his firm, I was not sure what’s the real reason. He named it True Mathematics (something like that) because it was supposed be a well oiled Data Science company, but now like every one he survives by offering some Sales Force solutions I think. Even people who worked under me earn more than his entire office that too just by coding from bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was once prompted by my friend about vector Data Base, I analyzed it and thought won’t it be great if we there are only $x$ number of vector operations, and we can store large volumes of data on a single silicon, why can’t we have databases baked into FPGA’s and chips and connected to cloud, this will make stuff efficient. My friend studied with me in college, I studied Electronics &amp;amp; communication, and he Computer Science. I was trying to bake idea for a startup into his mind so that I can use his office to get a patent, where we can stipulate vector processors and sell the IP’s to interested companies, and to my dismay I found out that my friend who is a qualified engineer did not know about VHDL, FPGA and so on. It was like visiting a doctor who just knows to prescribe medicine for fever and never knew about Covid, Nipah and so on. ‘I just know about Python and Java’ said my friend (or something similar to it), and it stunned me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was put into a college that was started by an illegal liquor seller, I still fume about how crappy education was and lament to my friends, but to my friends the college was great even though all it did was to train us to be “yes boss” person than to be thinkers. I was stunned my friends accepted this fate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seem to be a divide between people, people seem to either seek perfection or survival as their value, in real life its fuzzy. In real life I do use technologies that I would never use for my startup because I am paid to use, I do not open my mouth at work because my strong opinions could burn bridges, I kill animals and eat it though I know it causes pain and suffering, but at my core I seek perfection. What hurts me from decades before, or one or two jobs before makes me seek a better way of coding, better way of managing projects, better way of talking tech to younglings, to coach people and so on, but for many people just survival seems to be their core value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For survivors its just making ends meet till the month end, putting up a great show before friends and relatives in a function, sharing statuses that are void and bogus, and just carrying on with life and not seeking truth, in fact to live in the comfort of ignorance seem to be the value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until recent days I did have very low value about people who did not seek perfection. I considered God believers, drunks, smokers, drug takers, corrupt, rapist, survivors as very low people, but then wait, I began to think about my friend’s history. Have I gone hungry like them? Have I been in deep financial trouble like them? Do I have people in my family who make my life hell? Do I stay in a job which has bad boss? Has any tragedy ever struck me? Am I surrounded by foxes and jackals? The answer is no for all questions. But these people have faced it, and some are facing it. To face it and to survive in it and if lucky they have come out of it is itself a great achievement, this traumatized soul of theirs think its better just to survive and not to fall into abyss. For me having not worrying about many problems in life has opened my mind to seek what’s next and what’s perfect. May be if I faced problems like them, maybe I would be a corrupt, a drunk, a mere survivor who just lets time pass by without seeking perfection. Maybe I would be far worst psychopath than others when troubled, who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to cultivate more of an Ubuntu way of thought to understand about the world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">‘You don’t care about family, you know nothing about people who have family’ was the kind of words I heard from a guy whose company I was a director of, I was shocked. Nothing wrong had been done technically but here is guy losing his mind. The company did not have enough revenue, or he was trying to cut me out of his firm, I was not sure what’s the real reason. He named it True Mathematics (something like that) because it was supposed be a well oiled Data Science company, but now like every one he survives by offering some Sales Force solutions I think. Even people who worked under me earn more than his entire office that too just by coding from bed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This IIT professor is going to be fired for talking the truth about BJP and RSS</title><link href="/2023/09/10/this-iit-professor-is-going-to-be-fired-for-talking-the-truth-about-bjp-and-rss.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This IIT professor is going to be fired for talking the truth about BJP and RSS" /><published>2023-09-10T10:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-10T10:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/09/10/this-iit-professor-is-going-to-be-fired-for-talking-the-truth-about-bjp-and-rss</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/10/this-iit-professor-is-going-to-be-fired-for-talking-the-truth-about-bjp-and-rss.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeig3cbrlvzjjytnt6qizclsjcqh3hajhx7k6ymwdk3mxvgfmvxlnku.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tamilnadu should get water independence from India</title><link href="/2023/09/02/tamilnadu-should-get-water-independence-from-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tamilnadu should get water independence from India" /><published>2023-09-02T10:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-02T10:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/09/02/tamilnadu-should-get-water-independence-from-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/02/tamilnadu-should-get-water-independence-from-india.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreifbypwxy5rfw2czvuxddv2o77lcycffrmwehh6w7nytkdgcnfcdoa&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Duraimurugan - minister of water (Tamilnadu)&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to thank Duraimurugan, the way he handles Karnataka now, he is not talking with them, he is saying things will be taken care in the court. This has stunned that state which was and is conning us in case of Kaveri water issue for ages. In fact our neighboring states are using Tamilnadu as a mere sewage dump and storm water drain. Because we are part of India we are unable to report this in U.N, or take India to the court of justice international.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the near future, water is going to be really scarce, and water politics is going to peak. Our neighbors are going to use this as a political weapon to bully us. As a Tamil think, should we allow this to happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think independence for Tamilnadu is going to happen any time soon, and if we get independent, imaging how the political dynasties will treat us and imaging how many of us will be in prison, murdered and so on. I guess independent Tamilnadu will become a kind of dictator state or something since will have no higher power looking upon corrupt Tamil politicians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case of water issue, Tamilnadu has been true to India, while India has betrayed us repeatedly, we must get water independence at all cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have plenty of solar energy in our coast, why can’t Tamilnadu government establish solar-powered water desalination plants? This might take care of some costal water needs. We need to make sure all our rain water is stored, none should be let out into the sea without proper use. We must encourage reclamation used of water in homes. Say what water drains of a sink can be purified a bit and be used in flushes. Homes could install urinals for men which needs less water to flush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capturing water from air is another option, with huge coastline, moist air does travel inwards into Tamilnadu, we can fund businesses that sell devices that will condense this moisture to liquid water. These devices could be made mandatory in new homes built in Tamilnadu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we need to talk hard with center and build dozens of nuclear reactors which will supply ample power, this power should be used to desalinate water in coast and pumped back to farms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For all this to happen we Tamils should form relationships with nations that have done good R&amp;amp;D in water management like Israel, Libya etc. We must invite great scientists and form a water research institute to perfect technology and stay ahead of global warming. May b e we can contribute back to India which has betrayed us for so long, thus proving we are more Gandhian than Indians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Water independence is every Tamil’s birth right, and we should have it! I’m saying this fingers crossed as our corruption levels are enormous.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Duraimurugan - minister of water (Tamilnadu)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Slaves want to be slaves</title><link href="/2023/08/15/slaves-want-to-be-slaves.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Slaves want to be slaves" /><published>2023-08-15T23:48:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-15T23:48:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/08/15/slaves-want-to-be-slaves</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/15/slaves-want-to-be-slaves.html">&lt;p&gt;I studied in a very restrictive college called Panimalar Engineering in Chennai. It was so restrictive that it had rules like boys and girls should not speak with each other, the most stupid law there was we must reach college only using the college bus, I wondered why, they also said what dress we must wear (kind of like Iran), and there was a law saying girls should not wear high heel footwear, I really wonder who is going to look at heals of footwear?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I protested to my fellow friends about these stupid rules and asked them what they thought it served? Surprisingly they said these laws were good and aided our Engineering studies. With management being crack (but cunning enough to extract our parents’ wealth), most teachers being substandard (those good enough left the college soon), and most of my friends being illogical, I felt like being in a mental asylum, and I endured jail for 4 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think in real Jail we can go to library when we wish, but in my college it was not so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just imagine, you are a non mad man who is not praising Nithyanandha and you are in his Ashram where every one praises him. That kind of environment was my college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I was reading book about Sardar and saw this quote:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;A parrot which is kept in a cage for years does not like to come out even if the cage is kept open. Slaves even if they find out a way to free themselves from the bondage they hesitate to go that way. Long-time slavery generates a fascination for a state of slavery.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Sardar Vallabhai Patel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought of my friends working in slave companies, friends who use Mac (which includes me), iPhones, Windows, and Android phones (me inclusive). I thought of people who code in JavaScript and feel great about it. Parrots they are. I also thought of my friends who still supported my college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also thought of friend who said to me LinkedIn &lt;em&gt;‘You joined Panimalar knowing it’s stupid rules’&lt;/em&gt;, hell no, do I look like utter brain-dead?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I studied in a very restrictive college called Panimalar Engineering in Chennai. It was so restrictive that it had rules like boys and girls should not speak with each other, the most stupid law there was we must reach college only using the college bus, I wondered why, they also said what dress we must wear (kind of like Iran), and there was a law saying girls should not wear high heel footwear, I really wonder who is going to look at heals of footwear?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">8th standard kid driving a bike</title><link href="/2023/08/14/8th-standard-kid-driving-a-bike.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="8th standard kid driving a bike" /><published>2023-08-14T18:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-14T18:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/08/14/8th-standard-kid-driving-a-bike</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/14/8th-standard-kid-driving-a-bike.html">&lt;p&gt;I was standing in signal where Chennai One meets OMR, my car was just feet or two away from median divider and a small boy possibly 8th standard skillfully drove between my cars right rearview mirror and divider and made a U-turn, when the signal to make a U-turn was not turned on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though skilled, I was shocked to see a small boy driving a scooter, I scanned for policeman and none was there, the boy must have been a local who knew well and what he was doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t stop thinking about this boy’s parents, how irresponsible they are to let a kid drive at such a young age. OMR mostly consists of learned people, I am not saying learned people are intelligent, that’s different, but learned people don’t make their child do irresponsible things. So to see a boy in OMR shocked me a bit. We can see such kind of behavior in villages where people do not know the law, and don’t care to be responsible parents. There they confuse emotion and responsibility and anything that gives them good emotional feeling is responsible thing for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t stop thinking what kind of adult this boy will grow up, may be fuck a girl in his 10th standard and become a father? Who knows? He would get bribes and his parents wouldn’t care about it too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shouldn’t people who want to have kids know that they should be responsible to the society and should bring up productive and responsible kids needed for society? People are irresponsible and are breeding evil. I wonder what evil he is going to do, and how many are going to be affected by his irresponsible action when he grows up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another day I was in my car parked under a tree, early morning in Sithalapakkam, a boy with a juice carton in his left hand, sipping it with a straw controlling his scooter with his right hand drove past my car, stopped before it, drank all the juice, tossed the carton not into dustbin, but on to a bush nearby and drove on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here I am expecting India to be a great nation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was standing in signal where Chennai One meets OMR, my car was just feet or two away from median divider and a small boy possibly 8th standard skillfully drove between my cars right rearview mirror and divider and made a U-turn, when the signal to make a U-turn was not turned on.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Could Kandahar have been the capital of Murugan’s empire?</title><link href="/2023/08/09/could-kandshar-have-been-the-capital-of-murugan-s-empire.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Could Kandahar have been the capital of Murugan&apos;s empire?" /><published>2023-08-09T14:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-09T14:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/08/09/could-kandshar-have-been-the-capital-of-murugan-s-empire</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/09/could-kandshar-have-been-the-capital-of-murugan-s-empire.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreic3lns4rjkwmgtsnotlftsuivemmyefurccaxa3lhupce67xlnq3a&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People in my neighborhood are disturbing my tranquility by shouting praises for lord Muruga. Somehow people seem to think you need to show off your devotion for God to be in his good books. For some reason, the almighty God’s these days needs publicity, PR, lots of money, and people like priests to survive. Requiring so much support just for survival, we still consider her as the almighty, and claim ourselves Homo sapiens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thoughts ran, I was told by my mother that Kandahar, the present capital of Afghanistan is actually Gandhari Nagaram, that is, it was given as the gift to Gouravas as dowry when Gandhari was married to their family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listening to these praises of Murugan / Kandhan, I began to wonder could it be even older, could it have had the name Kandhan Nagaram, the city of Kandhan, today a God, but then a mighty warrior king who was undefeated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His armies might have marched from the Himalayas to the Peninsula, he might have been instrumental to have laid the basis of formal Tamil language, maybe he and Pandiyas were great friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kandan was so victorious, that Afghans when they saw Alexanders war tactics and victories started calling him Sikandar. They still call him like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreiggbc73r74d5fuvg4xfzviazfq7pyigisz6kebp6zirlyxx3ngyi4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What ever it was, I am sad that India which should have stretched from Afghanistan to Burma (both inclusive). And from Kashmir to Srilanka is not complete yet. We need a great leader like Murugan again to unite our nation and get back the lost bits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current Indian government is unable to pick up garbage, unable to vanquish dogs that bark and disturb my night sleep, it’s unable to eliminate cattle that litter streets and causes accidents, it’s unable to even reduce the prices of essential food items. Me expecting another Murugan emerging in a crippled nation like India is a tall wish that might never happen.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>