<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-09T21:22:32+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Evolution of skin dealing with fire / heat</title><link href="/2020/06/09/evolution-of-skin-dealing-with-fire.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Evolution of skin dealing with fire / heat" /><published>2020-06-09T21:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-09T21:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/06/09/evolution-of-skin-dealing-with-fire</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/06/09/evolution-of-skin-dealing-with-fire.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s1.ibtimes.com/sites/www.ibtimes.com/files/styles/lg/public/2014/12/15/fire.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today while making omelet an accident happened. I poured oil on tawa, then to spread it I broght the ladel upon it, the oil splashed and a big drop landed on my right hand middle finger. A beautiful blister formed, possibly it has some fluids inside. This will help my body fluids from oozing out, thus preventing dehydration and faster death. The top surface of blister is dry enough to prevent any bacterial growth, yet it traps fluids to act as a thermal mass in case the same part comes in contact with some hot substance once again. These fluids also provide a cradle or a packet of soup for my skin to grow, just like primordial life needed a soup of right stuff to evolve. I was bewildered. How did life learn to deal with fire?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fire became common only after humans harnessed it, they somehow found a way to make it, and tame it. Even the Jarwas of Andaman who may have settled in the island 60,000 years ago are believed not to have the knowledge of fire. In that case how did the skin evolve to deal with hot substances? I was terribly confused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see for anything to evolve, lots of failures should happen. Imagine an earth where there is fire burning all the time, primitive animals ventured near it, some got burned, most of those which got burned died, but some evolved a mechanism of blistering, that is flooding fluids under the burned skin, they survived. So as these animals were attracted to the fire, and they made contact with it, even though fire hurts, only those which developed blisters had higher chance of survival, and we are the descents of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But where on earth such fire burns all the time? You may find volcanic magma, and hot springs. But animals usually stay away, they know fire hurts. Unlike us who cannot live without fire / extreme heat which we need for cooking (possibly the Jarwas, and Icelandic people can live without cooking. The Eskimos are good in eating healthy raw meat which digests better) , animals can eat raw food and live. If abundant fire was not available and was there only then and there as forest fires caused by lightning strikes or friction, how on earth did life evolve the art of forming blisters?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully the answer came from Wikipedia, it said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A blister is a small pocket of body fluid (lymph, serum, plasma, blood, or pus) within the upper layers of the skin, typically caused by forceful rubbing (friction), burning, freezing, chemical exposure or infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ah friction! Friction causes heat, heat causes blisters. So as soon as life started to move fast, there would have been instances where it encountered friction, like sliding down on rock, like sandstone or something which causes extreme heat. This could have caused blisters in ancient animals. While running blisters could have formed on feet, hoofs were evolved to prevent that. This is very high chance of heating skin to cause damage than to wait for fire made by humans. A animal could have a fought and could have been pushed, so the one which had accidentally evolved the technique of blistering got less infection, survived better. So no need for nature to wait for humans to arrive and generate heat and burn forests to start selecting animals that can survive fire and heat better. If this blistering only started to evolve only 2 million years ago, (that is when intelligent human formed,) fire wounds by now would be one of the most fatal things as we wouldn’t have evolved sophisticated blistering as we see today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possibly there is a way to test this theory. Mostly aquatic animals may not be well enough to cope up with heat, and that too aquatic animals near the poles. If we can see how their skin reacts to heat, we may get an idea.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Misconceptions of a Programmer’s Life</title><link href="/technology/software/programming/2020/05/30/the-misconceptions-of-a-programmer-s-life.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Misconceptions of a Programmer's Life" /><published>2020-05-30T20:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-30T20:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/technology/software/programming/2020/05/30/the-misconceptions-of-a-programmer-s-life</id><content type="html" xml:base="/technology/software/programming/2020/05/30/the-misconceptions-of-a-programmer-s-life.html">&lt;p&gt;I see frequent posts from beginning programmers wondering what programming is like, and I think it’s useful to address those issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You program 8 hours a day at work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is probably the least true of all the things. Most programming jobs are maintenance jobs. The programs have all mostly been written years ago, and you are doing support, minor enhancements, bug fixes. Even if you get to do more than that, you are still not likely coding a large part of your day. It’s about meetings to decide what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, from my experience, unless you have some reason to dig deep into code (esp. if the code base is large), most people don’t bother. Our codebase is old and rickety. There aren’t comments. The business process isn’t exactly documented. I don’t want to wade through 2000 lines of Java code (per Java file) and try to understand the business behind it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless you’re working in a brand new project that needs a lot of code written (which I’ve been in), you are probably not doing a lot of programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A program is about programming&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work at a university. Students, esp. computer science students, complain about our old system that runs a “batch style” programming system. That is, the system shuts down overnight, does a bunch of data processing, and opens again in the morning. They wonder why the system can’t be Facebook or Google or YouTube, and be up 24 hours a day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I think many such people would be surprised how many people (or really, how few people) are supporting these systems. You’d think there’s a team of 20 developers doing the best they can to keep this stuff running, and it’s like a well-oiled machine, but sometimes it’s less than half a dozen people, and we barely know the software’s purpose, but can do minor fixes and keep stuff running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most software out there isn’t, as they say, rocket science. Sure, a few exceptions (say, SpaceX software). Most of the software encodes business practices, and most business practices are a weird arcane set of rules that have no basis in math or science, but is just how some company works. You write that in code, no matter how illogical it is. And often, the code, and a few old timers’ memories are what holds the project together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comments? Hah! A written business process? Hah! Programmers had one purpose: get the program to work. They didn’t think about who would maintain the code after they retired. The only saving grace was their background wasn’t so sophisticated as to create true spaghetti code (let’s use regular expressions and finite state machines and design patterns up the wazoo!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s often not the coding language (like Cobol) that prevents modernization (although it’s partly that), it’s that the business process was never formalized, and there are 100,000 lines of code no one wants to read (and only represents an &lt;em&gt;approximation&lt;/em&gt; of what the people who wanted the code wanted—and they’re retired too!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often point out the scene in the third Matrix movie where the councilman is talking to Neo about how these machines support their underground city, yet no one quite knows who built it or how it works. That’s a lot of software out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing from scratch is not such a common experience (at least, from my perspective), and even when you do, it’s not always as organized as it could be. We may call it software engineering, but most engineering involves others looking at your work, and having input into fix it. Code reviews aren’t the same thing as people inspecting a building and seeing it every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We often don’t rewrite things because the rewrite would be huge, would require a bunch of new developers, and doesn’t even have the support of the people we’re writing it for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a programmer, since I wrote the code, my opinion is the most important&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OK, so you may &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; programming, but do you know the business you’re working in? Many a programmer or startup guy thinks “You guys do something dumb, and I’m smart, so I can easily create a system that’s 10 times better than the crap you use. And you know what? I’m not even going to consult you about how the system &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; work. I’ll make up my own. You are such &lt;em&gt;idiots&lt;/em&gt;!”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, that may be, but they’re used to the system they are used to, and they’ve thought about their own (arcane) business process for a long time, and if you build something that is completely different from what they are used to, they won’t say “oh, we lack the intellect to understand your truly great software”, they’ll just not use your software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your user base is a bit older, and possibly, even if they aren’t, they will be used to doing things in a certain way. Maybe you can convince them that way isn’t smart, but if they questioned your lack of comments, your lack of coding structure, how what you wrote seems like gibberish, you might get defensive as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The point is that you’re often writing software or maintaining software by those who use the software every day. As a programmer, you might even have the luxury to walk away after you write a code, never having used the code as your users use them, and they may ultimately hire someone new who maybe pays attention to what they actually want, even if you think it makes no sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The program matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of you are learning to program. You think companies are willing to throw out a million line codebase because it’s &lt;em&gt;written in an obsolete language&lt;/em&gt;. Who’s going to write it? You? (You, Mr. Wineburg?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A million lines of code is something that could take a lifetime to rewrite. Do you plan to read the code to understand what it does? Could you even do that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any case, sometimes people think the program is king (or queen, or some elected position). It’s not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Say you’ve run this legacy program for more than a decade. It fills up tables and table of data. You, being a person who hates legacy code, wants new DB tables, and new ways of storing information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the problem. What do you do with all that old data? Oh, you want to throw it out? Start new? &lt;em&gt;Brilliant!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Every software shop is the same&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you look at the world of practicing doctors, they seem to fall (roughly) into two categories: those working in hospitals on patients that need somewhat urgent care (or are doing elective surgery), and doctors with private practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both seem to follow a similar structure, so that if you went from one personal care doctor to another, their structure would be about the same (waiting room, receptionist, files, someone to check your insurance, collect your copay). If you go get your car repaired at a mechanic, you expect a similar experience. If you go to a grocery store, you expect a similar experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People in the software industry have nothing close to this. Each company may have widely varying setups. There are companies with just one programmer that does everything. Could you run a grocery store with just one person? (Well, maybe if it’s a tiny one person operation selling very few items). Or a doctor’s office (probably not because of insurances, unless you’re some kind of boutique doctor that makes home visits, and even then, I suspect you’re hire someone to do the billing, etc).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The big companies can afford to have their own internal support structure that makes it easier for their average developer to deploy code. That support structure is often an internal thing, not an off-the-shelf, any small company can do it. If you were a car mechanic and wanted to open your own small shop, you’d probably know exactly what you need (at least, the very basics). These things probably have been (roughly) the same for decades, and even the new things, people probably generally agree on what is needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if you’re a small software shop…there’s no such standards. Do you want to use Atlassian tools? Or do you use a spreadsheet, or emails? Do you use some kind of company email? Or do you use personal email? There are lots of decisions, and it’s hardly standardized in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may think, say, version control is important. I guarantee there’s some software out there (maybe rare), that doesn’t use standard version control, and it probably does something important. And the people maintaining it may not even understand what version control is and why you need it. I’m serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s like going to a surgeon with a bottle of whiskey and a bowl of leeches and they say “What’s anaesthetic?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’ll rewrite everything!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I know engineers, they love to change things–Dr. McCoy, Star Trek: The Motion Picture”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the 1990s, the skill most programmers needed? The ability to read other people’s programs. Most early programmers could write code, but they really had a hard time &lt;em&gt;reading&lt;/em&gt; code, so they were almost always complaining that you needed a complete code rewrite to write that code in a way they could understand, without realizing the irony that the next programmer would want to throw away their code, and write it from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joel Spolsky, who used to blog many years ago (Joel on Software), used to say rewrites were basically evil. A functioning codebase should have been tested many times and many bugs have been removed. A new codebase will introduce new bugs and will be buggy. Software engineers aren’t that good about creating bug-free code (after all, what is a bug? are there specs?). He said it’s better to refactor to improve the code than to rewrite, but most developers like the feeling of an albatross of code off their neck that they don’t care about bugs they introducing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New code is wonderful!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But realistically, you need to know what you’re building, and knowledge of the ins and outs of a programming language doesn’t help you figure out what it is you’re building. And sometimes your experts also want to control the kind of software you’re writing (mostly from a usability standpoint).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I only have to understand a programming language&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many self-taught programmers think “it’s all about learning a programming language”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some complain: why do I need to know HTML? Why do I need to know CSS? Why do I need to know SQL? Why do I need to know version control? Why do I need to know Github? Why do I need to know math? Why do I need to know business? Why do I need a deploy system? Why can’t someone else test my code? Why do I need a bug tracking/task tracking software? Why do I need to read my emails? Why do I need to update my tickets?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hard enough for most of you to learn a programming language. But it’s often the tip of the iceberg. To support web programming, many programming languages have a web framework, and sometimes those web frameworks do a lot of magic, to “help you out”, and now, you thought you understood how a programming language works, but you don’t. (We used &lt;em&gt;annotations&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll love how it’s not crufty like the rest of Java!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You don’t program hours a day unless it’s brand new software, and even then.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You’ll probably spend as much time in meetings (if you get to be important enough) than programming.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There are generally two kinds of developers that survive in a company/organization that’s been around a while: those with strong technical skills, and those that have been around long enough to understand how things work (business-wise) even if they lack the technical chops. Sometimes (rarely), they are the same person.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You don’t need to know computer science that well to write software that basically works, esp. if you know the business well. A lot of software may require only basic math skills and some understanding of how the web works. It’s sort of the equivalent of a doctor that learned how to doctor online, and only learned 10% of what they should. They may still be able to heal most basic things, but not be able to do some other basic stuff. We don’t trust that in doctors, but in software, it might be OK.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Knowing the business is often at least as knowing the software, possibly more important.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Your customers likely don’t want you to make “improvements” to their software, esp. those that you didn’t bother to consult them with.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Most people tend to do maintenance programming, not green field (brand new) coding.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You often have to teach yourself newer technologies. Your senior developers aren’t usually willing to be teachers and teach you from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Communication skills are useful, but most developers became developers because they prefer to work alone. This doesn’t always lead to good software, no matter how skilled the person is.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You shouldn’t think you’re writing code for yourself, but for the next person that has to maintain it. Don’t be too clever. Someone else will have to deal with your code (and it could be you, two years later). Maybe write some comments or something.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Software can be developed in all sorts of ways, many not approaching “best practices” (which seems to change all the time). Not everyone is on the cutting edge (see New Jersey Cobol programs for filing unemployment). Being on that edge requires chasing a moving target that most companies think is a waste of time (why does Spring keep coming out with new versions–haven’t they figured it out by now?). This means that there is no typical way software is developed. Yes, many companies share similarities (they have a Wiki, they use Jira, they use Bitbucket, they have a deploy system, they do code reviews), but it’s not universal.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Your code is often not reviewed as much as it should, and you might get defensive about the comments you get.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Code consistency helps (if you can tell who wrote the code based on stylistic choices, that may not always be the best thing).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Credit:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/learnprogramming/comments/gtcwn4/the_misconceptions_of_a_programmers_life/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/learnprogramming/comments/gtcwn4/the_misconceptions_of_a_programmers_life/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I see frequent posts from beginning programmers wondering what programming is like, and I think it’s useful to address those issues. You program 8 hours a day at work This is probably the least true of all the things. Most programming jobs are maintenance jobs. The programs have all mostly been written years ago, and you are doing support, minor enhancements, bug fixes. Even if you get to do more than that, you are still not likely coding a large part of your day. It’s about meetings to decide what to do. Also, from my experience, unless you have some reason to dig deep into code (esp. if the code base is large), most people don’t bother. Our codebase is old and rickety. There aren’t comments. The business process isn’t exactly documented. I don’t want to wade through 2000 lines of Java code (per Java file) and try to understand the business behind it. Unless you’re working in a brand new project that needs a lot of code written (which I’ve been in), you are probably not doing a lot of programming. A program is about programming I work at a university. Students, esp. computer science students, complain about our old system that runs a “batch style” programming system. That is, the system shuts down overnight, does a bunch of data processing, and opens again in the morning. They wonder why the system can’t be Facebook or Google or YouTube, and be up 24 hours a day. First, I think many such people would be surprised how many people (or really, how few people) are supporting these systems. You’d think there’s a team of 20 developers doing the best they can to keep this stuff running, and it’s like a well-oiled machine, but sometimes it’s less than half a dozen people, and we barely know the software’s purpose, but can do minor fixes and keep stuff running. Most software out there isn’t, as they say, rocket science. Sure, a few exceptions (say, SpaceX software). Most of the software encodes business practices, and most business practices are a weird arcane set of rules that have no basis in math or science, but is just how some company works. You write that in code, no matter how illogical it is. And often, the code, and a few old timers’ memories are what holds the project together. Comments? Hah! A written business process? Hah! Programmers had one purpose: get the program to work. They didn’t think about who would maintain the code after they retired. The only saving grace was their background wasn’t so sophisticated as to create true spaghetti code (let’s use regular expressions and finite state machines and design patterns up the wazoo!). It’s often not the coding language (like Cobol) that prevents modernization (although it’s partly that), it’s that the business process was never formalized, and there are 100,000 lines of code no one wants to read (and only represents an approximation of what the people who wanted the code wanted—and they’re retired too!). I often point out the scene in the third Matrix movie where the councilman is talking to Neo about how these machines support their underground city, yet no one quite knows who built it or how it works. That’s a lot of software out there. Writing from scratch is not such a common experience (at least, from my perspective), and even when you do, it’s not always as organized as it could be. We may call it software engineering, but most engineering involves others looking at your work, and having input into fix it. Code reviews aren’t the same thing as people inspecting a building and seeing it every day. We often don’t rewrite things because the rewrite would be huge, would require a bunch of new developers, and doesn’t even have the support of the people we’re writing it for. As a programmer, since I wrote the code, my opinion is the most important OK, so you may know programming, but do you know the business you’re working in? Many a programmer or startup guy thinks “You guys do something dumb, and I’m smart, so I can easily create a system that’s 10 times better than the crap you use. And you know what? I’m not even going to consult you about how the system should work. I’ll make up my own. You are such idiots!”. Well, that may be, but they’re used to the system they are used to, and they’ve thought about their own (arcane) business process for a long time, and if you build something that is completely different from what they are used to, they won’t say “oh, we lack the intellect to understand your truly great software”, they’ll just not use your software. If your user base is a bit older, and possibly, even if they aren’t, they will be used to doing things in a certain way. Maybe you can convince them that way isn’t smart, but if they questioned your lack of comments, your lack of coding structure, how what you wrote seems like gibberish, you might get defensive as well. The point is that you’re often writing software or maintaining software by those who use the software every day. As a programmer, you might even have the luxury to walk away after you write a code, never having used the code as your users use them, and they may ultimately hire someone new who maybe pays attention to what they actually want, even if you think it makes no sense. The program matters Many of you are learning to program. You think companies are willing to throw out a million line codebase because it’s written in an obsolete language. Who’s going to write it? You? (You, Mr. Wineburg?) A million lines of code is something that could take a lifetime to rewrite. Do you plan to read the code to understand what it does? Could you even do that? In any case, sometimes people think the program is king (or queen, or some elected position). It’s not. It’s the data. Say you’ve run this legacy program for more than a decade. It fills up tables and table of data. You, being a person who hates legacy code, wants new DB tables, and new ways of storing information. Here’s the problem. What do you do with all that old data? Oh, you want to throw it out? Start new? Brilliant! Every software shop is the same If you look at the world of practicing doctors, they seem to fall (roughly) into two categories: those working in hospitals on patients that need somewhat urgent care (or are doing elective surgery), and doctors with private practices. Both seem to follow a similar structure, so that if you went from one personal care doctor to another, their structure would be about the same (waiting room, receptionist, files, someone to check your insurance, collect your copay). If you go get your car repaired at a mechanic, you expect a similar experience. If you go to a grocery store, you expect a similar experience. People in the software industry have nothing close to this. Each company may have widely varying setups. There are companies with just one programmer that does everything. Could you run a grocery store with just one person? (Well, maybe if it’s a tiny one person operation selling very few items). Or a doctor’s office (probably not because of insurances, unless you’re some kind of boutique doctor that makes home visits, and even then, I suspect you’re hire someone to do the billing, etc). The big companies can afford to have their own internal support structure that makes it easier for their average developer to deploy code. That support structure is often an internal thing, not an off-the-shelf, any small company can do it. If you were a car mechanic and wanted to open your own small shop, you’d probably know exactly what you need (at least, the very basics). These things probably have been (roughly) the same for decades, and even the new things, people probably generally agree on what is needed. But if you’re a small software shop…there’s no such standards. Do you want to use Atlassian tools? Or do you use a spreadsheet, or emails? Do you use some kind of company email? Or do you use personal email? There are lots of decisions, and it’s hardly standardized in the industry. You may think, say, version control is important. I guarantee there’s some software out there (maybe rare), that doesn’t use standard version control, and it probably does something important. And the people maintaining it may not even understand what version control is and why you need it. I’m serious. It’s like going to a surgeon with a bottle of whiskey and a bowl of leeches and they say “What’s anaesthetic?” We’ll rewrite everything! “I know engineers, they love to change things–Dr. McCoy, Star Trek: The Motion Picture” Back in the 1990s, the skill most programmers needed? The ability to read other people’s programs. Most early programmers could write code, but they really had a hard time reading code, so they were almost always complaining that you needed a complete code rewrite to write that code in a way they could understand, without realizing the irony that the next programmer would want to throw away their code, and write it from scratch. Joel Spolsky, who used to blog many years ago (Joel on Software), used to say rewrites were basically evil. A functioning codebase should have been tested many times and many bugs have been removed. A new codebase will introduce new bugs and will be buggy. Software engineers aren’t that good about creating bug-free code (after all, what is a bug? are there specs?). He said it’s better to refactor to improve the code than to rewrite, but most developers like the feeling of an albatross of code off their neck that they don’t care about bugs they introducing. New code is wonderful! But realistically, you need to know what you’re building, and knowledge of the ins and outs of a programming language doesn’t help you figure out what it is you’re building. And sometimes your experts also want to control the kind of software you’re writing (mostly from a usability standpoint). I only have to understand a programming language Many self-taught programmers think “it’s all about learning a programming language”. Some complain: why do I need to know HTML? Why do I need to know CSS? Why do I need to know SQL? Why do I need to know version control? Why do I need to know Github? Why do I need to know math? Why do I need to know business? Why do I need a deploy system? Why can’t someone else test my code? Why do I need a bug tracking/task tracking software? Why do I need to read my emails? Why do I need to update my tickets? It’s hard enough for most of you to learn a programming language. But it’s often the tip of the iceberg. To support web programming, many programming languages have a web framework, and sometimes those web frameworks do a lot of magic, to “help you out”, and now, you thought you understood how a programming language works, but you don’t. (We used annotations, you’ll love how it’s not crufty like the rest of Java!) Conclusions You don’t program hours a day unless it’s brand new software, and even then. You’ll probably spend as much time in meetings (if you get to be important enough) than programming. There are generally two kinds of developers that survive in a company/organization that’s been around a while: those with strong technical skills, and those that have been around long enough to understand how things work (business-wise) even if they lack the technical chops. Sometimes (rarely), they are the same person. You don’t need to know computer science that well to write software that basically works, esp. if you know the business well. A lot of software may require only basic math skills and some understanding of how the web works. It’s sort of the equivalent of a doctor that learned how to doctor online, and only learned 10% of what they should. They may still be able to heal most basic things, but not be able to do some other basic stuff. We don’t trust that in doctors, but in software, it might be OK. Knowing the business is often at least as knowing the software, possibly more important. Your customers likely don’t want you to make “improvements” to their software, esp. those that you didn’t bother to consult them with. Most people tend to do maintenance programming, not green field (brand new) coding. You often have to teach yourself newer technologies. Your senior developers aren’t usually willing to be teachers and teach you from scratch. Communication skills are useful, but most developers became developers because they prefer to work alone. This doesn’t always lead to good software, no matter how skilled the person is. You shouldn’t think you’re writing code for yourself, but for the next person that has to maintain it. Don’t be too clever. Someone else will have to deal with your code (and it could be you, two years later). Maybe write some comments or something. Software can be developed in all sorts of ways, many not approaching “best practices” (which seems to change all the time). Not everyone is on the cutting edge (see New Jersey Cobol programs for filing unemployment). Being on that edge requires chasing a moving target that most companies think is a waste of time (why does Spring keep coming out with new versions–haven’t they figured it out by now?). This means that there is no typical way software is developed. Yes, many companies share similarities (they have a Wiki, they use Jira, they use Bitbucket, they have a deploy system, they do code reviews), but it’s not universal. Your code is often not reviewed as much as it should, and you might get defensive about the comments you get. Code consistency helps (if you can tell who wrote the code based on stylistic choices, that may not always be the best thing). Credit: https://www.reddit.com/r/learnprogramming/comments/gtcwn4/the_misconceptions_of_a_programmers_life/</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Chinese Communist Immaturity</title><link href="/2020/05/29/the-chinese-communist-immaturity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Chinese Communist Immaturity" /><published>2020-05-29T20:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-29T20:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/05/29/the-chinese-communist-immaturity</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/29/the-chinese-communist-immaturity.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/newamericadotorg/original_images/Xi-Wanghuning_CpKfWnj.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long long ago, when President Radhakrishnan visited China, Chairman Mao greeted him, shaking his hand, President patted on Mao’s cheeks, embarrassing Mao. Though Mao was embarrassed, Radhakrishnan was all smiles as though he had met a child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideologies of these two countries can’t be more different. One killed people to gain it’s current state, another countries leader was prepared to die for freedom and not kill or harm its occupiers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India seem to have a magical soul, this country valued conscious life so much that most in this country are vegetarians. Not so long ago even before my home kolams were put using rice flour to feed ants, non vegetarian in my home is rarely eaten, things are changing though any way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right from my family culture I can tell you, we were implicitly trained never to be immoral, not to exercise our power over the weak, never to get seduced by wine, women, wealth. None told us, but if I just look at my ancestors way of living and if I see how much respect they commanded in society it speaks a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Chinese have that kind of morals too. They had Confucius, Tao, and others advising on the right and moral way of living, their beliefs and religion is as old as ours, they long for moral and spiritual knowledge and copied our Buddhism. But in a mad rush to show to the world that they are becoming a global power they have lost it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is a multiparty state with many voices, China is a single party state which wish to have just one voice, one brain and one thought. India has never invaded another nation despite enduring many, China today threatens India, Hongkong, Taiwan, Philippines, Vietnam to name a few. It has simply lost the art of coexistence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indian Chinese border has nothing but barren and inhospitable land, yet both countries spend millions trying to control it, such is the height of immaturity. India is nation that respects all religions, but China says religion is poison and actively destroys it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though we have seen escalation of violence against Muslims and Christians in India after BJP came to power, it no way comparable to China where entire Muslim province in the west has prison grade security, possibly their population will be controlled slowly and their numbers will not rise and dwindle. Very similar to the case of Tamils in Srilanka.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now after Corona, China has slipped to a new low. Xi Jing Ping came to power saying that China will be become great under him. Now we see how he handled Corona, though it has been contained in China, it let the virus spread to the world. Rather than taking responsibility of letting the virus out and silencing people of science and asking sincere apology, China simply wants to show the world how powerful it is and divert the attention of its people from Xi’s failures. That’s why we see aggressive moves against India, that why we see aggressive stand against Hongkong, though I must admit Hongkong is a integral part of China. That’s why China is beating if war drums, just to divert attention from truth and protect Xi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;India Should Not Be Afraid&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India should not be afraid of China a bit. If we really start to loose a war we can nuke them, yes it’s suicidal, but that’s what we have to do. We simply cannot and should not loose out to these mad guys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if conventional war starts, the worlds confidence in China would reduce a lot. The world is really pissed off by China, by the way it treated the crucial information it must have shared with the world, and it’s censorship of the scientific community. If India could raise the last billion in the war, we simply can outlast China, though with enormous losses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China has got lot to loose if it looses the war. It won against us in 1962, but lost in 1967. It then lost almost all wars it fought, even once it fought with tiny Vietnam. China could loose Tibet, the Muslims of China would demand autonomy given a chance, Hongkong might become like Kashmir and demand freedom, and the dream of Invading Taiwan will vanish. Plus China will loose its aquatic territories it is occupying by bullying it sea neighbors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel the good strategy is prepare for war, if it starts escalate it, and escalate soon to conventional missile war, then even if we still loose, make it a nuke war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support Modi Idiot if War Happens&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If war happens we must support the government we have, no matter what regrets we have about him (the idiot who supports a religion that tells to eat cow dung and drink cow urine). Yes he has led us into financial ruin, he is doing idiotic tasks like opening up the nation amid Corona pandemic rise, but compared to living under the Chinese communist, BJP is far better. But once we have won, and Tibet and Taiwan are liberated, then we can demilitarize Indo-Tibet border and use the savings to build nation (provided our politicians then are not corrupt).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Silku Smitha’s home should be converted to a memorial</title><link href="/india/politics/tamilnadu/aiadmk/jayalalitha/2020/05/22/silku-smitha-s-home-should-be-converted-to-a-memorial.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Silku Smitha's home should be converted to a memorial" /><published>2020-05-22T16:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-22T16:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/politics/tamilnadu/aiadmk/jayalalitha/2020/05/22/silku-smitha-s-home-should-be-converted-to-a-memorial</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/politics/tamilnadu/aiadmk/jayalalitha/2020/05/22/silku-smitha-s-home-should-be-converted-to-a-memorial.html">&lt;p&gt;Today I heard the news that Jayalalitha’s home will be converted to a memorial. I truly wonder why a proven criminal need to have one? Every person has two faces they say, I don’t know how true it is, but even if Jayalaitha’s another face was the C.M face, I don’t think she is a person who deserved to lead a state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were times when traffic were blocked in the road just because this idiot wants to go for walk. We all know that her subordinates behaved like her slaves even in public. For her adopted son’s wedding, entire Chennai came to a stand still. She was all show even when she was in power. After all a show girl who looted our nation is now going to have a memorial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her character was also not good, many times, to tap in the sentiments of people, she has claimed that she was sexually assaulted, one of the claims I remember was she claimed that governor Chenna Reddy, a highly respected guy misbehaved with her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-SyLGborBuWg/TisJstm2EgI/AAAAAAAAAxY/523cbvkadTc/s1600/7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take Silku Smitha for that matter, she has made more hearts of youth throb than compared to Jaya. Has better fan base. She might not have looked so beautiful as Jaya, but she compensated with her professionalism and acting. Jaya may be a highly professional actor, but when it comes to politics she is an absolute failure. Many decisions she took looked foolish and like Tuglak she had to reverse many of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though Silk was a glamorous and soft porn actor, her character was never questionable. She did not become a C.M to cheat and loot people. No court has said she was a criminal. Unlike Jaya who wanted people to fall at her feet, Silku treated all equally as far as we know. However it must be noted that Shakila claims negative aspects about Silk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silk was so famous and has a better and cleaner soul than Jaya. Then why not her home be converted to a memorial for people to remember for ever? Why this society wants to remember criminal Jaya?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today I heard the news that Jayalalitha’s home will be converted to a memorial. I truly wonder why a proven criminal need to have one? Every person has two faces they say, I don’t know how true it is, but even if Jayalaitha’s another face was the C.M face, I don’t think she is a person who deserved to lead a state.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Some useful gems for Ruby on Rails</title><link href="/programming/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/2020/05/21/some-useful-gems-for-ruby-on-rails.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Some useful gems for Ruby on Rails" /><published>2020-05-21T11:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-21T11:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/programming/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/2020/05/21/some-useful-gems-for-ruby-on-rails</id><content type="html" xml:base="/programming/web%20development/ruby/ruby%20on%20rails/2020/05/21/some-useful-gems-for-ruby-on-rails.html">&lt;p&gt;Some useful gems I use in almost all Rails applications&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/basecamp/local_time&quot;&gt;local_time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - An relatively older gem and stable, but this is a gem that includes a view helper and javascript helper to display relative time (i.e. ‘updated 2 minutes ago’)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/plataformatec/devise&quot;&gt;devise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Devise is still the go-to gem for authentication in most Rails apps. Its ease of use and existing features make it dead-simple to add authentication. For those looking for a simpler gem with a smaller footprint, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/binarylogic/authlogic&quot;&gt;Authlogic&lt;/a&gt; gets a runner up in this list for authentication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/collectiveidea/interactor&quot;&gt;Interactor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - When you start to follow the Service Object pattern, adding Interactor can help guide your context and result of those objects through a common interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/RolifyCommunity/rolify&quot;&gt;rolify&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CanCanCommunity/cancancan&quot;&gt;cancancan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Rolify allows us to assign roles such as User or Admin then CanCanCan will enable us to take those roles and apply authorization policies. However, there is a case for &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/varvet/pundit&quot;&gt;Pundit&lt;/a&gt; for those who like the Policy Object approach’s simplicity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ankane/lockbox&quot;&gt;Lockbox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - When you need to encrypt data in your database for compliance or even client security, Lockbox makes it very easy to do. Working with plenty of types out of the box, such as most database types, other Rails tools(ActiveStorage), and third-party gems(Shrine).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mperham/sidekiq&quot;&gt;Sidekiq&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - This is &lt;strong&gt;the gem&lt;/strong&gt; when it comes to running asynchronous tasks. Sidekiq is backed by Redis and has been long supported by the ActiveJob Rails abstractions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/kaminari/kaminari&quot;&gt;Kaminari&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - A simple yet powerful approach to adding pagination into your Rails applications. In many places, it is as simple a few drop-in changes, but can be used to on anything from ActiveRecord collections to plain Arrays. It also has templates to be used in many of the most known CSS frameworks such as Bootstrap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/stuyam/bootstrap-email&quot;&gt;Bootstrap Email&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Take the guesswork out of email design and CSS inlining inside of Rails Mailers. This gem allows you to use Bootstrap-like HTML structures, use a Bootstrap like design, and inline the CSS to work in most email browser/apps. Quite the timesaver!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/RubyMoney/money-rails&quot;&gt;money-rails&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - This will help standardize around common issues found when calculating money as well as providing a few template helpers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/MiniProfiler/rack-mini-profiler&quot;&gt;Rack Mini Profiler&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Everyone should know what their application is doing and where it is spending its time. This gem adds a profiler to the development pages and can include some nifty flame graphs when you really want to dig into the data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/rspec/rspec-rails&quot;&gt;rspec-rails&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/thoughtbot/factory_bot_rails&quot;&gt;factory_bot_rails&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/colszowka/simplecov&quot;&gt;simplecov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - I personally like to use RSpec over the default Rails test framework. Though, the community can be quite divisive on testing tools! With every test suite, I include FactoryBot to easily spin up objects for those specs and SimpleCov to dig into my test coverage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ryanb/letter_opener&quot;&gt;letter_opener&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Still my #1 gem for working with email in a Rails app. In your local development, it catches the outgoing mail and opens in a browser, rendering it as it would an email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/lostisland/faraday&quot;&gt;Faraday&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jnunemaker/httparty&quot;&gt;HTTParty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - When I am looking to handle an extensive HTTP API or system, I will reach for the infinitely configurable Faraday. Still, when there are only a few HTTP interactions needed, HTTParty is super simple to use to make HTTP calls.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Some useful gems I use in almost all Rails applications</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A very simple fix to low quality of Engineering</title><link href="/2020/05/20/a-very-simple-fix-to-low-quality-of-engineering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A very simple fix to low quality of Engineering" /><published>2020-05-20T21:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-20T21:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/05/20/a-very-simple-fix-to-low-quality-of-engineering</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/20/a-very-simple-fix-to-low-quality-of-engineering.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Indian-Engineer.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an Engineer, a Software Engineer, but I studied Electronics and Communication engineering in my college. When I came out of my college and even now, I don’t know how to solder a diode to a PCB, or to fabricate a PCB. My college Panimalar Engineering was a spoof. It did have good teachers, but some politics threw them out. One of the HOD even said to us, “here we need to be afraid of rowdys who are punes now, as they report about us to the management”. That is, it’s said that when Jeppiar was a hand of MGR and was a liquor kingpin, he had lot of rowdies under him, then after MGR’s death they started these colleges and these rodys were made as punes and they spied on staff and students. In fact we were literally living in North Korea. Naturally we got vexed and threw our brains into trash and just obeyed the management as zombies. Our 4 years which should be a sweet memory are years which we don’t want to think about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just because of these features, many colleges are technically incompetent. They are started by non engineer’s, people who have never practiced as engineer in the field and who doesn’t now what engineering is. Most are started by politicians who want easy money to run their parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These people naturally give headache to tech bosses like us, say we have a low budget project, we naturally tend to get the brightest and least experience person, we feel that new people out of college might be good after some training, but something happens in college that makes a person dumber than he was in his 8th std, college graduates come out really dumb, I don’t know why. It looks like even I managed to gain more knowledge under North Korean regime than these people who come out now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an engineer I was and am terribly upset, I had no solution or fix for it. But now I have found it out.  If the Tamilnadu government passes as a law it would be great, else colleges which say they provide quality education can take up on themselves and do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solution is this. Say you get a fees of 1.5 lakhs per year to train a student, then let’s say that you get fees of Rs 6 Lakhs in 4 years. Lets say that the student has finished the college, give the student 1% of the total fees collection every month as compensation till he gets the job, So a student who is out of job after finishing the college for 3 moths would have earned a minor compensation of Rs 6000/- per month, that is Rs 18000/- in total.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a student claims that he has got a job, then his degree certificate could be given to him, from that date on he can never claim any amount from the college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Tamilnadu government can force this upon colleges if it cares about it’s students rather than being a slave to rich barons. They possibly can even tell colleges to start an EPF kind of account called the non employment fund (NEF) to which colleges must pay it so that the student could draw it. India can even force online coaching websites to pay students compensation as well, or such sites could be marked fishy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel Engineering colleges that are truthful, and that have confidence in them and are serious about their quality will surely take up such idea.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A strategy to destroy religion</title><link href="/2020/05/16/a-strategy-to-destroy-religion.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A strategy to destroy religion" /><published>2020-05-16T09:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-16T09:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/05/16/a-strategy-to-destroy-religion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/05/16/a-strategy-to-destroy-religion.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/religion_is_poison.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is engulfed in blind faith, the time I write now, even during the time of dire crisis, there are more people who swear by the existence of gods, satan’s, spirits and other supernatural forces, than those who believe in free thought, exploration of ideas, finding out truth by experimentation. There is a group in India which claims that Corona is false, and your illness are not caused by viruses. It’s a bane on this society that such groups are protected by law too. I feel those people should be put as frontline workers in Corona treatment centers without any protection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During any crisis, blind faith surges, people think god is teaching us the lesson for our immorality and for badness in humanity, they never think why such a mighty force cannot create a uncorruptible humanity? But during this Corona crisis something has changed, data indicates that more people are following science, learning about virology and facts than calling their priests and spirits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are too many humans on this planet too, most of them only worth their dead meat, most humans are parasites too that are protected by law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to put a strategy to fellow rationalist around the world, a way to destroy religion. If our theory that religion makes humanity inefficient and makes it go in a wrong way is right, then religion is a self destructive force. We have proof for it, we have Brahmins in India who have made that country into their slaves and unproductive nation for at least 5000 years. Islam has banned the eating pork which would have fed millions in middle east thus ending hunger for many, the war between India and Pakistan is based on the notion that Islamic people and Hindu’s cannot live together. The list goes on and on. Billions around the world have been made miserable, inefficient and have even been slain by religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand people who have followed science have grown. Edison did not say oh god shed light so that I can see in the dark, he worked and found the light bulb, Samuel Morse did not sit and meditate so that his thoughts transmitted to brains on other side of the world, he seriously invented telegraph using kind of scientific methods. The result, we got a world that could work into night even when the god made the sun disappear, we got a closer humanity when god separated us by huge distances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel that we rationalist should ignore religious people, they are bound to get inefficient, bound to fail, and bound to follow science if they wished to survive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very good example can be found in India, where despite corona, a sect called Takrit-E-Jamat held Islamic meetings in Delhi, most of them got infected with virus, those people when faced with serious life and death situation did not run to their imams and pray to Allah for medicine to appear before them, they approached hospitals. Similarly a South Korean christian group almost surrendered after their meetings led to huge spread of Corona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today a mother carrying her dying child doesn’t run to temple, rings the bells and prays to god, she runs to a doctor who’s works are scientific. We have signals in junctions and proper education for the public to read and understand signals rather than a amman statue or vinayakar statue that in theory should keep a junction uncongested and smoothly running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As rationalism progresses, humans are giving up their wrong beliefs, these people are rationalist without them knowing it, it’s like people who drink milk calling themselves vegetarians, these people call themselves god and blind faith believers without knowing they truly trust science and rationalism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the way to defeat religion is progress, as a person following scientific way progresses, humans who are in blind faith and wants to improve will naturally shed his or her beliefs and would join us knowingly or unknowingly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vizag people won’t get Justice</title><link href="/india/capitalism/politics/corruption/andhra%20pradesh/vizag/2020/05/08/vizag-people-won-t-get-justice.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vizag people won't get Justice" /><published>2020-05-08T09:48:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-08T09:48:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/capitalism/politics/corruption/andhra%20pradesh/vizag/2020/05/08/vizag-people-won-t-get-justice</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/capitalism/politics/corruption/andhra%20pradesh/vizag/2020/05/08/vizag-people-won-t-get-justice.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://1000logos.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/LG-Logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am personally against India having so much population, I feel we must do all we can to reduce it, we humans are there everywhere like flies, but being a human it’s was hard to watch people falling down like dead flies in Vizag due  to chemical leak in L.G factory. It raises lot of doubts in me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is an establishment that has harmful substance in it, then why were residential buildings popped around it? Or how was the factory given permission to be established in residential area? Will the government officials be found out, their property be ceased and will they be hanged?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shouldn’t people of a place know about a factory that has harmful chemicals? Why the people never knew that there was a factory that had harmful chemicals? Why there was no education about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will L.G people be arrested and be hanged for mass murder? Or will the authorities will blame on Corona emergency to get off?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will people of India realize that they won’t get justice in Vizag mass murder as they haven’t got justice in Bhopal gas tragedy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will people of India realize that there is no difference between Congress and BJP. The only difference is one party demolishes mosques and kills Muslims and Christians?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a question I should ask myself: Why write blog, mostly my countrymen are utter fools to be corrected, when will I realize that?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A glimmer of hope for Alagiri</title><link href="/gossip/corruption/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/2020/05/02/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-alagiri.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A glimmer of hope for Alagiri" /><published>2020-05-02T14:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-02T14:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/gossip/corruption/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/2020/05/02/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-alagiri</id><content type="html" xml:base="/gossip/corruption/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/2020/05/02/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-alagiri.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2a/The_Union_Minister_of_Chemicals_and_Fertilizers%2C_Shri_M.K._Alagiri_briefing_the_media_on_%E2%80%98100_days_agenda%E2%80%99_of_the_Ministry%2C_in_New_Delhi_on_June_26%2C_2009.jpg/1200px-thumbnail.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I think a news circulated that Joy Alukkas owner died in middle east possibly due to Corona. The fact is some other guy called Joy Arakkal died there. Just imagine how happy Alagiri, a son of Karunadhi would have felt if he even heard this fake news, and thought it was true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story/gossip goes like this Joy Alukkas was about to open a branch in Madurai, before the day of opening, government officials there dug a trench before it claiming they have to do some corporation work there. It seems that Alagiri had asked bribe from them, they had refused to pay, so he decided to teach him a lesson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon it was said that top rowdy’s close to Alagiri came to know that an assassination team has been formed to finish off Alagiri, and it will take place before the opening of Joy Alukkas next day. The person who planned this was Dawood Ibrahim, a friend of Joy Alukkas, the gossip even goes that Dawood had invested in Joy. Confirmed the news was real Alagiri surrendered, the roads were mended, and Joy Alukkas opened as though nothing had happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also said that its because of this the DMK leadership was shaken and ultimatum was given to Alagiri by Dawood that he must not even dream of entering into any kind of politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just imagine who was Alagiri, the unshakable in Madurai, Stalin was nothing before him, we did not even know about Kanimozhi or something like that existed, and imagine how he fell almost because of no reason. Yes Alagiri’s men burned journalist in Dinakaran’s office which was part of DMK group, but I don’t think that would have contributed to his fall. I don’t think DMK or AIADMK value lives of people working in their party or in the businesses in which they have invested. A good threat by a terrorist would have shaken them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why I feel they don’t value life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine Stalin’s friend, he dies all of a sudden and people say it’s cyanide poisoning, looks like key witnesses in 2G case too have died in similar way by consuming cyanide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine Jayalaitha’s case, looks like some employees in Kodanadu died in mysterious accident. DMK and AIADMK are regimes which are no different from Noth Korea’s Kim dynasty, it’s we who people who think they are enemies and vote for one now and vote for other then. They are very clear in how to loot us and are super successful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why dont you avoid Joy Alukkas?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t buy gold. It’s because I believe gold has no value and is only worth to build toilets, but yes gold is a valuable element to scientist, it’s inert nature finds use in space science and in electronics because of its conductivity, but think whats the use of buying it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Economically as a storage Gold is good, but to convert currency into Gold and back to currency is a big process, plus they won’t give you the market value if you sell it back, I think you have to be a big trader for that. Better consider bitcoin which is mathematically secure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please research how people are treated in gold mines, and since there could be terrorist who are investors in these jewel shops, why fund them to kill us? Please think.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trivandrum</title><link href="/kerala/trivandrum/information%20technology/work/life/2020/04/26/trivandrum.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trivandrum" /><published>2020-04-26T14:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-26T14:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/kerala/trivandrum/information%20technology/work/life/2020/04/26/trivandrum</id><content type="html" xml:base="/kerala/trivandrum/information%20technology/work/life/2020/04/26/trivandrum.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/f/f0/Technopark_Trivandrum_Ariel_View_June_2014.jpg/1200px-Technopark_Trivandrum_Ariel_View_June_2014.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, I have thought to write this blog for some time, but now I think I have got some time for it, this is a guide for Tamils who want to work in Tech sector in Trivandrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trivandrum-is-not-cheap&quot;&gt;Trivandrum is not cheap&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first was about to goto Tribvandrum, my friends said that Trivandrum would be a cheap place. No it’s not. For example the P.G I stayed called Lotus PG, even to offer a 50sqft of space, they charged me Rs 5500/- per month, and guess what there is no hot water, the hall is empty without furniture, there are no plates in P.G to eat food got from Swiggy etc. The restaurants and food are not cheap too. They are as pricey or more costly than Tamilnadu. Maybe the guys over here have figured out that I.T people will pay any thing they ask for and hence are charging like hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food-is-not-of-good-quality&quot;&gt;Food is not of good quality&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The quality of food around technopark is not good enough. I had food poisoning twice in a month, almost all in my team had it. In fact people in my team were eating so called home cooked meals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-too-many-psychos&quot;&gt;Not too many psychos&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I have noted about Kerala is that there aren’t many psychos. For example in companies like Francium, Trumatics, Zanec, Kaaylabs etc there are psychopathic people. Mostly the boss or the second in command to him. But in Kerala I haven’t found it at least in the I.T industry. Somehow the company I consult for seems to have very nice HR’s to very nice Tech team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Keralites have a laid back life style, modest ambitions and know how to live life and not to fall into the rat race traps we have fallen into. Perhaps they don’t take loans, don’t do expensive spending like going to malls, buying gold, eating lavish food etc. The brains of Keralites seems to be good, far better than compared to Tamilians, or perhaps I am not in Kerala long enough to have noticed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;language&quot;&gt;Language&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Tamils have been spoiled by Banglore I think, every where you go in Banglore there is Tamil, we Tamil’s want Mangolians to speak Tamil if we goto Ulanbattar. I think Tamils went to Banglore and killed all the Kannda speakers (I think we really did that in Chola period), but Kerala is different, I did not understand a thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over here if some one calls you H.R it means not that they thought you are H.R of a company, but they had asked you if you need pickle for Briyani. If you say side dish, none knows a thing, you must say curry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kerala people speak like Tirunelveli people, words coming out rapidly, if you deconstruct them, some of it will be pure Tamil words which we do not speak now. They also remember some Tamil festivals like Aattukal Pongal which has got to do something with Kannagi, we Tamils have lost that festival though Kannagi is Tamil (possibly she lived before Tamil and Malayalam split).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like Tamil’s who feel inferior to people speaking good English, Kerala people feel so. I ask why? What’s wrong with Malayalam or any other language? They must feel proud of speaking Malayalam, they must use their time to grow their language and come out of this English subjugation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are some how okay with Hindi, we Tamils hate it. But imagine our stupidity, we said Hindi is not ours, but we have embraced English because we want to progress in Science and Tech and in Economics, but haven’t we Tamil’s let English rule us now? See the Germans, Japanese, Chinese, all these people speak their native and excel in these fields.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tamilian-food&quot;&gt;Tamilian Food&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be I’m a foodie and hence I am enjoying the taste of Kerala, but still it’s different. Once I thought potato with poori was bland, I fished out a green chili in the potato curry and bit to to give spice, and guess what? It was bland. I couldn’t believe it. Apart from few moments I enjoyed Kerala food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over here Briyani is not our Briyani, perhaps Kerala muslims are not Mughal muslims, they might have been descendants of Arbian people who traded with India’s western coast. Compared to ours I did not find Kerala briyani as exciting to put it mildly. And there is this thing called Kappa Briyani, when I ordered it, I thought it was a side dish, it looked like beef curry, I ordered parotta, fished out the beef and ate with it. Turns out that topica is a big crop in Kerala and it’s called Kappa and they make Briyani out of it, and according to us Briyani should have rice not kappa! My goodness, for the sake of heaven don’t order it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But other Tamils over here kinda hate the food here. They goto great lengths like employing cooks at their homes, going to Tamil Hotels that are far away etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is parota all the time, I love wheat products, but Tamils need rice, and that too the rice variety that originated from Tanjore, or a Tamil would not sleep that day if hadn’t had that rice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then for veggies, there is a brahmin in my PG who found it very difficult because in all hotels in Kerala you get beef. A Tamil Hindu will not go near it, Even Tamil Muslim and Christian would prefer mutton instead of beef. So if you are strict non beef eater it’s difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even the so called vegetarian Hotel Arya’s in VSSC road serves egg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ethnicity&quot;&gt;Ethnicity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps lot of Keralites in Tamilnadu may have white skin tone, but in Trivandrum, the people are like us. Walk in street, you would feel that these people are us. Not a bit different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you might know it’s Kerala if you see a woman wearing just blouse and lungi, that’s not common here in Tamilnadu, or perhaps the color veshti that’s worn in Kerala by men might give you a hint. But these people are just us, no different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;terrain&quot;&gt;Terrain&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No wonder we named them Malayalis, the people who are in the hilly region, almost every time you will be going up and down the hill. For a Chennai-ite like me, its very different, I realized I was livung in plains only after going to Trivandrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had lot’s of hills around Chennai too, but many have been mined off for gravel, in Kerala there are still hills and forests, looks like these people more respect their terrain and nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;size-of-it&quot;&gt;Size of I.T&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The size of I.T industry in Kerala is very tiny, people say entire Technopark even when doubled will fit into Mepz, Tambaram. And Mepz is just one small portion of Chennai’s I.T industry. Kerala is looking for slow and limited growth, not a mad rush toward globalization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are coming to Trivandrum in a hope of starting with a company and hoping to jump to neighboring building or next I.T park with a 30% hike, may be that won’t happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cheating-cab-and-auto-drivers&quot;&gt;Cheating cab and auto drivers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh damn, even if you order a cab from Uber the drivers ask for money over the metered rate. Over here too the auto meters don’t work and they demand 20 - 25 rupees a kilometer. So I better walk. If perhaps Corona did not interfere I would have got a bicycle to visit beach or library or for office commute every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My office is at a top of a hill, it’s good and bad. Good because it gives me exercise everyday, and bad because of the same reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;connectivity&quot;&gt;Connectivity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trivandrum is well connected to Kaniyakumari, Tirunelveli, but Chennai is really long, if you are okay with air travel, then Chennai is well connected too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually Chennai people are far different from rest of Tamil people, so if you try to find Chennai-ites in this city, you will be at a loss.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>