<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-04-16T07:22:21+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Another admission of defeat for Windows</title><link href="/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Another admission of defeat for Windows" /><published>2018-04-16T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/04/16/another-admission-of-defeat-for-windows.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.wallpapersafari.com/38/59/PYHvQk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Windows is slowly but surely giving way to GNU Linux. Linux’s desktop share is just
above 2%, but on the Internet scale GNU Linux rules. All computers that power our
Internet are critical systems and they run Linux. Most mobile phones use Linux
as Android. Many people who use Amndroid never know they are Linux users and
they vocally oppose using Linux on their desktops!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Microsoft is not as foolish as the people who use its OS. Looks like many
engineers on the M$ know that defeat of Windows is imminent, and they are giving
their way slowly ao that it would not look like a humiliating defeat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First is M$’s Azure. It offers Linux on its servers, and I bet there are more Azure 
instances that run Linux than Windows. Recently I had a problem with Windows.
In my office we use Python as we are a data science company, one of my coworker
had a problem in running a flask app. It worked perfectly on my system which was
and Ubuntu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a little bit investigation it was evident the way that the way Windows OS
functioned was a problem. I had an irrational resistance for installing GNU Linux on
her computer, but it was clear the resistance was irrational. There is a way to
combat irrationality, let the irrational people finish stuff. Work stopped and
fortunately for me, the person realized loss in productivity and it was the only
the way to go ahead, so I installed GNU Lubuntu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wondered if Windows was such a crap system, why are developers using it?
Are CTO’s around the world gone nuts? Haven’t they seen such a problem? But then
to my amazement, I found that Windows 10 now allows Linux subsystem to be
installed in it! Its not as good as full GNU Linux at your disposal, but rather
than fighting the free software community, M$ has recognized Linux which once it
famously called as the toy OS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like a Spartan phalanx Linux is advancing, though M$ is doing all it can to stop
Linux, it seems not enough. As more and more developers pour in to develop Linux
during their free time, M$ simply does not have the budget to win such a war, and
they know it really well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many economic theorist will be confused to  know that a capitalistic organization
is bowing to a communal force thats not interested in making a buck. Well, we
don’t know if the Universe is infinite, but we are sure that human stupidity is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/wsl/install-win10&quot;&gt;Install the Windows Subsystem for Linux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sharpen your axe</title><link href="/2018/02/25/sharpen-your-axe.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sharpen your axe" /><published>2018-02-25T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-25T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/25/sharpen-your-axe</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/25/sharpen-your-axe.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://panasian-hk.com/image/data/Product/Handtool/Hammer-and-Axe/Axe/3240_1-1_4_lb__felling_axe_tekton.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its was in  a project named places.com, a real estate website, I was into a
company called Zanec, that company had never seen Ruby on Rails, I was the first
guy into that company who knew Ruby, some how even without knowing the
technology they were holding a project possibly for 3 months! Let me come to
the point, my job was to lead a project and since I am a Rails guy I need to
provide JSON end points for front end Angular application. When I started to
work, the front end guys got frustrated with me. I was able to give API’s really
fast and I was seen slacking off most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being brought up in a culture where one is thought work is gain, they got hugely
frustrated seeing me get away with little work. They seem not to know that in Rails
automation is built into it. That makes me just a person who needs to flick a
switch to get it done. Claiming themselves as computer engineers, I failed to
see why they failed to see my automated advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next thing is happening in a company called Trumatics, where I am a partner.
We are trying to predict the sales of customer, and its just a regression problem
with little number of sample values. Though it looks complex, its just a line
of code in GNU Octave. Thats it. Fortunately Trumatics is built up of thinkers
who can listen, so things will go really smooth there :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see computers as my slave, I don’t see a point in getting frustrated about it
and working long hours in front of it. People who work for long hours before
computers look like idiots to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most computer or I.T people in India are like this: if asked to cut a tree, they
go on to cut it. They don’t mind if they have an axe, they simply don’t care if its
sharp, they just go about swinging the axe onto the trunk and they feel happy
about working a lot and feel they deserve pay for their stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many computer graduates don’t even have an axe, they just have a pen knife or
just their nails, and they work hard to fell a tree and go almost nowhere. I
concentrate on sharpening the axe and on my swing. I learn a lot, code a lot
in my mind before I physically code. I read a lot about software engineering, and
about how complex code must be structured so that it can be managed in a simple way,
I read a lot about how testing helps if you are coding deterministic programs.
Unfortunately as far as my knowledge goes, programs that change itself based on
data like A.I ones need different thought to test them. They can be tested any
way so TDD freaks need not panic :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its these sort of skills, puts me above others. Its strange to think many computer
people in India think themselves as programmers and not as mathematicians. They
seem not to know whats the difference between concurrency and congruency of a
Triangle. Its quiet pathetic. If you just know some loops, branching and think
you can survive in I.T industry, I wonder how?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not just workers who are stupids, the I.T middle management and upto the
companies CEO’s are stupid. Most companies in India put MBA’s and PMP’s who have almost no
knowledge of math and logical reasoning in their heads, as heads of project thats
based on computers which is purely mathematical and science. Its possibly due to
these reasons, our companies are not good enough.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Narendra Modi is Anti Indian</title><link href="/2018/02/24/narendra-modi-is-anti-indian.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Narendra Modi is Anti Indian" /><published>2018-02-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/24/narendra-modi-is-anti-indian</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/24/narendra-modi-is-anti-indian.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://s3.india.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/1203.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Modi is coming to Tamilnadu in order to launch a plan thats named after
Jayalalitha who is a criminal who ruled Tamilnadu for a long long time. Her band
called AIADMK which consists of murderers, theiefs, pimps, liquor makers,
rogues and rowdies still rule Tamilnadu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jayalaitha is a declared criminal asper Indian law and for a Priminster to
support her, proves that the person who is the priminster is not worth for the
job. So its better to say Narendra Modi is an Anti-Indian and we people are
foolish and corrupt to elect him as Priminster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Good news for working women in Tamil Nadu.&lt;br /&gt;PM Narendra Modi to launch the AIADMK government&amp;#39;s Amma scooter scheme today.&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/ITVideo?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#ITVideo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More videos: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/NounxnP7mg&quot;&gt;https://t.co/NounxnP7mg&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/iC9DCckU5z&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/iC9DCckU5z&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; India Today (@IndiaToday) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/IndiaToday/status/967269608964030464?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;February 24, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BJP’s double standards</title><link href="/2018/02/14/bjp-s-double-standards.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BJP's double standards" /><published>2018-02-14T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-14T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/14/bjp-s-double-standards</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/14/bjp-s-double-standards.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://tamil.oneindia.com/img/2015/06/08-1433748608-tamilisai-soundararajan46-600.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its funny how blatantly foolish BJP people are, and yet the people of this nation
have made them our leaders. BJP is a party that has admitted openly that it
fooled people to get to power. Look what it told to people, it claimed ‘if we
are voted to power, we will deposit a sum of 15 lakhs into each and every Indian
account. this would be done by getting by money looted from our nation and
that’s sashed in Swiss banks’. So after 4 years of power and just a year more
for BJP to fall, we are all 15 lakhs richer apart from our earnings! Are we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is not about that. This blog is to say how BJP is openly showcasing
ts double standard in Tamilnadu. I blogged about the shameful event of opening
a criminals portrait in Tamilnadu assembly. To my surprise, BJP a party that
respects law says it not wrong! Thats what Tamilisiai the BJP president here
says. But wait, if Jayalalitha ruled Tamilnadu and hence its not wrong to honor
her even though she is not a criminal, Tippusultan who ruled Mysore so well,
of course not all he did wasn’t right is unrecognized by BJP, why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very similar thing can be seen how BJP likes new politicians emerging in
Tamilnadu. Rajini is a good guy, Kamal is bad. Both have the same history!
Both just talk and move in front of screen and say what they do it art. What
else? Even Shakeela does it, but its much more better!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason is very simple. BJP is not worried about good or bad, or who will
be a better ruler or who is more eligible or who has more moral, its all about
who obeys Hinduisms idiotic ideology more. Thats it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;Reference&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/02/11/a-shameful-day-for-tamils.html&quot;&gt;A shameful day for Tamils&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/07/Why-not-Shakeela-become-next-Tamilnadu-CM.html&quot;&gt;Why not Shakeela become next Tamilnadu CM?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A shameful day for Tamils</title><link href="/2018/02/11/a-shameful-day-for-tamils.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A shameful day for Tamils" /><published>2018-02-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/11/a-shameful-day-for-tamils</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/11/a-shameful-day-for-tamils.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static.bengali.news18.com/static-bengali/2016/12/jayalalithaa1-630x420.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow 12th of February 2018 will be a very shameful day for all Tamils in
India. This day will prove that we are utter fools and have misused a great tool
given to us by Independence. We have elected such a government that will
inaugurate a picture of a convicted criminal in our assembly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short this proves that we have elected a gang thats such audaciously so
criminal and such dumb minded they don’t even realize that they are
inaugurating a picture of criminal in assembly and they don’t seem to realize
its wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jayalalitha is a criminal, she is a goon and thats been proven in court. If at
all we must allow her picture to be hosted in assembly, then it must be proven
that she is innocent. Dumb ass Edapadi and Paneerselvam are so so fools they
don’t even know to respect law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we don’t realize its wrong, no force in this universe will be able to save
us.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Heroku still makes money?</title><link href="/2018/02/02/how-heroku-still-makes-money.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Heroku still makes money?" /><published>2018-02-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/02/02/how-heroku-still-makes-money</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/02/02/how-heroku-still-makes-money.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://logz.io/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/heroku-logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wonder how Heroku makes money? According to me, Heroku does just one
thing, it makes deploying apps easy. Thats it. But there are other solutions if
you sweat a bit, and they makes it much easier and cheaper than deploying on
Heroku. One such thing is Capistrano-rails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder why so many Rails and other app developers are so lazy in buying
prepackaged solutions, when just a little knowledge of Linux is all thats enough
to set up your own deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its strange to me. If you really think Heroku is easy, one must give a try for
capistrano, if one has not done it, most probably that companies tech guys or
CTO is a fool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;Reference&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coderwall.com/p/ttrhow/deploying-rails-app-using-nginx-puma-and-capistrano-3&quot;&gt;Deploying Rails App with Capistrano&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Factual Beliefs</title><link href="/2018/01/28/factual-beliefs.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Factual Beliefs" /><published>2018-01-28T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-01-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/01/28/factual-beliefs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/01/28/factual-beliefs.html">&lt;p&gt;India obtained its independence is a a fact, but is India independent? If you say
yes thats a belief. Right from the processor I use on the computer I type and
the processor you use on the phone or what ever devise you read this article is
un-Indian. Most of us in the tech and tech based industry, in fact any industry
that is based on computers, rely heavily on foreign help for money. If they
say no, we are simply dust and economy would collapse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why then we think we are independent? Why we think there is God, though none has
sensed it? If we say we had sensed it, why we take our children to doctor and
not to a temple when there is a fever?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why we think these beliefs are fact? The reason is Human mind is flawed. For
example take my mind. Some of my muslim friends introduced me to Briyani, I
still love it, and they worship god, and I reject it. Why so? I should have
loved God too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When some one does something good to you, dopamine level in your brain
increases, this is registered by your brain that that person is a good one and
not that  his thought and action at that time was good to you. You perceive
that person has done good to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next time, that person might say something stupid, like God exists, but
since you have registered that person doing good to you, you natrually think
this too is good to you and you accept it without question as a fact. Though
this is a belief, since you trust that person, you consider this as a fact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any society, including rationalists, operate on factual beliefs. Its woven into
our brains. Even if you think you are out of this belief system, that thinking
could be a belief which you have not recognized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can one come out of this belief system? 100% no chance, but if you debate
intensely with other intelligent and within yourself (given that you are not
highly stupid), then you can to a certain degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One may ask why people fail to come out of these factual beliefs? Its simple,
we humans are social animals. We have survived because we relied on one another,
this bond is as strong as lunar cycles interfering in our sleep patterns,
possibly far far stronger than that. We trust others because we not only
benefited from others facts, but we got their trust by believing in their
beliefs. If we did not, that person would have thought we are stupid and would
mistrust us and we would loose socially. But there are few brave who stand for
facts. Its too be seen weather humanity is intelligent enough to believe them.
Historically they (the intelligent and humanity) have lost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason that one would not believe in facts is due to convenience. If
you are in India, its better to bribe an government official and get things
done and ruin your grand children’s future than you suffering a set back and
making your grand children’s future bright. People are not that intelligent
and shrewd enough to put right things to action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way its great to be on Earth and study this humans and universe, wonder when
this belief would be broken.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">India obtained its independence is a a fact, but is India independent? If you say yes thats a belief. Right from the processor I use on the computer I type and the processor you use on the phone or what ever devise you read this article is un-Indian. Most of us in the tech and tech based industry, in fact any industry that is based on computers, rely heavily on foreign help for money. If they say no, we are simply dust and economy would collapse.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why not Shakeela become next Tamilnadu CM?</title><link href="/2018/01/07/Why-not-Shakeela-become-next-Tamilnadu-CM.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why not Shakeela become next Tamilnadu CM?" /><published>2018-01-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-01-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/01/07/Why-not-Shakeela-become-next-Tamilnadu-CM</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/01/07/Why-not-Shakeela-become-next-Tamilnadu-CM.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-v9ZC06t1R-E/UazjzJSKcUI/AAAAAAAAAzI/rPjZlnq9tac/s1600/shakeela.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am wondering why not Shakeela become the next Tamilnadu C.M. I feel she has
got all the qualities. She has been doing exceptionally good and things to
Tamilnadu’s youth as its described by actor Vijay here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OSzlvFqhIM8?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well here are my points why she must become the Tamilnadu CM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Huge Fan Following&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shakeela has a huge fan following, more than what M.G.R had and more
than Rajini and Kamal combined. The youth love her more than Rajini and Kamal.
Well, I know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not an Tamil&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If its fate of Tamilnadu not to be ruled by a Tamil, then why ruled by a ugly
looking non-Tamil than spectacular Shakeela?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Huge Assets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Election is all about having assets and sharing them at the right time to win
people’s hearts. Shakeela has sure more assets than Karunanidhi and Sasikala
family and she knows when and how to share them to win peoples heart’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big Heart&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This needs no explanation, but Tamils like C.M with big heart and a C.M who
is transparent and open. Who can beat Shakeela on that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good friends with Neighbours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tamilnadu is in conflict with neighbouring states due to water sharing and many
other issues. Shakeela is an actor who is popular there too. So the youth
of our neighbors will realize sharing is caring and would share their stuff
with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ignorance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its the fate of Tamilnadu to have politically ignorant people as C.M. Any actor
can jump in then why not Shakeela?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well people what do you feel? I think it would be great if Shakeela becomes the
C.M. It will really get the youth interested in politics and prove glamor weighs
more than logic and truth.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Traffic police in Medavakkam are pathetic</title><link href="/2018/01/01/traffic-police-in-medavakkam-are-pathetic.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Traffic police in Medavakkam are pathetic" /><published>2018-01-01T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-01-01T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/01/01/traffic-police-in-medavakkam-are-pathetic</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/01/01/traffic-police-in-medavakkam-are-pathetic.html">&lt;p&gt;I have to drive through Medavakkam every day, and for past two weeks or more the
traffic police in Medavakkam are doing a pathetic job. They simply are not
regulating traffic, but just letting users determine when they must drive through
a junction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought the police were not present because they need to go and stand and
salute a politician who travels from point A to B in city. Politicians like
to be saluted by police a lot and one single politician here in Tamilnadu could
pull away 1000’s of police for such duty so that he feels powerful and great
about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing the politician says is he is threatened by anti nationals and
terrorist and his or her life is in danger, but the truth is terrorists and
Pakistanis won’t touch these people as ISI (Pak’s terror intelligence network)
knows that Indian politicians cause more damage to India than all terrorist in
this world combined. Terrorist have no way to escape law as they are uncorrupt
and admit to what they do and they don’t have any money to bribe officials
to get legal immunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way coming back to Medavakkam. I avoided bumping into vehicles and inched
my way and crossed the junction, and just after ten meter drive I saw a cop in
shade enjoying his days collecting bribes from motorist. What the hell?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cop’s in Medavakkam junction collect bribes from all commercial vehicles. They
just corner these vehicles and expect bribes from any where from Rs 50/- to Rs
500/-, once bribed the vehicles are let go. They do the same with motorcyclist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be no force that could stop them. Well collect bribes, India can
never be a uncorrupted nation. But once you collected bribe of Rs 1000/- at-least
divert traffic for an hour. Or pay some to divert traffic say Rs 150/- an hour
and you stay in  a shaded corner and collect bribes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish these cops are punished, but which cop in Tamilnadu is been really
punished for looting people?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I have to drive through Medavakkam every day, and for past two weeks or more the traffic police in Medavakkam are doing a pathetic job. They simply are not regulating traffic, but just letting users determine when they must drive through a junction.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I don’t wish people</title><link href="/2017/12/31/Why-I-dont-wish-people.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I don't wish people" /><published>2017-12-31T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-12-31T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/12/31/Why-I-dont-wish-people</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/12/31/Why-I-dont-wish-people.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/briyani_by_karthik_dad.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday was a great day. I felt like eating Briyani badly, one of my family
member purchased it and was on the way, then some one knocked. It was my neighbor
and what he had? Wow that was kind of unexpected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The briyani tasted great. It was delivered to us because he was celebrating his
birthday. I shook hands with him but I said nothing. Did I wish? No! One may
ask why and why I don’t wish people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well its simple. You meet a person and you congratulate because one has a
father, a mother and he is breathing. Do it to some one and see. It will look
absurd. Why? Because its natural for all person to have these. Similarly for me
its very natural to have a birthday, new year, end of the year and other
festivals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason I think its normal for a person to have a birthday, a death day,
so on and so forth. You have done nothing to deserve it. So why you need to
wish? It looks silly for me to wish people just because they are alive this new
year or this birthday. For some reason I don’t want to think that they or I will
be dead the next year so that we may not be able to wish each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a person has done something spectacular to amaze me, like some one made me
great briyani or a chicken soup which my wife makes (that bowls me down) I am
ready to congratulate them at that instant. Other times no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yday I had two briyani’s at a time and a food coma. Thanks for that if you
are my neighbor and read this.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>