<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-04T18:20:27+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Wish people had astronaut level psychology</title><link href="/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wish people had astronaut level psychology" /><published>2020-10-04T18:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-04T18:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/10/04/wish-peopl-had-astronaut-level-psychology.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/91/Bruce_McCandless_II_during_EVA_in_1984.jpg/720px-Bruce_McCandless_II_during_EVA_in_1984.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any thing can kill you in space within minutes, even in times of stress you need to be calm. There was a knock at our gate today, our ex-driver it was. He seems to have had a safari near our home and dropped by, one of us engaged him outside the gate and rushed to the bathroom to have a bath, the conversation lasted 15 minutes I think. The people, and even families who worked with us seems to love us and seem to have extreme loyalties crossing generations, but does that warrant foolishness?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chanakya said its not enough to be wise and intelligent, one must also avoid staying around fools. If one is around fools, their intelligence would be wasted. Think of what is happening here, the Church is open, stupid parents drag their kids to it, parents are taking kids to Tirupathi, I haven’t noticed mosques, but just today morning I saw a family of jam packed Muslims (our neighbors) in a car traveling from somewhere to our area. Pathetic. Not even in nightmares I have encountered a situation where I sould be in a place where I would be sourrounded by fools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are in a midst of an pandemic, I wish people reading this have the knowledge to look about it in the dictionary. People know it’s a pandemic and they invent reasons to travel, to mingle! I can’t imagine how stupid we are as a society. If those people who are idiots die I am okay, but if they spread virus around knowing or unknowing, that’s a bloody crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish schools one day start training people about psychology, about logical thinking, about staying calm during situations like these, possibly staying calm during one’s death too. I wish we had astronaut level of psychology training so that we don’t invent reasons to be a fool.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How I Make My Curses Work?</title><link href="/2020/09/30/how-i-make-my-curses-work.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I Make My Curses Work?" /><published>2020-09-30T23:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-09-30T23:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/09/30/how-i-make-my-curses-work</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/09/30/how-i-make-my-curses-work.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/5b/Statue_of_Kannagi.jpg/665px-Statue_of_Kannagi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my friend won’t buy a music player, he will listen to his music from his mobile or laptop, the reason? He is afraid that if he buys it he will die in a month because I gave the curse to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very long ago, one of my friend called and told me a business move that was selfish and annoyed me, I cursed him that since I can’t have my breakfast in peace, he won’t be able to have his breakfast today. Few minutes after that while he was boiling his tea a lizard jumped into it. Seeing the boiling lizard he said he wasn’t able to eat properly for a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My in-laws did very bad stuff to me, they boasted I was alone and they had 25 people in their family trained against me, kind of Mahabharat ratio 1:25, I cursed them for their wrong doing, as far as I know 2 people dies within 4 - 6 months and they were visibly shaken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my former boss did not treat me well, she amassed his wealth for her children and threw me out of job with framed reason, now none of her children are alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have got a reputation of getting my curses work. And how I do it? I am a rationalist and don’t believe in curses, but I do curse people which automatically comes out of my mouth. The reason they work is as good as Mohammad Azrudding winning most of his tosses, just pure luck. What else could it be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I do do is when something wrong happens to a person I had cursed, I contact them and tell them its because of the negative Karma they earned against me had got them into this trouble. This fixes in their mind, it’s a small world and word gets around that this guys wrath and word happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes it could be the case where just because I curse some one when they are really bad, and they know about their ill doings, their subconscious works to punish them. Like deaths in family. Say some one in your family is dying, you must do all you can to stop it, but your subconscious mind says you have done a bad thing and hence you must endure a loss rather than do all it takes to save the life, perhaps the you rather than to put in work and thought freeze thus loosing a person. Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But once I curse I forget about it. That’s it. That person is my friend again and I have almost nothing against him, I just wish things would go right, but seems that the word runs in their mind and they associate it with evil things that happens in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Experience/Advice from a 10+ year data scientist</title><link href="/2020/09/09/experience-advice-from-a-10-year-data-scientist.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Experience/Advice from a 10+ year data scientist" /><published>2020-09-09T09:36:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-09-09T09:36:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/09/09/experience-advice-from-a-10-year-data-scientist</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/09/09/experience-advice-from-a-10-year-data-scientist.html">&lt;p&gt;For context, I was in most people’s shoes here so this is why I want to give back some advice and inspiration. There’s a bit of misinformation in this subreddit so I’ll consolidate my thinking. DM me if you need specific advice&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Been working in quant/data science for 10-11 years now. Didn’t know where to go because this field didn’t exist when I was in school.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Self-taught. This is where my imposter syndrome appears but little did anyone know this. Learned SQL through sqlzoo, learned R as a hobby to day-trade (yahoo-finance api, zoo package, etc.), Python through codeschool(?) or codeacademy(?) in 2012 (it was free back then), Math through OCW/torrented whitepapers &amp;amp; textbooks, ML through whitepapers &amp;amp; textbooks (coursera did not exist yet)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Interviewed around a lot and got rejected a lot (100+). When I first began, this was not a field, but the interview process &amp;amp; rejections gave me grit and understand what to study. I interviewed for a lot of exciting startups (now public companies) before they were even big. A small hedge fund gave me a chance as a quant trader, and our group got shut down in a year. I got a second chance somewhere else and the company went public (data science was central to their strategy)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Data Science is exciting. This field has brought me around the world. Worked at a hedge fund, electricity markets, global consulting, somehow ended up doing A.I work, and now in a leadership strategy role. I don’t oversee data scientists anymore, they mostly report to my business function now but previously managed 20+ data scientists. Worked all over the globe and across many, many states.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advice:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Study and code everyday. Make it a habit. Blog posts, whitepapers, textbooks. I’ve lost this habit and I regret it – getting back into it. You should love learning, otherwise you’re in the wrong field.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Build up your foundations. Python/R, Probability/Stats/Calculus/LinAlg/DiffEq, Algorithms. This will help you understand a lot . Do take an algorithms &amp;amp; design course. Most problems are solved through a design approach / framework rather than a model.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Stay in touch with whats going on. hackernews/datatau/rweekly &amp;amp; understanding new Data Engineering trends, Tech Engineering Blogs. Example, when I read some company blog about their implementation of spark in 2014, I immediately started playing around with it with my models.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Always be humble &amp;amp; prepare to get humbled but remain self-confident and determined. Don’t be afraid.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Find a subject you like to get started. Loving data &amp;amp; modeling is one thing, but find an area that really interests you. For me, I started with time series (not for the faint of heart). This introduced me to a lot of difficult concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Find a product/field. For me it was Energy &amp;amp; Finance. It can be marketing, sales, finance, pure ML, pure optimization work, supply chain, etc. Being a general hobbyist will only get you so far.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, Data science is not all SQL. It depends on how close you are to the revenue generating side. If you’re making a quarterly report on demand, that isn’t data science. If you’re building growth models to accelerate users on your platform that tie to scale and revenue. SQL will get your dad but still have to come up with model&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taken from:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/iorbjg/experienceadvice_from_a_10_year_data_scientist/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/iorbjg/experienceadvice_from_a_10_year_data_scientist/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">For context, I was in most people’s shoes here so this is why I want to give back some advice and inspiration. There’s a bit of misinformation in this subreddit so I’ll consolidate my thinking. DM me if you need specific advice</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Life Of An Indian</title><link href="/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life Of An Indian" /><published>2020-08-27T08:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-27T08:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/caste/2020/08/27/life-of-an-indian.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/life_of_an_indian.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I don’t bet on gold?</title><link href="/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I don't bet on gold?" /><published>2020-08-18T21:12:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-18T21:12:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/08/18/why-i-don-t-bet-on-gold.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://dailytimes.com.pk/assets/uploads/2018/04/29/today-gold-prices-in-pakistan-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of my friend, Indians of course are stumped by why I don’t bet on Gold. There are two simple reasons for that, first I still expect to live another 50 years, and I still plan to have a family and leave my values and wealth behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the exact reason why you buy gold isn’t it? It will have a exchange value even 50 years from now? The answer is no. Gold will be as cheap as iron and other materials will become throw away cheap. Why? See this video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/y8XvQNt26KI?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speed at which SpaceX is going ahead with starship, the innovative ideas that other startups are coming up like 3D printed rockets like Relativity Space, it’s going to get very easy to reach orbit and back to earth. From orbit we have ion propulsion powered by solar in inner solar system and technology like powerball nuclear reactors in external system from Mars onwards. This will make enable us to bring and park asteroids near Earth and mine it’s resources and make even gold dirt cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.teslarati.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/BFR-2018-spaceship-and-booster-sep-SpaceX-2-crop.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup with the speed of human innovation, I think this will happen sooner than later. So let’s see. So definitely saving your wealth in the form of gold for your grand kids won’t work. In Napoleon’s table cutlery was made of very precious metal called Aluminum which was much costlier than gold, we now use it to make plates and pots for jail inmates because it’s so cheap now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;References&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.spacex.com/vehicles/starship/&quot;&gt;Starship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.relativityspace.com/&quot;&gt;Relativity Space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ion_thruster&quot;&gt;Ion Thruster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/nuclear-power-balls-triso-fuel/&quot;&gt;Powerball&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://x-energy.com/reactors/xe-100&quot;&gt;Xenergy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Silencing Prashanth Bhushan - Supreme Court Destroys India</title><link href="/india/justice/2020/08/15/silencing-prashanth-bhushan-supreme-court-destroys-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Silencing Prashanth Bhushan - Supreme Court Destroys India" /><published>2020-08-15T10:12:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-15T10:12:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/justice/2020/08/15/silencing-prashanth-bhushan-supreme-court-destroys-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/justice/2020/08/15/silencing-prashanth-bhushan-supreme-court-destroys-india.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1c/Prashant_Bhushan.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Prashant Bhushan - The Victim&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hardly surprising in an ultra orthodox religious rule that the justice system fails. It was by suppressing free and fair justice, extremist like Hitler came to power, and only in a similar way Modi can attain full control of India. In my mind there is no doubt he will become the dictator monarch of India and will destroy the nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today the supreme court is testing the waters. They are seeing how the nation would react if we bring clamp down on free speech. A very prominent lawyer Prashant Bhushan has tweeted facts about judges of supreme court, and he being a person who can bring out the truth, he tweeted with undeniable evidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fSlzBd26atc?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the judges had some moral left in them, they should have resigned and begged the nation to forgive them, but just like any other banana republic, people in power want to harass those who question their wrong doing. And since this stuff is exposing the amassing of wealth by BJP people, the government will back the judges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is only the first step. But I feel the soul of India is already destroyed. A nation tolerant to stuff, and nation that can listen to any one, and a nation that should think with common sense is no more. Just few months back a channel called Karuppar Kootam was banned because it made comments about Hinduism. Hindu’s couldn’t tolerate it, Muslims were afraid they were next to be questioned, Christians would have been alarmed too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For stupids to survive, say the BJP, RSS, any religion, cults etc, you should stifle common sense, free thought and free opinion, and India is well on way to evolve back to darkness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/what_is_fascism&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Prashant Bhushan - The Victim</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Time to fight back Hindi colonialist once again</title><link href="/2020/08/14/time-to-fight-back-hindi-colonialist-once-again.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Time to fight back Hindi colonialist once again" /><published>2020-08-14T09:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-08-14T09:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/08/14/time-to-fight-back-hindi-colonialist-once-again</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/08/14/time-to-fight-back-hindi-colonialist-once-again.html">&lt;p&gt;I saw this video on youtube&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4FSZPJAdBtU?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like this fucking Amith shah is trying to impose something on us, possibly Hindi. It’s time to get our adrenalin pumping and fight those northern colonialists once again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The North has always fancied conquering the South for long. If you take Ramayanam, its about a victory of an unworthy destitute from northern India over a fine ruler who ruled the South. Finally the Telugus, Mughals conquered us, and no wonder and the British did conquer us too. In fact people of Chennai and wealthy community of India, who were fed up by Mughals aided the British with wealth in conquering us. But at no time we lost our language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the Telugu (Kalappar) conquest, we lost our old Tamil script and moved to new one. This was refined during Periyaar times as we needed something to take advantage of the modern printing press, no longer we need to write on palm leaves, so we can leave out squiggly like characters that appear in languages like Malayam to Burmes which were formulated to be written on tender leaves. But all the time Tamil was Tamil. It’s even said that if Thiruvaluvar popped into existence today, he would understand what we speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tamil had a grammar and reached perfection state (செம்மொழி) even like 5000 years ago. We eliminated imperfect pronunciations like sha, ha, gha, ish, long ago, possibly even before Prakrit came into being, possibly we could have done it in Mesopotamia (modern Iraq) where we got our first written form. Yes cuneiform is a Dravidian script, it was called Tal (தள்), which means push in Tamil and other Dravidian language, because we pushed sticks into clay tablets to create it. Possibly Dravidians who came to India discovered their own writing very late after that. Today Hindi still has these incomplete pronunciations. Imagine the cognitive gap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we came below Vindhyas, Dravidians became very good at resisting things from north, possibly our war techniques improved. That’s why we still exists as Tamils till today. Our military might peaked in Chola period. We did not even hesitate to invade military schools in Kerala which was set to be created by Parasuraman’s disciple and was thought as invincible. Rajaraja’s invasion of these places (with ease) for spreading descent and Terrorism in Tamilnadu shocked Kerala like hell and created centuries of hate. Imagine, schools created by disciple of God been sacked like blowing dust away. Such super might, earned respect for Tamils. But we did then what Hindi people are doing to us now, we destroyed them completely and got the shit out of them and brought them to our ways. These people haven’t forgotten about it till now. Possibly that’s why Srilankan genocide was engineered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yghtSSnk1-8?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the way from Iraq to Singapore, many places have Tamil names. Just check the name of this mountain &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Sikaram&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Sikaram&lt;/a&gt;, where it is? What sikaram (சிகரம்) in Tamil means? What is the climate in Sudan (சூடு நாடு)? How is the sea shore in Eriteria (எரி கடல்)? What language isolated people in Cameroon (காமம் ஊர்) speak even today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vWyAYGlFZjk?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We find Thaayumaanavar representation in South America. Ancient ship bells in Newzeland have Tamil inscriptions on them. And these Hindi people think of imposing stuff on us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When India got independence, it was promised made to minorities that their beliefs and culture would not be touched.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/c_hd0YZlCiQ?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But look whats happening? We almost lost our Jallikattu. How many of us name our kids based on Sanskrit and Arabic names? In Dravidian culture women can worship and do pooja to God. How many temples have women priest now? We prayed to God in Tamil before. Today in marriage you don’t know if a Brahmin tells you to fuck your wife or tells the Gods to fuck her first. Yes we pay him for that. Yes it’s true that India was sexually very independent in the past, so those stuff were tolerated, and it became ultra conservative as it is now somewhere in the middle. Every religious text describes the beauty of God and Goddess and what they did in vivid detail. Indians saw these things as very normal things like we say to our friend today that we had idlis this morning. A whole section in Thirukural is dedicated for this, but won’t it be better if a Brahmin tells to the groom who would like to fuck his wife first in Tamil rather than in Sanskrit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Islamists are so bold that they demand Tamil muslims to ditch their language and pray to god in Arabic, fuck! Some how many mulims who I know feel Arabic is the way to worship God. In this regard the Arabs are no different than Aryans invaders who tarnished our culture. The funny thing is, there is no proof that prophet Muhammad existed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/j9S_xbjIRgE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do not have Tamil literature for Science, a very serious drawback. Tiny Japan has it in Japanese. Germans do their engineering and medicine in German. I should be ashamed of typing my blog in English. We have let English, another imperfect language to conquer us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will be interesting to know about this one nation one all theory. Will Amitshah admit that his father is not his father but Gandhi is his father? Because we live in one nation so we all must have one father! Will he admit Indira is his true mother, and his mother is nothing and fake? Then why he or any one can’t admit some one else is their parent, want us to admit another language in our minds. Tamil is our linguistic mother and it will always be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New Tamil Desam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would be happy and not worried if things flare up and we get our own country. Definitely we are doing far well above Indian average. We are the most urbanized state in India. Our development is homogeneous  compared to other states. We don’t have religious violence here, and people d reject caste politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we are separate nation, lot of countries will help us too. Countries like Srilanka, Canada, Australia, United Kingdom, Malaysia, Singapore, Mauritus have Tamil as their national language and may stand by our side. Our diaspora would love to see our nation lifted. Plus we can have a say weather or not we can allow people from North can make a living here, thus we can prevent our way of life from getting corrupted. We can have our kids studying for medicine and science without an external government and cultual interference and so on.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I saw this video on youtube</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">So the 5 Rafel’s are supposed to terrorize China and Pakistan?</title><link href="/india/politics/defense/rafel/2020/07/30/so-the-5-rafel-s-are-supposed-to-terrorize-china-and-pakistan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="So the 5 Rafel's are supposed to terrorize China and Pakistan?" /><published>2020-07-30T10:52:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-30T10:52:00+05:30</updated><id>/india/politics/defense/rafel/2020/07/30/so-the-5-rafel-s-are-supposed-to-terrorize-china-and-pakistan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/india/politics/defense/rafel/2020/07/30/so-the-5-rafel-s-are-supposed-to-terrorize-china-and-pakistan.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nationalinterest.org/sites/default/files/main_images/K98%20%281%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s said that IAS’s officers don’t like to work under Modi because most of their job would be to publicize what Modi has done. They despite their intelligence will be reduced to public realtionship officers. It’s also gossiped that far right Hindu groups have invested a lot in Indian news channels and have almost bought them so that they are a jaalara for Modi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the happening unfolding it looks so true. Yes India has inducted new combat aircraft after decades, but its five, thats it. Just imagine you write 5 letters in your exam paper and start dreaming of how you will become rank #1 in class, if that sounds so stupid, then this should also be stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rulers are elected to rule, to manage the nation, it’s a very very big task. If publicity is all the thing that BJP thinks, I think actress like Shakeela can talk with France to purchase nuclear power tech, defense etc and no matter what she does we will get a very free publicity and likes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rafel is a engineering marvel, no doubt. I am an engineer and I understand the difficulty the engineers would have gone through to make it work. Just imagine we had one Kalaam and he was not enough to lift up the nation, similarly even a very good weapon in small numbers is not enough to defend a country. Right now we are getting a media flood about Rafel, and I think it’s not much more than that in practicality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rafel is 4.5 generation aircraft, what ever the number means, but will the aircraft be able to run away  from very cheap set of 50 ground to air missiles launched against it? I doubt so. Even if it can escape many, imagine the pilot’s fatigue trying to mitigate say 50 missiles launched one by one against him. Russians have found ways to detect and bring down 5G aircraft’s and they are a defense based economy, and they will sell it to who ever can buy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope Modi’s government does not waste a lot of money in Rafel propaganda. Imagine if we can give Rs 10 Lakhs to some one in rural area, they can set up a small business and give employment to few. Possibly 8 of 10 business will fail, but, I hope you get my point, by consistent investment you will get things going. Imagine if Modi spends that amount giving ad’s to media, it might not help the nation so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do I think will BJP, RSS, Modi will change after me blogging like this? Definitely no. Possibly if 1000’s read it, may be ten of them will think before voting. If that person learns to think about politics, he will think about other stuff too. Possibly he or she can make others think. That’s what I hope to achieve with my blogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0mBJ0N0uj2k?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">There is obscenity in every religion and you should not know about it</title><link href="/2020/07/18/there-is-obscenity-in-every-religion-and-you-should-not-know-about-it.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There is obscenity in every religion and you should not know about it" /><published>2020-07-18T16:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-18T16:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/07/18/there-is-obscenity-in-every-religion-and-you-should-not-know-about-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/18/there-is-obscenity-in-every-religion-and-you-should-not-know-about-it.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4tcjE5gMDzI?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ever the BJP, RSS and Hindu fanatics want to ban something, then it means there is truth in that. This time it’s not just Hindu fanatics, even the Muslim fanatics want to ban Karuppar Kootam an Youtube channel that broadcasts Periyaar thoughts and their own opinion. I want to stress on their own opinion. This is unfortunately India, you have the right to say your opinion about any one, anything, it’s the duty of this nation to protect you. Or all in this nation must vote for a government that will change the constitution where free speech, thought and expression of opinion is banned. I think Modi is well on the way to do that. I also see a time where bright minds, and thinkers very soon will run away from India as they ran away from Hitler’s Germany. The fact that even Muslims are going against Karuppar Kootam is a good thing. It means these guys have the guts to do what Periyaar did not have, to go against Islam. I feel it’s Periyaars very big mistake of not going against Islam, Christianity, Buddhism, Sikhism and Jainiam. All religions are flawed and misguide people and they all must be eliminated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to obscenity in religions. All religions have obscenity in them. Lord Indra, in fact the King of God’s, just research what he did. Just check the Bible and Quoran. In it God even tells a person called Ibrahim to kill his own son. They preach child killing religions to kids even in India which wants to paint itself as a nation of peace. Funny! Today ISIS tells you to send your sons to battle in the name of God. I am sure very obscene stuff is there in Abhrahamic religions too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why they don’t want you to know?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, it’s the problem with humans. The pundits, Mullahs and Fathers have shown themselves as pure and through masses and religious gathering have interpreted a 1000 year old text in their own way. They have interpreted and modified it to suit to their public life styles. We all know how their private life’s are. Now if you look at the meaning the other way, it breaks the purity cloak in which they hide. They can no longer claim pure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those guys have made you worship stone, mad you worship a figure of Jesus that’s not at all Jesus (we don’t even know if he exists, and he could be a con man), made you believe if you offer prayer pointing in a direction it will do good. They have succeeded in making you swim on land, and they have succeeded in making you believe the religion is pure, which is not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who are the people who go against Karuppar Kootam?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not saints who have touched the non existent God are going behind this gang that exposes these stuff (of course Karuppar Kootam spice up their expose), but it’s those people who are married, impure, had and are going to have kids, those who watch midnight masala are the people who are going against this Karuppar gang. It is just to be seen if the courts will uphold the law of free opinion or give in to government and vote bank pressure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dravidianism and Aryanism</title><link href="/2020/07/11/dravidianism-and-aryanism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dravidianism and Aryanism" /><published>2020-07-11T12:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-11T12:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/2020/07/11/dravidianism-and-aryanism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/11/dravidianism-and-aryanism.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Kalaignar_M._Karunanidhi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Karunanidhi&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Karunanidhi&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know Karunanidhi could have looted and somehow escaped till last, there was another politician called R.Venkatraman who was also our president. There are no stains on Venkatraman as we know, he is so pure say like Manmohan Singh, Kalaam etc, none would even dare to think evil or try to frame up corruption against him. But this is what I heard about their families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see as government people, if there is any repair in their house say plumbing, electrical or any other civil repair, the Public Works Department (PWD) people would visit and do it, so we in the real estate would hear about them. This is what I heard about their families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/f/ff/R_Venkataraman.jpg/800px-R_Venkataraman.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;R.Venkatraman&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;R.Venkatraman&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Venkatraman’s family, if one would visit it, the worked wouldn’t even be asked if he needs water, Venkatraman family could have been a strict Iyer family, and their strict austerity would have meant that they will never mingle with workers. May be the PWD people realizing this, never even asked or dared to ask something as plain as water to drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to Karunanidhi family. If people visit there, they say they might be interrupted by his wife Dayalu Ammal or Stalins wife and will be offered coffee or something to drink. The will be invited for snack or food, the woman and daughter in law of the house that would serve them. In short though you had gone to Karuna’s home as a worker to do some task, you would be treated kind of a guest, respected as equal human. People who went there to fix things would say that how simple the women in Karuna’s home were, women sat down and used &lt;em&gt;aruva manai&lt;/em&gt; to slice vegetables they would say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the difference between Aryanism and Drividianism. In Aryanism you have created and branded yoursef as Aryan and possibly as Brahmin because you think you are somewhat superior to others just because of your birth and / or because due to grace of God. On the other side there is Dravidianism which is essentially nothing, and makes no fuss, you are just a normal human being, mingling with others as though you and they are equal. Now imagine visitors visiting these two homes, who will they like to vote for? The Congress or the DMK with Karuna championed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is also the reason many people are moving away from Hindusim in India, mainly people who belong to caste who are not treated right even today. People who belong to so called upper caste look down upon them. I don’t think the BJP or RSS would revive Hinduism, it’s Hindus themselves must realize their mistake and treat all equal. This very behavior too led to the death of Sanskrit too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prakrit was the local language talked by Indians in the North and Dravidian languages like Tamil were talked by people  in South, but Aryans wanted to be different, they want to keep themselves above all and invented an artificial language called Sanskrit which was used for nothing other than to show their superiority and maintain secrecy. Books about old Indian lives tell that even women in Brahmin homes were disalloved to speak Sanskrit because women were considered impure. Such was and possibly is their level of austerity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This also makes one thing clear, people of Aryan mindset can never fully rule India till the date Indians have rationalism and some sense of dignity left in them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Karunanidhi</summary></entry></feed>