<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-11-27T03:19:34+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why India must promote lab grown meat</title><link href="/2022/11/27/why-india-must-promote-lab-grown-meat.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why India must promote lab grown meat" /><published>2022-11-27T03:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-27T03:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/27/why-india-must-promote-lab-grown-meat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/27/why-india-must-promote-lab-grown-meat.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/53/Tandoori_chicken_laccha_piyaz1_%2836886283595%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few days ago I read in an article that FDA had approved lab grown meat for human consumption. Soon Americans will be able to eat their food without killing animals. This will start small, but will become the primary source of very cheap non-vegetarian food soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Say you want to at goats liver, say that’s the part that is in demand in your region, for that you must raise an entire goat, to access the liver you must kill it. In western world animals are killed by carbon dioxide poisoning, so they feel like they go to sleep, and they die slowly without them knowing it, but here in India we still kill animals by cutting them up, it causes pain. We as a conscious living thing want to live, but we do evil to animals even though as a human we know they experience pain when they are culled. So ethically we must not kill, but we do it, but today science has given us tool to obtain meat without killing a thing, and we must make full use of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All religions that originated in India, Jainism, Buddhism, and Sikhism, advocate not to kill animals, but for nutritional needs we kill them. Even Aryanism which first favored eating of animals like horse and cow, after entering India became a bunch of cults called Hinduism today. Most branch of Hinduism today advocates not to eat meat. Somehow this land passivized avid non-vegetarians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike Arabia and Europe, where agriculture is not as easy, Indians had mastered taming of water long ago, and we produced surplus of grain, so we were able to be empathetic towards animals and get away by drinking milk. Religions evolved here have always advocated being kind to animals and to see them as our own. Even today in many household’s rice flour is used for kolams, so that ants could feed off it and be not hungry. So our land due to is nature advocates not to kill animals and be kind to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is an environmental benefit too, say just to get say kidney of goat, you must raise the entire goat by using current practices, this requires lot of energy and time, with selective cloning, we can just grow the kidney of goat in vats with far less energy and time involved. Meat industry is one of the worst polluters and emits a lot of carbon dioxide and methane, this new technique of growing animal parts in vats will make it supremely efficient thus reducing global warming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meat that does not grow in animals which gets disease, emotional, tired, and that can grow faster in vats and in much more energy efficient way will cost less. Indians need to eat a lot of meat, we are under nourished, and we have a lot of carbs. An average Indian eats 2.2Kg of meat a year, an average American eats 140Kg of meat a year. An average Indian looks really frail compared to a guy from USA, we need to improve our nutrition. One way to do is to drastically reduce price of meat by artificially producing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeiddxklcr5ykr45fhew7hho2qzic3y36a5qvrdu5yq7vgdaqwfb2wi/Baked-bug-kabob.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Bug Kebab in Cambodia.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eating of insects too is far more efficient and more economical than eating meat. It’s naturally healthier, I with HRD ministry in India promotes insect diet too, but once again insects are conscious, have emotions, and may not want to die. But I do feel we must promote insect protein for healthier India. All over in eastern Asian countries people eat insects, why not us?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might say that Muslim community in India might eat only slaughtered meat. Let them continue with slaughter, but 75% percent of India still can enjoy ethical lab grown meat and not have the guilt of enjoying food by causing death and pain. I don’t think many Islamists in India follow strict Islam. I have seen none pray 5 times a day, my friends drink, some of them abroad eat bread (even bread in west contains lard), pork is a delicacy for them. People will change, imagine a guy watching his neighbors buy meat for ₹50/- and he need to shell out ₹400/-, definitely common sense will kick in. So I strongly feel India must promote lab grown ethical meat for all good it has in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OWRwrQI3XOY?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/M-weFARkGi4?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is this what Quran tells about women?</title><link href="/2022/11/26/is-this-what-quran-tells-about-women.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is this what Quran tells about women?" /><published>2022-11-26T17:15:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-26T17:15:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/26/is-this-what-quran-tells-about-women</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/26/is-this-what-quran-tells-about-women.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeiemfn6f2ztnxoutpbu2fjoyopn2vgt2b43qrax2g5appyg3vpipcq/is_this_what_quora_teels_about_women.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Some strange scam on Linkedin</title><link href="/2022/11/23/some-strange-scam-on-linkedin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Some strange scam on Linkedin" /><published>2022-11-23T09:01:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-23T09:01:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/23/some-strange-scam-on-linkedin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/23/some-strange-scam-on-linkedin.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeidyyiaccku4dj7w6sgp5bqgcu7x6mjrhkwcrx6uuop7lh54x64uia/Screenshot%202022-11-22%20at%201.51.28%20PM.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be some scam going on Linkedin which targets founders and investors in companies. This group seems to be tempting us with something. I received the above message which are very identical from two linked in accounts, one from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/shubham-ravindra-9360a91b7/&quot;&gt;Subham Ravindra&lt;/a&gt;, and another from a girl called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/papiya-d-3a25081b8/&quot;&gt;Papiya&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After this happened Papiya’s account seems to have disappeared. I don’t respond to these messages anyway. This blog is just to warn my fellow founders.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This man should be our Prime Minister</title><link href="/2022/11/23/this-man-should-be-our-prime-minister.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This man should be our Prime Minister" /><published>2022-11-23T07:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-23T07:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/23/this-man-should-be-our-prime-minister</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/23/this-man-should-be-our-prime-minister.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeihlqjyb6nnkdov6sowsd252zyidzz6daqihjwtthyhzbgxwpq4qli/redditsave.com_the_truth_hindustanis_want_to_say_out_loud_well-lnhd19k2ph1a1.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Not satisfied with Sithalapakkam’s Jai Biriyani</title><link href="/2022/11/20/not-satisfied-with-sithalapakkam-s-jai-biriyani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Not satisfied with Sithalapakkam&apos;s Jai Biriyani" /><published>2022-11-20T19:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-20T19:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/20/not-satisfied-with-sithalapakkam-s-jai-biriyani</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/20/not-satisfied-with-sithalapakkam-s-jai-biriyani.html">&lt;p&gt;When you take the petrol bunk left turn while you cross Sithalapakkam’s panchayat office, you will see Jai Biriyani. Biriyani there is cheap, I think it costs ₹110/-. It tastes moderate, the first time I bought the chicken was bit rubbery, possibly not cooked fully? I am not sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the second time I bought kushka and chicken 65, it cost ₹170/-, there was a small piece in kushka which excited me, the chicken 65 was deep fried, came with few pieces of sliced onion and one eighth piece of lemon. It was more enjoyable than biriyani as this time there was no rubbery chicken, but that day I had a mild stomach upset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope Jai Biriyani improves. But I don’t think I will be buying from them again. The staff over there are all Tamil, so you won’t have language difficulty, they are respectful. I hope they improve quality.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">When you take the petrol bunk left turn while you cross Sithalapakkam’s panchayat office, you will see Jai Biriyani. Biriyani there is cheap, I think it costs ₹110/-. It tastes moderate, the first time I bought the chicken was bit rubbery, possibly not cooked fully? I am not sure.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Elon Musk and my style of work</title><link href="/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elon Musk and my style of work" /><published>2022-11-20T19:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-20T19:05:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/20/elon-musk-and-my-style-of-work.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/34/Elon_Musk_Royal_Society_%28crop2%29.jpg/544px-Elon_Musk_Royal_Society_%28crop2%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Elon Musk - The evil boss you must avoid.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I push for 16 hour work week, with four-hour work days. I strongly feel that knowledge workers should have life, should spend time with their family and loved ones, think and reflect, should get new ideas. This I feel will cultivate a healthy brain and will ultimately increase productivity of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Elon Musk doing in Twitter looks very evil to me. For some reason even people of science and creativity, when they move to management, they become task masters without brains. They seem to forget where true productivity lies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are times when I finished coding for a sprint (2 weeks long one) in 2 hours, but yes all those other paper work does cost more time, but the core issue only takes two hours. There are times when even the sprint got over I haven’t started coding as the details were murky, or my understanding was not right. I understood a lot of things when I am away from keyboard, something works in your brains background while you enjoy life, all of a sudden most elegant solution pops up, and you implement it, and it works!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow management people never seems to understand it, their view of knowledge work is like viewing a repetitive work in a factory. Humans are like automated robots to them. If a robot can drive 1000 bolts in an hour, then it must drive 4000 in four hours. In my view a human or biological system is not like that. We get tired, we get energized, we sometimes find work rewarding, and sometimes boring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not worried about Twitters future, or its success or failure, I am long time user of Diaspora, I use Mastodon, and I have deleted my Facebook long ago. I am worried about the dangerous precedent Elon is setting in the I.T industry. With people like him, the industry will be populated by mindless ‘yes boss’ human bots who are there for a paycheck, than for the passion of coding.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Elon Musk - The evil boss you must avoid.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This woman is such a great stupid, BJP people would love to have her in their party</title><link href="/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This woman is such a great stupid, BJP people would love to have her in their party" /><published>2022-11-14T12:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-14T12:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/14/this-woman-is-such-a-great-stupid-bjp-people-would-love-to-have-her-in-their-party.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeictysiokuwms63ywicar2wb5qe7stgf4edaalrwil4nnvzarcmlyi/redditsave.com_tamil_should_not_be_a_compulsory_language_in-dmws7qd2ioz91.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pragamin</title><link href="/2022/11/07/pragamin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pragamin" /><published>2022-11-07T20:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-07T20:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/07/pragamin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/07/pragamin.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeicikohkfb75id5ulkphzklqdhl6vlrlika2doguph2hqbsghurimq/pragamin.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bullshit Job</title><link href="/2022/11/06/bullshit-job.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bullshit Job" /><published>2022-11-06T21:44:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-06T21:44:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/06/bullshit-job</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/06/bullshit-job.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeibxqlrrhrtuiv3mk3hnaiwm4p5ioqu7x7ji4valbecsm5x5ck3hku/bullshit_job.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vadacurry in Hotel Archana Bhavan in Sithalapakkam is good</title><link href="/2022/11/06/vadacurry-in-hotel-archana-bhavan-in-sithalapakkam-is-good.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vadacurry in Hotel Archana Bhavan in Sithalapakkam is good" /><published>2022-11-06T08:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-06T08:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/11/06/vadacurry-in-hotel-archana-bhavan-in-sithalapakkam-is-good</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/06/vadacurry-in-hotel-archana-bhavan-in-sithalapakkam-is-good.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/bafybeig3ntb2jinitbxrihvgqkmf6ftehedzf3jpo4wc56dh426kg2vsce/dosai_vadacurry.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You turn left from the Sithalapakkam Panchayat office (the petrol bunk bend) and head towards Shankarapuram, you will see a hotel called Archana Bhavan. That hotel is not good for dining, it has got not fully closed space, you need to dine almost on platform. The ambience in front of the hotel is also not good. Dog and cow shit littered before the hotel and none bothers to keep it clean. I have seen dirty pigs grazing just meters away from the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no proper running water wash basin in the hotel, you will see a sink on the platform, near that a bucket containing dirty water with food particles floating in it and a tumbler near it, that’s the water they give you to wash hands. Once I went there to dine, and seeing this I returned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is good however is their vadacurry if you get parcel of it, it costs ₹20/-. It’s nice oily and tasty. I have tried their idyappams with their vadacurry, it’s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>