<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-25T08:03:29+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Good that people are turning away from engineering</title><link href="/2019/04/25/good-that-people-are-turning-away-from-engineering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Good that people are turning away from engineering" /><published>2019-04-25T00:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-25T00:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/25/good-that-people-are-turning-away-from-engineering</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/25/good-that-people-are-turning-away-from-engineering.html">&lt;p&gt;Its good that people are turning away from Engineering. We have lot and lot of terribly bad engineers. A lot of greed from families who want to become quickly rich from their kids has spoiled a generation, and the result, like a buildings built out of cardboard, we have extremely low quality engineers all around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Market is market and it responded. Engineers today don’t get respect and they are treated like shit. Lot of people who never ever would have been interested in Science and Technology hold an engineering degree today. And they do menial jobs like data entry and get paid low, really low. I Think I saw it in reddit, a person has complained that an engineering graduate earns less than a pani poori vendor. True, very true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So as price for an engineer drops, people are moving away from it, and that’s good. Because good engineers who are passionate about their jobs will stick with it, and people who hold engineering degrees and who are not passionate about it will leave. This is a very good correction. I welcome it with a huge smile.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Its good that people are turning away from Engineering. We have lot and lot of terribly bad engineers. A lot of greed from families who want to become quickly rich from their kids has spoiled a generation, and the result, like a buildings built out of cardboard, we have extremely low quality engineers all around.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Money money money, Sulekha wants my money</title><link href="/2019/04/24/Sulekha-wants-my-money.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Money money money, Sulekha wants my money" /><published>2019-04-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/24/Sulekha-wants-my-money</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/24/Sulekha-wants-my-money.html">&lt;audio controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;/sounds/Call@0091%2089391%207(00918939178428)_20190424185841.mp3 &quot; type=&quot;audio/mpeg&quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the audio element.
      &lt;/audio&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the audio element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Banning TikTok is a violation of freedom of expression</title><link href="/2019/04/21/Banning-TikTok-is-a-violation-of-freedom-of-expression.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Banning TikTok is a violation of freedom of expression" /><published>2019-04-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/21/Banning%20-TikTok-is-a-violation-of-freedom-of-expression</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/21/Banning-TikTok-is-a-violation-of-freedom-of-expression.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.theweek.co.uk/sites/theweek/files/2018/12/tiktok.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is a democracy, which means one has got freedom of expression. One should have the right to express himself and herself in the form of text, voice, images, videos and action. And we should be okay and tolerant with it. We can ignore those expression, that’s our right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example I am an atheist living in a highly religious nation. I do get irritated and feel sorry when people worship God, and to put it mildly, God is not present. Yet we as a nation spend billions in the name of God every year, and still our policy makers have not banned this blind faith. Why? Because it interferes with the freedom of expression. Even we rationalist try to explain the stupidity of blind faith to the faithful than to lobby the government and seek a ban on God and religion. Because being a stupid is your right and expressing your stupidity is your right too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same is the case with TikTok. one can use it for entertainment to cajole himself, or one can use it to waste away his life. One can use it to share a cooking tip or a scientific experiment, or one can use it to share porn. Its ones wish. Democracy should be tolerant and should not obstruct the flow of information and should not affect ones will and ability to express in any way possible. Its unfortunate that India is not a democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Harassing China&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From being a Soviet colony, India has now become colony of the USA, so India must do something that pleases its ruler. USA is harassing China recently, like giving trouble to Huawei. USA is unable to control China diplomatically, neither China can be contained economically and it cannot be defeated militarily. Unlike India, its leaders can’t be bribed easily and hence harassment to submission could be one strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly European leaders will not obey the will of USA as they head sovereign nations,and hence USA has picked up India as one of its hit man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to use TikTok&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though you cannot download TikTok from Google app store, you can get its APK else where. Just visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://apkpure.com/tiktok/com.ss.android.ugc.trill&quot;&gt;https://apkpure.com/tiktok/com.ss.android.ugc.trill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/17/tiktok-india-bans-video-sharing-app&quot;&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/17/tiktok-india-bans-video-sharing-app&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I left Trumatics</title><link href="/2019/04/11/why-i-left-trumatics.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I left Trumatics" /><published>2019-04-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/11/why-i-left-trumatics</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/11/why-i-left-trumatics.html">&lt;p&gt;I am an Engineer and I would like to be one. An engineer is basically a scientists who applies science to do a task, most probably to make people smile, or in some case to make people weep, like in the case of weapon design. No matter what ever an engineer does there is an ethic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are ethics even for a decoit; Ben Hall for example never killed a person even though he was a decoit. He never shot a police man who came to kill him in his final hours. Weather a engineer does good or bad they must have ethics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were two ethics that were violated in Trumatics. the first, my friend Umashankar screamed at us, it was becoming evident to me that he was screaming because he was ignorant of what was going on. He wouldn’t take an effort to cure it. He wouldn’t trust us, or take in enough knowledge to cross verify what we were doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, the team, they seem to need spoon feeding and unlike adults they were quiet incapable of teaching themselves and finding things out. This made my life really difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Treating people fair, and self-learning I feel are engineering ethics. That was not been followed in Trumatics. To make the matters worst Trumatics was nodding to absurd client requirements, possibly because of money shortage, and pressure was building up in a unnecessary way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company prior to Trumatics, named Zanec was a good one, but most people left that office because of one person called Varadarajan, aka Varda. For no reason he would make lives of of people miserable. He was a natural parasite, evolution has made him that way and there was no cure. Its like telling a cholera bacteria not to cause cholera, then it won’t be a cholera bacteria at all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You just need one person to ruin the company. I don’t know from where this evilness arises, but it does. Possibly only evil humans survived and thrived and they killed the good ones, so its part of our genes. May be nothing can be done about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ben_Hall_(bushranger)&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ben_Hall_(bushranger)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I am an Engineer and I would like to be one. An engineer is basically a scientists who applies science to do a task, most probably to make people smile, or in some case to make people weep, like in the case of weapon design. No matter what ever an engineer does there is an ethic.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why vote for Congress or BJP when good blood flows in you?</title><link href="/2019/04/05/Why-vote-for-Congress-or-BJP-when-good-blood-flows-in-you.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why vote for Congress or BJP when good blood flows in you?" /><published>2019-04-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/04/05/Why-vote-for-Congress-or-BJP-when-good-blood-flows-in-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/04/05/Why-vote-for-Congress-or-BJP-when-good-blood-flows-in-you.html">&lt;p&gt;Many people I interact with say that they are either going to vote for Congress or the BJP. I ask “why?”. We know the history of these parties. In this blog I am going to say why you should not vote for any of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;promoting-killers&quot;&gt;Promoting Killers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP kills cow eaters and non Hindus, Congress killed Sikhs. Both parties promote the accused Narendra Modi and Kamalnath to higher ranks. These parties that have such a large gatherings can’t even find a single person who is true and untainted? That’s amazing!! and shows to their lack of strictness and lack of commitment. When families in our nation weep for their lost ones due to communal violence, all these parities could do is to promote the tainted up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not talking about these people winning in court. Even if they have won in court, all the parties should have done is revoke their suspension and kept them as a basic worker and no more than that. Its strange that Narendra Modi and Kamalnath are irreplaceable. Its shows that these parties are unable to find a better talent in this vast India which shows their inefficiency. Should we vote for such inefficient parties?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dynastic-politics&quot;&gt;Dynastic politics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both BJP and Congress are dynastic according to Scroll.in, in BJP 31% of its MP’s come from some form of hereditary, and in congress its 33%. Just because we all recognize Gandhi’s we tend to assume Congress is dynastic and BJP is not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again these parties are inefficient in selecting people to lead it. Rather than screening the nation and hand picking people who are truly interested in national welfare, these parties settle for the familiar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we citizens too settle for the familiar rather than screening candidates in our constituency, we will make our nation just another BJP and Congress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;same-source-of-funding&quot;&gt;Same source of funding&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both the BJP and congress, if they win will get funded by very same businesses, and they will enact laws that will benefit few oligarchic rich and will ignore us. So whats the difference?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scams&quot;&gt;Scams&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both parties are scandalous. Just because BJP ruled for only few 10+ years, their looting are less compared to around 70+ years of looting’s of congress. If we extrapolate BJP , they are nothing but congress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;zero&quot;&gt;Zero&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/this_guy_gets_it.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, Prinyka Herself admits it, and BJP didn’t deny it. The truth comes out some how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;elect-some-one-new&quot;&gt;Elect some one new&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you blind? Look around and bring some one new. Lets see what the new person does.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Many people I interact with say that they are either going to vote for Congress or the BJP. I ask “why?”. We know the history of these parties. In this blog I am going to say why you should not vote for any of them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rahul is not speaking about UBI.</title><link href="/2019/03/27/rahul-is-not-speaking-about-ubi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rahul is not speaking about UBI." /><published>2019-03-27T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-03-27T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/03/27/rahul-is-not-speaking-about-ubi</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/03/27/rahul-is-not-speaking-about-ubi.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/e/e5/Rahul_Gandhi.jpg/1200px-Rahul_Gandhi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In desperation to win votes, Rahul and Modi are coming up with lots of stuff, and they are funny. First lets look at Modi, the BJP tried to own counter strikes for Pulwama, they almost celebrated like they fed, brought up and trained Abinandhan. They created the Sardar statue, now I think its abandoned by its staff due to lack of pay. They are trying hard to bring back Nirav Modi and Vijay Mallaya back, even though these fugitives I think have contributed huge amounts to the BJP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Rahul drops a bombshell. He said families that receive less than Rs 6000/- per month will get a amount of Rs 6000 from government. Well, this is a impressive scheme, I am sure this idea never would have risen in brain dead Rahul’s mind, but rather in the mind of some intelligent guy in the Congress. But any way credit goes to Congress for thinking about this plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tough it looks impressive, we need to know how government is going to count the salary of a person who receives so less? These people operate by cash, you can’t really monitor them! How do we know that a congress worker cannot control accounts of a an entire very poor village thus he getting all this money and donating some parts of it to the party?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This scheme is different than UBI. In UBI, theoretically all people receive a basic income. Lets say that your boss for some reason has turned sour on you, and your life under him has become hell, you want to quit, but what will you do for the next month? UBI might not offer you pay as high as your salary, but you know you have a basic pay to survive. Under UBI all citizens are equal, and all must get a basic pay and all subsidies must be stopped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would be happy if the Congress or any other party proposed the UBI of Rs 1000/- per Indian per month, and not some scheme targeting specific people for votes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ruby on Rails Developer needed in Chennai.</title><link href="/2019/02/27/ruby-on-rails-developer-needed-in-chennai.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ruby on Rails Developer needed in Chennai." /><published>2019-02-27T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-27T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/02/27/ruby-on-rails-developer-needed-in-chennai</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/27/ruby-on-rails-developer-needed-in-chennai.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I run a Small company called &lt;a href=&quot;http://trumatics.com&quot;&gt;Trumatics&lt;/a&gt; in Chennai. We need a developer who can be a team lead for a team of two other trainees. The applicant should be a confident coder, and should have the skill to navigate demanding client requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be expected to be in office for 40 hours a week and give daily status updates. We expect the person to  be a full stack developer and have experience of at least 3 years of intensive coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may send your resume to ak@trumatics.com .&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello,</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Echo cancellation in Ubuntu</title><link href="/2019/02/24/echo-cancellation-in-ubuntu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Echo cancellation in Ubuntu" /><published>2019-02-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/02/24/echo-cancellation-in-ubuntu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/24/echo-cancellation-in-ubuntu.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-same-origin allow-scripts&quot; src=&quot;https://peertube.xtenz.xyz/videos/embed/f3c9a4f8-f89e-44d9-bfe6-5c84d6360011&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">சைவம்</title><link href="/2019/02/22/%E0%AE%9A%E0%AF%88%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%AE.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="சைவம்" /><published>2019-02-22T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-22T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/02/22/%E0%AE%9A%E0%AF%88%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/22/%E0%AE%9A%E0%AF%88%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%AE.html">&lt;audio controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;/sounds/saivam_Feb 16_9_37_PM.mp3 &quot; type=&quot;audio/mpeg&quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the audio element.
      &lt;/audio&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the audio element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Donald Trump is an Idiot</title><link href="/2019/02/07/donald-trump-is-an-idiot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Donald Trump is an Idiot" /><published>2019-02-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/02/07/donald-trump-is-an-idiot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/07/donald-trump-is-an-idiot.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/56/Donald_Trump_official_portrait.jpg/379px-Donald_Trump_official_portrait.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have heard stories about Trump, how much idiot he is. My friends say some of their American clients gets furious when name of Trump gets mentioned. Many in USA view it as a disgrace and depletion of intelligence to America for him to have got elected. Well, here in India we have been electing very stupid leaders in my state Tamilnadu. We Tamil’s are so idiot that we don’t even realize that we have been electing idiots for decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way this blog is about Trump. I was thrown back when Trump linked Socialism to lack of freedom in State of Union speech. Socialism has got nothing to do with lack of freedom or has got nothing to do with freedom. Socialism is nothing more than social living. Its like you teaching your kid share its lunch with a friend in class who has forgotten its lunch. Its that simple. You can see Socialism with mother who has lot of kids. A kid that faces challenge gets more attention, for example a new born child receives more attention than a kid that’s able to go to school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Socialism can be forced or unforced. You helping your neighbor, or community is a unforced socialism, but say a class teacher forcing your kid to share its lunch with the one who has failed to bring it is a forced one. In a similar way capitalism can be forced and unforced. A free market is a free capitalism, but are we consulted before making economic laws, or are few business people consulted before a law in made in a capitalistic land? Aren’t the will of the super rich are forced upon us? Think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An economic model chosen by a community has got nothing to do with the sense of freedom. Sense of freedom is a relative term and its very hard to define. Its hilarious that a person who is controlling the most powerful nation on this planet cannot grasp it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>