<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-03-31T07:41:59+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why Khalistan now?</title><link href="/2023/03/31/why-khalistan-now.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Khalistan now?" /><published>2023-03-31T00:22:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-31T00:22:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/03/31/why-khalistan-now</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/03/31/why-khalistan-now.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://yu7.in/T475WF &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video above shows people in queue, I saw this on Reddit, these people are standing to get flour. First I thought it was Afghanistan, but then it turned out to be Pakistan. While the elite there seem to have a good life, people are suffering. Pakistan never gave up its Jihad on India, it wants to destroy us entirely, but its economic situation is such that it cannot fund terrorists. Remember Pakistan is a country that values Jihad and Terrorism far higher than good life of its people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even strong Islamic countries like the UAE, Saudi Arabia don’t see the point anymore to sponsor their proxy wars against India, they are staying away from funding terrorism in Pakistan. After the solar cell and electric vehicle revolution, the age of oil is fast coming to an end, if these countries don’t reform, their economies would collapse. For good economics, one has to shake hands with atheistic China, and secular India. Pakistan did shake hands with China, but its still obsessed with destroying India. Looks like brains of ISI and its army is screwed and nothing can be done about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With funding for Islamic terror running out, Pakistan is looking for something cheap. Looks like its agents are talking with Sikh separatist who want a separate nation called Khalistan. Ideally Khalistan should be from Afghanistan, all the way into Punjab, into Kashmir and to Tibet. In today’s scenario that’s impossible, but for Pakistan, all it needs is to give trouble to India, and may be all you need as a Sikh separatist is a moral boost, so that reality could be ignored, and it looks like that moral support is provided by Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afghanistan followed Pakistan, Pakistan’s own people followed Pakistan, now we know their fate. I think this will be the same fate of Khalistan separatists who follow Pakistan very soon. Khalistan seekers will become deeply religious, highly intolerant, strict, unproductive and hence economically weak, but will have a mindset of war and violence. Maybe they too will starve to death one day.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Better prison than tyrant</title><link href="/2023/03/25/better-prison-than-tyrant.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Better prison than tyrant" /><published>2023-03-25T09:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-25T09:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/03/25/better-prison-than-tyrant</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/03/25/better-prison-than-tyrant.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/8c/David_-_The_Death_of_Socrates.jpg/1644px-David_-_The_Death_of_Socrates.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Socrates said what he said and faced death for it. Nehru said what he said and he faced prison. Maybe Rahul Gandhi is following the footsteps of his great-grandfather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every civilization faces dark ages, and this is a dark age for India. We are ruled by a dictator who cannot stand criticism and who cannot face journalists. In short Modi is incapable of being a democratic leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Rahul said is simply a democratic way of living. He said this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Why do all these thieves have Modi as their surname? Nirav Modi, Lalit Modi, Narendra Modi.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Rahul Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One can react to it in many ways, one is to accept it true and so get angry about it and try to eliminate such comments, another one is to ignore it, another way is, if one is getting an impression that people with name &lt;em&gt;Modi&lt;/em&gt; in it are corrupt, take a simple survey. Go to a place where lot of Modi’s live, find out how many of them were kept quiet when Muslims were massacred, find of out many of them have done jewelry and sports fraud. If say more than 30% of them have done it, maybe we are up to something, else you have got a statistics to show that what Rahul Gandhi said only applied to three Modi’s who are an exception, and most of them are normal people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreicc27xjje2nsdjbahg5edklydkf5ngwuuhb5wdu72st6tnp6r255e.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Using Rahul Gandhi controversy to make people forget Adani scam.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s sad to see Nation going down the drain in hands of BJP. Rather than going behind possible criminals like Adani, finding out how that group caused so much losses, publishing the truth and taking legal action, this dictatorial just want to banish people who question it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreiewfblq3tx7kg37vibeeeho2vafn3cmlq4soxvia732o2hu5j4vci&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What path Rahul Gandhi is taking seems to be the right one. It’s better goto prison and even get executed by the tyrant Modi than to live under his rule. I’m sure those who put salt in food and eat, and people who do experience shame will follow Rahul.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tamilnadu government school rocks</title><link href="/2023/03/17/tamilnadu-government-school-rocks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tamilnadu government school rocks" /><published>2023-03-17T23:34:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-17T23:34:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/03/17/tamilnadu-government-school-rocks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/03/17/tamilnadu-government-school-rocks.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeibk7xzmlyinnjsfrwcmwzepgo5aqix4767wbqt72ctxf2mdwvelxi &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine if in a private school kids could throw off their duppata since its their choice. I studied in a college called Panimalar, if any girl there would arrive to college without a duppata, she would be sent back home, her parent will be called the next day, they would be humiliated and made to cry, their family would be insulted by the management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am really proud of the DMK government in this case. Yes they are looters, yes people died in mysterious ways when 2G scam went on, yes they loot public money to construct remembrance structures for Karunanidhi, Stalin can’t even banish stray dogs that bark every day in my street spoiling my sleep, he cannot give a month long of power without interruption, DMK can’t even sports minister or chief minister outside Karunadnidhi’s family, it has no democracy, but they are making impoverished realize their power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The author in the video is said to have written book, possibly calling girls not to wear duppatas, the girls in this school seems to have read it and got fascinated by it, and they threw it off when the author visited their school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreiemvtgaybjsjotpf6geeqgkysxwn2oailoiulkfj2bougva3ooyxi&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We in India make fun of Iran, Saudi Arabia and Islam for forcing women to abide by dress code, but this author has clearly seems to have explained that India is almost no different from these religious fanatic nations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish parents in Tamilnadu who send kids to private schools visited government schools, make their kids join there, and donate the high amount of money they would pay to private school to the government school in which their kids study.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the kids in this school, we parents should get educated, and not fall on corrupt private schools feet since they charge a lot just to cheat us and ruin our kids life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Otto</title><link href="/2023/03/05/otto.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Otto" /><published>2023-03-05T13:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-05T13:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/03/05/otto</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/03/05/otto.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeih5pne7e2uo7xpfdqjj6bfl2r33sn4y7gib7tfe42w3bqkkli4i4m.ipfs.dweb.link/a-man-called-otto.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saw A man called Otto yesterday, it was a nice movie that tells deep problems of the society of today. It is a fact, I.Q scores of people are dropping, as an old man, Otto feels that the world is becoming stupid. This movie taunts capitalism and talks about the natural communist in everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otto is an engineer, the capitalist in his company have decided to make his junior the boss of him and reduced his roles, thus forcing Otto to resign so that it looks good on them (they didn’t fire him you see). He lives in an area where capitalistic real estate people learn about medical conditions of old people and try to grab the houses. The real estate people bash the nearby wooded area and build condos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This condo thing rang bells in me. Come to my area Sithalapakkam and check where are the parks, you will be surprised. I myself haven’t verified it, but gossip did go around that the politicians converted it into flats and sold it off. All I know is there isn’t a decent park in my area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otto decides to kill himself, but fails repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie also talks about the goodness of communism, the natural human tendency to help. Otto himself helps people. In his life there are two great people, one is his wife, she married him despite knowing he is unemployed and broke, she supported his education. This happened in 50’s and 60’s. Think about no, how it would be to have a spouse who is an economic liability? We are slaves of capitalism today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otto wife dies and Otto loses interest in life until a new Latino neighbor turns up. She is full of communist heart, she cooks and gives food to Otto, she demands help from him and make him feel he is part of her family. All this softens Otto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie also made me think about capitalism today. Before we had land for homes, we could grow our own vegetables to some extent, but today we are controlled by market prices. Today walking space and parks are scarce, instead we have gyms, we are forced to exercise on machines which harbours someone’s sweat and bacteria, and we pay for it like fools. There is no pooja rooms in home, the society is filled with corporate god (wo)men and psychiatrists. One has no place to exercise his soul in private today. Soon there will be homes without kitchen, and we all will be forced to eat by ordering in apps. Capitalism pushes population up devastating natural resources and warming the planet. We are slaves to our companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, be a goat, don’t think, and fell happy licking the capitalist boosts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Esther Crawford slept on her office floor to deliver for her company but was still tossed out like dirty bath water. Don’t know who needs to hear this, but live for yourself and not any institution. Your job won’t ever love you. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/sz7wRx69oy&quot;&gt;https://t.co/sz7wRx69oy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/S4WnUusSUI&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/S4WnUusSUI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Uju Anya (@UjuAnya) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/UjuAnya/status/1629928288519847936?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;February 26, 2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Adani could have done if it was pure</title><link href="/2023/02/17/what-adani-could-have-done-if-it-was-pure.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Adani could have done if it was pure" /><published>2023-02-17T10:40:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-17T10:40:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/17/what-adani-could-have-done-if-it-was-pure</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/17/what-adani-could-have-done-if-it-was-pure.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/ff/Gautam_Adani.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Gautam Adani&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business is supposed to empower humanity, empower life. When I started making websites it had simple purpose, you can say a lot in it than what you can say in a vising card, and you can tell it to anyone on this planet who has a computer. The bet was in far future every home will have a desktop computer. Now most of you will be reading this on your palm top which is wrongly called as mobile phone (phone is just one functionality that the computer in your palm could do).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s that simple business is, you add value, and look for undervalued things now that will be valuable in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So looking at Adani stocks today (the range of the graph below is 3 months):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreidq3smq7xbx5n5eopszzzkigc5jn6sovwib5k6uunhsnsa56mf2ya&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has kind of halved in value, and that’s because of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://hindenburgresearch.com/adani/&quot;&gt;Hindenburg report&lt;/a&gt;. I thought Modi would have banned this site saying it’s a national threat, but well, he hasn’t banned BBC either. Thankfully Hindenburg does not have its offices in India, or else Modi would have raided it with tax men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adani haven’t submitted any comprehensive counter to Hindenburg, so this has put nervousness into its investors. If I had a stock in dubious company, definitely I would sell it. So in this blog I want to tell you what Adani could have done if it is a pure company:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome Hindenburg analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, asking doubts about a business is a good thing, it helps to find faults and fix it, so Adani should have welcomed questioning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ask time for report analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next it could have asked time to analyze the report, in that time it could have set an executive team to analyze it, prepare answers to Hindenburg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reply to Hindenburg&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next would be a comprehensive reply to Hindenburg, it could be congratulating Hindenburg to have found faults and ways Adani would take steps to repair it, or to present their own facts countering Hindenburg. It’s as simple as that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happened?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way Adani is behaving is as though it’s an unquestionable King. This I feel is due to the fact that it receives unconditional support from Indian dictators and neither Adani, nor the government feel that they are answerable to investors and people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This simply means Adani and India will keep feeling great, just like Pakistan felt great all these years, until the day of inevitable collapse, and then nothing can be done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeidpmc7dcrmk55cmajktgkqemvezwex7x4jwv5c2olzddkzuagrjpq &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Gautam Adani</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">It’s 2023 and still religion is strong in Tamilnadu. Shame.</title><link href="/2023/02/15/it-s-2023-and-still-religion-is-strong-in-tamilnadu-shame.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It&apos;s 2023 and still religion is strong in Tamilnadu. Shame." /><published>2023-02-15T14:01:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-15T14:01:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/15/it-s-2023-and-still-religion-is-strong-in-tamilnadu-shame</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/15/it-s-2023-and-still-religion-is-strong-in-tamilnadu-shame.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeicuqlwb6mjqwkcxz33pxatvvytdihgqizt5niv43khtj7b5ah7gcq &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ancient religious knowledge</title><link href="/2023/02/14/ancient-religious-knowledge.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ancient religious knowledge" /><published>2023-02-14T19:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-14T19:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/14/ancient-religious-knowledge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/14/ancient-religious-knowledge.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeifyyvt2hs55cfd6gwpe7mljfchdlpeeppnvjj2yo7nir2pfnpuwty &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The lion in parliament hunting Adani</title><link href="/2023/02/11/the-lion-in-parliament-hunting-adani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The lion in parliament hunting Adani" /><published>2023-02-11T11:44:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-11T11:44:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/11/the-lion-in-parliament-hunting-adani</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/11/the-lion-in-parliament-hunting-adani.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeia56vdus65fnuvgmacn5zly7xbhybbvffiijppwg2i72fuvbj5bxu &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vote for Naam Tamizhar in Erode East</title><link href="/2023/02/06/vote-for-naam-tamizhar-in-erode-east.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vote for Naam Tamizhar in Erode East" /><published>2023-02-06T11:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-06T11:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/06/vote-for-naam-tamizhar-in-erode-east</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/06/vote-for-naam-tamizhar-in-erode-east.html">&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_pCUrA-v3sA?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently a bunch of North Indians had chased and bashed Tamils in Tiruppur. Tamilnadu government says there is some fault on Tamils too. In recent Coimbatore bomb blast too DMK people claimed that it was a cylinder that went off, they defended the terrorists in open sun without shame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can’t trust DMK, all they need is to make Udhayanidhi Stalin as CM,a and after that Inbanidhi. To achieve that, they would let the northerners occupy and destroy us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;joining-hands-with-congress&quot;&gt;Joining hands with Congress&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafkreibzmx4dlw4cmq5k3gl4yisg5s6geytajrjvaauebj5fvkt4bgiajq&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK has joined hands with Congress which is a northerner’s party. The Congress needs Hindi heartland votes. DMK needs support of a pan India party so that they won’t get persecuted in criminal and corruption cases. So DMK will behave like a Hindi party. No doubt about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus DMK and Congress want dynatic politics and never will they want to put rightful ruler on throne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dynastic-politics&quot;&gt;Dynastic Politics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/4/46/E._V._K._S._Elangovan_at_Marriage_Function_12.jpg/1429px-E._V._K._S._Elangovan_at_Marriage_Function_12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;E.V.K.S Elangovan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK is a pure dynastic party. When India got independent, I think we made 100’s of kingdoms secede and we made it into one India. When Kingdoms lost power, naturally those people were liberated from dynastic rule and rule of democracy blossomed. But DMK, Congress and even other parties are brought in dynastic politics withing democracy which I think is ultra dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Erode east does not belong to Elangovans family. I am sorry for his son’s death, this has left Erode East a void constituency, but I wish Congress was able to find a non dynastic person who truely love the people of Erode than to make a dynastic one stand in elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To his credit I must say Elangovan is a very good person comparatively to other scoundrels in politics. But the way his family (Elangovan and his living son), tried to have them nominated by congress for Erode East leaves me with bitter feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-not-aiadmk&quot;&gt;Why not AIADMK?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Palanisamy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Edapaadi Palani Samy&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t like AIADMK because it’s led by EPS. He conducted Thoothukudi massacre and AIADMK as a party watched rather than impeach him. Kodanaadu people have died under mysterious circumstances and we public have no information what’s going on. May be EPS is a super killer who knows to get away with things. We must be very careful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;vote-for-naam-tamizhar&quot;&gt;Vote for Naam Tamizhar&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/14/NAAM_TAMILAR_PARTY_LOGO_MODERN.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not believe Seeman, the leader of Naam Tamizhar is a pure person. Savukku Shankar has laid charges against him, Seeman was smart, visited Savulku in prison and stood support, now Savukku does not speak about Seeman. Maybe both have become corrupt now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/w2DNBj7abJo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further more even if Naam Tamizhar is corrupt, and they get elected, they must build connections to start looting en masse, this will give us some breathing space. They might not be as efficient looters as DMK and Congress people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to purity of soul, Naam Tamizhar is okay comparatively. I am not telling there are no robbers, scoundrels, looters, money hungry businessmen in it. I just don’t know who are there in the party. But relatively it’s pure. May be if DMK and Congress are HIV infection for India, Naam Tamizhar is Tuberculosis, maybe it will take more time to kill India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naam Tamizhar has never kept alliance with other parties that have proven or unproven corruption record. I see that as a Major plus. They speak against Noth Indians aggression against us. DMK needs Congress and ADMK needs BJP so they won’t stand for Tamils, wheras naam Tamizhar will as they do not bow to North India. I see some form of Tamil spirit left in Naam Tamizhar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a citzen of india, as a Tamil who feel we must be protected in our last refuge (we must not become like Srilankan Tamils), I urge the people of Erode East to vote for Naam Tamizhar. I am not saying they will give a golden rule, but at least we can start to escape from Hindi aggression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2zTOh2XRtwo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">USA plans war with China</title><link href="/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="USA plans war with China" /><published>2023-02-03T09:31:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-03T09:31:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/02/03/usa-plans-war-with-china.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeicyczvr4fks6pfm75xrq3crperwl3odipurlzqqlekg6emyszhdsy &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/dBQlE&quot;&gt;https://yu7.in/dBQlE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry></feed>