<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-07-30T00:03:40+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Dark Tamil Nadu under M.K.Stalin’s Rule</title><link href="/2021/07/29/dark-tamil-nadu-under-m-k-stalins-rule.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark Tamil Nadu under M.K.Stalin&apos;s Rule" /><published>2021-07-29T23:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-07-29T23:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/07/29/dark-tamil-nadu-under-m-k-stalins-rule</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/07/29/dark-tamil-nadu-under-m-k-stalins-rule.html">&lt;p&gt;Today I had a power cut from 8:50 AM to 5 PM. In Edapaddi Palanisami rule these things never happened so much. Some how he  was a good chief minister who kind of kept up his promise. Some how it seems from a Chennai person’s view that DMK could be very much corrupt compared to AIADMK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually ADMK warned the people that if when Stalin came to power, electricity would be cut in many places in Tamil Nadu. May be the DMK guys know to sell away our coal, pocket the money, and blame AIADMK for crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know corruption started in Dravidian movement in a big scale from Karunadhi era, we had massive power cuts during his rule which Jayalalitha fixed it and Edapaadi maintained it. But Stalin seems to be like his father, breaking up things that was fixed during the AIADMK rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Stalin took power I had to take 3 days of leave due to power cuts. I don’t think I am in a company that would tolerate these kind of things, already I am served a notice that my work is going slow. Today would have been the 4th day of leave due to power cut but I was sick due to Covid shot and had to call for a leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though Edapaadi did lick the feet of BJP, I think its better to have a CM who gives us better services than loot us in the name of Drividianism. If we promote DMK &amp;amp; family, the future generations would only see Dravidian movement as a synonym to corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Though this blog was written on 28 Jul 2021, I wasn’t able to publish until 29 Jul 2021 due to frequent power cuts than ran up to midnight.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today I had a power cut from 8:50 AM to 5 PM. In Edapaddi Palanisami rule these things never happened so much. Some how he was a good chief minister who kind of kept up his promise. Some how it seems from a Chennai person’s view that DMK could be very much corrupt compared to AIADMK.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Plugins I would Like to Have in My Chat and Calls</title><link href="/artificial%20intelligence/machine%20learning/data%20science/work/productivity/2021/06/18/the-plugins-i-would-like-to-have-in-my-chat-and-calls.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Plugins I would Like to Have in My Chat and Calls" /><published>2021-06-18T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-18T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/artificial%20intelligence/machine%20learning/data%20science/work/productivity/2021/06/18/the-plugins-i-would-like-to-have-in-my-chat-and-calls</id><content type="html" xml:base="/artificial%20intelligence/machine%20learning/data%20science/work/productivity/2021/06/18/the-plugins-i-would-like-to-have-in-my-chat-and-calls.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1373463/thumbs/o-BORING-MEETING-facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a software developer. Somehow lazy guys seem to dominate this field, and I am lazy. Despite being in this field for nearly 20 years, I do not understand why we have so much meetings. Till this day I do not understand what most people in my meetings talk, but I have to be there. I have no doubt this is the fate of many software developers and office goers out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having said that, and knowing that our life revolves around chat and calls, it would be nice if we have the following plugins in our chat and calling programs to ease life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fake my text plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay this is text based plugin that chat’s with your colleagues on channels like Slack and Teams so that they think you are there. When it cannot chat and finds that its beyond its capacity to handle, only then you get a notification to interfere. When ever you interfere, the algorithm learns and becomes better and handles similar situation well the next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a software developer I need to concentrate hard, and all of a sudden I get a &lt;em&gt;Hey&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Hi&lt;/em&gt; in my chat that just breaks down the thought data structure I had built up in my brain, and its annoying. This plugin will save me lot of time and make me lot productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dress me up plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/EHE-GcCOktU?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live in Chennai, a hot place. I wear a light dress, and for meetings I switch dresses so that I look professional. Long ago there was a mobile app which you can point at any one and it will show them naked real time, the A.I algorithm will undress them and show to you. Why can’t we have an algorithms that does the reverse where it dresses one up. No matter what ever I wear or not wear, this will dress me up and show like I am a pro. This will save lot of world’s time, won’t it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fake me plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the ultimate plugin that will fake you entirely so that there is no need for you to be in front of the cam. May be it would also talk for you and be your replacement virtually. May be that’s in far future. For now, your zoom could be hooked up to your earpods where you will talk, and this plugin will fake your camera feed and make you appear real to others while you take a stroll in the park listening to meeting and talking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brief me up plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the meeting time one does not talk, one does listen to a boring talker, thats utter waste of time. Given that humans are poor communicators, it would be nice if there is a plugin that would prepare a highlight video feed or few lines of text which summarizes the entire meeting. This would save us lot of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world of artificial intelligence has excellent applications to be cracked. Jump in! May be &lt;a href=&quot;https://neuralink.com/&quot;&gt;Neural Link&lt;/a&gt; will make humanity just one brain and eliminate all meetings.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DMK trying to give god back to people</title><link href="/religion/hinduism/india/tamilnadu/dmk/politics/2021/06/12/dmk-trying-to-give-god-back-to-people.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DMK trying to give god back to people" /><published>2021-06-12T20:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-12T20:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/religion/hinduism/india/tamilnadu/dmk/politics/2021/06/12/dmk-trying-to-give-god-back-to-people</id><content type="html" xml:base="/religion/hinduism/india/tamilnadu/dmk/politics/2021/06/12/dmk-trying-to-give-god-back-to-people.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.siasat.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/DMK-logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Rising Sun - DMK Logo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t like DMK for many reasons. The first is dynastic politics. We all know who is the next chief minister after Stalin is. It’s hard to believe none in DMK did not work as much as Stalin to deserve the CM post, and it’s kind of funny to know why there wasn’t a vote or a contender to Stalin when he tried to become the leader of DMK, that too when DMK claims that it’s a party that respects democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from that DMK is the epitome of corruption, possibly the most corrupt organization on this planet. It’s said that they have made looting a scientific process thus making it untraceable. I would have been very happy if something other than DMK, ADMK came to power in Tamil Nadu. Any way…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was seeing the news today. What DMK is doing to Hinduism is great. Actually in Hinduism God is equal to all, so just a particular Brahmin caste doing poojai in temples is bullshit, DMK is trying to reverse that. Looks like very soon any one from any caste can become a poosaari and do poojai in temple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality any one can be a brahmin, the title brahmin should not be given to someone who is been born to a brahmin, but it should be given to some one having very great personal qualities. For example A.P.J.Abdul Kalaam fits very perfectly into the description of a brahmin, but he is a staunch Muslim and yet a brahmin. Some how things changed and now a person born to a person who claims he is a brahmin is calling himself a Brahmin. Somewhere down the line things were hijacked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/K0HqkC0jbJ8?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So letting all caste people to become poosari, DMK is demolishing the myth that God is accessible to us only via brahmins, a myth that has gripped this nation since Aryans set foot on the Indus valley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing is, if you have noticed, women in our house do the poojai mostly. Before Aryanism took over, women in society were priests. In ancient India there was almost no difference between a man and a woman. After the arrival of Aryanism, women’s rights got reduced and they were pushed away from God at least in the public places. The arrival of Abrahamic religions, namely Christianity and Islam, cemented the myth that women are subordinate to men. DMK is trying to reverse that. Now women too can become priests in Tamil temples. That’s great. In fact Amman cult which is relatively untouched by Ariyanism and other invasions still has many temples who’s priests are women. Non vegetarian is served in the temple as prasatham, animal sacrifices are allowed. DMK has always stood by women’s rights and these changes are laudable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally this language issue. God is equal to all and could be called out in any language, but the myth that Sanskrit is a deiva bashai and Tamil is a eecha bashai has been spread by Aryans. Till today a Tamil can’t understand what the poosari in Temple tells to the gods when he prays for him. One sould be able to understand what the poosari says to God. In Tamil Nadu Tamil should be spoken to Gods, not some extinct language. DMK is bring Tamil into temples, now any one will know what is been prayed for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thank Stalin for these stuff. Despite giving power cuts and disturbing my tranquility and profession he is doing good to make god equal to all. I thank him and the DMK and wish all the very best to Dravidian movements success. the ultimate success would be eliminate God itself and make people see the truth, but it’s not the right time to take such drastic move.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rising Sun - DMK Logo</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Living without killing is morally satisfying</title><link href="/2021/06/02/living-without-killing-is-morally-satisfying.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Living without killing is morally satisfying" /><published>2021-06-02T23:06:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-02T23:06:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/06/02/living-without-killing-is-morally-satisfying</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/06/02/living-without-killing-is-morally-satisfying.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://clarionindia.net/portal/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/meat-shop-kolkata-india.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corona is causing problems to many, but for me till now it has been a blessing in disguise. One of the many things it has done to me is to make me work from home. It was the dream of many I.T professionals to work from anywhere because we knew it could be done. What the management guys can’t achieve was achieved by a virus without a brain. No wonder! No way a virus has less brains than management people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is not about that. It’s about living without eating non-vegetarian. I was an avid meat eater, I cannot live without meat. I eat any meat, my family is bit different. My family is an orthodox one, so they should buy meat from a trusted muslim, the animal should be sacrificed in halal way so that we do not bring in bad spirits into the house. Sea food is not considered muslim, so its okay to buy from any one, but now looking at fisher folks and how indisciplined they are with hygiene, its a no now, possibly till this pandemic ends. So after lockdown, when the shops were closed and meat was available only from apps, who knows how they were cut? There was no meat in my home. It is now totally vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though I loved meat very much, before eating it I would always imagine how the animal would have suffered while it was been cut alive. It’s a conscious life! How the fish would have gasped for breadth like a dying corona patient just because some human would be happy in the near future because of its death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We humans don’t want to be killed, cut up, and chewed up by any other thing, but we do it shamelessly to other species. I think of all these things and eat meat. I even suspected if I was addicted to non-vegetarian, and especially biriyani.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost all religions born in India ban the killing of conscious life for ones pleasure. It’s a very unique Indian idea, seen almost no where in this world where we have realize our happiness should not be based on suffering of a conscious being. It’s a very very unique Indian thought. Being an Indian, I would say thinking about the animals suffering and sacrifice for me crossing my mind before I start to eat is a no-brainer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming to my addiction, I really suspected that I was addicted to non-vegetarian food, but after the meat ban in my home, I am now living as vegetarian, and I am vindicated from having tho think “am I addicted meat?”. May be I am not addicted to animal meat. Most importantly knowing that my life is not based upon suffering of conscious being is a refreshing and morally satisfying thought.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Failed start for Stalin</title><link href="/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/stalin/covid/2021/05/13/failed-start-for-stalin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Failed start for Stalin" /><published>2021-05-13T23:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-05-13T23:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/stalin/covid/2021/05/13/failed-start-for-stalin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/stalin/covid/2021/05/13/failed-start-for-stalin.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.veethi.com/images/people/fullsize/M._K._Stalin_20170709020708.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would rather say that M.K.Stalin is having a failed start of his CM post. It was funny when he announced lockdown, he himself ignored Corona and campaigned shamelessly, more of his shamelessness was revealed when he asked for donations from people for the CM fund to fight Corona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would gather people and ask votes and spread the disease, then when he comes to power he will say the disease has gone beyond control, would not take responsibility for it, then ask for money to correct his mistake. It’s a miserable failure of leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to the lockdown. His implementation of the lockdown is funny. It’s night 11:12 now, and the ban was supposed to be in place since 12 noon, just now a bike passed my door. Where the heck is the ban? Just an hour ago I think the local DMK leader car (without flag) crossed my house in Sithalapakkam. News reports of heavy traffic in Saidapet and Guindy Chennai. He put an excellent policy, and just like Modi he is unable to implement it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They say 10,000 police are in Chennai implementing the ban, lol! I wonder if the account books are recording crores of rupees are spent in implementing the ban.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would rather say DMK itself is a failed party. It’s values are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not to promote religion. But many in the party are religious.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To be democratic. You know how Stalin rose up to power.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To give equal chance at leadership to all. you know most leaders are from a few families.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To promote Tamil. This blog is written by a Tamilian and is in English. Kanimozhi’s school teaches in English.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not to loot. We all know that DMK is THE KING of looting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK is not a dravidian party, its a party to make Udhayanidhi Stalin the Chief minister because no one in DMK has worked as hard for the party :D. All other party member’s except Udhyanidhi have no balls it seems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need a party that is Democratic, Drvidian, Atheistic, that grows Tamil and better’s the lifes of Tamilians, gives chance to people who love people, and bubbles up leaders than dynasty. Will Tamils ever wake up and create this change?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why India won’t win over Covid?</title><link href="/2021/04/24/why-india-won-t-win-over-covid.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why India won&apos;t win over Covid?" /><published>2021-04-24T20:40:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-24T20:40:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/04/24/why-india-won-t-win-over-covid</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/24/why-india-won-t-win-over-covid.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s01.sgp1.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/article/157943-msvocffheg-1619027775.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deaths are mounting in India and looks like there isn’t enough place to cremate people. Yet this is just the start of Covid in India, more is yet to come. This might ravage us for for 3 to 10 years, who knows? May be a miracle could make it less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are speaking how the governments have mishandled the situation and so on. To me this battle had been lost long ago, and unfortunately we won’t win it, which means, all who will die of covid will die and the remaining will get natural immunity and might suffer some cost like reduced lifespan etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog I will tell my opinion, why and how it happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lost-a-long-time-ago&quot;&gt;Lost a long time ago&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://germarrudolf.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/three_monkeys.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had lost the battle with Covid long ago, even before the first Covid formed. I won’t forget, when I was working in a company, my car got repaired and a nice friend of mine offered lift. We talked about many things. Once he said that 80% of salary goes just to meet  health and education expense. When a true honest Muslim says such a thing, it hits you. A person well disciplined than me is struggling in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In India, you don’t have the right to kill yourself. The country might kill you by sentencing you, but you do not own your life. In that case the country should guarantee the wellness and happiness of every citizen. Each citizen should be well educated, well fed, should have well health. But here I see a very good citizen complain about this nation. A sign that India has failed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have privatised and commercialised health and education. Meaning you have to have money to have these things. India and Indians have lost to Covid or what ever health pandemic that would hit them at that very time when they slowly accept privatisation of essential services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had lost the moment we stopped selecting good leaders to rule us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ignorant-people&quot;&gt;Ignorant people&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/culturalsamvaad.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/1200px-Descent_of_the_Ganges_Pallava_period_7th_century_Mahabalipuram_6_23621236598-e1570786632817.jpg?resize=600%2C400&amp;amp;ssl=1&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Rat worshipping a cat, a sculpture in Mahabalipuram, India&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are still ignorant. Just a peek outside my window and I can see tens of people and only few of them wearing mask. Even those who wear mask, wear a cloth one which is not so effective and now even surgical masks which I use normally seems to have little effect. They are telling us to wear a thing called triple layered mask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people are still ignorant, and looks like they might realize only if death happens nearby. For a non ignorant and well educated population one should have an excellent education system which India had lost long ago. So we cannot expect a learned populace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stupid-government&quot;&gt;Stupid government&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.newindianexpress.com/uploads/user/imagelibrary/2018/6/13/w600X300/modichan.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BJP government is stupid (so is congress). We were failing in economy well before Covid, and Covid exploited our weaknesses well. The government does not know what its doing, it would say there is enough vaccine and the next day news would report that vaccine centres have run out of it. All BJP governments have been out of touch with common populace and this one wants to give press statements that would make stock markets go little higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short this government which did say Covid will be won in 21 days has failed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the people so are the rulers. How cam you expect an ill educated population to choose a non stupid leaders?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wrap-up&quot;&gt;Wrap up&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, let’s hope that our deaths will decrease human pressure and harm on this environment and reduce global warming. I don’t think India will become an educated and aware nation any time soon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pandemic Violation’s</title><link href="/2021/04/03/pandemic-violations.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pandemic Violation&apos;s" /><published>2021-04-03T22:03:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-03T22:03:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/04/03/pandemic-violations</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/03/pandemic-violations.html">&lt;p&gt;One good thing about Corona is that not all of us will die, but many of us might be crippled in some way that we may not be realise. Maybe less of brain function, less of bodily functions which are not visible, may be our lifespan will decrease and definitely we won’t be aware of it now, who knows what else happens due to invasion of such fast changing virus?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many humans, and by some miracle even if all get HIV, some of us will survive by a random mutation in our gene. In fact scientist have identified prostitutes in Africa who can perfectly co exist with HIV. So Corona, HIV and whatever will not kill us all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a virus that could have been eliminated easily. All it was to be done is for the governments to ensure none came out their home for a certain time period. Like a nation in disaster, or like politician seeking votes door to door, politicians and beuracrats could have gone door to door and distributed essentials for people to stay in. May be getting votes is much needed for this nation than saving humans who are slowly been killed by corona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way this blog is not about Corona’s lethality and how politicians have fooled us ever since the Brits fooling us ended, this is about who violates the pandemic and what could be the cause in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have seen many not wearing masks even now, though doing so and washing hand, and not going out might have eliminated this disease. I began to wonder why? Why are people failing to do such a simple steps which could have such a positive effect on humanity? The reason is broad thinking seems to be absent. Its like a driver taking to the wrong lane of the road in a traffic jam, for him its him and his well being matters and not the greater good. This reminds me of evolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see in evolution, the intelligent monkey chose the intelligent and out evolved man so slowly in many generations. I think this process is very well alive. When I see a person who is destructive and less intelligent, I naturally tend to repel away from them, no matter how much powerful and wealthy and important they are. May be I feel one day a super intelligent humans will evolve out, who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any way this blog is about my observations of the stupids, those who do not wear mask, crowd around, travel, do not sanitise and are just intelligent enough to come up with humpty reasons for being an idiot. My observation is those people definitely are not so broad minded and think narrow, and they think of today, and I have never seen them think big or radiate intellectuality out of them. Even among those stupids I can divide them into few classes. One is the not educated ones, we can do nothing about those people, they don’t know what an pandemic is, or how their movement will kill somebody, they need to see the virus take a knife and stab some one for them to belive it’s a killer. Next you have got educated one, why on earth a person who can watch news, read a paper, understand its content can be so stupid? One thing I have noticed is, such kind of peoples parents are ill educated, if ones parents are ill educated and if one is educated, I see that person behaves like an idiot. That person moves around, travels, may not wear mask and sanitise regularly. It’s been highly consistent in my observation. Another group of people I see is the religious, highly religious people are not wearing masks. That’s no wonder because for ages I know being religious and shutting your mind even if you are super educated on paper is a mark of stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-you-must-not-violate&quot;&gt;Why you must not violate?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say you have Covid with no symptoms, and you travel without precaution, then you infect a person on travel and that person feels nothing, that person has old people in his home and they get it and die, then it means you have killed them. It’s as simple as that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine your loved one slipping a banana peel, falling down on the pavement with their head jutting out into the road, and a lorry runs over it. The person who threw the peel is just few steps away from you and laughs because its not his mistake to have killed your loved one, its your loved one who has stepped over it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">One good thing about Corona is that not all of us will die, but many of us might be crippled in some way that we may not be realise. Maybe less of brain function, less of bodily functions which are not visible, may be our lifespan will decrease and definitely we won’t be aware of it now, who knows what else happens due to invasion of such fast changing virus?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Suicides Should be a Human Right</title><link href="/philosophy/life/myth/religion/belief/2021/03/20/suicides-should-be-a-human-right.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Suicides Should be a Human Right" /><published>2021-03-20T14:41:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-03-20T14:41:00+05:30</updated><id>/philosophy/life/myth/religion/belief/2021/03/20/suicides-should-be-a-human-right</id><content type="html" xml:base="/philosophy/life/myth/religion/belief/2021/03/20/suicides-should-be-a-human-right.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/8c/David_-_The_Death_of_Socrates.jpg/1644px-David_-_The_Death_of_Socrates.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;The Death of Socrates&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I thought you how to live, I’ll teach you how to die - Socrates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In many parts of the world, one can choose their own leaders. Well, that’s what we are told to believe, and we are also told that we have control of our life, it’s our life and our right until we infringe upon some one else’s right. Well then why shouldn’t one have the right to kill oneself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;you-are-not-infringing-on-others-right&quot;&gt;You are not infringing on others right&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When one kills himself, or the better herself :D, that person is not infringing on other peoples right, but they are just shutting off. That’s it. It’s their idea that this universe and humanity sucks and they don’t belong here, I feel if any society calls itself free should honour it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-they-tell-its-wrong&quot;&gt;Why they tell its wrong&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t really know why they say it’s wrong and why many religious and political leaders encourage one to live despite making lives hard. May be because if say some one says “God I want mutton briyani now”, and to his dismay discovers that God doesn’t deliver and he kills himself, then the amount of money the religious leader gets when all people who discover that God does not exist and commit suicide dwindles. The religious leader, can’t have a great life, and most religious leaders are control freaks who want to control lot of people. If people are not afraid of death, then this control becomes really hard, and if they don’t work for him he may not have the life he or she desires. Imagine how Nithyanadha would feel of Ranjitha killed herself rather than sleeping with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till this day, we were made to believe leaders of business, religion and politics should be respected and its because of them people have a better life, but when Corona struck and human interaction was banned the world productivity dropped, some how all of a sudden the world realised that it’s productivity comes out of people who work, rather than from the people who have money, dream and thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;He who is not afraid to die is your master - Roman saying&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus say your boss threatens you with a miserable life, only to find out that you have killed yourself the next day, he would feel frustrated, definitely his business would suffer some loss, and if people are bold enough to commit suicide, bosses can’t really abuse them. Human productivity is built on abuse, frustration, sweat and blood than humaness. If people escape these things quick, then these people can’t say to the world they had made it more productive and they are successful and have a large house, a car because of their work (which they really didn’t do).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possibly its because of that its said that killing yourself is cowardice and the comedy is throwing before enemy fire and defending against enemy is also a near act of suicide, but those things are glorified :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So one getting killed is wrong if it’s weakens the institutional leaders, and if killing of you strengthens them, then it’s right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;spain-granting-rights-to-die&quot;&gt;Spain granting rights to die&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I saw a news that Spain is granting rights to die for people who are in severe medical pain. That’s a good step, but I feel its rubbish that any civilisation could call itself free if it does not allow killing of oneself as easy buying a briyani. But ya briyani is prized really high because of human stupidity, well that’s another blog.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Death of Socrates</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Indian middle class can end Islamic terrorism?</title><link href="/energy/renewable/india/saudi%20arabia/religion/islam/politics/corruption/terrorism/2021/03/11/how-indian-middle-class-can-end-islamic-terrorism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Indian middle class can end Islamic terrorism?" /><published>2021-03-11T21:53:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-03-11T21:53:00+05:30</updated><id>/energy/renewable/india/saudi%20arabia/religion/islam/politics/corruption/terrorism/2021/03/11/how-indian-middle-class-can-end-islamic-terrorism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/energy/renewable/india/saudi%20arabia/religion/islam/politics/corruption/terrorism/2021/03/11/how-indian-middle-class-can-end-islamic-terrorism.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/123AD/production/_97796647_gettyimages-76069264.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If voting made a difference,
they wouldn’t let us do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As middle class of India, we run this nation. Vijay Mallaya, Neerav Modi, Lali Modi, loot and get away abroad, here this Modi boasts he does this thing and and that thing and does nothing but to crash our economy even before the great pandemic. For every loss our baapus make, the looting that our politician do, tax evasion our bosses make, we middle class have paid ta for it (like huge taxes in petrol, even salt and toothpaste is taxed, our income too is taxed) and we are the true citizens of India. We never felt proud about it as we are looted every second, and we never boasted about it. We have always felt things are out of our hand, and thats true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But time is very strange, it gives an opportunity for us to change something. I am not talking about Democracy. No matter what ever party comes to power, they will obey the rich and ignore others. I am talking about energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My house is on a dirt road for the 14 years of my stay in Sithalapakaam, we had nothing but dirt road. Vehicles pass, and even for minimum of traffic dut gets settled every where in my room. Imagine if we can reduce oil import, save our nation money, say we save Rs 100/-, I am sure Rs 99/- will be looted away, but the Re 1/- might go into making my road a tar road. So please read this blog to know hw you can save my country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-modi-wont-eliminate-terrorist&quot;&gt;Why Modi won’t eliminate terrorist&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://theindiaobserver.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/31895204_10214039392993167_7017601988976181248_n.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi is simply stupid. In his short rule, Vajpyee fought Kargil, exploded nukes, brought Pakistan to its knees, with 7 years of Modi rule he must have liberated Boluchistan and Sindh from Pakistan, instead he sank us into despair with demonitization. One of the reason given was terrorist have their money in Rs 500/- and Rs 1000/- notes, and if this demonitization happens it will cripple them. Are we free of terrorism now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi simply has the ability to make news and do nothing in reality. He just wants fame and an illusion to surround him, that illusion is he must always feel that he is the greatest priminister ever, which is rubbish. I think he is competing with Indira Gandhi and Rajiv Gandhi to become one of the worst priminister this nation had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RSS, BJP and Modi need the Arabs, the Terrorist, because they are organisations that is built on hate of Muslims and Christians. If these people are gone, then it becomes pointless for them to exist. The same way Pakistan military needs India to justify its existence to Pakistani people and loot them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi is just a show. He can’t eliminate terrorists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;prophet-muhammed-did-not-exist&quot;&gt;Prophet Muhammed did not exist&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s come to Islam. None knows if Prophet Muhammed really existed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/j9S_xbjIRgE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if he did, he is definitely disillusioned person. We have lot of swamiji’s that claim they have seen God, heard God’s messages. Do we believe them? We feel they are better off meeting a psychologist than telling idiotic stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we have tools of science and lot of documentation to probe into the brain, but imagine war torn Arabia, they never had these tools and these thoughts we have now, and they suffered a lot. So lot of messiahs rose. One of them could be Muhammed or he might have been a person who was made up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ramayana was written because Aryans envied us and wanted to conquer us. They want to paint us as monkeys and demons, they wanted us to be some one who should either serve them or be destroyed. In similar way the Arab had their eyes on India and Rome, both are very profitable trading regions. It’s very possible that they inserted text into Quoran that it’s the will of God and words said by Muhammad that Islam would conquer Rome and India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though many nations have left the desire to Isamize India because we have been steadily raising in power ever since independence despite the huge corruption we have, the existence of Pakistan cannot be justified if India wasn’t its enemy, so its holding onto this dream. Being a Sunni nation, Saudi Arabia supports Pakistan in all ways possible, because any nation thats controlled by Islam is a territory controlled by Mecca which os owned by the Saud’s for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must be very careful with Aryans and Arabs. Or we will be known as slaves in History.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-want-khaliphet-in-chennai&quot;&gt;We want Khaliphet in Chennai&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am very certain that still the idea of Kaliphat, that is all of the world should be ruled by a single Islamic leader is there in the minds of many hard core Muslims. Rather than the acknowledging the progress we humans have made, outgrowing religion and growing into science, these religious leaders want to take it back. Not even a decade ago I think a friend of mine told me that while he was travelling in bus in Mount Road, may be somewhere between the U.S consulate and Thousand Lights mosque he saw a bunch of protesting Muslims who were shouting “we don’t want democracy, we want kalipha”. He was shocked, because these muslims were in Tamilnadu and had grown with us and had been an indispensable part of us, yet somehow they are controlled by the age old Arabic thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must be very careful of these forces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Religion is poison. - Mao Zedong&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;oil-or-energy-is-islam&quot;&gt;Oil (or energy) is Islam&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.gettyimages.com/vectors/oil-derrick-inside-symbol-of-islam-vector-id516214527&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few days ago I saw an article that Saudi Arabia wants to be a leader in Hydrogen future. So they now know people won’t buy into this Oil myth any more. Islam, the radical one, some may say it’s not Islam at all, is now fuelled by Saudi Arabian Oil. The Sauds know that the world is shifting, even though batteries can store renewable power, to store in such huge quantities as the world energy needs grows, there isn’t known Lithium deposits that are present on Earth. One of the best was t store power is by splitting water, and storing that Hydrogen either liquified, or as ammonia or as methane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately Arabia is blessed with Abundant sunlight so they can split up water by electrolysis and ship the hydrogen. We in India who have abundant sunshine, buy hydrogen from these terror sponsors, we will be killed by them possibly even into the next millennium. This should stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;use-solar-power&quot;&gt;Use solar power&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://sustainabilitynext.in/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/solar-panels.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what can we middle class can do? Much of middle class live in flat system or in rental homes. This blog is not for them. For people who are living in their own independent homes consider switching to solar power. The initial invest would be high, but it will pay off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First electrify your home with solar, this will cut our nations coal import. Next if you are using LPG for cooking, disconnect it, move to electric stoves, microwaves and electric ovens. In fact we are getting our LPG from possible terror sponsoring nations. Next buy electric car, it will charge over night using solar power stored in batteries, so in the morning its like having a car who’s petrol tank has been filled for free. Plus electric car means less maintenance. This when done by lakhs of Indian middle class families will surely give a blow to these nations that sell us energy and use it to conduct terror attacks on our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-i-dont-trust-the-government&quot;&gt;Why I don’t trust the government&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might say the government is doing solar power projects and big companies are involved in it, so why should we do it. I say why not? We know the speed of the government, we know that government can play politics and it’s easy for them to get bribes from few power companies than some how forcing 1 crore or so middle class families to bribe them just because we now produce our won power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next a central provider means transmission losses, these can be cut if power can be obtained from our roof tops. Even if its power companies are private, you can’t say there is no politics and corruption inside those corporates. So power lines may fail one day. There is chance of having monopolies and duopolies so nothing good happens to us ultimately which roof top solar avoids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;History does not give the weak and oppressed much chance. It gave us a chance in 1940’s as Hitler tried to invade Britain and we used it to gain independence. Now I feel we are getting a rare chance to circumvent politicians, religion, corporates who are oppressing us now to get partial power independence. Let’s grab it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be if 10 billion dollars are saved a year, may be out of that 100 million might be put for public use after 99% corruption, and possibly in that some money might be used to convert the dirt road I live in into a tar road, thus improving my standard of my living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its all in your hands.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Neighbours Watch on Myanmar’s Killings</title><link href="/power/politics/asia/class%20warfare/myanmar/2021/03/02/why-neighbours-watch-on-myanmar-s-killings.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Neighbours Watch on Myanmar&apos;s Killings" /><published>2021-03-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-03-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/power/politics/asia/class%20warfare/myanmar/2021/03/02/why-neighbours-watch-on-myanmar-s-killings</id><content type="html" xml:base="/power/politics/asia/class%20warfare/myanmar/2021/03/02/why-neighbours-watch-on-myanmar-s-killings.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.worldtravelguide.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/Think-Myanmar-Yangon-120786004-petrzurek-copy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tuned into Al-Jazeera today and predictably the military Junta in Myanmar has started to fire live ammunition into the crowds. My initial instinct was Myanmar is our sister nation, we share more history and culture with it. Its writing looks like more of old Tamil, Telugu and Kannada as they were developed curved representations so that it could be written on palm  leaves without tearing it. Myanmar is a Buddhist nation, a religion thats purely Indo-Napalese, but what’s Nepal without India? They are 100% our blood. But its neighbours are mute. Only Indonesia is trying to rake up the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People might say don’t get involved in politics, stay safe, but it because of evil minds and bad politics, lives are lost in Myanmar. For people of a country to prosper, it’s not just that country, even its neighbours should be right. Unfortunately Myanmar has got wrong neighbours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact if people of Myanmar were okay for military intervention by its neighbours, then Indian and Bangladeshi artillery should be firing, troops should be amassing on Myanmar while Indian missiles streak in and strike their military targets thus weakening them and giving the people an upper hand. Yet we act as though people of our blood when killed it doesn’t matter. Why so?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bangladesh&quot;&gt;Bangladesh&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://assetsds.cdnedge.bluemix.net/sites/default/files/styles/very_big_1/public/feature/images/2021/02/28/mushtaq-.jpg?itok=wjBikphv&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Slain Bengali Writer Mushtaq Ahmed&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its funny. Bangladesh was born because the will of people there was oppressed by Pakistan so much that people started to pour into India. And having limited resources and India being starving nation then, we had to fix it. We simply can’t keep feeding people thrown out by our neighbour, so we indulged in war, defeated Pakistan, and may be we were paid damages thus offsetting loss. Yes war is Economics, don’t mistake it. Ever wonder why the world watches 1000’s killed in Africa today? There is no money there. None will thank, plead guilty and pay you if you conquer that hell infested land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay coming back to Bangladesh. Today its just the opposite. We have got Bengali government that has enacted  Digital Security Act (DSA), arrested people and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/02/26/world/asia/bangladesh-mushtaq-ahmed-dead.html&quot;&gt;one prominent guy even died in custody for a facebook post&lt;/a&gt;. Mushtaq Ahmed is his name. Bengalis are rising up against the government and government needs to quell them. Now this situation is like very similar to Myanmar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So think, the Bengali government wants to silence its own people, now how can it say to Myanmar that please let freedom of public opinion in your nation while I silence my people with DSA?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;india&quot;&gt;India&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://stb.india.com/bengali/sites/default/files/styles/zm_700x400/public/2014/10/05/29672-modi10514.jpg?itok=fhJdH6OK&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Our Modi Mastan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I talk about India? Oh God! This Modi. All of a sudden farm bills are brought into force without discussion in parliament. PubG and TikTok are ban with claims that they will hurt Chinese economy, thats the intelligence this government has. Now all of a sudden there is law, once gain without discussion in parliament on OTT platform regulation. When people revolted against polluting Vedanta copper plants in Thuthukudi, they were shot and killed like dogs and neither Modi or Edapaadi Palanisamy has been hung for it. Protesting farmers are ignored, the PM won’t speak with them. This government is experimenting all ways to undermine democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why on Earth India under such a dictator would even want to raise a hair against Myanmar? In fact Modi and his team will be observing taking notes from the Junta so that BJP can gain absolute power here in India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;thailand&quot;&gt;Thailand&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bf/King_Rama_X_official_%28crop%29.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;I think Thai’s are supposed to worship this guy as God&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thailand though its Priminister is elected democratically, none can touch its monarchy. They can do what they want and none can question them. Unfortunately people of Myanmar are part of 10,000+ year old east Asian culture where there are classes. the class of Kings, the class of Bosses, the class of Workers, the lower classes cannot question the upper ones, it’s a huge taboo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact if I visit Thailand, I could get a life term just for writing these words. That’s how worst Thailand is. Do you think Thailand will raise its voice against similar minded oppressive Junta?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-for-myanmar&quot;&gt;What’s for Myanmar&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.vanityfair.com/photos/54ca8e44b624d6910574b5ea/master/w_2560%2Cc_limit/image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Aung Sung Su Kyi - The should be Priminister of Myanmar&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We the people of India should not forget that Myanmar is facing these huge problems and its people are left helpless because non democratic nature of countries surrounding it. First we as Indians should try to make our country more democratic so that our neighbours become democratic too, and help will arrive if one day we too are oppressed by Modi, Amit Shah or the Gandhis or who ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember this is not just Myanmar’s problem. This is a class war between people who think who can control public and public who think they should be having voice. This war is taking place in the deepest regions of Africa, in the companies I worked, and in the glittering place called USA. There is always and oppressor and oppressed. The oppressor is always afraid of free speech, alternate opinion and truth leaking out. I hope humans are smart enough to break open it. I hope people around the world start seeing this as a local problem in many places and unite to fight the oppressors who oppress us and the oppressor within us which wants to conquer the Universe and become The God.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>