<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-10-16T20:50:55+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Installing Ruby 3.0.2 on Mac M1</title><link href="/apple/mac/m1/programming/ruby/asdf/2021/10/16/installing-ruby-3-0-2-on-mac-m1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Installing Ruby 3.0.2 on Mac M1" /><published>2021-10-16T20:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-10-16T20:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/apple/mac/m1/programming/ruby/asdf/2021/10/16/installing-ruby-3-0-2-on-mac-m1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/apple/mac/m1/programming/ruby/asdf/2021/10/16/installing-ruby-3-0-2-on-mac-m1.html">&lt;p&gt;I was going through some of my personal projects, some were on Ruby 3.0.0, some were on Ruby 3.0.1. When ever I pushed code for my startup (I hope it won’t become a fucked up), it said ‘common upgrade to Ruby 3.0.2’. Yes it should be done, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2021/07/07/ruby-3-0-2-released/&quot;&gt;there are some security fixes that you should not ignore&lt;/a&gt;, so do upgrade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fired up my terminal and typed &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;asdf install ruby 3.0.2&lt;/code&gt;, for some suprising reason it said 3.0.2 does not exists, that is the formulas are not updated may be. I even thought of removing asdf and move to trusted RVM, but then digging documentation, I gave this command&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ ASDF_RUBY_BUILD_VERSION=master arch -x86_64  asdf install ruby 3.0.2
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ASDF_RUBY_BUILD_VERSION=master&lt;/code&gt; tells that to pull from master branch of asdf ruby, so its kinda latest, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;arch -x86_64&lt;/code&gt; tells that we must compile it like X86 architecture and not for Mac M1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this it installed 3.0.2 like charm and I ported my project from 3.0.1 to 3.0.2 and pushed it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was going through some of my personal projects, some were on Ruby 3.0.0, some were on Ruby 3.0.1. When ever I pushed code for my startup (I hope it won’t become a fucked up), it said ‘common upgrade to Ruby 3.0.2’. Yes it should be done, there are some security fixes that you should not ignore, so do upgrade.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BDD kills software industry productivity</title><link href="/2021/10/09/bdd-kills-software-industry-productivity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BDD kills software industry productivity" /><published>2021-10-09T14:31:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-10-09T14:31:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/10/09/bdd-kills-software-industry-productivity</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/09/bdd-kills-software-industry-productivity.html">&lt;p&gt;Software Industry is a knowledge industry, it’s core value lies in its people, the knowledge stored in their brains, the intelligence they develop and willing work they put in, for some reason even veteran’s I see are creating companies that are business driven, of course business is a key to I.T industry, but the companies are mostly doing Business Driven Development (BDD), which pulls down the productivity out of the company decreases the efficiency of software industry as whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me tel you an example. Recently I took an I.T project, I was supposed to lead it, instead I crashed out of it. I was told to bring up Ruby on Rails software on my laptop, which I did partly, and to complete it I need to take dump of MySQL from server. None seems to know its password. The project manager assigned me tickets even before its done and kept asking me the status of tickets. I got annoyed, he then tried to arrange meeting with management. I was convinced he is a perfect manager, and there is no future for me in this project. He was just a messaging and annoying spam bot. I stopped responding to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project had no tests, it had no documentation, and none seemed to know what is what. This company was business driven, had no idea what right knowledge could do, had no will to empower its employees. Their idea was since I am experienced I will pick it up and generate them riches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was into another reverse e-commerce company before, one funded by Al-Gore, it had subcontracted some of its work to a company in Chennai, and it’s boss was a stupid. This company made lot of money, no doubt, but it made a unsustainable move where it made employees feel working hard and long means they are dedicated and great engineers. Kind of like 996 philosophy by Jack Ma. This company made work lot lot difficult, over here too finding knowledge was hard. I could take time, get the right knowledge and finish the work, but for the boss, if he knows something, then by default every one should know it, an hence work should be finished in half the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I worked hard, but my body took a toll and I had to quit. I am happy that I quit. Even today those employees talk very sad and depressed to me, wheras I have gone to create a new services company, and am creating my own productivity product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-need-kdd-pdd-and-hdd&quot;&gt;We need KDD, PDD and HDD&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tech work is knowledge work really. Many technical projects are there because its not focused on money, but its focuses on passion of people. GNU/Linux, Libre Office, Mastadon, VLC and so on, and they are successful. These are Passion and Happiness Driven Development, some are NDD (Need Driven Development). A for profit company too can have all these attributes. Here is how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;start-with-enough-money-or-will-and-time&quot;&gt;Start with enough money or will and time&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you start a company, you have to meet with lot of uncertainties, you have to have enough money and will to solve it. Trying to start on a dying budget and killing other people (at least mentally) because you do not have enough resources is not the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;do-not-have-project-managers&quot;&gt;Do not have project managers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do you need some one who does politics for a living? And that one just serves as a pipe, delivering messages from one place to another and not much else. Try to get passionate people. If a business proposal does not attract passionate people, then don’t take that business, better beg and survive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;make-sure-knowledge-is-freely-available&quot;&gt;Make sure knowledge is freely available&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In both the case studies / experiences I have told you above, my freedom of communication was restricted, I wasn’t allowed to talk to client freely. In reverse e-commerce company I have to kind of rehearse with my boss on what I would say to the client, if by mistake I told something, he (my boss) would be really pissed. He was like a big brother all the time. Knowledge wasn’t freely available and scientific progress does not work that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If can, invest in systems where employees will get right knowledge sooner, sit with newbies and coach them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;believe-money-will-follow-skill-and-knowledge&quot;&gt;Believe money will follow skill and knowledge&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It happened for me! It will happen for you. Follow your passion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kdd-vs-bdd&quot;&gt;KDD Vs BDD&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current company I run is called &lt;a href=&quot;https://datamaking.com&quot;&gt;DataMaking&lt;/a&gt;, and we are investing in bringing up skills of people. We are boldly rejecting projects that doesn’t deserve to be a software project, and one that does not have a listening leadership. And till now not a single day hs goneby where I went to bed with regret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe in this growth curve:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bdd_vs_kdd.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given same resources and opportunities, a company following BDD will grow fast initially and get profits, but it will plateau out as it will finally start to rely on management and marketing people to fuel growth, but look at the green curve where the company  invested in KDD, it will make a loss initially, but once it has caught it will over take the BDD curve, eventually it too would plateau out if it follows conventional business practices and falls to management guys, the tricks is not to make that happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will that happen in DataMaking? Time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Software Industry is a knowledge industry, it’s core value lies in its people, the knowledge stored in their brains, the intelligence they develop and willing work they put in, for some reason even veteran’s I see are creating companies that are business driven, of course business is a key to I.T industry, but the companies are mostly doing Business Driven Development (BDD), which pulls down the productivity out of the company decreases the efficiency of software industry as whole.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How the Universe could measure Time?</title><link href="/2021/10/07/how-the-universe-could-measure-time.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How the Universe could measure Time?" /><published>2021-10-07T14:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-10-07T14:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/10/07/how-the-universe-could-measure-time</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/07/how-the-universe-could-measure-time.html">&lt;p&gt;I never got sleep for few days when I was studying 11th standard. I learned time is not same for every one. Time might be ticking slow for me because I am on massive Earth, traveling at incredible speeds through space, where’s an atom entering black hole could have much slow rate of tick, may be some where in void stationary space if there were people watching me on earth and the atom thats near black hole, they could be experiencing ticks much faster as their region is relatively mass less, and their clocks in their hand is stationary to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we kind of measure time depending on speed of light which we believe is of constant velocity, but velocity of light is based on time, so there is a circular dependency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog I would like to say how I think this universe keeps track of time. It could be right or wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;time-is-memory-of-state-transitions&quot;&gt;Time is memory of state transitions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say that there is universe, and nothing happens in it, then there is no flow of time. Now say all of a sudden universe switches from state S1 to S2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/time-created.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then if the state S2 and the universe remembers it was in state S1, then we register it as time has passed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;short-time&quot;&gt;Short Time&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say that there is registry of only few states (or state-transitions) available in this universe, then we say the universe is very young.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/short-time.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there another state transition takes place, and the memory of it persists,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/long-time.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;then we say universe has got bit more older.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;could-time-reverse&quot;&gt;Could Time reverse?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say that the universe has gone from state S1 to S4 as shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/time-reversal.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now if there is possibility of universe going back from S4 to S3 by completely forgetting about S4, then we can say time has reversed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/time-reversal-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now if that happens, there is no way of knowing it as there is no memory of S4 in S3, and hence no evidence of time reversal has taken place. May be there is time reversal is happening all the time (nice pun!), and we have no way of knowing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now if time does reverse and universe gots to state S3, then it may or may not take the same path again. The universe may go from S3 to S4, or from S3 to S5 or may be to some other state as shown:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/time-reversal-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-time-travel-may-not-be-possible&quot;&gt;Why Time travel may not be possible?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If universe reverses time we may never be aware of it because sate of the universe includes its memory. Let’s see a scenario as shown in the diagram below&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/time-travel-impossibility.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Universe goes from state S1 to S4, then back to S1, in this case S1 knows that it came from S4, so this is the case of cyclic universe. May be as Sir Roger Penrose suggested universe could go to a state where its just another big bang.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ypjZF6Pdrws?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once S1 remembers state of S4, may be that might affect the next state, may be it might not transition to S2 because of randomness, or if the universe is only deterministic, it will only go to S2 and no other state and so on to finally going to S4 and returning back to S1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a very deterministic cyclic universe, all that had happened will happen again and all that is going to happen would have happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-there-time&quot;&gt;Is there Time?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time is just the memory of states of universe, that’s it. It’s the remembrance of these states we call time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;probabilities--birth-of-new-universe&quot;&gt;Probabilities &amp;amp; Birth of new Universe&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would be interesting to investigate if universe is in state S1, the is the universe is really deterministic? Or it has the chance to take on multiple states as shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/new-universe.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If universe can slip into multiple states from current state, then is there is a probability associated with it? Can that probability be measured?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the universe is in state S1, and it slips into state S4 a special state where there is no memory of S1, then it would look like the birth of a new universe which arose from nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;get-the-diagrams&quot;&gt;Get the diagrams&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can download the diagrams of this blog &lt;a href=&quot;/diagrams/How-universe-keeps-track-of-time.drawio&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I never got sleep for few days when I was studying 11th standard. I learned time is not same for every one. Time might be ticking slow for me because I am on massive Earth, traveling at incredible speeds through space, where’s an atom entering black hole could have much slow rate of tick, may be some where in void stationary space if there were people watching me on earth and the atom thats near black hole, they could be experiencing ticks much faster as their region is relatively mass less, and their clocks in their hand is stationary to them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Still using x86 for asdf on M1 Mac</title><link href="/mac%20m1/programming/ruby/version%20management/asdf/2021/10/05/still-using-x86-for-asdf-on-m1-mac.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Still using x86 for asdf on M1 Mac" /><published>2021-10-05T15:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-10-05T15:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/mac%20m1/programming/ruby/version%20management/asdf/2021/10/05/still-using-x86-for-asdf-on-m1-mac</id><content type="html" xml:base="/mac%20m1/programming/ruby/version%20management/asdf/2021/10/05/still-using-x86-for-asdf-on-m1-mac.html">&lt;p&gt;I have to code for a legacy project using Ruby 2.6.6. I am using M1 Mac and using asdf as my version manager. As soon as I tried&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ asdf install ruby 2.6.6
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It threw out an error, which you can get it &lt;a href=&quot;https://gitlab.com/-/snippets/2184880&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, the system stored it in a log file. Then I remembered that I installed my previous Ruby 3.x using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.driftingruby.com/episodes/a-rubyist-s-apple-m1-review&quot;&gt;this tutorial&lt;/a&gt; from Drifting Ruby. What I need to do now was to specify that we need to use X86 architecture, and so I gave this command&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ arch -x86_64 asdf install ruby 2.6.6
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it worked like charm.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I have to code for a legacy project using Ruby 2.6.6. I am using M1 Mac and using asdf as my version manager. As soon as I tried</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The local body elections in Sithalapakkam</title><link href="/2021/10/05/the-local-body-elections-in-sithalapakkam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The local body elections in Sithalapakkam" /><published>2021-10-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-10-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/10/05/the-local-body-elections-in-sithalapakkam</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/05/the-local-body-elections-in-sithalapakkam.html">&lt;p&gt;Speakers were blaring till yesterday in my road 3rd street, Skylab Avenue, wooing us to vote, it was bloody annoying. I was unable to concentrate with all those noise. It’s local body elections here. DMK people were all at my place, my home received two rice bags, I think a total of 100 Kg of rice and a &lt;em&gt;thukku&lt;/em&gt; from mostly DMK politicians so that we would vote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the other guys, brought in a sari’s and cash, people in my home refused it citing it was insulting, and just few feet away was the 100 Kg rice we received, but that rice and &lt;em&gt;thukku&lt;/em&gt; wasn’t insulting due to some way, may be because it was given by our friends! We have friends who are corrupt. Wonder what it says about us to this world? Any way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how elections in Sithalapakkam is going to be: corrupt, and bribed. People might vote for the politician who bribed them the most. Even after the elections there will be stray dogs and cow shit on the roads, garbage will b overflowing, my street will not have a tar road, I am typing the blog under DMK imposed power cuts, looks like some one stole 2 Lakh tonnes of coal from our power plants and most likely the culprits won’t be found. Ya how will any culprit say that he is guilty? you need to have superior brain for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that’s the state of Sithalapakkam elections. India is long dead, now people with our skin color have taken our freedom and good life away, and we don’t know how to destroy them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is one way however my friends, receive all that you get from the politicians and vote for a person who hasn’t bribed you. May be he is good.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Speakers were blaring till yesterday in my road 3rd street, Skylab Avenue, wooing us to vote, it was bloody annoying. I was unable to concentrate with all those noise. It’s local body elections here. DMK people were all at my place, my home received two rice bags, I think a total of 100 Kg of rice and a thukku from mostly DMK politicians so that we would vote.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dark Tamil Nadu under M.K.Stalin’s Rule</title><link href="/2021/07/29/dark-tamil-nadu-under-m-k-stalins-rule.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark Tamil Nadu under M.K.Stalin&apos;s Rule" /><published>2021-07-29T23:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-07-29T23:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/07/29/dark-tamil-nadu-under-m-k-stalins-rule</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/07/29/dark-tamil-nadu-under-m-k-stalins-rule.html">&lt;p&gt;Today I had a power cut from 8:50 AM to 5 PM. In Edapaddi Palanisami rule these things never happened so much. Some how he  was a good chief minister who kind of kept up his promise. Some how it seems from a Chennai person’s view that DMK could be very much corrupt compared to AIADMK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually ADMK warned the people that if when Stalin came to power, electricity would be cut in many places in Tamil Nadu. May be the DMK guys know to sell away our coal, pocket the money, and blame AIADMK for crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know corruption started in Dravidian movement in a big scale from Karunadhi era, we had massive power cuts during his rule which Jayalalitha fixed it and Edapaadi maintained it. But Stalin seems to be like his father, breaking up things that was fixed during the AIADMK rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Stalin took power I had to take 3 days of leave due to power cuts. I don’t think I am in a company that would tolerate these kind of things, already I am served a notice that my work is going slow. Today would have been the 4th day of leave due to power cut but I was sick due to Covid shot and had to call for a leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though Edapaadi did lick the feet of BJP, I think its better to have a CM who gives us better services than loot us in the name of Drividianism. If we promote DMK &amp;amp; family, the future generations would only see Dravidian movement as a synonym to corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Though this blog was written on 28 Jul 2021, I wasn’t able to publish until 29 Jul 2021 due to frequent power cuts than ran up to midnight.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today I had a power cut from 8:50 AM to 5 PM. In Edapaddi Palanisami rule these things never happened so much. Some how he was a good chief minister who kind of kept up his promise. Some how it seems from a Chennai person’s view that DMK could be very much corrupt compared to AIADMK.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Plugins I would Like to Have in My Chat and Calls</title><link href="/artificial%20intelligence/machine%20learning/data%20science/work/productivity/2021/06/18/the-plugins-i-would-like-to-have-in-my-chat-and-calls.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Plugins I would Like to Have in My Chat and Calls" /><published>2021-06-18T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-18T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/artificial%20intelligence/machine%20learning/data%20science/work/productivity/2021/06/18/the-plugins-i-would-like-to-have-in-my-chat-and-calls</id><content type="html" xml:base="/artificial%20intelligence/machine%20learning/data%20science/work/productivity/2021/06/18/the-plugins-i-would-like-to-have-in-my-chat-and-calls.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1373463/thumbs/o-BORING-MEETING-facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a software developer. Somehow lazy guys seem to dominate this field, and I am lazy. Despite being in this field for nearly 20 years, I do not understand why we have so much meetings. Till this day I do not understand what most people in my meetings talk, but I have to be there. I have no doubt this is the fate of many software developers and office goers out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having said that, and knowing that our life revolves around chat and calls, it would be nice if we have the following plugins in our chat and calling programs to ease life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fake my text plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay this is text based plugin that chat’s with your colleagues on channels like Slack and Teams so that they think you are there. When it cannot chat and finds that its beyond its capacity to handle, only then you get a notification to interfere. When ever you interfere, the algorithm learns and becomes better and handles similar situation well the next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a software developer I need to concentrate hard, and all of a sudden I get a &lt;em&gt;Hey&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Hi&lt;/em&gt; in my chat that just breaks down the thought data structure I had built up in my brain, and its annoying. This plugin will save me lot of time and make me lot productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dress me up plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/EHE-GcCOktU?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live in Chennai, a hot place. I wear a light dress, and for meetings I switch dresses so that I look professional. Long ago there was a mobile app which you can point at any one and it will show them naked real time, the A.I algorithm will undress them and show to you. Why can’t we have an algorithms that does the reverse where it dresses one up. No matter what ever I wear or not wear, this will dress me up and show like I am a pro. This will save lot of world’s time, won’t it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fake me plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the ultimate plugin that will fake you entirely so that there is no need for you to be in front of the cam. May be it would also talk for you and be your replacement virtually. May be that’s in far future. For now, your zoom could be hooked up to your earpods where you will talk, and this plugin will fake your camera feed and make you appear real to others while you take a stroll in the park listening to meeting and talking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brief me up plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the meeting time one does not talk, one does listen to a boring talker, thats utter waste of time. Given that humans are poor communicators, it would be nice if there is a plugin that would prepare a highlight video feed or few lines of text which summarizes the entire meeting. This would save us lot of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world of artificial intelligence has excellent applications to be cracked. Jump in! May be &lt;a href=&quot;https://neuralink.com/&quot;&gt;Neural Link&lt;/a&gt; will make humanity just one brain and eliminate all meetings.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DMK trying to give god back to people</title><link href="/religion/hinduism/india/tamilnadu/dmk/politics/2021/06/12/dmk-trying-to-give-god-back-to-people.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DMK trying to give god back to people" /><published>2021-06-12T20:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-12T20:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/religion/hinduism/india/tamilnadu/dmk/politics/2021/06/12/dmk-trying-to-give-god-back-to-people</id><content type="html" xml:base="/religion/hinduism/india/tamilnadu/dmk/politics/2021/06/12/dmk-trying-to-give-god-back-to-people.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.siasat.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/DMK-logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Rising Sun - DMK Logo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t like DMK for many reasons. The first is dynastic politics. We all know who is the next chief minister after Stalin is. It’s hard to believe none in DMK did not work as much as Stalin to deserve the CM post, and it’s kind of funny to know why there wasn’t a vote or a contender to Stalin when he tried to become the leader of DMK, that too when DMK claims that it’s a party that respects democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from that DMK is the epitome of corruption, possibly the most corrupt organization on this planet. It’s said that they have made looting a scientific process thus making it untraceable. I would have been very happy if something other than DMK, ADMK came to power in Tamil Nadu. Any way…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was seeing the news today. What DMK is doing to Hinduism is great. Actually in Hinduism God is equal to all, so just a particular Brahmin caste doing poojai in temples is bullshit, DMK is trying to reverse that. Looks like very soon any one from any caste can become a poosaari and do poojai in temple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality any one can be a brahmin, the title brahmin should not be given to someone who is been born to a brahmin, but it should be given to some one having very great personal qualities. For example A.P.J.Abdul Kalaam fits very perfectly into the description of a brahmin, but he is a staunch Muslim and yet a brahmin. Some how things changed and now a person born to a person who claims he is a brahmin is calling himself a Brahmin. Somewhere down the line things were hijacked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/K0HqkC0jbJ8?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So letting all caste people to become poosari, DMK is demolishing the myth that God is accessible to us only via brahmins, a myth that has gripped this nation since Aryans set foot on the Indus valley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing is, if you have noticed, women in our house do the poojai mostly. Before Aryanism took over, women in society were priests. In ancient India there was almost no difference between a man and a woman. After the arrival of Aryanism, women’s rights got reduced and they were pushed away from God at least in the public places. The arrival of Abrahamic religions, namely Christianity and Islam, cemented the myth that women are subordinate to men. DMK is trying to reverse that. Now women too can become priests in Tamil temples. That’s great. In fact Amman cult which is relatively untouched by Ariyanism and other invasions still has many temples who’s priests are women. Non vegetarian is served in the temple as prasatham, animal sacrifices are allowed. DMK has always stood by women’s rights and these changes are laudable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally this language issue. God is equal to all and could be called out in any language, but the myth that Sanskrit is a deiva bashai and Tamil is a eecha bashai has been spread by Aryans. Till today a Tamil can’t understand what the poosari in Temple tells to the gods when he prays for him. One sould be able to understand what the poosari says to God. In Tamil Nadu Tamil should be spoken to Gods, not some extinct language. DMK is bring Tamil into temples, now any one will know what is been prayed for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thank Stalin for these stuff. Despite giving power cuts and disturbing my tranquility and profession he is doing good to make god equal to all. I thank him and the DMK and wish all the very best to Dravidian movements success. the ultimate success would be eliminate God itself and make people see the truth, but it’s not the right time to take such drastic move.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rising Sun - DMK Logo</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Living without killing is morally satisfying</title><link href="/2021/06/02/living-without-killing-is-morally-satisfying.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Living without killing is morally satisfying" /><published>2021-06-02T23:06:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-02T23:06:00+05:30</updated><id>/2021/06/02/living-without-killing-is-morally-satisfying</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/06/02/living-without-killing-is-morally-satisfying.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://clarionindia.net/portal/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/meat-shop-kolkata-india.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corona is causing problems to many, but for me till now it has been a blessing in disguise. One of the many things it has done to me is to make me work from home. It was the dream of many I.T professionals to work from anywhere because we knew it could be done. What the management guys can’t achieve was achieved by a virus without a brain. No wonder! No way a virus has less brains than management people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is not about that. It’s about living without eating non-vegetarian. I was an avid meat eater, I cannot live without meat. I eat any meat, my family is bit different. My family is an orthodox one, so they should buy meat from a trusted muslim, the animal should be sacrificed in halal way so that we do not bring in bad spirits into the house. Sea food is not considered muslim, so its okay to buy from any one, but now looking at fisher folks and how indisciplined they are with hygiene, its a no now, possibly till this pandemic ends. So after lockdown, when the shops were closed and meat was available only from apps, who knows how they were cut? There was no meat in my home. It is now totally vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though I loved meat very much, before eating it I would always imagine how the animal would have suffered while it was been cut alive. It’s a conscious life! How the fish would have gasped for breadth like a dying corona patient just because some human would be happy in the near future because of its death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We humans don’t want to be killed, cut up, and chewed up by any other thing, but we do it shamelessly to other species. I think of all these things and eat meat. I even suspected if I was addicted to non-vegetarian, and especially biriyani.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost all religions born in India ban the killing of conscious life for ones pleasure. It’s a very unique Indian idea, seen almost no where in this world where we have realize our happiness should not be based on suffering of a conscious being. It’s a very very unique Indian thought. Being an Indian, I would say thinking about the animals suffering and sacrifice for me crossing my mind before I start to eat is a no-brainer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming to my addiction, I really suspected that I was addicted to non-vegetarian food, but after the meat ban in my home, I am now living as vegetarian, and I am vindicated from having tho think “am I addicted meat?”. May be I am not addicted to animal meat. Most importantly knowing that my life is not based upon suffering of conscious being is a refreshing and morally satisfying thought.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Failed start for Stalin</title><link href="/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/stalin/covid/2021/05/13/failed-start-for-stalin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Failed start for Stalin" /><published>2021-05-13T23:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-05-13T23:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/stalin/covid/2021/05/13/failed-start-for-stalin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tamilnadu/politics/dmk/stalin/covid/2021/05/13/failed-start-for-stalin.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.veethi.com/images/people/fullsize/M._K._Stalin_20170709020708.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would rather say that M.K.Stalin is having a failed start of his CM post. It was funny when he announced lockdown, he himself ignored Corona and campaigned shamelessly, more of his shamelessness was revealed when he asked for donations from people for the CM fund to fight Corona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would gather people and ask votes and spread the disease, then when he comes to power he will say the disease has gone beyond control, would not take responsibility for it, then ask for money to correct his mistake. It’s a miserable failure of leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now coming to the lockdown. His implementation of the lockdown is funny. It’s night 11:12 now, and the ban was supposed to be in place since 12 noon, just now a bike passed my door. Where the heck is the ban? Just an hour ago I think the local DMK leader car (without flag) crossed my house in Sithalapakkam. News reports of heavy traffic in Saidapet and Guindy Chennai. He put an excellent policy, and just like Modi he is unable to implement it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They say 10,000 police are in Chennai implementing the ban, lol! I wonder if the account books are recording crores of rupees are spent in implementing the ban.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would rather say DMK itself is a failed party. It’s values are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not to promote religion. But many in the party are religious.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To be democratic. You know how Stalin rose up to power.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To give equal chance at leadership to all. you know most leaders are from a few families.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To promote Tamil. This blog is written by a Tamilian and is in English. Kanimozhi’s school teaches in English.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not to loot. We all know that DMK is THE KING of looting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMK is not a dravidian party, its a party to make Udhayanidhi Stalin the Chief minister because no one in DMK has worked as hard for the party :D. All other party member’s except Udhyanidhi have no balls it seems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need a party that is Democratic, Drvidian, Atheistic, that grows Tamil and better’s the lifes of Tamilians, gives chance to people who love people, and bubbles up leaders than dynasty. Will Tamils ever wake up and create this change?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>