<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-10-15T13:54:52+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Good that Chennai people have lost trust in Tamilnadu</title><link href="/2024/10/15/good-that-chennai-people-have-lost-trust-in-tamilnadu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Good that Chennai people have lost trust in Tamilnadu" /><published>2024-10-15T13:53:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-10-15T13:53:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/10/15/good-that-chennai-people-have-lost-trust-in-tamilnadu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/10/15/good-that-chennai-people-have-lost-trust-in-tamilnadu.html">&lt;p&gt;It takes good education and freedom of thought to see through the glare. For millennium we Indians were made to believe a ruler, be it ancient Kings, the British or the bogus democracy called India. At least now, in the time of crisis, I am happy that people of Chennai have stopped trusting the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mudichur-being-vacated&quot;&gt;Mudichur being vacated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People of Mudichur, near Tambaram are vacating their homes because of rain warning. I think it was flooded atleast twice in the past, the government did nothing about it. Now rather than being there under the reign of unhelpful government, people are abandoning that place. Thats good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;parking-on-velacherrys-bridge&quot;&gt;Parking on Velacherry’s bridge&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people have parked their cars on Velacherry bridge to avoid the vechiles from getting drowned. They are not believing the fucking Tamilnadu governments Chennai flood control system. We know who comes to power in Tamilnadu, and how they come tp power. Is it because of merit? Is it because that person has done something good to the nation? No. No. We all know how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder how people even bought property in Velacherry? It is bough area and naturally it will get flooded. I wonder why the government even allowed people to settle there? I still feel strongly that Velacherry and Pallikaranai should be returned back to nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To return back to nature, the Tamilnadu government should stop all registration of properties in that region, so no new real estate activity takes place. This will plunge the value of property over there. The government I feel should put restriction to stop any human building activity. May be in the span of 100 years it will become a swamp again and would absorb some amount of floods Chennai gets in future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be the citizens of Velacherry can sue Chennai corporation of Cheating them, making them believe that Velacherry is a habitable area, thus draining their millions. I wish the court will force the government to buy back the property from people in Velacherry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why&quot;&gt;Why?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think 20cm of rain per day in Chennai is drainable (that’s what government claims, we do not know how much corruption and malpractice are involved), the question is why not 40cm?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is Chennai storing rain water to be used in drought months? If not, why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How much water is sent to the ocean? Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why Chennai can host a F4 car race, air show, but not fend of flooding? It’s just water that comes down, not molten metal. Are we so tech incompetant?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many engineering colleges in and around Chennai, are they sleeping? Why can they even publish a proposal? If they can’t what’s the use of their existence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;quit-chennai&quot;&gt;Quit Chennai&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If such incompetent, corrupt governments are ruling Chennai, people think, why you should buy a property in Chennai? Why you must work here with higher spending, higher pollution, higher risk of floods, murders and rowdyism, drugs and intolerable traffic, garbage, stray dogs and cows to name a few? Why can’t we have stable power supply, in rain? Why are we so weak in technology to achieve these?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It takes good education and freedom of thought to see through the glare. For millennium we Indians were made to believe a ruler, be it ancient Kings, the British or the bogus democracy called India. At least now, in the time of crisis, I am happy that people of Chennai have stopped trusting the government.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Times I felt bad using Ruby on Rails</title><link href="/2024/10/10/times-i-felt-bad-using-ruby-on-rails.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Times I felt bad using Ruby on Rails" /><published>2024-10-10T08:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-10-10T08:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/10/10/times-i-felt-bad-using-ruby-on-rails</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/10/10/times-i-felt-bad-using-ruby-on-rails.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/34/1936_Paraparaumu_train_derailment_rescue_work.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your happiness does not depend just on your intelligence, but also on the place, and community you live in. Imagine Galileo amongst the Christians, helpless and hopeless because he was right, but to the world around him, he was wrong, a witch, and punishable. What should I do in situations like this? I have no clue. I am not even Galileo, and the world will forget me as soon as I die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog, I would like to note that I regret using Rails because of people around me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;zanec&quot;&gt;Zanec&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first was this company, Zanec. Till then, I was involved in small Rails projects and large PHP projects, but in Zanec when I could code fully in Rails, I was happy. It was for a real estate website, &lt;a href=&quot;https://places.com&quot;&gt;https://places.com&lt;/a&gt;. I don’t think places work now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, at that time, we had to work with a Ukrainian called Dennis Volchov or something, I am not sure of his name. And at that time, Ukraine was invaded by Russia (2014). This Dennis does not know Rails, half-baked in Ruby, and he insisted that Rails migrations are antipattern; he does not want migrations, no matter what we said, he did not want it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a Rails guy, it was frustrating for me. According to him, SQL (Data Definition Language) should be noted in a file, he simply did not understand what migrations are and how easy it is to reverse them. He did not like the concept of a lot of migration files in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;db/migrate&lt;/code&gt; directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost hope and thought this was my fate. But by some miracle, the client believed in me, and though he did not stop Dennis sabotaging Rails migrations, he did support me on many occasions. The client name was Joe Mathew, he was from a company called Software Worx, which he ran. Till that date, he was the best client I ever had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also shielded me from internal politics at Zanec, without which I wouldn’t have lasted so long. I am a technician, not a politician.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trumatics&quot;&gt;Trumatics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I met an excellent guy at Zanec called Umashankar (Uma as we called him). I was captivated by his philosophy and leadership. He created a company called Trumatics, I wanted to join it, and he let me in. Things did go well initially. But then, when it came to the Rails project, Uma did not understand incrementally building a Database as we went along with the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For him, the database should be defined first using Entity Relationship Diagrams (ERD), and then the database should be created, and only then should the app be coded. He is an affirmative person, but he did let me do the project in my own way, maybe I explained to him, and he got to know what Rails was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike the people who ran Zanec, he was not a person who totally lost touch with tech, so he let me do my way. I think I worked on a project for a company named Zynalog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as my bad time would have it, something changed in him, he stated to shout at me,  at the people in office in an intense way, and we had no clue what was going on. One day I couldn’t bear the pressure, and though I was one of the directors of the company, I quit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the last things I knew about him was that he was bad-mouthing about me, but who cares? I am sure people who are closely aligned to facts have better chance of succeeding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a few years back we did have a friendly call where he was saying how engineers (freshers) knew nothing, and should be significantly coached up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dream of creating a better Zanec, that would be technically good, and a company that would be loved by employees went up in smoke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;healthicity&quot;&gt;HealthiCity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I worked for a company called HealthiCity, and I would say that its VP Kekin Gada was my best client to date. In the JD it was said that one must have basic / little knowledge of React. I thought there would be a front-end developer, and when he is absent, I would need to consult him and make some minor front-end changes. The interview was about Ruby, and it was nothing for me. I cleared it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once in the company, I regretted,  I was made to learn ReactJs, it sucked. &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/29/rails-killed-reactjs-now-its-burning-the-corpse.html&quot;&gt;Rails had already killed ReactJs even before it was born&lt;/a&gt;. I wondered what made someone who claimed they knew Rails, make a Rails developer code in ReactJS?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out the people in HealthiCity are from a services company called Big binary, and for them, ReactJS is like God, no matter how unproductive it is, it should be used in the Rails project. They made the mistake of choosing React, and since the top leadership till now has failed to acknowledge their mistake, they are making people code in ReactJS + Rails at gunpoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was forced to learn ReactJS; there was a class for ReactJS held, I was forced to code CSS; and I don’t know if blue goes well with orange or what. I don’t give a damn about font and design. Design bugs were assigned to me. It was hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One good thing born out of this was &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/injee&quot;&gt;Injee&lt;/a&gt;. Since I needed to learn ReactJS, I needed a back end, I thought, why not code a zero-configuration instant backend, and so was born Injee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a back-end developer who was forced to learn front-end against my will, but I feel Injee will free up front-end developers to learn back-end. So even though I suffered, it led me to create something that will reduce the suffering of others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;would-love-to-work-with-pure-rails-people&quot;&gt;Would love to work with pure Rails people&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/Shanghai_maglev_train.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still think Rails is one of the best frameworks for developing web apps. Though my knowledge of &lt;a href=&quot;https://clojure.org/&quot;&gt;Clojure&lt;/a&gt; is challenging it. I would like to work with pure Rails people. That would be really refreshing. In my country, India, most people are half-baked when it comes to knowledge of tech. They are willing to work extra hard but are not willing to come out of their pea-brain thought, and people are not willing to change, be efficient and follow the Rails way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want really stable, awesome apps created, contact me, and I will be able to help you. If you are a pure  Rails person and want me to work with you, I am thrilled.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Not surprised that Tamilnadu has become breeding ground of Islamic terrorists</title><link href="/2024/10/02/not-surprised-that-tamilnadu-has-become-breeding-ground-of-islamic-terrorists.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Not surprised that Tamilnadu has become breeding ground of Islamic terrorists" /><published>2024-10-02T11:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-10-02T11:47:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/10/02/not-surprised-that-tamilnadu-has-become-breeding-ground-of-islamic-terrorists</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/10/02/not-surprised-that-tamilnadu-has-become-breeding-ground-of-islamic-terrorists.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/banner-for-hizbollah-leader-in-chennai/big-banner-raised-for-the-slain-hezbollah-terrorist-leader-v0-lm8c7b0hbxrd1.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Tamils are good at keeping the BJP and RSS at bay. They are a terrorist organization that revolve around the myth that God exists, and some Sanskrit chants will take you to the foot of the God. But we Tamils have turned a bind eye to rise of Islamic terrorist in our land. Islam is no different from Hinduism, it too revolves around the myth of God, and it replaces Sanskrit with Arabic, that’s it. It’s more foreign to us than Hinduism, which mostly bred in our country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recognize North Indian as occupiers and destroyers of our Tamil culture, trying to impose their culture, language and religion on us, it could be once Tamil was spoken in Harappa and well into Afghanistan, but look what are we reduced to now, but if we leave Islam to take hold of land, we will become like the Christian of Lebanon, a people willing for peace but dragged into war due to Jihadist ideals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It worries me to the fact that a big banner has been erected for slain Hezbollah leader in Chennai.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://archive.org/download/banner-for-hizbollah-leader-in-chennai/big-banner-raised-for-the-slain-hezbollah-terrorist-leader-v0-145g9lrgbxrd1.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally I want India to get closer to Israel, yes there are extremist Jewish elements in Israel, but they are muted. I want India to get closer to Israel to tap into the strides they have made in defence, and in science and technology. When India denies Tamil Nadu of its rightful share of river water, and we just get polluted water from our neighbouring states, we need a country like Israel to build desalination plants for us. We India face Islamic threat from Pakistan and now from radicalizing Bangladesh, we may need to fight multi front war soon, for that we need to learn from Israel, the techniques on how they constantly survive Arab assault. We also need to learn a lot from Israeli intelligence service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-are-not-at-all-shamed&quot;&gt;We are not at all shamed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel we Indians need to be shameful that we lost to religion, if we hadn’t been religious, Pakistan and Bangladesh would have been our land. India I feel should be a progressive state that depends on science, and not on old books that say that it’s because of God everything happens, that’s rubbish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though we have lost so much of territory, and even though we lag the world so much in GDP, scientific progress and so on, we Indians are not at all shamed, and we don’t realize religion is a chain that has tied us down. Without having sense of what has happened and what’s going on, how are we any better than a corpse? I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rise-of-islamic-terrorism-in-tamilnadu&quot;&gt;Rise of Islamic terrorism in Tamilnadu&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The governments of Tamil Nadu as well as in Kerala, just because they want to oppose the rise of BJP, they are sympathising with Islamist who long for power and who could be holding hands with Arab terrorists. It’s a dire threat to India I feel. Muslim children are thought to believe their Mosques and Imams blind, so if a imam is radicalized, a lot of Muslim kids will think what he says is the interpretation of Quran and could be converted into a terrorist at the flick of a switch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not long ago, may be 1.5 to 2 years, a Islamic terrorist tried to convert a LPG cylinder as a bob, placed it in a car and detonated it in Coimbatore. Thankfully, he is not well-trained and his sloppy bomb did not cause severe damage. But do you know what story was circulated in Tamil Nadu? It was said that some cylinder transported in a car by a poor Muslim guy accidentally detonated. It’s to that lengths the DMK went to shield the terrorist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blast at Rameshwarm cafe in Bangalore too I think has tie-ups with Chennai, and people here gossip that the Sri Lankan church bombings have been coordinated from Mannadi, Chennai. But the Tamilian DMK government turns a blind eye. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;may-be-money-laundering&quot;&gt;May be money laundering&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.wionews.com/sites/default/files/styles/story_page/public/2024/07/25/445590-tamilnaduuae.png?imwidth=400&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not long ago, we know Stalin visited the Middle East and spoke with Arab leaders. DMK says it’s a state visit, but people gossip that it’s money laundering. The looted money from us goes to Arabs, and they reinvest it here so that it becomes white. Do you think Arab will help Stalin without any agenda? How can we be sure that they haven’t commanded Stalin to turn a blind eye toward Islamic terrorism, and radicalization of Tamil Nadu?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why if NIA officials enter Mannadi, Chennai, Muslims block them and hinder the investigation and DMK does nothing about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wake-up-tamils&quot;&gt;Wake up Tamils!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like RSS and BJP which are radical elements in India and are curse to our nation, so are Islamic parties. Unless we Tamils wake up and remove from power the DMK which has tie-up with Islamic parties and Arab leader who openly back Jihadist in the name of Quran and Allah, we Tamil Nadu will become like another Palestine, being invaded by Sri Lanka weary of Islamic attacks from us, the world will be cut out from us, women will be converted to slaves in their own home, all miseries of religion will descend upon us. Do you want such a Tamil Nadu?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Better economists, than donors as our leaders</title><link href="/2024/09/29/better-economists-than-donors-as-our-leaders.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Better economists, than donors as our leaders" /><published>2024-09-29T18:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-09-29T18:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/09/29/better-economists-than-donors-as-our-leaders</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/09/29/better-economists-than-donors-as-our-leaders.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/9d/Shri_P._Chidambaram_taking_charge_of_the_Union_Finance_Minister%2C_in_New_Delhi_on_August_01%2C_2012.jpg/1038px-Shri_P._Chidambaram_taking_charge_of_the_Union_Finance_Minister%2C_in_New_Delhi_on_August_01%2C_2012.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;P. Chidambaram&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vijayakanth donated a lot, and wanted to be our CM. Now Vijay is following his path as sun has set down on his film career. Let’s say that Vijay has 10,000 crores of wealth, even if he donates everything, do you think it will be enough to solve Tamilnadu’s problems?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might donate to get publicity, but in reality apart from it buying temporary loyalty from some, it does nothing more. Yes, some might think that person who donate are the saviours of Tamilnadu, but they are fools I say. They should do the maths and will quickly realize donations does not do a dent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need economists for our land, these are people who are trained in history of knowledge, they better know how to distribute wealth, and where to put it so that there is maximum yield. For example Manmohan Singh did liberalization, and I type this blog on a Mac (but don’t buy Mac, I was a stupid and I bought it), if liberalization did not take place, may be the computers we have on this planet might be very crude. India’s electronics options would have been very limited, and the world wouldn’t have had Indian minds to design a better product. Liberalization is good. Manmohan also secured a place for India in ITER. Imagine we’re having super cheap fusion energy, say in 200 years from now. He did not build Ram temples, and do anna dhanam! He knew what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly he had an alliance with DMK, which is super corrupt, and it brought him down, of course the congress had and still has a very weak leadership, it was not based on merit, but based on bloodline, so he wasn’t able to manurer as much as he liked. His period, under Narashima Rao and he as Prime Minister, is a golden period for Indian economics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want my fellow Tamils to wake up, search for  better minds who are highly qualified and educated. Vijay or Vijayakanths shadows won’t do, neither would DMK which has become a family affair, rather than choosing their leader based on one’s work, they use bloodline to choose it. We need someone like Manmohan, and someone may be more. Maybe what about Chidambaram, and congress rule in Tamilnadu? What about Pazha Karupaiyya? He is not an economist, but he can identify one, make him as finance minister of our state, and listen to that one, thus propelling our state possibly to $2 Trillion economy. I would also like to pitch in Palanivel Thiyagarajan, but he is a DMK loyalist. As I said, DMK has lost its soul, I don’t think it has touch with the people, and it’s an absolute waste when it comes to democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s think and talk about it so that we increase the possibility of change.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">P. Chidambaram</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Capistrano, Ruby 3.3.5 - no implicit conversion of nil into String (SSHKit::Runner::ExecuteError)</title><link href="/2024/09/29/capistrano-ruby-3-3-5-no-implicit-conversion-of-nil-into-string-sshkit-runner-executeerror.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Capistrano, Ruby 3.3.5 - no implicit conversion of nil into String (SSHKit::Runner::ExecuteError)" /><published>2024-09-29T18:18:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-09-29T18:18:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/09/29/capistrano-ruby-3-3-5-no-implicit-conversion-of-nil-into-string-sshkit-runner-executeerror</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/09/29/capistrano-ruby-3-3-5-no-implicit-conversion-of-nil-into-string-sshkit-runner-executeerror.html">&lt;p&gt;I was updating my app &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in&quot;&gt;yu7 URL shortener&lt;/a&gt; a while back when this error appeared &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;no implicit conversion of nil into String (SSHKit::Runner::ExecuteError)&lt;/code&gt;. Things seemed to work well on Ruby 3.2.2, but it broke loose on 3.3.5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On investigation, I found out that it was caused by gem &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;net-ssh&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/capistrano/capistrano/issues/2146#issuecomment-1856140815&quot;&gt;https://github.com/capistrano/capistrano/issues/2146#issuecomment-1856140815&lt;/a&gt;. The latest fixed version is available in capistrano 3.1.7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in my &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Gemfile&lt;/code&gt; I changed to this one&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;gem&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;capistrano&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;~&amp;gt; 3.17&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;require: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;false&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cap production deploy&lt;/code&gt; worked like a charm.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was updating my app yu7 URL shortener a while back when this error appeared no implicit conversion of nil into String (SSHKit::Runner::ExecuteError). Things seemed to work well on Ruby 3.2.2, but it broke loose on 3.3.5.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The missing feedback in corporates and companies</title><link href="/2024/09/21/the-missing-feedback-in-corporates-and-companies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The missing feedback in corporates and companies" /><published>2024-09-21T20:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-09-21T20:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/09/21/the-missing-feedback-in-corporates-and-companies</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/09/21/the-missing-feedback-in-corporates-and-companies.html">&lt;p&gt;Not long ago, I had a a call with my boss. It was about a ticket that got delayed. There was a bug in it, I explained that my server-side code was okay, and there is something wrong in the JavaScript library that’s causing this bug. My boss, as usual, was sure I was the culprit, he told me how to debug the Rails app, and I listened even though I had been coding in it more than 15 years. He explained it to me as though I were a kid. I just listened without protesting. No storm lasts forever. I am a mountain range, I weather millions and  billions of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, it turned out that the QA  was an inexperienced or sloppy one, she did not know how to distinguish between a new feature or as bug, and she conveniently called what should be a new feature as bug. Later, I would find out that if our APP was less buggy, the QA would be put on to the noose and asked why there were few bugs. So they frame a new feature as a bug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I coded the new feature, it took some time to understand D3js, but I finished it and was proud of it. The thing is, my boss was absolutely wrong, and he is still thinking he was absolutely right, and I created a bug. He was so sure that the data I sent to the front end was wrong and caused the bug. He never had the intelligence to question, ‘Why did the front-end developer who developed the code for this chart display not check the data integrity and raise it?’. In that case, if I had sent the data wrong, I would have had an instant feedback. Simple!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one of the Machine Learning companies where I was a Director, my co-director suddenly thought 100, with a margin of \(+-\) 20% error means the values ranged from 60 to 120. He wouldn’t budge. I assure you, he passed engineering, and I still wonder how he passed, and I wonder why I chose to work with him. He became s difficult to deal with, so I came out of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In every company, there is a way to give feedback from the more powerful to the less powerful ones, but there is no way for the less powerful ones to grade the more powerful one. That’s a fatal flaw. That’s not democratic. That’s not freedom. If one gives an open opinion in an Indian company, he will find himself boiling in a soup very soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel there must be an anonymous feedback system in every company where one can rate his or her boss, so that the real truth comes out. Otherwise, corporate lifestyles will dominate, and people will believe their destinies are like those of soulless machines and zombies. Fact-less thoughts will dominate brains, and less and less efficient bosses will be created, ruining humanity. We need a reverse feedback system.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Not long ago, I had a a call with my boss. It was about a ticket that got delayed. There was a bug in it, I explained that my server-side code was okay, and there is something wrong in the JavaScript library that’s causing this bug. My boss, as usual, was sure I was the culprit, he told me how to debug the Rails app, and I listened even though I had been coding in it more than 15 years. He explained it to me as though I were a kid. I just listened without protesting. No storm lasts forever. I am a mountain range, I weather millions and billions of them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">ChatGPT beats Youtube on many occasions</title><link href="/2024/08/28/chatgpt-beats-youtube-on-many-occasions.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ChatGPT beats Youtube on many occasions" /><published>2024-08-28T13:25:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-28T13:25:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/28/chatgpt-beats-youtube-on-many-occasions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/28/chatgpt-beats-youtube-on-many-occasions.html">&lt;p&gt;I was watching this video&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3_fcZApGq1I?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to know how much Gold is there in Earth. This video went on blah blah, and I was not able to find out the answer by skipping here and there. I asked ChatGPT this question and here is the answer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chatgpt.com/share/421d6287-bfae-414b-a26f-bb05f73d8a74&quot;&gt;Total Gold on Earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The total amount of gold on Earth is estimated to be around 244,000 metric tons. However, this estimate includes both the gold that has already been mined and the gold that remains in the ground. Here’s a breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mined Gold&lt;/strong&gt;: Approximately 201,296 metric tons of gold have been mined throughout human history.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unmined Gold Reserves&lt;/strong&gt;: The U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) estimates that about 53,000 metric tons of gold are still in the ground and economically viable to extract with current technology.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;These estimates only account for accessible gold. There is also a vast amount of gold deep within the Earth’s core, which is currently inaccessible to us. Some estimates suggest that there could be as much as 1.6 million metric tons of gold in the Earth’s crust and mantle, but this gold is distributed in such low concentrations that it’s not economically feasible to mine it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-severe-problem-with-youtube&quot;&gt;A severe problem with YouTube&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think YouTube forces one to create video’s of length so that it can fit in more ad’s. For a person like me who does not want to waste time and want to get precise and fast information, this is a severe problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to wait and wait in a video, and you don’t know where the answer to the question is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;use-chatgpt-more&quot;&gt;Use ChatGPT more&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel that ChatGPT is a competitor to YouTube as well. Suddenly video have become the least dense material to seek precise information, and that’s good. May be in the future, videos are there just for entertainment, and A.I. will be there for information and productivity stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;videogpt&quot;&gt;VideoGPT?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need an A.I. that can distill information in videos and answer us precisely. I wish OpenAI mines YouTube too so that we have super precise way to seek information than to look at boring videos.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was watching this video</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">POST should return status 201</title><link href="/2024/08/21/post-should-return-status-201.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="POST should return status 201" /><published>2024-08-21T19:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-21T19:51:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/21/post-should-return-status-201</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/21/post-should-return-status-201.html">&lt;p&gt;I have been coding webapp’s for more than 17 years, and I discovered just yesterday that a successful POST should return status 201.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my office, though I am a Ruby on Rails developer, they told me to code in ReactJS too. Things were hieroglyphs, I never understood it, but there I was staring at a ticket, I never finished it. I hated JavaScript, then after learning a bit of React, I started to hate it more. I still can’t believe humans with embarrassing low intelligence exist, that they can invent JavaScript and React.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any ways, to learn React, I need a backend, I can’t keep creating back end for this and that. I started to think if we can have instant backend for front end developers, and I came up with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://injee.codeberg.page/&quot;&gt;injee&lt;/a&gt; (in memory JSON store) project. It served me well, I was able to create frontend apps because I had a ready-made back end all the time. I am still working on injee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not an expert on HTTP protocol, since injee should provide highly standardized API’s my research suggested that a successful POST should return status 201, and not 200.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why I insist that developers should have a side project, or must contribute to open source projects. At work its work work work, you don’t give a thing about your learning, you trade your existence for money, you can’t expect life in it. If I did not have side project I would have never discovered it may be even in next 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason side project I find enhances my soul. May be because it’s not Agile, and I don’t have to touch this depressing JIRA to log my time, I don’t have tell to someone every day I worked. I don’t have to rush because I won’t lose out on my appraisal and slip into poverty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Injee has not been just refreshing to my soul, about 15+ front end developers have been freed from creating a backend. It’s ironic, because in my work I am unable to free myself from JavaScript and ReactJS even though I am a Ruby on Rails developer and never claimed myself as front end guy, but here, to learn front end tech, I was able to create a project that frees up frontend devs from their miseries of creating a back end server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/19199872/best-practice-for-restful-post-response&quot;&gt;‘Best’ practice for restful POST response&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vinaysahni.com/best-practices-for-a-pragmatic-restful-api&quot;&gt;Best Practices for Designing a Pragmatic RESTful API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I have been coding webapp’s for more than 17 years, and I discovered just yesterday that a successful POST should return status 201.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I missed these stuff in my college</title><link href="/2024/08/19/i-missed-these-stuff-in-my-college.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I missed these stuff in my college" /><published>2024-08-19T10:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-19T10:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/19/i-missed-these-stuff-in-my-college</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/19/i-missed-these-stuff-in-my-college.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/e/eb/12-inch_silicon_wafer.jpg/768px-12-inch_silicon_wafer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was young, I disassembled watches, clocks, those times (in 1980’s) it was all mechanical, I could understand how it worked. But when I opened a radio set, I was puzzled. No matter what I did, I could not find how it worked, it just puzzled me, the same stuff happened when I opened a quartz watch and hand held games, there was big black lump with wires from it, and it worked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took up Electronics and Communication Engineering in my college, theoretically I did learn how they worked, but though my degree says I am a first class engineer, I know I am not. I don’t know how to make a PCB, I can’t even solder a resistor to PCB, leave alone soldering a temperature sensitive Zener diode. Though I finished studying electronics engineering., I could not repair a single electronics device in my home. Shame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure none of the staff in my college Panimalar Engineering had a tie-up with engineering firms, they were out of sync with practicality. I am afraid any of them can implement &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/02/task-which-will-fail-99-percent-of-tamilnadus-electronic-engineers.html&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;. It’s not just a problem in my college, it’s a problem India faces, and is facing for decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is said that when my family was in Gandhinagar, Adyar, my granddad rented out apartments, in one of them there was IIT professor of electronics. A sony radio in my home got repaired, and my granddad took it to him, that guy did not say that he cannot repair, he just had the radio in his home for a long time, realizing that he was not an electronics engineer as he claimed, my granddad got the radio back from him and got it repaired from a local shop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder, if engineer is not useful to community, why you call that one a engineer? Why should that person exist in the first place? Won’t it be good if his body is cremated or buried so that he or she will serve as fertilizer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why am I writing this blog? I went into engineering thinking that I can at least repair a radio set, but I came out without even knowing to create a PCB, or to solder a resistor to a PCB. There was nothing seriously practical in my college. I was dismayed. Recently I was searching on the internet to buy a discarded silicon wafer, I did not work in chip manufacturing, I never will, no matter how much I desire, so I thought why can’t I buy a discarded silicon wafer, frame it and hang it on my wall. The miracle of silicon tech is earning me money, I want to honor it and remember it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I searched ebay, and I searched amazon India, and to my surprise they do sell blank silicon wafers, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.in/Ultranano-Silicon-Scientific-Laboratory-Research/dp/B09LV195B4&quot;&gt;here is a n-type one&lt;/a&gt;, they are so cheap, colleges can stockpile it and if they can build a small fab, can teach students how to create a small chips. It will be a excellent learning for electronics students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.in/99-99-Monocrystalline-Semiconductor-Material-Production/dp/B0C4ZQHSKV&quot;&gt;raw silicon been sold&lt;/a&gt;. For th humongous fees colleges demand today, these investments per student is nothing. They can buy it, and along with a induction furnace, graphite crucible and molds, try to cast their own wafers!!! It won’t be perfect, but they can try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be if a colleges does this, may be students now and in future may not feel void when they come out of engineering, they will feel they are engineers. They might be able to solve industrial problems, say when they are in their 3rd year of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skeptical&quot;&gt;Skeptical&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure all engineering colleges are here to extract money from rich parents, definitely they won’t be doing it. May be students should form groups, should pool in investment of say 1 to 5 lakhs, think of problems to solve using electronics, think of how they can build IC’s on wafers, wafers from silicon, buy or forge the instruments need to do it and execute it. Else even 100 years from now, Indian engineers will be waste.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Aryan BJP, Dravidian Kerala</title><link href="/2024/08/16/aryan-bjp-dravidian-kerala.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aryan BJP, Dravidian Kerala" /><published>2024-08-16T11:32:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-16T11:32:00+05:30</updated><id>/2024/08/16/aryan-bjp-dravidian-kerala</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/08/16/aryan-bjp-dravidian-kerala.html">&lt;p&gt;It’s no wonder Modi did not announce Wayanad tragedy as a national disaster. BJP being a party submissive to Aryan culture does want to destroy India’s Dravidian past. It’s not now this has been happening, its been happening for thousands of years. As a Tamilian I can say that lot of Tamil works were destroyed, because Tamils listened to Aryans words. Shankaracharya, the betrayer of Tamils, said that Tamil is an eesha baasha, I think it translates the language of lower class people.  Aryans cannot tolerate Dravidians for some reason, Aryan literature depict us as Asuras, people with evil mind and desire. They even celebrate good Dravidians like Mahabali been killed by their God’s Vishnu who in his incarnations has committed many adharma and atrocities, shamelessly promoted caste and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than another Gujarat, where Brahmin feet lickers went from home to home of Muslims and slaughtered them, this time nature itself has slaughtered a lot of non-Aryans. This, BJP will think is a gift to them by their Gods. Now the BJP’s strategy would be to add to the misery as much as possible so that the communist government in Kerala gets bad name. Well that’s what the stupids in BJP think tank would think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayanad is a tragedy, the timing the disaster happened, they way it happened, the gory way it happened, all are tragic, its scale is very high. I am personally against Kerala, for all its hydrological problems, to cover its corruption, it’s government always blame the Mullai Periyaar dam to steer the public attention and anger onto Tamilnadu. This time it couldn’t do it, it would seem rubbish if it blamed Tamilnadu. Tamilnadu was smart, the next day this tragedy happened it announced Rs 5 crore relief for Kerala, thus stopping any anti-Tamil forces in Kerala making a move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally felt no Tamil should have helped Kerala. In an unjust way they blamed us many times to cover their corruption, and they should be left to suffer. But this blog is not about Tamilian’s feeling of been betrayed by Malayali’s, this is analysis of BJP’s reaction to Wayanad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel BJP has failed the nation by not announcing Wayanad as a national disaster. They have violated Raj dharama of looking at every citizen as equal. If Anatha Padma Sami Temple, or if Guruvaayur Temple got destroyed, will the BJP be so mute? Won’t they announce it as a national tragedy immediately to please the upper caste Hindus?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People of Kerala should not only reject BJP and RSS. They must reject Bharminism, Aryanism. If Sanskrit is spoken in their temples, a Malayali should feel ashamed of it and must strive so that Gods are prayed to in Malayalam. They must realize that Kerala is Dravidian state and Dravidians have got longer and richer history than Aryans who merely walked into our lands and are trying to destroy our culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least in politics Kerala people have got more brains, they have elected a communist government. Why don’t they realize that time for religion is over, and why don’t they reject religion and embrace science and race ahead?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It’s no wonder Modi did not announce Wayanad tragedy as a national disaster. BJP being a party submissive to Aryan culture does want to destroy India’s Dravidian past. It’s not now this has been happening, its been happening for thousands of years. As a Tamilian I can say that lot of Tamil works were destroyed, because Tamils listened to Aryans words. Shankaracharya, the betrayer of Tamils, said that Tamil is an eesha baasha, I think it translates the language of lower class people. Aryans cannot tolerate Dravidians for some reason, Aryan literature depict us as Asuras, people with evil mind and desire. They even celebrate good Dravidians like Mahabali been killed by their God’s Vishnu who in his incarnations has committed many adharma and atrocities, shamelessly promoted caste and so on.</summary></entry></feed>