<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-05-15T10:14:54+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Oruthee, a good movie with few glitches</title><link href="/2022/05/15/oruthee-a-good-movie-with-few-glitches.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Oruthee, a good movie with few glitches" /><published>2022-05-15T10:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-15T10:14:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/05/15/oruthee-a-good-movie-with-few-glitches</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/05/15/oruthee-a-good-movie-with-few-glitches.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.sify.com/uploads/oruthi-ubpmwaaehbcib.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always looked at Malayalam films with amazement. Why can’t we Tamils make films like them? Yes we did have this Jai Bhim which rocked the movie world and kicked off few Vanniyar Terrorist into action for their personal gains, that movie is just one in ten thousand, or perhaps one in a million. The movie that rocked terrorist before was Roja by Maniratnam, terrorist even threw bombs in his home proving his greatness. I also enjoyed Writer and Thaanakaaran recently to be fair with Tamil films.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But some how Malyaalis are able to make films that are believable, relatable and with good stories which we Tamils are unable to do, and Teleugu people really really suck in making movies. I totally avoid Telugu movies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently watched Oruthee, which was good, except but few dramatic scenes. It’s a good movie that shows how easily middle class people are exploited in this nation by rich, how the rich make their hard earned incomes vanish knowing that middle class has no choice. I personally think middle class are the broiler chicken of Indian rich, we are allowed to breed so that we can offer services to the rich and their dynasties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie also shows the foolishness of middle class people trusting the legal services offered by India, but this movie does not show if the legal service finally colludes with the rich and cheats them or does justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie too shows some police officers in Kerala are good people and do want to service the public. In Tamilnadu thats almost extinct! Here people simply do not trust the police. Due to incidents like Thutukudi Masacare; The case of Felix and Jayaraj; Thecase of Vignesh killing by the police, we in Tamilnadu call our police as Kollum Karangal (கொல்லும் கரங்கள்), which means killing hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oruthee is a movie that all middle class people in India, perhaps the middle class of the world should see. It also shows the plight of Kerala, where people can’t find work and had to goto work for nations that support terror activities against us. In that way I am proud of Tamilnadu, despite dynastic politics, a foolish party that worshipped a queen, we are some how able to provide better jobs though not the best. We Tamils are mostly slaves in our own land than being slaves in a foreign land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie also shows the stupid state of Kearla, over there looks like police complaints should be registered in foreign english than their own mother tongue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also like the title, Oruthee (ஒருத்தி) means a single woman, or it can also be interpreted as a fire (ஒரு தீ). It depends the way women see themselves as. We all know how Kannagi saw herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/SvHc5NHfCoc?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The myth of notice period</title><link href="/2022/05/14/the-myth-of-notice-period.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The myth of notice period" /><published>2022-05-14T21:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-14T21:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/05/14/the-myth-of-notice-period</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/05/14/the-myth-of-notice-period.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeih2vzegddcq6wplmlsrs4dhq2r4lqy24ggjcufnaffyuyylq5t7ga.ipfs.dweb.link/redditsave.com_how_to_quit_101-172abv0qyfz81.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sensing hot or cold</title><link href="/2022/05/13/sensing-hot-or-cold.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sensing hot or cold" /><published>2022-05-13T21:56:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-13T21:56:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/05/13/sensing-hot-or-cold</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/05/13/sensing-hot-or-cold.html">&lt;p&gt;When you touch something you sense it’s hot or cold, but my experience tells me that first brain first senses an extreme in temperature and only then it decides if some thing is hot or cold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It happened during cold weather I think, I turned the tap and touched water, I just removed my hand since the water was extreme or very away from my body temperature, and a split second from it I sensed I just touched cold water and not hot so I proceeded further to wash my hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if some one has done research about it, but this pattern seems to be everywhere, the brain gets alert first when something triggers it, then it thinks about it and sees if something is positive or negative (or classifies it).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be this is an energy saving act of brain, if everything is done in parallel and with same energy intensity, then our brain will consume too much energy (which is costly in nature), may be it puts various parts to low energy state and triggers some parts to high energy or processing state after some activation. It’s very similar to we having multiple cores (some very specialized) on our computer and most of them are at sleep most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">When you touch something you sense it’s hot or cold, but my experience tells me that first brain first senses an extreme in temperature and only then it decides if some thing is hot or cold.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Never Derail</title><link href="/2022/05/11/never-derail.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Never Derail" /><published>2022-05-11T11:39:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-11T11:39:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/05/11/never-derail</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/05/11/never-derail.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.etimg.com/thumb/msid-56799366,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-80923,overlay-economictimes/photo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder how they think in 37 signals. According to me Ruby on Rails is a miracle web development framework. they selected very right language Ruby, they seem to have thought about how you can write very messy code with Ruby, so they put up a very opinionated framework called Rails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to think of learning Rails as learning to become an engine driver. Learning to walk is relatively easy; to go to a near by shop located at one’s street corner and buying few things, walking would suffice. If you want to goto a port and transport tonnes of coal to a power station 100 miles away you need a railway infrastructure, and that’s what Rails gives you. You need to learn about it all to become a Rails developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails promise’s one thing, if you obey it’s rules it would work fine, if you derail it, it’s just a pile of mess.  Being a Rails developer, to my astonishment I am seeing this promise come true again and again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog I am going to tell you how Rails was derailed many times in my career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;derailing-by-using-front-end-frameworks&quot;&gt;Derailing by using front end frameworks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails follows MVC architecture, the &lt;strong&gt;V&lt;/strong&gt; in that stands for View, yes Rails has got a view layer, and tremendous support for Ajax which can make pages dynamic and it has got this thing called Turbolinks till Rails 6 which makes clicking of links Ajax, and now it has got Turbo, a full fledged framework to support very dynamic pages that needs almost no refreshing. Using a front end framework is an anti-pattern. You are simply turning Rails into a  JSON or GraphQL source. If you do so decouple front end and back end development. Just use the Model and Controller in Rails and pump out data to be consumed by your devices like mobile app and front end framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making a Rails developer to work on a  front end is like asking an engine driver to paint his train, no that won’t work. The paint job would be in a mess and would peel off any time. Rails developers are good at putting out HTML, JSON and GraphQL (that too when they know about it well). As of now not many Rails dev’s know GraphQL thoroughly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;derailing-thinking-that-full-stack-includes-design&quot;&gt;Derailing thinking that full stack includes design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again full stack does not include design. Designing requires a different kind of brain, it might also need to think about UI and UX. Rails is all about business logic delivered fast. Many people confuse that designing is a part of Rails and that gives us headaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;derailing-by-using-unsupported-databases&quot;&gt;Derailing by using unsupported databases&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Postgres is very much supported DB in Rails. The community has moved in that direction. I have seen projects where one uses Oracle or Microsoft SQL and see that Ruby does not work well with it. Use a data store that support Rails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have also seen people using Mongo (or some weird NoSQL), and even Neo4j with Rails, and getting involved in productive bottlenecks. All I can say is you are a software engineer, think dude think. Don’t be dumb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your project has grown too large, try using something like Cockroach DB, that’s just drop in replacement to PostgreSQL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;use-activejob&quot;&gt;Use ActiveJob&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least in 3 project’s I saw Rails been used with Kafka, okay but hasn’t Rails got nicely integrated ActiveJob? The Rails community has realized the need of doing intensive tasks that could fail, and has provided an excellent abstraction layer. I see some companies using Sidekiq and ActivJob and processing nearly TB’s of machine generated data and generating more data due to it :D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kafka is great but integrate with Rails with a proper abstraction like an API where a Rails dev fires an API to create task and queries it to know its status. Kafka should be handled totally separate way. A Railway engineer should not worry about what happens to a parcel is delivered at a Railway station, messages to Kafka is like parcels a train delivers to a platform. Trying to push it into Rails may or may not work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;follow-convection-over-configuration&quot;&gt;Follow convection over configuration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encountered a situation where emailing stuff was so abstracted from Rails, I had to define same email template in multiple locations. A lot of configuration should be set. I was given a reason for this, but I was not convinced. Use Rails convention. Never violate the rails way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails is battle tested, 37 signals and other top companies are using it, and they are iterating their products fast and moving along with trend. I believe they are right in many ways. So follow Rails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-creating-a-knowledge-base&quot;&gt;Not creating a knowledge base&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I do freelancing, I find in many projects the client fails to create knowledge base and documentation for his product. Never I have seen a document that says you need to have imagemagick installed on the server you are deploying, and that sucks. One should create a good enough knowledge base so that it gives lot of information to developers. If your developers are too techi and cannot write english, then hire some technical writers to assist them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Never in a Rails project I have seen an architecture diagram describing if you need a redis connected to it, never have I seen a diagram if the current deployment is behind load balancers or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans can understand far better using diagrams than reading text, that too reading code is hard. So putting diagrams is not bad. May be consultancy should be formed to evaluate a companies tech knowledge base and reveal its shortcomings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tdd&quot;&gt;TDD&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please! Yes do TDD 100%, please! Else forget about fast changes and upgrading your product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails is very thought out, they have lasted the test of time, I think for two decades and they are still roaring like lions. I don’t know who chose the name Rails, but if you derail, things go awry like a real railway system. Either be on track, create knowledge for the driver to understand well when convention is broken, don’t break the convention too much so that it becomes hard for others.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">mkcd Make and change directory</title><link href="/2022/05/07/mkcd-make-and-change-directory.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="mkcd Make and change directory" /><published>2022-05-07T21:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-07T21:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/05/07/mkcd-make-and-change-directory</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/05/07/mkcd-make-and-change-directory.html">&lt;p&gt;Often I run into a problem, I need to create a directory using &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;mkdir&lt;/code&gt; and I have to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; into it. Some times I need to create a directory structure like this: &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;~/code/folder/sub_folder&lt;/code&gt;, the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;folder&lt;/code&gt; might be missing or the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;code&lt;/code&gt; might be missing. So I found the following shell command which will &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;mkdir&lt;/code&gt; with padding and changes i.e &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; to the created directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paste the line below in your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;~/.bashrc&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;~/.zshrc&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-shell highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;function &lt;/span&gt;mkcd &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;mkdir&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;-p&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$@&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;amp;&amp;amp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;eval cd&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\&quot;\$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$#\&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&quot;; }
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;source&lt;/code&gt; it as shown:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-shell highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$ &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;source&lt;/span&gt; ~/.zshrc
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the following command will create the directory structure and will change to it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-shell highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$ &lt;/span&gt;mkcd ~/code/folder/sub_folder
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Often I run into a problem, I need to create a directory using mkdir and I have to cd into it. Some times I need to create a directory structure like this: ~/code/folder/sub_folder, the folder might be missing or the code might be missing. So I found the following shell command which will mkdir with padding and changes i.e cd to the created directory.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Recursion in Clojure</title><link href="/2022/04/21/recursion-in-clojure.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recursion in Clojure" /><published>2022-04-21T16:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-04-21T16:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/04/21/recursion-in-clojure</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/04/21/recursion-in-clojure.html">&lt;p&gt;Just want to make a note so that I don’t forget. I am reading Clojure to build very complex, concurrent systems that deal with lot of data. Using OOPS for that is a pain, it collapses when we hit about 0.2 million lines of code. I had done recursion in Clojure and this is how it works:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-clojure highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;;; recursion.clj&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;defn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print-array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;let&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first-element&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;first&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;rest-elements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;rest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first-element&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
      &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;do&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first-element&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print-array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;rest-elements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)))))&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print-array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;])&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the program above we are printing an array element by element. The function we wrote for that is called &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;print-array&lt;/code&gt;, note how at the end we are calling the same function from that function like this: &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;(print-array rest-elements)&lt;/code&gt;. Well, this is all good, but the book Getting Clojure says this will slow up the computer if you have lot of elements, instead it tells us to use &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;recur&lt;/code&gt; as shown below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-clojure highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;;; recursion-2.clj&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;defn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print-array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;let&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first-element&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;first&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;rest-elements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;rest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first-element&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
      &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;do&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first-element&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;recur&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;rest-elements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)))))&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print-array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;])&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;recur&lt;/code&gt; should be the last line of a function and so it is in the case above. As an OOP guy I find that bit disturbing that &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;recur&lt;/code&gt; should be in the last line, but I found OOP disturbing while learning it being a C programmer. Some how this will prevent the computer from slowing down!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Just want to make a note so that I don’t forget. I am reading Clojure to build very complex, concurrent systems that deal with lot of data. Using OOPS for that is a pain, it collapses when we hit about 0.2 million lines of code. I had done recursion in Clojure and this is how it works:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Possibly a web app with pure Ruby. But will it be on time?</title><link href="/2022/04/18/possibly-a-web-app-with-pure-ruby-but-will-it-be-on-time.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Possibly a web app with pure Ruby. But will it be on time?" /><published>2022-04-18T20:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-04-18T20:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/04/18/possibly-a-web-app-with-pure-ruby-but-will-it-be-on-time</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/04/18/possibly-a-web-app-with-pure-ruby-but-will-it-be-on-time.html">&lt;p&gt;Some time back,  don’t know when I saw this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2022/04/03/ruby-3-2-0-preview1-released/&quot;&gt;https://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2022/04/03/ruby-3-2-0-preview1-released/&lt;/a&gt; and I couldn’t sleep that night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a programmer, like every programmer I want to finish a job quick for my client and get my pay with a smile. I was able to do it when I coded with PHP, I was able to do it when I coded in Ruby on Rails. In fact Ruby on Rails had a thing called RJS (Ruby Java Script). I don’t know who made it, but it was genius. In Rails it combined with Prototype and Scriptaculous and made writing front end a charm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then they moved to Coffeescript and jQuery, in my mind not a wise move, but it kind of worked, we were writing JavaScript-ish that sucked compared to RJS, but Coffeescript made it bit easy. I was presented with this learning curve to learn this jQuery. All this parent, child relationship made it suck, but I learned. I was still able to create apps faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today while developing a Rails app I don’t understand what’s going on. There is thing called webpack, yarn and I have to search for blogs to make jQuery and Twittter Bootstrap work with it. That’s pain, but once done productivity improves unless some idiot propose a brand new JavaScript library to be included so the project becomes cool. I personally thought going JavaScript way sucked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I for long wished Opal became a part of Ruby on Rails. I wished code was easy to write as in the days of RJS. Today if you are writing software with Rails 5 or 6, you need to know about node, yarn, webpack and blah blah to be comfortable with it. It’s like a mini framework in this framework called Ruby on Rails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JavaScript has a philosophy that’s different than Ruby I suppose.  Ruby was clearly written to make programmers life easy, when I switched from PHP to Ruby I could see it. PHP ecosystem meant deployment happiness, which Rails robbed away from us, thus paving way for companies like Heroku to overcharge us, but when it comes to total cost of developing webpages, Rails was okay. Butt this JavaScript, my God! It would make atheist like me to think that there was a previous birth and I had done very bad things to inherit this super bad Karma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus reading that Ruby might run in the browser was a kind of faint light in a dark hell. A distant and very faint light, but better than nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to think, even though Microsoft is an ultra evil company, they developed Blazor &lt;a href=&quot;https://blazor.net&quot;&gt;https://blazor.net&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9BhbGbTsyeE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have this vision of making developers build full webapps with just C# and thus avoid JavaScript. Isn’t that good? For a while I even thought of ditching Ruby on Rails and switching to Blazor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All hopes not lost&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Rails developer I would say that all hopes are not lost, it’s possible to develop apps without writing much of JavaScript:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://d1snj8sshb5u7m.cloudfront.net/Rails7.mp4 &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see that Rails is getting matured. May be one day doing Rails project might be as good as doing a pure Ruby project. I have to go through this tutorial when I have free time &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hotrails.dev/turbo-rails&quot;&gt;https://www.hotrails.dev/turbo-rails&lt;/a&gt;. May be I can get off writing a web app with almost no JavaScript very soon. Let’s see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On Time?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am really pissed off creating web pages today. In India people jump into things without trying things out. People, even in small projects introduce Angular, React into front end without knowing who created it and why it was created. Today you are considered a full stack developer only if you know these JavaScript framework. May be one day a full stack developer would also include VHDL and chip design as their profile, after all webpages are served by Integrated Circuits which too are part of stack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be I will learn Julia (Python sucks for DataScience) or something, finish writing my DataScience book &lt;a href=&quot;https://cliz.in/dsbuk&quot;&gt;https://cliz.in/dsbuk&lt;/a&gt; and escape the world where we take stuff out and put into RDMS via web apps. I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be I will learn Clojure, avoid JavaScript all together by using it in backend and using ClojureScript in front end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s nice to be in a world dominated by free software. We have lot of choices. It’s up to programming languages and frameworks now. Will they  help us create better web apps without relying upon JavaScript, or else they will make people mad and drive them away? Time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Some time back, don’t know when I saw this post https://www.ruby-lang.org/en/news/2022/04/03/ruby-3-2-0-preview1-released/ and I couldn’t sleep that night.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">R.N.Ravi crushes Tamils in Tamilnadu</title><link href="/2022/04/14/r-n-ravi-crushes-tamils-in-tamilnadu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="R.N.Ravi crushes Tamils in Tamilnadu" /><published>2022-04-14T22:43:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-04-14T22:43:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/04/14/r-n-ravi-crushes-tamils-in-tamilnadu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/04/14/r-n-ravi-crushes-tamils-in-tamilnadu.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/60/R.N._Ravi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;R.N.Ravi&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our politics is dominated by scoundrels, and R.N.Ravi is no different. Rather than respecting the constitution and being a governor who does his duties well, he is just obeying the BJP and delaying to sign laws passed by Tamilnadu government. The question is “why?”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the second world war there was a massive famine in India. Winston Churchill had transported all Indian grains to England to feed their army and people. Millions of Indians died and Winston Churchill was awarded the Nobel Prize. So why the world turned a blind eye to massive deaths in India?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today everyone empathizes with Ukrainians, thats great, but the world forgot about Tamil genocide in Srilanka, the world barely remembers genocide of Kurds by Turkey and genocide conducted by Bokoharam. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A simple answer is they are not us. People empathize and want to uplift only people who they can associate with. It’s a natural phenomenon. That’s how human brans work. Those who cannot empathize with us should not be allowed to rule us. It’s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Tamils should never let BJP conquer us. For more than 5000 years, the Hindus have made us worship Gods in their language Sanskrit. Said that Tamil is the language of people born to prostitutes and so on. Now we see one who holds such kind of values is our governor, and a party that holds such kind of value, the BJP, is ruling India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP people are so blind that it’s said that it’s minister Nirmala Sitharaman when questioned about rising onion prices seems to have said that she is not bothered about it because she does not consume onions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP wants us to blindly believe that they are the ones who should rule all over India. They want us to believe that they are divine, unquestionable, unappeasable, because they have got this divine power by drinking cow urine and eating cow shit every day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In those states that are ruled by parties that don’t eat shit and drink urine,
BJP is irritating the government by telling the governor to be a impediment to the government appointed by the people. This is pure murder of democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Tamils should take a note of it, we must talk, blog, vlog about it, so that the world knows about Modi and his BJP. Many think he is great, but none knows how he is destroying us Tamils in Tamilnadu. Modi is not one of us, and BJP people smelling his farts and eating his shit is not one of us too. They are just Sanskrit speaking Winston Churchills. The world must know that Modi ruled India is not constitution respecting democracy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">R.N.Ravi</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Finding outer products of vectors - Python Vs Julia</title><link href="/2022/04/03/finding-outer-product-of-vectors-python-vs-julia.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Finding outer products of vectors - Python Vs Julia" /><published>2022-04-03T20:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-04-03T20:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/04/03/finding-outer-product-of-vectors-python-vs-julia</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/04/03/finding-outer-product-of-vectors-python-vs-julia.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Python&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-python highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kn&quot;&gt;import&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nn&quot;&gt;numpy&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;as&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;np&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;np&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;([&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;])&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;b&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;np&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;array&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;([&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;])&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;np&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;outer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;b&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Output&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;array([[3, 4],
       [6, 8]])
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-julia highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;x&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;x&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;x&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;b&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;x&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;x&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;x&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;b&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;&apos;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Output&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;2×2 Matrix{Int64}:
 3  4
 6  8
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Python</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I Love Ruby 3, front cover</title><link href="/2022/03/27/i-love-ruby-3-front-cover.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Love Ruby 3, front cover" /><published>2022-03-27T08:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-03-27T08:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/03/27/i-love-ruby-3-front-cover</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/03/27/i-love-ruby-3-front-cover.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello World! And hello Ruby community!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am happy to announce the release of I Love Ruby’s new front cover, and here it is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafybeicjk7vvjv7xivcz2m2cmfmxr5ioeuriedw2vm6wjyoawtiq6ls2dm.ipfs.dweb.link/i%20love%20ruby%20front%20cover%20final.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It features playing kids discovering Ruby and running towards it. I hope you like it. I wish I have all the time writing and refining my books, but life has other plans for me. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z34jYvHK27o&amp;amp;list=PLe1T0uBrDrfNyJ8u6V_3fdwtFdSWPpU7M&quot;&gt;My Ruby books video series&lt;/a&gt; has stalled too. It’s sad to say it, as my book is really innovative, I think I came up with the idea of naming things starting with &lt;em&gt;i&lt;/em&gt; even before Apple did it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I am working for a company who’s app is coded in Rails, but some of its front end is in React 🤮 (Matz is nice so I am not nice to even out this world). As I am tanking up my JavaScript knowledge and spending all my time learning it, I start to hate it more, at the same time my love for Ruby becomes brighter. Why can’t every one think like Matz and DHH? Matz (and other Japanese Ruby contributors), if you are reading this blog, watch lot of Rajinikanth movies and do something to kill JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you people like the cover, and please encourage me so that I have the will to proceed. Please do discourage and spot mistakes so that I can improve my book. I expect this from Ruby beginners. In short give me lot of feedback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One may contact me at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:mindaslab@protonmail.com&quot;&gt;mindaslab@protonmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or signal me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://signal.me/#p/+918428050777&quot;&gt;+91 8428050777&lt;/a&gt;. And yes you can get my Ruby book here &lt;a href=&quot;https://i-love-ruby.gitlab.io/&quot;&gt;https://i-love-ruby.gitlab.io/&lt;/a&gt;. I will update it soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gpVA5mx73UE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello World! And hello Ruby community!!</summary></entry></feed>