<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-10-18T01:23:55+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Quiet proud of my Engineering training</title><link href="/2017/10/18/Quiet-proud-of-my-Engineering-training.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quiet proud of my Engineering training" /><published>2017-10-18T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-18T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/10/18/Quiet-proud-of-my-Engineering-training</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/10/18/Quiet-proud-of-my-Engineering-training.html">&lt;p&gt;I am really quiet proud of my Engineering training, despite once again due to
enormous pressure from my client, people asked me to take shortcuts and I did
not budge. I wouldn’t say that I did not get sad, I was upset very much, but
I did not budge and do some nonsense to satisfy people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am proud because I trained myself as an Engineer. The college I studied which
is called Panimalar engineering did a worst job and I came out as totally
ignorant person. From that day on I trained myself in programming, assembling
different systems to create a product and most importantly technical and
engineering ethics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow any thing may happen, I might be accused of my bad attitude and fired from
project simply because I was honest with my client, or worst people could work
with me with a grudge against me, people may not trust me for a long time thats
for sure. The sad part is, some people who don’t trust me and fall to the feet
of client would be engineers too, thus upholding indignity that Indian engineers
have brought to their profession due to their ill training and inability to keep
pace with current progress, and there is a real chance that they would betray me
like Peter betraying Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I am proud of myself of being unshakable and sticking to the truth, the
people who are supporting me in my defiant stand is my mom who is non
engineer! How ungrateful I have been to her till now and how much I understand
of how much she understands me now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I am really quiet proud of my Engineering training, despite once again due to enormous pressure from my client, people asked me to take shortcuts and I did not budge. I wouldn’t say that I did not get sad, I was upset very much, but I did not budge and do some nonsense to satisfy people.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What I hate about medium</title><link href="/2017/10/11/What-I-hate-about-medium.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What I hate about medium" /><published>2017-10-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/10/11/What-I-hate-about-medium</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/10/11/What-I-hate-about-medium.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://logok.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/Medium-logo-2015-logotype.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medium is popular blogging platform, but I moved away from  it to Jekyll and
Jekyll was good. Let me tell you why I don’t like to blog any more on medium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medium wants to track you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medium loves to track you. It wants to know what your interests are? What you
like to read? Who you follow? Are people working in Medium your friends to know
these details about you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though medium does not force you to login, look at this ugly tool bar at the
bottom&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/messing_up_as_developer.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medium reduces your reading area, it forces you to sign in to read so that it
knows about you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You don’t know what they do with your data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you really know what Medium does with your data and the behavioral data
they collect from you? Do they sell it to others? Share it to NSA? Who knows?
This is the major problem we face today using software as service platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anonymous commenting not possible&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even to comment on ones blog, one needs to login to medium and have a medium
account. Thats ridiculous. Commenting means you have more interest on that
particular topic, so you can be sold more ads about it. Thats why they want you
to login so that they can track about you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blog migration is hard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Migrating your blog content away from Medium is hard. Unlike Wordpress you do
not have a good migration tool or a tool where you can download all your data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happens if you delete your blog?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In medium, none know what happens if you delete your blog or account.
Does it really get deleted? Your details are kept by them even if you have
deleted your account? Who knows what they are doing without your knowledge?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All these questions have made me to log off medium, I wish you too do the same.
Its far far better to have your own server, possibly a wordpress one and blog
with it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Electromagnetic Field Theory Book</title><link href="/2017/10/08/electromagnetic-field-theory-book.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Electromagnetic Field Theory Book" /><published>2017-10-08T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-08T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/10/08/electromagnetic-field-theory-book</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/10/08/electromagnetic-field-theory-book.html">&lt;p&gt;Get it &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.calvin.edu/~pribeiro/courses/engr315/EMFT_Book.pdf&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Get it here.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why people use JIRA</title><link href="/2017/10/07/Why-people-use-JIRA.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why people use JIRA" /><published>2017-10-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/10/07/Why-people-use-JIRA</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/10/07/Why-people-use-JIRA.html">&lt;p&gt;Jira is a popular project management tool used by thousands of projects, but do
developers really like it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;how much jira do we have to use before we&amp;#39;re agile?&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; 0operator (@sadoperator) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/sadoperator/status/916077741845258242?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;October 5, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they don’t, then why people use Jira? Well, Information Technology industry
is more about deception than real science and software, and Jira is much needed
by management folks for deceiving their client, so they use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jira has done lot of brand building&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, Jira has done lot of brand building, it has made people to believe using
it will make things cool ad people have some how believe it. Some how none who
bat for Jira can publish a scientific study that Jira has improved their
efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jira is a jargon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of clients are ignorant, you tell them that you are using big data with
blockchain and everything is managed by Jira where he can know the status of
the project at his finger tip, then he would succumb to the jargon and think you
are great and you really know stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jira introduces inefficiency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clients and management like to see their team sweat out even if things are
really easy. Trust me, I am a programmer for 15 years and I have seen how people
make simple things complex and make you go mad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jira introduces inefficiency into project, it makes the project difficult to
manage and you need managers to do it. This creates fake jobs, plus having a
manager means the company can bill the client more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atlassian needs to survive&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Atlassian is one big corporate mess of fat ass bosses who needs to feed like
pigs, go on to Italian holidays, stay in star hotels and claim that they have
changed the world for good by introducing Jira, if you don’t use them
they have to make a living by cheating the world in another way. So please trust
and use Jira without questioning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay happy living like a goat as ignorance is bliss.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Jira is a popular project management tool used by thousands of projects, but do developers really like it?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What can I do if computing prices are falling?</title><link href="/2017/10/02/What-can-I-do-if-computing-prices-are-falling.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What can I do if computing prices are falling?" /><published>2017-10-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/10/02/What-can-I-do-if-computing-prices-are-falling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/10/02/What-can-I-do-if-computing-prices-are-falling.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.pngall.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/Server-PNG.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we got a new client, he wanted to migrate from a previous service provider to
us. We have built a web agency thats cutting edge, we have developed automation
to such an extent that manual labor is reduced by 90%, and we are aggressively
pursuing Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend asked how much the infrastructure of the new client will cost, I said a
price that would baffle him, it was just 1/400th the price of the previous
service provider that had been milking our to be client. My friend flew on a rage,
‘you open source people just think about cost, there are other aspects there is service, value and
business angle’ he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I gave an another quote thats 12 time larger than the previous one and said
you can pay and buy beefy machines if you like, none stops you, but for this
project this look enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global server prices have fallen. We don’t rely on Amazon, Rackspace,
Heroku and stuff like that, we just simply use our own trusted server bank that
has enough replication to prevent data loss. To our surprise we found our offering
to be faster than Digital ocean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital Ocean is just a startup, which means that it barks and markets a lot
than it bites and does real stuff. Something is wrong with their server which
take lot of time to respond. And Amazon AWS is far worst, one would never know
why it stops or starts all of a sudden and why it lags more. Too much
virtualization I suppose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who are in the closed source, in the Microsoft camp can’t imagine if
something is darn cheap it can be good. They simply lack imagination. Possibly
they will value shit more higher than gold if some one can sells it to them at
greater price. And people who are in Microsoft, and Apple technological products
are doing just that, they are selling shit and are feeling good about it because
you have paid a higher price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow free software people I see are able to look beyond the money and
corporate glare, possibly none is trying to make them dumb, or possibly they are
more democratic or something. They seem to have more common sense.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">India is not just two party state</title><link href="/2017/09/27/India-is-not-just-two-party-state.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="India is not just two party state" /><published>2017-09-27T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-27T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/27/India-is-not-just-two-party-state</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/27/India-is-not-just-two-party-state.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/Flag_of_India.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my friends tweeted this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;If not modi who else, Shall we bring back Manmohan?. I not seeing much difference between congress and BJP other than communal issue&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Jahith Hussain (@jahith) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jahith/status/912988494632427521?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;September 27, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was response to this tweet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Should Narendra Modi continue as Prime minister of &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/India?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#India&lt;/a&gt;? | &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/Politics?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#Politics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Karthikeyan A K (@karthik_ak) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/karthik_ak/status/912956326598213633?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;September 27, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked blunt to twitter users weather Narendramodi should continue as Indian P.M
or not? Its right for a person to vote, its right for a person to change his
choice of vote to any candidate or to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/None_of_the_above&quot;&gt;NOTA&lt;/a&gt;
at any time I feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people think about instability. What will happen if one can vote again and
again, possibly multiple times a day? Won’t governments change just like that? Yes it
will. But isn’t a job of citizen of a democracy to be educated and not bring
instability in a nation? Or does a person think its the duty of the government to
force stability in a land that it rules? Which do you think is right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People seem to be having wrong notion, they feel people or nation can decide
better if we had limited choices. People feel like there must be a one major
ruling party and one minor ruling party, they must keep the nation stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I respect their thought. I respect them choosing not to have choice, but now
take the case of India, my nation. We have two major parties, one is Congress
which is ultra corrupt and another one is relatively less corrupt or good at
hiding corruption, its called as Bharathiya Janatha Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lets say that I am a Biz tycoon dealing with billions of dollars a month. How
long it would take for me bribe leadership of these two parties? No matter who
comes to power, since I control the money I control the law, the flow of
information and hence citizens of my nation will think I am good guy all the time
unless a miracle happens. One or two might find out what I do, but its easy to
eliminate or silence them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now lets see how dynamic democracy works and how it will make politicians
tremble. In dynamic democracy any one can vote any time, or the voting time
period is reduced shortly, say 10 days (I wish it could be 10 minutes). You can
cast your vote once in every 10 days and it will be anonymous. Lets say that
10,000 people vote in a village, say if
there is more than 6000 votes registered in past 10 days, then the system will
count the votes, who ever has majority will be elected and dismissal order will
be sent to the person who was on power and if he had lost. Things will be
automated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dynamic democracy requires two steps, two very independent thing. There will be
voting Kisoks all over the country. It will have two independent systems. The
first is an access system. It will take in your biometric and check if you
unlocked the system in past 10 days. If the system was not unlocked it will
order the voting software to take charge. The voting software doesn’t know who
you are, it will simply list the candidate and record a vote. Thats it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The access control software and the voting software shares no data. In fact the
voting can be recorded and shred in block chain to make it really transparent. Knowing
that one can be evaluated every 10 days will put shivers on politicians spine,
will make them obey to people quick rather than to dodge them in a hope that
they will forget it during the next voting season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-will-happen-because-of-dynamic-democracy&quot;&gt;What will happen because of Dynamic Democracy?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dynamic democracy is not just voting reform, it should also be the way one
stands for election. One should be able to stand as candidate in a place just by clicking
few buttons in an app. Why do you think one need to pay the sate or follow
formalities for one to be elected? That looks stupid to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So any person having the right idea should be able to become candidate,
challenge the incumbent in an instant. This way we will have richness, and not just people
sticking to two parties. We must not go by party politics, instead we must go 
by idea politics and elect
people who align with our ideas and are passionate about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see no different between parties and cults. I wish people who rule us be
independent thinkers and free souls.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jim Mattis should not be allowed to fool India</title><link href="/2017/09/26/Jim-Mattis-should-not-be-allowed-to-fool-India.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jim Mattis should not be allowed to fool India" /><published>2017-09-26T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-26T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/26/Jim-Mattis-should-not%20be-allowed-to-fool-India</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/26/Jim-Mattis-should-not-be-allowed-to-fool-India.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static.atimes.com/uploads/2017/06/US-Jim-Mattis-Shangri-La-Dialogue-June-3-960x576.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing has happened because the Congress leadership is ultra stupid, we have
a government made up of stupids at he center (stupids have won over ultra
stupid ones). Since stupids have ruled us long, the USA is simply using us as
their Colony so that it citizens could be merry, just like the repeat 70 years
ago when the British exploited us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India should think about India and Indians. We must think about ways to make
ourselves better and place trust in Science, Technology, Philosophy, Reasoning
and Logic. No matter how hard that Jim Mattis (visiting US diplomat) pushes,
we must not intervene in Afganistan militarily. It would be destructive to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have already invested a lot in Afganistan and haven’t got anything in return
yet. Afganistan is failure of USA’s foreign policy. Any country that had
relation with United Kingdom and USA has some kind of problem, Afganistan is one
among them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Afgan’s or USA wishes to give us money in advance, what can India do is to
sell its weapons to the Afgan army, we can train their military as our military
is one of the best disciplined in the world. We can repair Afghan defense and
offense installations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its not a great situation to see the Taliban occupying 47% of Afganistan, but
this is what you will get if you have religion preside over logic and
administration. Afgans will never realize it. They might fight hundreds of
battles to get foreigners out of their land, but they are too afraid to fight
a battle to keep religion out of state affairs. They are simply doomed if no
miracle happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our operations should be in Pakistan, we must weaken it by a million cuts.
India should not go behind the Pakistan’s military, ISIS and terrorists as they
are doing a good job of getting the county plunging into abyss, but India must
target liberation of Boluchistan. With war on western and Eastern front,
Pakistan will have difficult time to concentrate on pumping terrorist into
Kashmir.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All I am saying is this, its not the fate of Indian soldier to die on someone
else’s soil, lets use this situation to test our weapons, technology progress
and political theory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wonder how many Indian politicians are corrupt and will let USA treat us as
another colony? We must wait and see.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A murder of democracy in Tamilnadu</title><link href="/2017/09/24/a-muder-of-democracy-in-tamilnadu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A murder of democracy in Tamilnadu" /><published>2017-09-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/24/a-muder-of-democracy-in-tamilnadu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/24/a-muder-of-democracy-in-tamilnadu.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.nmtv.tv/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Vidyasagar-Rao.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its fascinating to see how much of our democratic process is undermined by our
state government and the BJP at the center. Clearly EPS government has lost
majority and it just maintains it on paper by dismissing MLA’s who would vote
against it. Every thing is watched by the governor who is just another jerk only
fit to wash the feet of BJP and RSS people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its fascinating to see how much the BJP and the RSS have moved away from the
great days of Atal Vajpyee who resigned from office of PM just because he was
short of one M.P vote. Now for the BJP its all about technically and staying in
power and showing a blind eye to moral responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BJP has become a force that would protect any one who falls to at feet. What
an shameful existence. We Tamilians are fools too. The youth who came out to the
streets to save our Jallikattu culture will not come out to restore democracy.
These very same youth will get money for their vote. Is there any proof they or
their family members are not morally inferior?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its a shameful time to live as Tamilian in India. Once again after the English
we are subjugated by the Hindi’s and none takes a note of it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unicultural society possible?</title><link href="/2017/09/23/unicultural-societypossible.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unicultural society possible?" /><published>2017-09-23T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/23/unicultural-societypossible</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/23/unicultural-societypossible.html"></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Indians should be ignorant</title><link href="/2017/09/14/indians-should-be-ignorant.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Indians should be ignorant" /><published>2017-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-09-14T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2017/09/14/indians-should-be-ignorant</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/14/indians-should-be-ignorant.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-QidAjbf28eo/USz7ifNi6AI/AAAAAAAAFG4/1VNv2BewvBQ/s1600/saraswati.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The government is afraid of people getting knowledge. Well thats what the signal
Indian government is sending out. Recently it had blocked &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/&quot;&gt;Archive org&lt;/a&gt;,
why? Well none knows why really why? But in India somehow government seems to get away violating
the constitution now and then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its strange that a country that calls itself a democracy is unwilling to let
its people experience the world via the internet 100%. India claims that its citizens
have the right to information and free speech, and right to have rights granted
by our constitution but its really good at hiding things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take for instance the article 49-O which we know now as NOTA or No To Anybody. This
means in each election apart from the list of candidates provided, the voters
should have a NOTA option. That is they should be able to tell that they like
to vote for none. For more than 60 years our politicians have stealthily kept
this right given to us by our constitution away from us. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why a ruler who really wants to respect constitution of India do such a thing?
The reason? Politicians if they can fool people at every opportunity thats
available to them, they will fool us for their gain. It doesn’t matter we are
ruled by Congress, BJP or some coalition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Panama papers have named lot of people who were indulged in looting their
nation and stashing money into Panama. Because of its leak the Pakistani
Priminister Nawaz Sharif had to step down, but why it hasn’t affected India?
Whole India gossips that a mere actress like Aishwariya Rai had evaded taxes and
stashed wealth in Panama, have you ever wondered why and how she is free? Infact
she is not even a drop in the vast ocean of India’s wealth thats looted and
stashed in other countries. Why are we more weaker in implementing justice than
Pakistan who we regard as barbaric tribesmen invading our land?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Internet helps people to distribute things like Panama papers, Wikileaks documents
and others in much easier fashion. These things can be easily hosted on &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/&quot;&gt;Archive org&lt;/a&gt;
or &lt;a href=&quot;https://thepiratebay.org/&quot;&gt;Pirate bay&lt;/a&gt; and so on for all Indians to see, and
it terrifies the Indian government, the oligarchy and the rich to know that people
have the way to know and find out about their corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact time and again Torrent sites gets banned in India all of a sudden and we
don’t know why. When an Islamic terrorist puts up a site say about how he plans
to destroy India, it will be banned here. We as citizens are not allowed to know
who threatens us, and most important we should never know why he is doing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is actively discouraging bitcoin too as it fears that people will find true
financial freedom and possibly big money banks won’t be able to fund political
parties. Having a good relationship between banks and politicians is important.
For example there is a guy called Vijay Mallaya who looted India of 9000 crores
and is happy in London. India is simply doing nothing because he might have nexus
with Subramaniya Swamy of the Ruling BJP. So since this guy has looted the bank
which is called SBI, to offset its loss it (SBI) starts to loot people. SBI says SMS
bank statement is charged, there is charge if you maintain a balance thats low, there is a charge
if you move money in and out of your account, there is charge if you breathe.
So it lost 9000 crores to a man connected with politicians and is now aiming to
loot Rs 900 from each of its 10 crore customers. With bitcoin that won’t be the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are an Indian, there is just one thing you must know. Your government says
you are a free citizen, and its say it is good . Then why the hell its blocking
us to use the internet in free way? Doesn’t things smell fishy here?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>