<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-01T20:14:41+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Julia will eventually oust Python</title><link href="/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Julia will eventually oust Python" /><published>2019-12-01T20:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-01T20:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python</id><content type="html" xml:base="/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/1/1f/Julia_Programming_Language_Logo.svg/1024px-Julia_Programming_Language_Logo.svg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a strong feeling that Julia will eventually oust Python for data science and artificial intelligence. The reason is this, speed and distributed computing. Python is an excellent language, even if you are not from a computing background and want to write programs, Python is a good language to start. But Julia has the following advantages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julia is super fast, even compared to C it has very simmilar speed with far less complicated syntax. So if you take a machine learning package in Julia, all its source can be just in Julia. Let’s take Python for example, we use numpy a lot, and at its base its not written in Python, its written in C and is wrapped with Python. That’s not Python!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you write everything in Python, things will get really slow and your grand child will see the result of your code’s output. I don’t think people want it that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distributed Computing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julia is a new language, Python was written as a toy language for system admin purpose, Julia on the other hand is a new one and understands the modern computing needs. Distributed computing, Concurrency and true Parallelism (not multithreading), which are difficult to achieve with pure Python. Though other packages are available, they are not python.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Python for Industry &amp;amp; Julia for research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now many companies that claim can do A.I work need to do it quick. It’s more easy to get Python developers, tell them to learn some A.I in 2 months and start to code. So Python may be good for industry. But think of an A.I researcher who wants to improve a learning algorithm and finds its source code in C or C++, that guy would rather write a new implementation in Julia than using those difficult languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel in slow, but in an exponential manner Julia packages will increase and root out Python in Data Science, I feel it’s only a matter of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blessed by Scientific Community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole software industry once thought THE MICROSOFT way was the way to develop software, but the scientific industry embraced &lt;a href=&quot;https://fsf.org&quot;&gt;free software&lt;/a&gt;, now many companies are using Linux on their desktops, Linux dominates Mobile market, even Apple uses lot of free software components in its ecosystem, Microsoft has surrendered to Linux today. What was touched by the scientists, and ridiculed by the software industry won. Today I feel Julia is getting such a blessing from the scientific community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember we in the software industry are here to make money with computers, though we have the brain enough to think, the mad pursuit of money and/or climbing the corporate ladder have left us with the intelligence of fighting lions and tigers. Where’s our tax sponsors these scientists who can take time to think, they do not have to fight much, outfox some one, get into office politics and meet very strict deadlines. They have intelligence of Chimps. Evolution tells that Chimps evolved into Humans who are hunting down and made Lions and Tigers almost extinct.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Galaxies on an Oscillating base</title><link href="/2019/11/17/galaxies-on-an-oscillating-base.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Galaxies on an Oscillating base" /><published>2019-11-17T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-11-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/11/17/galaxies-on-an-oscillating-base</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/11/17/galaxies-on-an-oscillating-base.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://cdn.spacetelescope.org/archives/images/screen/heic1107a.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read an very exciting article here &lt;a href=&quot;https://futurism.com/the-byte/something-strange-synchronizing-distant-galaxies&quot;&gt;https://futurism.com/the-byte/something-strange-synchronizing-distant-galaxies&lt;/a&gt;. It looks like galaxies in our universe are synchronising, that is they are rotating in the same rate, kinda moving together despite their large separation. Scientists are puzzled about it and don’t know why it’s happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many things have puzzled us, the lightning, now we all know it’s just bunch of electrons, before we thought God’s were playing marbles in sky. We thought all clock’s tick at the same rate, but our assumption seems not to agree with the way universe is behaving, we now know time is not the same everywhere thanks to relativity &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_dilation&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_dilation&lt;/a&gt;. Similarly there are many stuff we still don’t know about this place we are in. If we are lucky, our humanity in some form will survive for billions of years and find the answers to almost all questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding galaxies synchronisation, take metronomes synchronisation. You put a bunch of them on an oscillating platform, they exchange energy between them and synchronise as shown here&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Aaxw4zbULMs?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a similar way I think two galaxies that synchronise together are doing so either due to random coincidence or exchange of information. The information could be energy or some weird stuff we haven’t found out. Possibly our universe wobbles, say you start walking, then our universe wobbles to synch with you. Say two star’s crash, our universe wobbles. That is every action in this universe transfer’s energy to a base that’s omnipresent, and this base transfers it’s energy to everything. Something like that could enable galaxies to sync.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possibly our universe would have wobbled very harmoniously, that is all parameters in it would have expanded and collapsed at the same time, and our big bang is nothing but a small luminescence created by it, just like we have sonoluminescence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/puVxGnl_3y8?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Encounter with a psycho</title><link href="/2019/10/28/encounter-with-a-psycho.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Encounter with a psycho" /><published>2019-10-28T09:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-10-28T09:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/10/28/encounter-with-a-psycho</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/10/28/encounter-with-a-psycho.html">&lt;p&gt;It has become a ritual that when the marketing person arrives in my office, we both go for a tea and a snack. We both are foodies. The service lane near my office is not too wide, it can fit just two lorries side by side. Friday gone we ventured out in the evening for tea, and we saw a car blocked by a lorry. There was already a cement raw material truck packed along the side and we noticed a strange scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A red car was trying to get off the service lane, a waste water truck was parked besides the truck parked at the edge of service lane. The lorry driver was in front of the lorry, though the car is honking and beaming its headlights on him, he was cool, he doesn’t seem to care about the world. It was a very strange scene. Here was a guy who knew that he was causing inconvenience to people, but does not seem to care  about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought the lorry drivers memory got erased like we see in the movie Men In Black. I thought he forgot everything, about who he is and what he is doing and hence he is behaving in a strange way. The car was honking and flashing light on his face, but he seems not to bother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually when I see such strange people, I keep away. Even if a normal guy known to me behaves strangely I keep away, but my friend raced his bike ahead and encountered the driver. When we enquired about him we came to know that the guy was blocking the road because he was angry that the truck meant for cement raw material was parked in the spot he used to park, out of this anger he was blocking the service lane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that driver did not suffer from sudden memory loss like I thought, he had full memory, but was a psycho who does not care about others, but was willing to hurt the world just because he suffered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work in Info Tech industry. We hire the best people who are mathematical and logical in their thought, so we don’t see much psycho’s and mentally retarded people in our job. People who are like that get promoted to mangers and other non technical posting because they are able to hurt people if they are not satisfied. To encounter such kind of people is really strange for me. My friend is in marketing, and looks like he seems to deal with psychopaths almost every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend was a skilful negotiator and made the lorry guy look for another spot for parking and hence the issue was resolved. It was only after my marriage I really encountered psychopathic people often. Before that even in tech field I did encounter psychos, but since I.T field is large, you can shun them and jump off to another project where you will meet a sane mind. But these kind of people fascinate me. I want to know why people are stupid when they can gain so much not being one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as humans are illogical I will be fascinated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It has become a ritual that when the marketing person arrives in my office, we both go for a tea and a snack. We both are foodies. The service lane near my office is not too wide, it can fit just two lorries side by side. Friday gone we ventured out in the evening for tea, and we saw a car blocked by a lorry. There was already a cement raw material truck packed along the side and we noticed a strange scene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Modi Creates Hitler Durbar In India</title><link href="/2019/10/06/modi-creates-hitler-durbar-in-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Modi Creates Hitler Durbar In India" /><published>2019-10-06T10:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-10-06T10:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/10/06/modi-creates-hitler-durbar-in-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/10/06/modi-creates-hitler-durbar-in-india.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.timesnownews.com/story/1556527065-modi_hitler_twitter.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actions of Modi are textbook actions of Hitler. They both share a very similar personality. First, there is no direct evidence that Hitler ordered killing of Jew’s in Germany, and there is no evidence that Modi ordered killing of Muslims in Gujarat, or day to day discrimination of beef eaters in our country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hitler was bloody ignorant, fortunately for Germany he was not as ignorant as Modi. But both Modi and Hitler are ignorant enough that they never listen to other people around them. That’s what is happening yo our economy. Demonetization, GST, caused economy to fall and these guys never really acknowledged it until now. Now they take half hearted reforms which are doing nothing much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third is going behind political opponents. People, eminent ones wrote a letter against lynching of beef eaters and crimes against minorities in India, now the 49 people who wrote the letter are booked with sedition charge. This is what Hitler did exactly. If any one made him feel uncomfortable, they became threat to Germany and hence serious charges were laid against them and they are banished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi has mastered the art of bending the law to his favor. All over Tamilnadu there is ban on keep roadside banners because it caused a death of a young girl named Subasree. Thankfully since she is a good looking girl, media pulled it up to get viewer count, and this pressure forced the courts to order not to put any kind of banners on street. But for Modi’s Mahabalipuram visit this law doesn’t apply. Banners will be kept praising him and Chinese dictator Xijingping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany was a democracy before the rise ofHitler. Hitler rose and made Germany lick his boots and brought Germany to its doom. The patterns, what Modi does, their psychology matches closely. It would be interesting to see India trip and fall under Modi. Once we have fallen, I wonder how much long will it take for our country to come back as major power again, or will India disappear? I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Man with a woman</title><link href="/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Man with a woman" /><published>2019-09-26T19:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-26T19:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.wallpapers13.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/Sunset-romantic-couple-in-an-embrace-love-Wallpaper-HD-915x515.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have found this annoying trend, a man drives his car is okay, but when he is with his family and kids his driving is weird and confused, just like his life is. He goes slow even when the road is fast, brakes sudden, seems to have no aim and destination, just like a married man behaves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am beginning to wonder if a man with a woman is just like man with a liquor bottle. Being with a woman increases dopamine level just like being with liquor bottle. A man with them becomes aimless compared to the external world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more dangerous is, a man to get a bottle of liquor will do what ever he wants, even if it’s evil, similarly a man who wants to get a woman will do what ever he wants, even it means evil to the very woman he wants to have. Think about the Pollachi incident for women, think about many petty crimes that happen so that one can drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a man is with liquor or with a woman, will act strange too. Try disturbing a drunk. Look at all those people making illegal money via bribes and other stuff. Mostly they have a family story which to their mind gives them the right to break the law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of Karunanidhi, what he has done to us just because he wanted to fuck his wife’s! His son is leader of the party as though there is none else who could lead, his grandson is next in line so that Stalin can be with his wife. Though not proven its gossiped that their family is #1 in looting this country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So…. Have pity on these people. Evolution has created men to crave for women. Given a chance we all men will have as many women as we could, and as much liquor or any kind of dope we could. But we have a brain powerful enough to think, to put ourselves into the view of others. It’s as simple a person who does not want to eat by killing a conscious life just because he himself does not want to be cut up and knows the pain it causes. So think, even if you are a man with a woman or liquor, try acting like an evolved man, and not like an ape. Know that you are part of this huge universe and not just clam contained in a shell called family. It’s difficult to think broad for something that has evolved out of a baboon, but it’s possible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mistrust In Eastern Cultures</title><link href="/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mistrust In Eastern Cultures" /><published>2019-09-23T08:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-23T08:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures.html">&lt;p&gt;The Gulf War, though having one of the best armies in the middle east Iraq lost, and it lost badly. It did to USA the second time, and once again it lost very badly. The Arabs tried to conquer Israel, a tiny nation that had nothing and they lost, and they lost it bad. Long ago in Tamilnadu, despite being brave and having a disciplined military, the Maruthu bothers lost to the British. China lost to western powers during the Opium wars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question here is why? Why do people who are in the East loose to people who are in the West? One reason I can think of is that there is an element of mistrust in the east. Sadam does not trust his generals for the fear that he will be ousted by them. The Arab countries though they are all Islamic nations, they are deeply divided into Wahabi, Shia Islam and so on. During the Maruthu era in Tamilnadu, the Paalayam rulers were in a power struggle and deeply mistrusted each others. All this aided enemy victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did find it recently in the people I opposed, I expected a logical good fight, a debate of ideas, but the other side crumbled. They then I found out deeply mistrusted the people who in-fact came to their aid. They did not respect fellow humans. I, filled with western ideas had an open mind, and they could not deal with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We might think of Tamil villages a good place to live, may be it is, but people over there mistrust their neighbors and envy them. A neighbor will go into deep state of depression, hate and envy if one has converted a thatched roof house to one with tiles. He, the neighbor, will do all he can to spread a bad word about him, how that one earned in an illegal way and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just in Tamils, I find this deep sense of mistrust in Kerala people too. For a Keralite family is important. If a family is headed by a fool, then all the people in family are foolish too. Let’s say that a girl is a Hindu and she falls in love with a muslim, or say she is a feminist and wants to goto Aiyappan temple, that’s it, if the family head is offended, like goats almost all people in the family will be offended and mistrust the girl. Her life is finished. Or she must listen to the family head and mistrust a muslim boy proposing to her. This type of stupidity I find, makes Malayali’s deeply divided and unprogressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we in East must be open to ideas, listen to others and try starting to trust people. Yes some trust might fail, some might betray you, but unless one knows that you trust him and have given the full freedom to work, he or she cannot work for you 100% and be productive.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Gulf War, though having one of the best armies in the middle east Iraq lost, and it lost badly. It did to USA the second time, and once again it lost very badly. The Arabs tried to conquer Israel, a tiny nation that had nothing and they lost, and they lost it bad. Long ago in Tamilnadu, despite being brave and having a disciplined military, the Maruthu bothers lost to the British. China lost to western powers during the Opium wars.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Good Woman Driver</title><link href="/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Good Woman Driver" /><published>2019-09-14T08:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-14T08:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver.html">&lt;p&gt;Yesterday as usual around 8PM I think I was driving home from office. The roads I drive are quite dangerous, there are lots and lots of potholes, now someone has filled some of them with sand and seems to have compacted them a bit well,  plus you have got these people, Chennai people who do not give a damn about traffic rules. To add to that the street lighting would be awful, most of them would have their headlights turned high beam, sometimes against those  bright headlights it would be difficult to see the roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving in Chennai is not just looking at the road and driving. None follows rules here, some one would cut before you. Overtake you without warning, from the opposite side a scooter or a fast car would over take a tanker despite knowing that it would cause a lot of discomfort to you. You must look at the road, you must look at the eyes, hands, wheels of other vehicles too to determine their next move and drive by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add to the woes you have this Road Transport Officers who are perverts, they make it difficult for men to get license, so there are men who bribe them and get their license and being a pervert they grant license to woman just like that. Because of this people who go in car’s like me, when we spot a woman driver on bike we tend to keep distance. Their driving seems shit, their vehicle could change direction any time, sway from one side of the road to other, brake and so on. You need to get a man drunk to do that feat, woman do it just like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the matters worst, if you hit a woman, or a bike with a kid on it, or even a bike with a family driven by man, you will be blamed for it no matter who has made the mistake. Woman, kids and family are like cows in India, they can do what ever they want. Cows here shit and urinate on roads, drop their dung, stand on the road unmoving and obstructing traffic and none bothers about them or even complain. If you hit them or shoo away, our priminsters Hindu men, will come out drag you out and beat you, because you have abused the Hindu Goddess Lakshmi. These people of so found of cows, one of their favorite drink is cows urine, it like Coca-Cola here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay with all these in mind, yesterday I was driving behind a woman who was on a blue scooter. Definitely I thought she was a crap driver. She was wearing a red saree, black border with golden silk threads in the black woven into intricate pattern. If she did something stupid and I hit her, possibly she was having an auspicious occasion, and hence she was wearing a rich dress, the people would gather around and blame me like hell. I tried to over take and clear her off my mind, but the bad roads and opposing traffic did not permit that. I maintained my distance from her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After sometime I notices something strange. Unlike many woman on road, she did not make a mistake, she was driving perfect. She had a blue helmet too that matched her color of her bike. ‘Woman thinking about road safety? Wow!’ I thought. But I persisted, after nearly 5 minutes and 3 kilometers of this tense follow up I was able to over take her. Thank fucking God, I raced away, and no more woman scooterist I saw ahead of me from then on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roads filled with crap woman driver, I must clap for this one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yesterday as usual around 8PM I think I was driving home from office. The roads I drive are quite dangerous, there are lots and lots of potholes, now someone has filled some of them with sand and seems to have compacted them a bit well, plus you have got these people, Chennai people who do not give a damn about traffic rules. To add to that the street lighting would be awful, most of them would have their headlights turned high beam, sometimes against those bright headlights it would be difficult to see the roads.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Jesus won’t cut in, in India</title><link href="/christianity/religion/india/2019/09/02/why-jesus-won-t-cut-in-in-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Jesus won't cut in, in India" /><published>2019-09-02T20:41:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-02T20:41:00+05:30</updated><id>/christianity/religion/india/2019/09/02/why-jesus-won-t-cut-in-in-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/christianity/religion/india/2019/09/02/why-jesus-won-t-cut-in-in-india.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/f-qodKHzei4/maxresdefault.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story of Jesus, isn’t it so wonderful. God fucks Mary, and some innocent idiot marries her because God cannot take care of the women he fucks, and then their son is born and it endures pain to wipe out the sins of man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The theme of the story is self sacrifice, how the son of God sacrificed himself for others. And its the same story that’s told to Hindus and Indians. Were we moved? Mostly not. The ignorant believe in everything, we can do nothing about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why many religions in India won’t believe in Jesus is because many religions have many many messengers of God. Saadhu’s they are called. Over here you don’t be to be born to a whore fucked by God to reach God and make sacrifice for humanity. In fact many son’s and daughters of God have died doing bad stuff, and in vain due to their evil karma. Over here there are many ways to reach God. One is by doing good deeds, and other is by doing no deed at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saadhu’s do no deed. By the time I finished writing this blog may be 10 to 100 saadhu’s would have died all around India praying for the well being of not just the humanity, earth, the solar system, but praying for the well being of the universe / everything as a whole. Unlike the life of Jesus where he must be dragged on and then forced to make a sacrifice, these saadhu’s voluntarily sacrifice themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People here have seen many attain jeeva samadhi in a voluntary way every year, and a story of just one sacrificing himself for the humanity which is nothing but an insignificant spec in this vast universe will looks funny to Hindus and other religions here. Its only due to the existence of ignorant Hindus and mostly people who wish to switch sides for money, this so called Christianity which is a crap compared to religions here has penetrated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Rationalist Like Buddhism</title><link href="/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Rationalist Like Buddhism" /><published>2019-08-25T11:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-25T11:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/08/25/why-rationalist-like-buddhism.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_1.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One would see rationalist talk ill about almost all religions, but not much against Buddhism. It would look counter intuitive, rationalists are here to slam all religious practices, and why not they slam Buddhism so much? Buddhism was slammed, that too by a rationalist nation China. By the time it slammed Buddhism, this religion had become impure, and was well diverged from in initial teachings. Yes one has the right to be stupid and follow Tibetian Buddhism, but China thought its the duty of the state to teach rationalism to the people and bring them out of their stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buddhism has lot of belief that are untrue. They believe in previous and past life, they believe in Karma which is  a kind of accounting system that keeps track of ones good and bad deeds and assigns a score (very similar to loyalty score assigned by China to every citizen), Buddhist believe in spirits and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Buddhists have got many things wrong, they had invested a lot in psychological studies and had got one thing right. That is they figured out that ones happiness and sadness is not the function of external world, but lies within ones brain. Its very true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a man who has a corrosive family, none in his family respect him and they just abuse him. Just imagine Leo Tolstoy, the world knows how his family abused him. So imagine a man like him and he is very sad because of his family. Now imagine he goes to  a liquor shop and drinks. His wife, children and relatives are the same, but he finds his sadness disappears and he starts to feel a kind of forgetfulness and happiness. I wonder Tolstoy was a drunk, but writing gave him happiness despite everything around him was pulling him down. As you see from this example these people are able to ignore the sadness and are able to generate happiness. That’s what Buddhism says, it says you r feelings can be detached from the world around you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People believed that ones happiness and sadness was controlled by God, or some supernatural forces, but Buddhism said that one can manufacture these feelings in ones mind. A trained Buddhist can choose to become sad when he wants to, and can become happy when he wants to. He can observe and comment and debate about himself, a trait very very few in humanity have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ever God is knocked off, blind faith is shut down, we rationalist are happy and feel that humanity is one step closer to the truth, and hence we love Buddhism despite all its shortcomings.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The BJP has got more than an Economic Debacle</title><link href="/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The BJP has got more than an Economic Debacle" /><published>2019-08-17T19:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-08-17T19:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/india/economics/religion/bjp/2019/08/17/the-bjp-has-got-more-than-an-economic-debacle.html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/A9VOMfY4bOo?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BJP does this and that, but whats happening to the economy? Its sliding. What’s happening to the fuel prices? Its going high. Your saving looks like its dwindling. Businesses are closing down and top tycoons in India are coming out to speak against the government economic policies. Without strong economy a country is finished. I am quite sure Modi will loose all what Manmohan Singh has built up. When Modi one day goes, perhaps we will be beggars and can be happy that we were not ruled by a ruler controlled by Italy, but one controlled by the magical properties of cow dung and urine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay the econ is down, to fix it you need to have brains, not swearing, not ability to burn your midnight oil, not ultra nationalism, you need to have brains without anger, and that one Modi’s cabinet that doesn’t have. I am not worried about Modi making us poor, whats the use of worrying after giving a garland to a monkey, its going to make a mess of it, according to the monkey it did the right thing. I am worried about India becoming just another Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see once Pakistani earned more than an Indian. If Indian earned Rs 100, a Pakistani earned Rs 165, but now look what has happened to their country. They have to beg for $ 6 billion, which is actually nothing, and they are not getting it. The reason is their stupidity, obsession with something other than the economy. They were corrupt, fortunately right now we feel BJP is less corrupt than the Paki’s. Either they are un-corrupt or are good at hiding corruption. The next big mistake they made is to let religious people take over their country. When that happened, passion started to take over and development got a back seat, and down went Pakistan. Who can save them now? Not their Allah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its Allah in Pakistan and its Ram in India. That’s the only difference between Pakistan and Indian politics now. I do expect India to go down in economy quick and none should be able to do anything about it. Then what would happen? The people with relatively good economic minds, the Congress will come to power, improve economy and corruption, and then we can elect this religious fanatics once again to waste away our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And life goes on. But will that happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see when fanatics come to power, a nation goes a full transformation. When the liberal Shah was in power in Iran, a woman can wear a bikini in beach, what now? Think! Once upon a time in University of Peshawar students had bands, wore jeans, what happened now? Afghanistan was a thriving country, what happened after the Taliban rule?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Economic debacle is the first phase of transformation from civilized to religious rules. When economy goes down you can’t purchase things, you may not have a job, if you do you will not be paid well. You won’t have a good purchasing power. Life becomes harder. When life becomes harder where will you go for help? God men. And think what the BJP and RSS consists of. They have fanatic God men who think its their right to control our lives. I am very confident we are going there, and possibly no force is going to stop them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>