<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-12-09T08:35:40+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">This Is When We Actually Become Adults, According to Science</title><link href="/2025/12/02/this-is-when-we-actually-become-adults-according-to-science.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This Is When We Actually Become Adults, According to Science" /><published>2025-12-02T11:26:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-12-02T11:26:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/12/02/this-is-when-we-actually-become-adults-according-to-science</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/12/02/this-is-when-we-actually-become-adults-according-to-science.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vogue.com/article/this-is-when-we-actually-become-adults&quot;&gt;https://www.vogue.com/article/this-is-when-we-actually-become-adults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The long-held belief that the brain fully develops by age 25, marking the onset of adulthood, is a myth.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New research from the University of Cambridge indicates the brain’s adolescent phase extends until the early 30s, with “adult mode” neural wiring typically stabilizing around age 32.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The study identifies five broad phases of brain wiring across the lifespan, with pivotal turning points at ages 9 (transition to adolescence), 32 (transition to adult), 66 (early aging), and 83 (late aging).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This stabilization around age 32 means the brain’s architecture doesn’t significantly change for decades, corresponding to a plateau in intelligence and personality, and a tendency to become “more stuck in your ways.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.vogue.com/article/this-is-when-we-actually-become-adults</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Google chrome becomes unusable for me</title><link href="/2025/12/02/google-chrome-become-unusable-for-me.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Google chrome becomes unusable for me" /><published>2025-12-02T06:33:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-12-02T06:33:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/12/02/google-chrome-become-unusable-for-me</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/12/02/google-chrome-become-unusable-for-me.html">&lt;p&gt;Today I checked Chennai’s weather on my companies phone. It did not use &lt;a href=&quot;https://search.brave.com&quot;&gt;brave search&lt;/a&gt;, and it did not have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.firefox.com&quot;&gt;Firefox&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;https://adnauseam.io/&quot;&gt;AdNauseum&lt;/a&gt; in it. Google showed some results and I opened one of it’s recommendations on the browser, which happened to be Chrome. It was appalling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firefox + Adnauseum combo removes all ad’s, removes those JavaScript running those ads, so the articles are nice to read, the page loads and behaves faster. With Chrome, its almost impossible to install Adnauseum, and the page loaded was filled with annoying ads, and it was slow and clunky. Yak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firefox + Adnauseum, gives every person a premier access to the internet. Imagine a YouTube without ads, even without paying the $9 per month subscription. It also prevents one being spied to a certain extent, and it’s all for free!!!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today I checked Chennai’s weather on my companies phone. It did not use brave search, and it did not have Firefox with AdNauseum in it. Google showed some results and I opened one of it’s recommendations on the browser, which happened to be Chrome. It was appalling.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Music eases surgery and speeds recovery, Indian study finds</title><link href="/2025/11/28/music-eases-surgery-and-speeds-recovery-indian-study-finds.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Music eases surgery and speeds recovery, Indian study finds" /><published>2025-11-28T10:17:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-11-28T10:17:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/11/28/music-eases-surgery-and-speeds-recovery-indian-study-finds</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/11/28/music-eases-surgery-and-speeds-recovery-indian-study-finds.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c231dv9zpz3o&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An Indian study found that playing music during general anaesthesia significantly reduced the required doses of anaesthetic drugs like propofol and fentanyl.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Patients who listened to music experienced faster, “clear-headed” recoveries, lower stress hormone levels, and better blood pressure control during surgery.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The study involved 56 adults undergoing laparoscopic gallbladder removal, with one group listening to calming instrumental music via headphones while the other did not.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Researchers suggest that even under general anaesthesia, the brain’s auditory pathway remains partly active, allowing music to influence the body’s internal state.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Music helps mitigate the body’s natural stress response to surgery and intubation, which typically leads to increases in heart rate, hormones, and blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The findings indicate that this simple, non-pharmacological intervention could humanize operating rooms, reduce drug dependency, and modestly improve patient recovery outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c231dv9zpz3o</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Uselessness of Fast and Slow in Programming</title><link href="/2025/11/19/the-uselessness-of-fast-and-slow-in-programming.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Uselessness of Fast and Slow in Programming" /><published>2025-11-19T00:08:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-11-19T00:08:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/11/19/the-uselessness-of-fast-and-slow-in-programming</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/11/19/the-uselessness-of-fast-and-slow-in-programming.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from &lt;a href=&quot;https://jerf.org/iri/post/2025/the_uselessness_of_fast/&quot;&gt;https://jerf.org/iri/post/2025/the_uselessness_of_fast/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Programming uniquely spans vast orders of magnitude, from nanoseconds to months of computation, making terms like “fast” and “slow” ambiguous.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Software engineers frequently work across a 19-order-of-magnitude range of operational speeds, a scope uncommon in most other disciplines.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Human brains and current terminology struggle to meaningfully differentiate performance across such a broad spectrum.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Developers often overemphasize “requests per second” benchmarks for web frameworks, neglecting that their application code is typically the bottleneck, not the framework.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Most web development performance needs are well within the capabilities of commodity frameworks, making speed an irrelevant selection criterion for many.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For extremely performance-critical systems like commercial databases, language choice and optimization at the nanosecond level are crucial.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The concept of “premature optimization” is complex, but understanding the rough order of magnitude of operations helps prioritize where optimization efforts are truly beneficial.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In systems with vast magnitude differences, “little things” (e.g., nanoseconds) often do not add up to significant savings compared to larger bottlenecks (e.g., milliseconds).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vague terms like “fast” and “slow” in software discussions lead to misunderstandings and project delays, as different teams may hold vastly different performance expectations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It is crucial to replace general performance descriptors with specific metrics, benchmarks, and orders of magnitude to facilitate clear communication and informed decision-making in software engineering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from https://jerf.org/iri/post/2025/the_uselessness_of_fast/</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Surprising Benefits of Giving Up</title><link href="/2025/11/18/the-surprising-benefits-of-giving-up.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Surprising Benefits of Giving Up" /><published>2025-11-18T19:42:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-11-18T19:42:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/11/18/the-surprising-benefits-of-giving-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/11/18/the-surprising-benefits-of-giving-up.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://nautil.us/the-surprising-benefits-of-giving-up-1248362/&quot;&gt;https://nautil.us/the-surprising-benefits-of-giving-up-1248362/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Research suggests that “quitting” or adjusting goals in response to stress or challenges can often be healthier and more beneficial than persistent grinding.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A meta-analysis of 235 studies found that letting go of impossible goals and re-engaging with new ones can restore purpose and well-being, reducing stress and improving physical and psychological health.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Factors like negative feedback, “action crises,” and personality traits (e.g., optimism, emotional resilience) influence an individual’s flexibility in goal-striving.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Disengaging from goals was linked to reduced stress, anxiety, and depression, while adopting new goals was associated with improved social and physical functioning, purpose, and personal growth.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Future research aims to determine the optimal timing for people to either persevere with their goals or change course.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://nautil.us/the-surprising-benefits-of-giving-up-1248362/</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Delhi bomb blast indiacates we have a education problem</title><link href="/2025/11/12/delhi-bomb-blast-indiacates-we-have-a-education-problem.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Delhi bomb blast indiacates we have a education problem" /><published>2025-11-12T09:44:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-11-12T09:44:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/11/12/delhi-bomb-blast-indiacates-we-have-a-education-problem</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/11/12/delhi-bomb-blast-indiacates-we-have-a-education-problem.html">&lt;p&gt;Education increases the chance of one being rational and calm, but it’s not always the case. Take for example Rajaji, he is extremely educated, well regarded, but he advocated religion, blind faith, gurukula system, and told that son should follow fathers path in profession. Now take Periyaar, I think he studied till 4th standard, but when it comes to reforming people, he had better ideas, which fortunately Tamilnadu adopted and is reaping dividends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People need to be trained to look into facts, they must have rationalist thought, if someone says there is God, and he wants you to do this and that, one must ask ‘why that fucking God is not speaking to you?’, you must think why its showing partiality? Why can’t it elevate everyone to the level of Nanak, Jesus, Mohammad, and Saints, and why it has only the power to interact with only some people, and why it expects us to obey them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India is country that unfortunately recognizes religion, religion is based on beliefs and not facts. Even today we have a religious government, a Prime Minister called Modi, under whose rule in Gujarat, a genocide took place. In such a country, how could we expect people to have an education that will teach them to question things, probe for facts and come to possibly a right conclusion?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just imagine the irrationality of the Delhi attack. Within 2 minutes the lost lives will be filled by births, in 24 hours the road will be mended (it’s a VIP and prestige area, not like the places we commoners live), normalcy will resume, things will be forgotten. Even if terrorists managed to nuke 5 Indian cities, all at once, India will survive and will not give up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bomb blast would have only brought misery to doctors family who did it, given India more intelligence to crack down on terror, and would have brought extreme misery to the people who have died. One day if India reclaims the stolen territory of Pakistan, it will be as cold as Israel invading Gaza, may be no mercy would be shown, millions of innocent lives there will be terminated, or put into disarray for nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately all the terrorists have achieved is to make the nation speak their name for possibly a week, instead they could have helped many to become doctors, treated people well, could have become tall figures in their community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;revamp-education&quot;&gt;Revamp education&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First we need to do is to &lt;strong&gt;ban religious schools&lt;/strong&gt;, that spread a falsehood that some great power called God exists. People should be thought that God is a product of dissolutioned mind, a product of mind with less facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second thing that needs to be done is &lt;strong&gt;remove all traces of religion from our curriculum&lt;/strong&gt;, let the parents of kids tech them religion, or if the God is so powerful, let him install religion into everyone’s brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third thing we must do is to &lt;strong&gt;teach kids to think like a philosopher&lt;/strong&gt;, teach them to question everything, tech them how to look at facts, probe for truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then final thing is, we must also &lt;strong&gt;teach them science, and history&lt;/strong&gt;, which are full of facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;educational-dark-age&quot;&gt;Educational dark age&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately we in India are living in a educational dark age, education is politicized, Religion is brought into politics, management ethos are forgotten and idiots are made to rule our nation, and states. People don’t even know how to choose a right candidate from voters list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if educational reforms are implemented, it will take decades for bright and debating minds to emerge. Till that day we have to face the poison of religion and irrationalism. I think India will never become a rational nation again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Education increases the chance of one being rational and calm, but it’s not always the case. Take for example Rajaji, he is extremely educated, well regarded, but he advocated religion, blind faith, gurukula system, and told that son should follow fathers path in profession. Now take Periyaar, I think he studied till 4th standard, but when it comes to reforming people, he had better ideas, which fortunately Tamilnadu adopted and is reaping dividends.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">For my GenZ - Curing the cancer that grips Mother India</title><link href="/2025/10/31/for-my-genz-curing-the-cancer-that-grips-mother-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="For my GenZ - Curing the cancer that grips Mother India" /><published>2025-10-31T21:17:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-31T21:17:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/31/for-my-genz-curing-the-cancer-that-grips-mother-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/31/for-my-genz-curing-the-cancer-that-grips-mother-india.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5c/Bharat_Mata_bronze.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Mother India&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corruption&quot;&gt;Corruption&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a cancer that grips most nations, as well as our mother India. Corruption. Though we drove out the Brits, one of the reasons why we drove them out is because they looted our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Periyaar, being a wise man said that Independence is a dark day. He went on to say, that we are merely replacing white skinned looters with dark ones. 70 years on, that’s the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right in my state in Tamilnadu, while we struggle to make a living, the deputy CM, Udhayanidhi Stalin, flies to Thailand in a private jet, celebrates diwali with his family, and comes back. Over here he puts a scene that he will destroy sandhana dharma (a draconian Talibanistic Hinduism), while he shamelessly celebrates a religious function being in an atheistic party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the center, Jai Shah’s wealth jumps. Nitin Gadkari’s sons company shares soar because he seems to run an ethanol company, and Gadkari passed a law that Indian fuels should have ethanol blend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine, what did Udhaya, Jai, and Gadkari do to deserve an opuluent lifestyle? What gave them the right to control the lives of millions of people, live a lifestyle where electricity never flickers in their homes, they drive on roads without potholes, get excellent health, they no need to worry about the tution fees of their kids, while we struggle?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;think&quot;&gt;Think&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was happy to see the protests in Bangladesh and Nepal. It put the power of people before the few elite. The people thought them who is really the master. In India, even though the GenZ works more than 10 hours a day, are of slaves of the capitalists, they can’t afford insurance, and family, they are keeping quiet. It’s a mystery for me why they do so, but calm an steady is a blessing. Plus sudden disruption does cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GenZ might not create a physical storm, but don’t let the storm in your mind, that could extinguish the flames of people who loot, and create inequality in our nation, die out. Keep feeding the storm with facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think about the opulence of elite, think why you can’t live like them? Never stop thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;talk&quot;&gt;Talk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the use og thought if you keep it with yourself? So talk. Though we call ourselves democratic, India is not a democracy. If you talk, as I do in this blog, you will face trouble. If you question, you will face trouble. But then what choice do we have?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all cannot migrate to Scandinavian countries where corruption is low. This is our land and we must clean it up. Else you must be happy to accept the elite, the lords, you must be happy enough that your child, grandchild, and generations following them  will be servant of theirs. If that’s okay, be happy. It’s your choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are happy to see your mother gripped in forever disease, which cannot be cured, then think who you are?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;act&quot;&gt;Act&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Protests are good, but they are dangerous, if something really drastic should be done, then yes thats one of the ways to achieve it. I am not against protest. But then imagine the cost, you go out, just because someone looted our nation, at the end of the day your family could be crying over your dead body. Worst the police could pick you up and make you live the life of a cripple. They could make you walk in and out og courts forever. If that’s okay, I salute you. I don’t have the bravery and resources to do it, but if you are a brave, all my heart goes to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a better way. You goto a polling booth, how many symbols / candidates you see? Just two? Many right? About how many of them you know? Only two? Why? Or worst, you just vote for one among that two, so that you can feel satisfied that the person whom you voted for has won. But at what cost? You have given a poison injection to your mother India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When there is an election, and you are going to vote, why don’t you do research about say five to ten candidate, not just the top two? Why don’t you tell people around you, what you like about those candidates, what you don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could form groups, where members of the group can meet the not so known candidates, you can discuss about those candidates on tiktok (ah free speech! banned in non democratic countries!), insta, youtube, facebook or whatever. People will become more aware of them. Votes will spread. This will put pressure on the duopoly, duopoly is a cancer to democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T.N.Seshan once said, ‘today’s election is like this, you have to choose between one who shoots you, or one who strangles you.’ or something like that. But there are so many candidates on the voters list, isn’t the duty of every citizen to know about at-least 5 of them? Then come to a conclusion on whom to vote? Out o f the 5 you researched, maybe, 3 of them, the part they are representing has been involved in corruption, may be 2 of them have no black marks on them. Isn’t it wise to give chance to those who are clean?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure if elections are rigged, I am not sure even if India is democratic, there seems to be a huge gap between the elite and us, there seems no ladder for us to climb and reach up to them. If we don’t stop them now, think, will we be lucky enough again to get another Gandhi? Bagat Singh? Or Netaji? Think.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Mother India</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When you’re drained but your brain won’t switch off</title><link href="/2025/10/31/when-you-re-drained-but-your-brain-won-t-switch-off.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When you&apos;re drained but your brain won&apos;t switch off" /><published>2025-10-31T20:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-31T20:51:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/31/when-you-re-drained-but-your-brain-won-t-switch-off</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/31/when-you-re-drained-but-your-brain-won-t-switch-off.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.indiatoday.in/lifestyle/wellness/story/when-youre-drained-but-your-brain-wont-switch-off-2809567-2025-10-30&quot;&gt;https://www.indiatoday.in/lifestyle/wellness/story/when-youre-drained-but-your-brain-wont-switch-off-2809567-2025-10-30&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cultural Shift and “Productivity Anxiety”:&lt;/strong&gt; Modern society ties self-worth to productivity, leading to “productivity anxiety” where people feel uneasy or guilty when not actively working or improving, viewing rest as a form of failure.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Societal Pressure and Social Media:&lt;/strong&gt; Constant competition, the celebration of busyness, and social media comparisons exacerbate the pressure to be constantly productive, making individuals feel like they’re falling behind if they rest.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fear of Unresolved Thoughts:&lt;/strong&gt; Many avoid rest to prevent confronting buried thoughts, worries, or unresolved emotions that surface in moments of stillness, making true rest uncomfortable.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chronic Stress and Other Factors:&lt;/strong&gt; Chronic stress, fear of judgment, perfectionism, over-identification with roles, and constant digital connectivity further hinder the ability to truly relax.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital “Rest” is Not True Rest:&lt;/strong&gt; Engaging with screens (Netflix, social media) is often mistaken for rest but is actually another form of mental exhaustion, preventing genuine mental and physical rejuvenation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redefining and Learning to Rest:&lt;/strong&gt; True rest is essential for well-being, involves disconnecting from digital devices, practicing mindfulness, setting boundaries, and acknowledging thoughts rather than escaping them, thereby recharging for better focus and energy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.indiatoday.in/lifestyle/wellness/story/when-youre-drained-but-your-brain-wont-switch-off-2809567-2025-10-30</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How a chorus of synchronized frequencies helps you digest your food</title><link href="/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How a chorus of synchronized frequencies helps you digest your food" /><published>2025-10-31T17:54:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-31T17:54:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/31/how-a-chorus-of-synchronized-frequencies-helps-you-digest-your-food.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html&quot;&gt;https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Biological systems often exhibit synchronization, like fireflies or fish, but the mechanics are complex, as seen in brain blood vessels.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;UC San Diego researchers studied the gut’s peristalsis to understand how oscillations synchronize, finding a “staircase effect” where similar frequencies lock onto each other.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This research used a classical model of coupled oscillators, simplified by the gut’s unidirectional nature compared to the brain’s complex vasculature.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The new mathematical solution explains how food moves and is churned in the digestive tract and could aid in understanding gastrointestinal motility disorders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The study determined key features of the staircase phenomenon in the gut, which had not been precisely understood before.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The researchers plan to apply these findings back to the more complex, multi-directional oscillations observed in the brain’s vasculature.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://phys.org/news/2025-10-chorus-synchronized-frequencies-digest-food.html</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kafka is fast – I’ll use Postgres</title><link href="/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kafka is fast -- I&apos;ll use Postgres" /><published>2025-10-30T16:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-30T16:29:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/30/kafka-is-fast-i-ll-use-postgres.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks&quot;&gt;https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The tech world is divided into two camps: one chasing buzzwords and adopting popular but potentially inappropriate solutions, and the other prioritizing common sense, pragmatism, and first principles.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “common sense” camp is gaining traction due to the “Small Data” movement (acknowledging sufficient hardware for most data sizes) and the “Postgres Renaissance” (Postgres’ growing capability to handle diverse use cases).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The article argues that Postgres can effectively handle many functionalities typically assigned to specialized systems like Elasticsearch, MongoDB, Redis, and Kafka, covering over 80% of use cases with 20% of the effort.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Benchmarks were conducted for Postgres as a Pub/Sub messaging system, demonstrating competitive performance with Kafka at lower scales (e.g., 5 MB/s ingest, 25 MB/s egress on a 3-node cluster).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Postgres Pub/Sub performance scaled significantly on a 96 vCPU single node, achieving 238 MiB/s write and 1.16 GiB/s read throughput, though a custom design approach was used.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Benchmarks for Postgres as a Queue also showed strong performance, with a modest single-node setup handling thousands of messages per second and an HA setup exceeding 2000 messages/second.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The author advocates for defaulting to Postgres, emphasizing the quality-of-life benefits and reduced organizational complexity compared to specialized distributed systems for small-to-medium scale.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Premature optimization by adopting complex web-scale technologies for non-web-scale problems is deemed an “anti-pattern” due to significant organizational and financial overhead.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “Minimum Viable Infrastructure (MVI)” approach is recommended: choosing familiar, “good-enough” technology, solving real problems with minimal features, and leveraging widely adopted systems like Postgres.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “it won’t scale” argument is refuted by citing OpenAI’s successful use of unsharded Postgres for massive read loads, the long timeframe for reaching critical scale, and the concept of overdesign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://topicpartition.io/blog/postgres-pubsub-queue-benchmarks</summary></entry></feed>