<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-10-20T11:08:58+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Varq</title><link href="/2025/10/20/varq.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Varq" /><published>2025-10-20T11:07:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-20T11:07:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/20/varq</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/20/varq.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/&quot;&gt;https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The text describes the traditional craft of making “varq” (edible silver and gold leaf) in Hyderabad’s Old City, highlighting the sensory experience of finding a workshop through the rhythmic hammering sound.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Varq, used as an edible decoration for sweets and other dishes, has a long history in India, with mentions in ancient Ayurvedic texts for its medicinal properties and later refined in Mughal courts as a symbol of luxury and status.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Historically, varq was made by hand-beating silver between sheets of ox gut or cowhide, a meticulous process passed down through generations of artisans.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Despite rising silver prices leading some sweet shops to use cheaper machine-made or aluminum substitutes, the tradition of hand-beaten varq persists, with a few remaining artisans preserving this delicate art.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The term “varq” itself has Sanskrit and Persian origins, both meaning “leaf” or “sheet,” reflecting its ancient roots and cultural significance across different eras in India.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.cntraveller.in/story/why-india-covers-its-mithai-in-silver-and-gold/</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shell fish is better than fish</title><link href="/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shell fish is better than fish" /><published>2025-10-16T18:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-16T18:05:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/16/shell-fish-is-better-than-fish.html">&lt;p&gt;Summarized from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish are presented as a superior alternative to fish for combating sarcopenia, the age-related loss of muscle mass.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish protein is highly bioavailable and rich in amino acids like leucine, effectively stimulating muscle protein synthesis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They are packed with essential minerals (zinc, selenium, iron) and B vitamins, which act as “activators” for muscle health and cellular processes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish contain taurine, an amino acid that protects muscles from oxidative stress, supports mitochondrial health, and improves endurance, crucial for aging bodies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unlike larger fish, shellfish are low in the food chain and generally do not accumulate heavy metals like mercury, making them a safe and clean food source.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Regular shellfish consumption, combined with appropriate exercise and lifestyle, can significantly reduce sarcopenia and frailty, promoting vitality in old age.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An anti-sarcopenia lifestyle encompasses not only diet (like shellfish) but also movement, adequate sleep, hydration, inflammation management, good digestion, hormonal balance, sunlight exposure, and social connection.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shellfish contribute to overall health beyond muscles by supporting nerves (B12), protecting joints and bones (muscle pull), and aiding brain function (blood sugar regulation).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The text emphasizes that sarcopenia is preventable and reversible, not an inevitable part of aging, and small, consistent choices, including incorporating shellfish, can make a significant difference.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The ultimate vision is an active, independent, and joyful aging experience, free from the limitations often associated with muscle loss, made possible by a holistic approach centered on nutrient-dense foods like shellfish.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Summarized from: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2JzD5oA4ams</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Plan is not execution, it’s communication</title><link href="/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Plan is not execution, it&apos;s communication" /><published>2025-10-10T12:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-10T12:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/10/plan-is-not-execution-its-communication.html">&lt;p&gt;I think Eisenhower said something like, though it does not work, plan is essential. I am in software industry, and we programmers have been asked often the question: ‘what is our plan?’, ‘when is the deadline?’, and we do give a plan and estimated deadline, and most of the time, it won’t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who are ignorant feel bad about it. In IT industry, people who work are less stupid, and usually the stupidest person gets to the top due to Dunning Kruger effect. So they don’t have intelligence to separate between plan and real world happenings. So if a plan fails or slips, the intelligent person who did the plan is put to a toss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is complex. You don’t plan to brush your teeth, it happens, you don’t plan to breathe. You plan only when you are not sure, you plan only when you are not made up for the task, when you are unsure. That is you plan only when there is element(s) of uncertainty, or some difficulty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not intelligent for a person to take a plan as execution, instead it should be treated as communication. This is what a person is going to do. It might happen happen in the way planned, but there is a good chance that it won’t, the course might change, we might even scrub it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wise person sees plan, and pads it up with more resources, to take the shock(s) of reality, he also plans for failure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I think Eisenhower said something like, though it does not work, plan is essential. I am in software industry, and we programmers have been asked often the question: ‘what is our plan?’, ‘when is the deadline?’, and we do give a plan and estimated deadline, and most of the time, it won’t work.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Buddha killed Islam, and Christianity even before they were born</title><link href="/2025/10/01/buddha-killed-islam-and-christianity-even-before-they-were-born.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Buddha killed Islam, and Christianity even before they were born" /><published>2025-10-01T21:16:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-10-01T21:16:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/10/01/buddha-killed-islam-and-christianity-even-before-they-were-born</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/10/01/buddha-killed-islam-and-christianity-even-before-they-were-born.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ia902808.us.archive.org/11/items/buddha-statue_202510/Buddha%20Statue.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you know the right facts, you can easily kill blind faith. Buddha as I know did not like Hinduism, the tradition of sacrifices, the tradition of yagnas (sacred fire offerings) didn’t appeal to him. He didn’t know what was reality, and why we suffered? So, he went on long quest to ask his inner self. In the end he emerged with something that would kill any faith that’s based on God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see in religions like Hinduism, Islam, Christianity, Sikhism etc, there is God, depending on your good or bad deeds, God rewards or punishes you. If you are rewarded, you feel happy, if you are punished, you feel sad. Right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, Buddha found out the powerful fact that happiness and sadness lies entirely within you. You can turn it on or off as per your will. That is you can stay happy, and calm, all the time if you wished too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can stay happy all the time, what can God do to you even if it exist? Of course, people in those times did not have the scientific tools to disprove God, they wouldn’t even be able to explain what lightning was, they had no idea about nuclear fusion that powers the sun. So Buddha said, it didn’t matter if God exists or not. If you can take control of your feelings, then God doesn’t matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly God became powerless before this fact. I wonder what would have happened if these thoughts had reached Arabia, there could have been no Christianity, and no Islam. Jews would have struggled to hold ground against such a powerful fact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If these thoughts had reached Afghanistan and Iran, Zoroastrianism would have had tough time, Zorastrians invented the concept of God, may be single God (Ahura Mazda), they invented the concept of heaven and hell, and these concepts stuck with later religions. What would have happened if they discovered that this God was powerless before an well trained brain which can control its thoughts and feelings? It’s really funny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They might have got mad, wanted to destroy India and Buddhism.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They might accept Buddhism and abandoned their religion.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They could have coexisted.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They could have  formed a new mixed religion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But yea, it would have made a very different world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">All major Tamil politicians have killed Innocent Tamils</title><link href="/2025/09/29/all-major-tamil-politicians-have-killed-innocent-tamils.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="All major Tamil politicians have killed Innocent Tamils" /><published>2025-09-29T09:32:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-09-29T09:32:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/09/29/all-major-tamil-politicians-have-killed-innocent-tamils</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/09/29/all-major-tamil-politicians-have-killed-innocent-tamils.html">&lt;p&gt;If you are a powerful (wo)man in Tamilnadu, you can get away with the murder. This is the writing on the wall I could see. The recent culprit is actor Vijay. He has killed 40 people, and nothing happens to him. He has failed to lead, after the deaths happened in his rally, he proved himself coward and fled to Chennai rather than stand with people who have suffered and died for him. Neither Vijay, nor his party TVK, seems to have no inkling of guilt, they are unapologetic till now. They have announced price for lives lost, and price for injury, thats it. As the courts once said, Vijay is not a true life hero, just a hero before the cameras. Vijay however filed a case and made the court retract this statement. But the statement made by the court is the truth, time has proven it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The history of killing innocent life’s, and politicians being unapologetic is a long one in Tamilnadu, the so called Tamilian leaders have been no beeter than the Brits in this regard. Now let’s see one by one, how major politicians killed innocent people and still remain unapologetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stalin&quot;&gt;Stalin&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tamilnadu under stalin I believe has at least 28 lockup deaths. Not so long ago, I think 63 people died in drinking illicit liquor. Stalin who was heartbroken by this 40 deaths in Vijay’s rally, stood firm and unapologetic when he killed these people. He simply didn’t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even before coming to power Stalin started to kill Tamilians. Watch his election rally, it took place in covid times, and DMK took no measures in preventing spreading of the disease. Once elected into power, Stalin shamelessly asked Tamils to donate, so that he can fight the disease which he spread. Not even EPS apposed to this evil preelection campaigns of Stalin, because he too followed no covid guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was an Airshow conducted in Chennai, it was very poorly organized and 5 people died in it. The DMK government closed the mater and swept the dirt under the rugs. They are unapologetic till now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eps&quot;&gt;EPS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I said before, EPS too campaigned as though there was no covid, had no regard for Tamilian lives. He is famous for killing atleast 12 activist who protested against the Sterlite copper factory in Thuthukudi. ADMK and EPS are still unapologetic about it, he played a drama to the media that, its only after watching the news that he knew the murders had been committed. The whole state knows that police will not resort to firing without orders from the CM, Its not simple matter to fire on people, it should be done only after lot of approvals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was in EPS time that all people who were associated with the Kodanaadu Jayalaitha property robbery case died in mysterious circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In EPS era too there were lockup deaths, the most famous case was that of Felix, and Jerald I think. Father and son duo was tortured in lockup and lilled by the Tamilandu police, just because they had verbal spat. None who is associated with that case is hanged yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Stalin and EPS are super weak CM’s who are unable to control the Tamilnadu police, no matter how barbaric the police becomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;karunanidhi&quot;&gt;Karunanidhi&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2G case was going on, Kanimozhi was in a soup. The civil war in Srilanka was on, the Sinhala forces had the upper hand. As a leader of Tamils, Karunanidhi should have stood up, prevented the defeat of the LTTE, but he stood down because he need to concentrate and save Kanimozhi from the 2G case. Then DMK threaded the line of Pranab Mukerjee and said that the war was over, while Sinhala troops were mascaraing Tamils en-masse. Finally this led to the death of Velu Pillai Prabhakaran, the hope of Tamils. Even Prabhakaran’s young son was killed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to save his girl, Karunanidhi wiped of an entire Tamil civilization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;jayalalitha&quot;&gt;Jayalalitha&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jayalalitha is one of the worst Chief Minister’s ever to rule in india according to me. She cared nothing about people. Traffic need to wait for hours, just because she wanted to take a walk on the roads. She was shameless, totally irresponsible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was some holy festival called Mahamagam. Jayalaitha had gone to some crowded place to take a dip in some holy pond or something. There was a private area for her to be drenched in holy water. Her arrival itself added more congestion to the crowds. Just to disperse the crowds, its said that some police guy called Walter Devaram shot rounds in the air, the crowd panicked. There was stampeed, and people died. ADMK is still unapologetic till now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Periyaar was right when he said that independence of India is a black day. He said the only the skin color of the rulers will change. Just like General Dire has no concern for life and killed a lot in Janian-wallah-bagh, India’s post independence leaders have no concern for the lives of people. They are intoxicated by the power, wealth and richness, and they think they are untouchables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A society is like a stew, scum floats to the top often and it need to be stirred often to break the scum. I feel that we Indians are  ot stirring up India often, we are not scaring politicians often, neither we have &lt;a href=&quot;/2010/01/31/dynamic-democracy.html&quot;&gt;Dynamic Democracy&lt;/a&gt;, and we have decided to be their slaves forever.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">If you are a powerful (wo)man in Tamilnadu, you can get away with the murder. This is the writing on the wall I could see. The recent culprit is actor Vijay. He has killed 40 people, and nothing happens to him. He has failed to lead, after the deaths happened in his rally, he proved himself coward and fled to Chennai rather than stand with people who have suffered and died for him. Neither Vijay, nor his party TVK, seems to have no inkling of guilt, they are unapologetic till now. They have announced price for lives lost, and price for injury, thats it. As the courts once said, Vijay is not a true life hero, just a hero before the cameras. Vijay however filed a case and made the court retract this statement. But the statement made by the court is the truth, time has proven it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why can’t Aircraft replace buses?</title><link href="/2025/09/20/why-can-t-aircraft-replace-buses.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why can&apos;t Aircraft replace buses?" /><published>2025-09-20T04:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-09-20T04:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/09/20/why-can-t-aircraft-replace-buses</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/09/20/why-can-t-aircraft-replace-buses.html">&lt;p&gt;A few months back, a friend of mine took me to Banglore in a bus. I couldn’t sleep in the rocking motion, and because of the the stale air in the bus. It was hell. The next day I had to attend a tech summit and I had to keep my concentration alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Months before that, may be even a year ago, I had to travel in a sleeper bus in Maharashtra, it was equally hell. I just couldn’t sleep. We arrived at a destination at 2PM, I was so disillusioned because of the sleeplessness, I thought we arrived at a 5-star hotel. It was only the next day I really found out it was marriage hall. But the trip was memorable, Maharashtrian hospitality aced!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do wonder how people travel in buses? And I also wonder if people needs to travel in buses? Why can’t we have lot of cheap Aircrafts that enable us to travel between cities? Yes I do hate airport checkups, but air tavel does save time. Yes economy class seats are crampy, but its for a short duration. We need faster transports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One way of doing it is opening more airports, for some reason, India is very slow in that. Another thing is to privatize railways so that we have better trains, and trains that run faster. Plus we also need innovative transports like airships, and helicopters a lot, and cheap. Why not autonomous aircrafts?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a dream where a person should be able to go from any city from India, to any other city, within 2 hours, and that too whenever he wants. This will change the dynamics and truly integrate India. I want the busses, the old clunky, rocky way of travel, to die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the first stage of killing slow busses is more airports, and air travel, this also includes airships, and helicopters that need less infrastructure. The second stage is faster trains that rival aircrafts. The killer stages wil be hyperloops, flying cars etc. I feel India is too slow in providing revolutionary transports to its citizens.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A few months back, a friend of mine took me to Banglore in a bus. I couldn’t sleep in the rocking motion, and because of the the stale air in the bus. It was hell. The next day I had to attend a tech summit and I had to keep my concentration alive.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Proud of Chennai’s no honking tradition</title><link href="/2025/09/16/proud-of-chennai-s-no-honking-tradition.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Proud of Chennai&apos;s no honking tradition" /><published>2025-09-16T21:04:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-09-16T21:04:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/09/16/proud-of-chennai-s-no-honking-tradition</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/09/16/proud-of-chennai-s-no-honking-tradition.html">&lt;p&gt;I am born and brought up in Chennai. Yesterday evening I was driving from Medavakkm to Sithalapakkam, and I think I just herd only 1 bike honk, apart from that nothing. For reason unknown, people in Chennai have become civilized and don’t honk as much as say other cities in Tamilnadu or India. Drivers in my city seem  to observe the road and drive rather than honk and rush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not everyone follows this less, or no honking stuff. Especially people who do not have the privilege to get educated honk a lot, like cab divers, politicians etc, apart from them, and some uncivilized psychopaths, Chennai seems to be slipping into civilized driving culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure how long this will last, or if this culture will improve. Yes, chennai has its challenges, its filthy, its looted by both DMK, and ADMK, left, right and center. Only VIP areas are clean, with stray dogs, and so on, there is rampant use of drugs, and drug related violence, there seems to be a land mafia here, grabbing the lands of innocent. I think recently homicide, and murders have gone up. Yet among this darkness, I notice that Chennai’s roads are getting quieter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find that people in the area I grew up, Adyar, exhibit very civilized driving culture. People around OMR too exhibit civilized driving culture. But as you move towards Tambaram, people drive like mad. I am not sure what is the cause of lack of civility?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I drive, old family members if they travel with me, often ask me, why I am not honking even at turnings, they simply don’t notice that I drastically slow down, observe and turn slow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing is controllability of vehicles. With modern digital controls, we can control the vehicle in a ways that’s not possible say 15 years ago. Many cars today do not crash. I think all these things are contributing to safer and relaxed driving conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t expect other cities in Tamilnadu, and India to follow Chennai’s example. But I think it’s a good thing that Chennai is not following the example of other cities. I hope that people in Chennai will be more civilized in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I am born and brought up in Chennai. Yesterday evening I was driving from Medavakkm to Sithalapakkam, and I think I just herd only 1 bike honk, apart from that nothing. For reason unknown, people in Chennai have become civilized and don’t honk as much as say other cities in Tamilnadu or India. Drivers in my city seem to observe the road and drive rather than honk and rush.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tamilnadu needs to have dignity temples</title><link href="/2025/09/04/tamilnadu-needs-to-have-dignity-temples.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tamilnadu needs to have dignity temples" /><published>2025-09-04T09:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-09-04T09:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/09/04/tamilnadu-needs-to-have-dignity-temples</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/09/04/tamilnadu-needs-to-have-dignity-temples.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/b/b8/Kottravai_at_peruvudayar_temple%2C_Thanjavur.jpg/500px-Kottravai_at_peruvudayar_temple%2C_Thanjavur.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kottravai at Peruvadayar Temple, Thanjavur. Well after the Aryan culture had invaded us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was taking a walk in Sithalapakkam today morning, and indignity hit my ears like a sledge hammer, some temple was blasting some Sanskrit chants from it’s speaker. Here we are calling ourselves Tamil’s and we have allowed a invaders language to be used to talk to our Gods. Shame. Why do we call ourselves Tamils then, when we let someone speaks to Gods in an alien language we don’t understand? Why don’t we call ourselves ‘feet lickers of the invaders’?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not worried about other civilizations in the Indian subcontinent, I don’t know if they care about, or if they have dignity. If they think their language is good enough to talk to the Gods, and they have shred of their their dignity left, they wouldn’t have allowed Sanskrit to replace it. I don’t think they call themselves dignified people, but we Tamils call ourselves dignified, so I am very much worried about us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite wave after wave of real and soft wars, till today, we have held, we are powerful now than the north. There is no better time to push out the invader’s culture than now. Most of the Tamils who are reading this blog are God believers, you were told to believe, and  you believe, leaving out your logic, though, and brain. I do agree, it takes lot of energy to rewire your brain, and if I say don’t believe in God, because it’s spoof, it won’t work. So I am telling to take a step in a direction we could take. We need dignity temples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what’s an dignity temple? It’s a temple where the Gods are worshipped in a language we understand, Tamil, and not in an invaders language. It’s a temple that’s open, that is any one can touch our Gods, its not that only some people so called the “elite” are allowed to go near our Gods, and touch it. In this temple, our Gods’s are open to every one. That is even people of different religions like Sikhism, Christianity, Buddhism, Islam can worship our Gods, touch it and give offerings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must also revive true Tamil culture. Most of the God now like Vishnu, Pilliyar, Karthikeyan may not be Tamil Gods. Our Gods were Kortavai, Kadal Om, Vel Om etc, which were been morphed by invading cultures. We need to revive these Gods and erect pure Tamil temples. We need historians to probe deep back into our culture and tell who we truly are, so that we can truly revive our Tamil culture, since we are too weak brained to follow the footsteps of Periyaar, and become sane atheists.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Kottravai at Peruvadayar Temple, Thanjavur. Well after the Aryan culture had invaded us.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Allah could be Indran</title><link href="/2025/08/22/allah-could-be-indran.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Allah could be Indran" /><published>2025-08-22T19:11:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-08-22T19:11:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/08/22/allah-could-be-indran</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/08/22/allah-could-be-indran.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nabataea.net/media/01explore/08FoundingIslam/Photos/Baal_Ugarit_Louvre_AO17330.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Huubal, the God from which Allah evolved&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muslims around the world worship a single God called Allah. But that was not the case before Islam. Allah was the king of many Gods, Just like God Indran in Hindu Mythology. In fact Indran was once widely worshipped in India, and then I think people cooked up negative stories about him and he lost his fame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Allah and Indran had three daughters. I think in Hinduism, at least two the daughters of Indran, named Devaiyani, and Valli got married to Muruga. Jayanthi was another daughter, by winning over Sooran, I think Jayathi (which means victory, or sometimes birth) became one with Murugan too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Christianity, their God is highly forgiving, but in Islam, Allah is very strict, just like Indran.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allah was once represented by crescent in Arabia, though Islam forbids representation of God, still the pagan way of crescent is used. Even today Muslims worship a stone called Kabha, revolve around a building that houses it in Mecca, all remanence of pagan practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moon in India is called Chandran. Did the ancient Indian the moon worship of Chandran slowly morphed into Indran? Is it Chandran of the Indu’s, which became Indran? Did this Chandran King of Gods move to Arabia and became Allah, the king of Gods there? I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you look at religion and myth, the same stuff would be copied and morphed to fit needs. Take Soora Samharam, and Ramayana, very similar. Jesus is nothing but retold story of Mithra, which appeared in Rome 2000 years prior to Jesus era. As the Jews say, Jesus never existed. Even we have no proof of prophet Mohammed’s existence, and all could have been a spoof to bring people in line to an ideology, align them to a way of life. The concept of heaven and hell were invented by Zoroastrians, and many other religions copied it. Islamist dropped eating pigs to market their religion to the Jews. So nothing is original.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I strongly feel, Allah is nothing but the retold and morphed story of Indran, the king of Gods.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Huubal, the God from which Allah evolved</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SQL challenge of the day, by Timmy Kurian</title><link href="/2025/07/06/sql-challenge-of-the-day-by-timmy-kurian.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SQL challenge of the day, by Timmy Kurian" /><published>2025-07-06T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2025-07-06T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2025/07/06/sql-challenge-of-the-day-by-timmy-kurian</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/07/06/sql-challenge-of-the-day-by-timmy-kurian.html">&lt;p&gt;Lifted from: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/timy-kurian-88597526_sqlchallenge-sqlinterview-dataengineering-activity-7347327190063071233-6rax?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=member_desktop&amp;amp;rcm=ACoAAArx5IoBZ1QlV3uo-mV_zNQXTgm4ETiUIeA&quot;&gt;Timmy Kurian’s Linkedin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given a table “employees” with columns “employee_id”, “first_name”, “last_name”, “department_id”, and “salary”, return the top 3 employees with the highest salaries for each department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sample Tables (CREATE + INSERT):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sql&quot; data-lang=&quot;sql&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;CREATE&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;TABLE&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;employees&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;employee_id&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;INT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first_name&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;VARCHAR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;last_name&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;VARCHAR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;department_id&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;INT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;salary&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;INT&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sql&quot; data-lang=&quot;sql&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;INSERT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;INTO&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;employees&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;VALUES&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;John&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Smith&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;100000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Jane&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Doe&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;95000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Bob&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Johnson&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;80000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Samantha&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Jones&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;85000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;5&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Mike&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Williams&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;120000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Emily&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Brown&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;110000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;7&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;David&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Lee&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;75000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Sarah&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Miller&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;70000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Query:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sql&quot; data-lang=&quot;sql&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;department_id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first_name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;last_name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;salary&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;department_id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;first_name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;last_name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;salary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;RANK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;OVER&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;PARTITION&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;department_id&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;ORDER&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;salary&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;DESC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;AS&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;salary_rank&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;employees&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;AS&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;ranked_employees&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;salary_rank&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explanation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This query uses a window function to rank employees within each department by their salary, and then selects only the top 3 employees for each department. This is achieved by using the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;RANK()&lt;/code&gt; function with a &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;PARTITION&lt;/code&gt; BY clause, which will reset the ranking for each department. The outer query then filters out any employees with a salary rank higher than 3. This solution allows for ties in salary to be included in the top 3.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Lifted from: Timmy Kurian’s Linkedin</summary></entry></feed>