<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-26T21:40:11+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hotel Gokulam Park Sabari Sucks</title><link href="/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/21/hotel-gokulam-park-sabari-sucks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Gokulam Park Sabari Sucks" /><published>2019-12-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/21/hotel-gokulam-park-sabari-sucks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/21/hotel-gokulam-park-sabari-sucks.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.trvl-media.com/hotels/2000000/1790000/1784600/1784528/46e7bf35_z.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, a bunch of people @ office wanted to go to an unknown and untested hotel to get drunk at night. I wasn’t so sure of the idea, I just want to drive home and on the way have something, but those folks wanted to get drunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was in 50-50 mood. A friend of mine had taken me to a tea shop near Zeeshan and I had chicken sanwidch at lunch, I was kind a half to three quarter full, plus the new hotel my friends were calling for a drink was beyond tollgate and I had to waste Rs 54/- for that. Rs 50/- would be equivalent to 10Km of my drive from office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I joined this office as a consultant, I was promised work from home, liberal work ethics, but now they seem to suspect me for not working or something. I thought bad times had passed when my wife left me, then I had my partner in Trumatics who started yelling me, so I had to leave that company, and when I thought that I was in a good office at this one, and after few months of working, this boss too gets mad at me, he accuses me of taking more than 15 minutes to drink tea, and when I am not in office at 11 AM he gets upset. I have never seen this behaviour in good I.T company. Later to my happiness I found that he was behaving like this way to many other people, particularly to senior employees. So I am forced to spend a lot on fuel as my consultations is far far off from city and I must be there unless I am ill or something. So spending another Rs 54/- on a toll / travel did not look wise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then one of my friends popped in and offered me a bike ride and I was in. No need to pay tolls. The hotel we went was Gokulam Park Sabari. There was a bar at the terrace, the ambience was good and clean. There wasn’t many people there. It was a bar cum restaurant. Out of the dozen of us, only three drank. I ordered a mutton briyani, a tandoori platter, asked the waiter what he would have if he were me, he said chilli eggs and I ordered that one too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dish took long time to come, really long, somewhere between 20 minutes to half an hour. the chilli eggs came first and they were good. Then came the briyani, it was kind of tasteless, but you could eat it if you don’t mind rough meat. The raitha was good, it was made of cucumber as onions can be eaten by only the rich in India, the brinjal curry was not good, it was like brinjal’s in some kind of tasteless sauce, but they weren’t too bad either. Then came the tandoori platter, the chicken in it seemed to smell like it was soaked in some kind of medicine or something, it smelled like some kind of chemical. The prawns were okay, and so was the minced mutton tandoori, but the fish smelled, I even thought it was rotten. I just don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once eaten, the bad smells stayed in my mouth and it would stick, I just lost appetite for eating and lost happiness. I love real good food and people who make it, but this was hell. I know in pubs attached to restaurants they serve low quality food because people who drink sans the sense of taste and they would eat almost anything without complaint. Here too that seems true, but the taste was real worst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you had put some one in prison and want him to suffer, I guess you can serve him this food. One would realise that life has no meaning after eating this one. Well that’s the truth, but realising it mellows your enjoyment. I did not even eat a third of what I should have eaten. I just sat there enjoying the breeze at their terrace pub. Looks like the drunkards in our office did not seem to mind the waste food they were served.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hard part is not that. I had gone to the hotel expecting to have great food and great time, so I had my hunger raising, when I drove back home beyond 10:30 PM, all others food shops were closed and I had to sleep kind of hungry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How I see non Chennai people</title><link href="/2019/12/10/how-i-see-non-chennai-people.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I see non Chennai people" /><published>2019-12-10T19:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-10T19:45:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/12/10/how-i-see-non-chennai-people</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/12/10/how-i-see-non-chennai-people.html">&lt;p&gt;I am born and brought up in Chennai. I travel almost to no other place because I find all I want here. In fact my mission is to never leave my bedroom. I want to earn from my bed, buy suff from my bed, its all possible with todays technology. Trying to be a non nomadic human has made me see people outside Chennai as some what different. They seem to look like weird animals to me. Here is what I found or think about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here when I say non Chennai, that person has come into Chennai, or is a resident of Chennai and visits his so called native. The pure Chennai people are those who have no native, do no visits to their natives so that they are not corrupted by outside Chennai values, and they do not associate with some other city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Their driving is crazy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, possibly driving in Chennai is crazy, so I find it crazy when some one from outside Chennai drives here. I found a vehicle with licence plate TN 76 V… and he was driving right into potholes while we skilfully avoided it. He also drove slow and would not let us pass him. He was such a dork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I must admit that the road from Sithalapakkam to Sirusseri has one of the worst potholes in India. I also have a feeling that ITEL bribes beuracrats and politicians to deliberately keep these roads in this condition, but we somehow find a way to avoid these potholes and drive without much complaint. We certainly don’t drive into it like other people who follow traffic rules do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Absolute no respect for women&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A strange thing about non Chennai people I find is, they have very little respect for women. A guy from Kerala who is my friend and resides in Sithalapakkam once asked “why are women are there on street?”. I thought something happened to his brain, if we certainly had flying cars and bikes, why do we need to use these damn streets? I thought.  But then after further conversation I found out that in his part of India women don’t go out after 6 PM or something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t imagine that kind of situation happening here. Perhaps if the Taliban or IS or some Kaliphate conquer’s Chennai that might happen, but here you can find women almost at any time on street, it’s definitely not looked in a bad way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Women smoke, I see lot of women in Tasmac Elite, I don’t think they are bad or immoral, women now are wearing dresses that are truly good to watch ;) and it’s good! They must be able to express themselves in the way they want to. That’s freedom. I don’t understand why non Chennai people find it hard to digest it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Family Values&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non Chennai people have high family values, possibly like Nithyandha’s followers have high value on him. This doesn’t mean that family members of non Chennai people are good, or non fraud’s or something. It’s just because kids born in non-Chennai families are trained to obey elders without questioning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We Chennai people however won’t hesitate to question our own elders and parent’s We behave just like lord Karthikeyaa did with his family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tradition and belief in Gods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find both Chennai and non-Chennai people believe in God equally, but all friends I know do go to temples knowing that God is spoof, and they know that these traditions suck, but they do it because they do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For non Chennai people, tradition has a real value. I don’t know what exactly. It’s not about pleasing ones mom, wife or relatives, but it seems to be about them, they say it has real value. I don’t know if they are dumb or something, but they stick by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visiting Village&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup, no matter how crowded it is, non Chennai people visit their villages during festive season. Without seeing their native they are dead. They come to Chennai to earn, Chennai gives them everything they want, but it’s the village they want, but with their beautiful villages they cannot make money somehow but they must depend on this hellish Chennai. I find it ironic. They must be brave and kick Chennai out of their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My city is Chennai, I love it and make money out of it, but tomorrow if I need to settle in Banglore I don’t mind it and I will fall in love with it. Banglore will become my city. Some how my brain does not exist a lot in fuzzy state where I am confused where I should really live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Living for some mission pission and vision&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non Chennai people seems to be soul heavy like lead. They seem to live for a cause like family, parents blah blah. Dependence on them is very high. Some how they seem to have someone depending on them and that becomes their mission, pission and vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chennai people mostly live for themselves. They seem to think the world is made for them and people are there to serve them. This thought runs through our minds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pee Outside&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find it really annoying, but non Chennai people who I know pee just outside on the road. This I don’t find a bit with my Chennai friends. Perhaps India isn’t fully sanity conscious, but I find it really unacceptable. Perhaps there is some good things in Indian tradition we Chennaites do not know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liberation and Culture shock&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find that for some who move to Chennai from other parts of Tamilnadu, Andhra, and Kerala, it’s a real liberation. Especially for girls. They really seem to enjoy the freedom this city offers. None seem to look at them and judge them, that seems to be a blessing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For others it’s a culture shock. Once outsider is in Chennai, let’s say our driving methodology, our way of talk, our mannerism seems to offend them in some way. Possibly it’s like a Brahmin going to USA and seeing some one eating beef and sinking into deep depression.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I am born and brought up in Chennai. I travel almost to no other place because I find all I want here. In fact my mission is to never leave my bedroom. I want to earn from my bed, buy suff from my bed, its all possible with todays technology. Trying to be a non nomadic human has made me see people outside Chennai as some what different. They seem to look like weird animals to me. Here is what I found or think about them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Supriya In OMR Sucks</title><link href="/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/07/hotel-supriya-omr-sucks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Supriya In OMR Sucks" /><published>2019-12-07T09:30:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-07T09:30:00+05:30</updated><id>/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/07/hotel-supriya-omr-sucks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/food/hotel%20reviews/2019/12/07/hotel-supriya-omr-sucks.html">&lt;p&gt;This hotel in Supriya, that fucking Andhra mess sucks. Really sucks. Me and my friends went there to eat briyani, the briyani over there comes in the form of a kushka, for both mutton and chicken briyani you get the same kushka. If you order mutton briyani, they give kushka with mutton gravy, if you order chicken briyani, they give kushka with chicken gravy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chicken gravy was okay, but the mutton gravy was hot to taste. For a person like me its okay, but for my friends it was too much and they struggled with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ordered two kushkas and mutton and chicken gravy. I was okay about this arrangement, but for many in Tamilnadu it would be like, you goto a tea shop and order tea, the vendor gives you a donkey, sugarcane, rights to a gas field, right to mine iron etc… You need to milk the donkey, extract sugar from sugar cane, mine iron and make cylinders and stove, from the gas field you need to extract gas, liquify it and put it in cylinder and finally make tea. But for me that’s okay, for me its like having briyani with multiple flavours at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only side dish they offer is raitha, that is chopped onions in diluted butter milk, so diluted in fact you feel its for a drink than a raitha. You kinda need to hunt for onions in it. We also ordered extra rice, and to our surprise it came with a cost too. Most Andhra mess, and Madurai mess offer rice as compliment with briyani, over here it costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing I don’t like is stinginess of the hotel, I was burning hot eating the briyani, or to say chilli mutton rice mix, for the extra plain rice I reached for moore kulambu in next table, the fucking hotel owner / manager stopped me saying that moore kulambu is only for meals. It really hurt me. As my friend outside the hotel remarked, we eat for Rs 500/- and this guy won’t spare Rs 5/- worth of moore kulambu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compared to Tamil hotels which are stingy, Andhra hotels offer bountiful food, in some Andhra hotels I have emptied a mini bucket full of pakodas because it was so tasty, I have seen these Andhra guys enjoy watch people eating their food than like Tamil’s who worry about the customer consuming his profit margin, but here, Supriya has been Tamilianized,  they are no more an Andhra mess which we all love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then back at office, we all did not feel well, I got a mild stomach upset, so I do doubt about the hotel’s hygiene. Lack of hygiene and lack of the hospitality of these Andhra people make me feel bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few days later another friend of mine ate meals over there and got stomach upset too. So….. You think abut it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This hotel in Supriya, that fucking Andhra mess sucks. Really sucks. Me and my friends went there to eat briyani, the briyani over there comes in the form of a kushka, for both mutton and chicken briyani you get the same kushka. If you order mutton briyani, they give kushka with mutton gravy, if you order chicken briyani, they give kushka with chicken gravy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Julia will eventually oust Python</title><link href="/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Julia will eventually oust Python" /><published>2019-12-01T20:13:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-01T20:13:00+05:30</updated><id>/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python</id><content type="html" xml:base="/data%20science/artificial%20intelligence/2019/12/01/julia-will-eventually-oust-python.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/1/1f/Julia_Programming_Language_Logo.svg/1024px-Julia_Programming_Language_Logo.svg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a strong feeling that Julia will eventually oust Python for data science and artificial intelligence. The reason is this, speed and distributed computing. Python is an excellent language, even if you are not from a computing background and want to write programs, Python is a good language to start. But Julia has the following advantages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julia is super fast, even compared to C it has very simmilar speed with far less complicated syntax. So if you take a machine learning package in Julia, all its source can be just in Julia. Let’s take Python for example, we use numpy a lot, and at its base its not written in Python, its written in C and is wrapped with Python. That’s not Python!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you write everything in Python, things will get really slow and your grand child will see the result of your code’s output. I don’t think people want it that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distributed Computing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julia is a new language, Python was written as a toy language for system admin purpose, Julia on the other hand is a new one and understands the modern computing needs. Distributed computing, Concurrency and true Parallelism (not multithreading), which are difficult to achieve with pure Python. Though other packages are available, they are not python.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Python for Industry &amp;amp; Julia for research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now many companies that claim can do A.I work need to do it quick. It’s more easy to get Python developers, tell them to learn some A.I in 2 months and start to code. So Python may be good for industry. But think of an A.I researcher who wants to improve a learning algorithm and finds its source code in C or C++, that guy would rather write a new implementation in Julia than using those difficult languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel in slow, but in an exponential manner Julia packages will increase and root out Python in Data Science, I feel it’s only a matter of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blessed by Scientific Community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole software industry once thought THE MICROSOFT way was the way to develop software, but the scientific industry embraced &lt;a href=&quot;https://fsf.org&quot;&gt;free software&lt;/a&gt;, now many companies are using Linux on their desktops, Linux dominates Mobile market, even Apple uses lot of free software components in its ecosystem, Microsoft has surrendered to Linux today. What was touched by the scientists, and ridiculed by the software industry won. Today I feel Julia is getting such a blessing from the scientific community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember we in the software industry are here to make money with computers, though we have the brain enough to think, the mad pursuit of money and/or climbing the corporate ladder have left us with the intelligence of fighting lions and tigers. Where’s our tax sponsors these scientists who can take time to think, they do not have to fight much, outfox some one, get into office politics and meet very strict deadlines. They have intelligence of Chimps. Evolution tells that Chimps evolved into Humans who are hunting down and made Lions and Tigers almost extinct.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Galaxies on an Oscillating base</title><link href="/2019/11/17/galaxies-on-an-oscillating-base.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Galaxies on an Oscillating base" /><published>2019-11-17T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-11-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/11/17/galaxies-on-an-oscillating-base</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/11/17/galaxies-on-an-oscillating-base.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://cdn.spacetelescope.org/archives/images/screen/heic1107a.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read an very exciting article here &lt;a href=&quot;https://futurism.com/the-byte/something-strange-synchronizing-distant-galaxies&quot;&gt;https://futurism.com/the-byte/something-strange-synchronizing-distant-galaxies&lt;/a&gt;. It looks like galaxies in our universe are synchronising, that is they are rotating in the same rate, kinda moving together despite their large separation. Scientists are puzzled about it and don’t know why it’s happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many things have puzzled us, the lightning, now we all know it’s just bunch of electrons, before we thought God’s were playing marbles in sky. We thought all clock’s tick at the same rate, but our assumption seems not to agree with the way universe is behaving, we now know time is not the same everywhere thanks to relativity &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_dilation&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_dilation&lt;/a&gt;. Similarly there are many stuff we still don’t know about this place we are in. If we are lucky, our humanity in some form will survive for billions of years and find the answers to almost all questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding galaxies synchronisation, take metronomes synchronisation. You put a bunch of them on an oscillating platform, they exchange energy between them and synchronise as shown here&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Aaxw4zbULMs?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a similar way I think two galaxies that synchronise together are doing so either due to random coincidence or exchange of information. The information could be energy or some weird stuff we haven’t found out. Possibly our universe wobbles, say you start walking, then our universe wobbles to synch with you. Say two star’s crash, our universe wobbles. That is every action in this universe transfer’s energy to a base that’s omnipresent, and this base transfers it’s energy to everything. Something like that could enable galaxies to sync.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possibly our universe would have wobbled very harmoniously, that is all parameters in it would have expanded and collapsed at the same time, and our big bang is nothing but a small luminescence created by it, just like we have sonoluminescence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;316&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/puVxGnl_3y8?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Encounter with a psycho</title><link href="/2019/10/28/encounter-with-a-psycho.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Encounter with a psycho" /><published>2019-10-28T09:59:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-10-28T09:59:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/10/28/encounter-with-a-psycho</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/10/28/encounter-with-a-psycho.html">&lt;p&gt;It has become a ritual that when the marketing person arrives in my office, we both go for a tea and a snack. We both are foodies. The service lane near my office is not too wide, it can fit just two lorries side by side. Friday gone we ventured out in the evening for tea, and we saw a car blocked by a lorry. There was already a cement raw material truck packed along the side and we noticed a strange scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A red car was trying to get off the service lane, a waste water truck was parked besides the truck parked at the edge of service lane. The lorry driver was in front of the lorry, though the car is honking and beaming its headlights on him, he was cool, he doesn’t seem to care about the world. It was a very strange scene. Here was a guy who knew that he was causing inconvenience to people, but does not seem to care  about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought the lorry drivers memory got erased like we see in the movie Men In Black. I thought he forgot everything, about who he is and what he is doing and hence he is behaving in a strange way. The car was honking and flashing light on his face, but he seems not to bother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually when I see such strange people, I keep away. Even if a normal guy known to me behaves strangely I keep away, but my friend raced his bike ahead and encountered the driver. When we enquired about him we came to know that the guy was blocking the road because he was angry that the truck meant for cement raw material was parked in the spot he used to park, out of this anger he was blocking the service lane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that driver did not suffer from sudden memory loss like I thought, he had full memory, but was a psycho who does not care about others, but was willing to hurt the world just because he suffered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work in Info Tech industry. We hire the best people who are mathematical and logical in their thought, so we don’t see much psycho’s and mentally retarded people in our job. People who are like that get promoted to mangers and other non technical posting because they are able to hurt people if they are not satisfied. To encounter such kind of people is really strange for me. My friend is in marketing, and looks like he seems to deal with psychopaths almost every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend was a skilful negotiator and made the lorry guy look for another spot for parking and hence the issue was resolved. It was only after my marriage I really encountered psychopathic people often. Before that even in tech field I did encounter psychos, but since I.T field is large, you can shun them and jump off to another project where you will meet a sane mind. But these kind of people fascinate me. I want to know why people are stupid when they can gain so much not being one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as humans are illogical I will be fascinated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It has become a ritual that when the marketing person arrives in my office, we both go for a tea and a snack. We both are foodies. The service lane near my office is not too wide, it can fit just two lorries side by side. Friday gone we ventured out in the evening for tea, and we saw a car blocked by a lorry. There was already a cement raw material truck packed along the side and we noticed a strange scene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Modi Creates Hitler Durbar In India</title><link href="/2019/10/06/modi-creates-hitler-durbar-in-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Modi Creates Hitler Durbar In India" /><published>2019-10-06T10:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-10-06T10:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/10/06/modi-creates-hitler-durbar-in-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/10/06/modi-creates-hitler-durbar-in-india.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.timesnownews.com/story/1556527065-modi_hitler_twitter.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actions of Modi are textbook actions of Hitler. They both share a very similar personality. First, there is no direct evidence that Hitler ordered killing of Jew’s in Germany, and there is no evidence that Modi ordered killing of Muslims in Gujarat, or day to day discrimination of beef eaters in our country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hitler was bloody ignorant, fortunately for Germany he was not as ignorant as Modi. But both Modi and Hitler are ignorant enough that they never listen to other people around them. That’s what is happening yo our economy. Demonetization, GST, caused economy to fall and these guys never really acknowledged it until now. Now they take half hearted reforms which are doing nothing much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third is going behind political opponents. People, eminent ones wrote a letter against lynching of beef eaters and crimes against minorities in India, now the 49 people who wrote the letter are booked with sedition charge. This is what Hitler did exactly. If any one made him feel uncomfortable, they became threat to Germany and hence serious charges were laid against them and they are banished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modi has mastered the art of bending the law to his favor. All over Tamilnadu there is ban on keep roadside banners because it caused a death of a young girl named Subasree. Thankfully since she is a good looking girl, media pulled it up to get viewer count, and this pressure forced the courts to order not to put any kind of banners on street. But for Modi’s Mahabalipuram visit this law doesn’t apply. Banners will be kept praising him and Chinese dictator Xijingping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany was a democracy before the rise ofHitler. Hitler rose and made Germany lick his boots and brought Germany to its doom. The patterns, what Modi does, their psychology matches closely. It would be interesting to see India trip and fall under Modi. Once we have fallen, I wonder how much long will it take for our country to come back as major power again, or will India disappear? I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Man with a woman</title><link href="/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Man with a woman" /><published>2019-09-26T19:02:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-26T19:02:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/26/man-with-a-woman.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.wallpapers13.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/Sunset-romantic-couple-in-an-embrace-love-Wallpaper-HD-915x515.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have found this annoying trend, a man drives his car is okay, but when he is with his family and kids his driving is weird and confused, just like his life is. He goes slow even when the road is fast, brakes sudden, seems to have no aim and destination, just like a married man behaves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am beginning to wonder if a man with a woman is just like man with a liquor bottle. Being with a woman increases dopamine level just like being with liquor bottle. A man with them becomes aimless compared to the external world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more dangerous is, a man to get a bottle of liquor will do what ever he wants, even if it’s evil, similarly a man who wants to get a woman will do what ever he wants, even it means evil to the very woman he wants to have. Think about the Pollachi incident for women, think about many petty crimes that happen so that one can drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a man is with liquor or with a woman, will act strange too. Try disturbing a drunk. Look at all those people making illegal money via bribes and other stuff. Mostly they have a family story which to their mind gives them the right to break the law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of Karunanidhi, what he has done to us just because he wanted to fuck his wife’s! His son is leader of the party as though there is none else who could lead, his grandson is next in line so that Stalin can be with his wife. Though not proven its gossiped that their family is #1 in looting this country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So…. Have pity on these people. Evolution has created men to crave for women. Given a chance we all men will have as many women as we could, and as much liquor or any kind of dope we could. But we have a brain powerful enough to think, to put ourselves into the view of others. It’s as simple a person who does not want to eat by killing a conscious life just because he himself does not want to be cut up and knows the pain it causes. So think, even if you are a man with a woman or liquor, try acting like an evolved man, and not like an ape. Know that you are part of this huge universe and not just clam contained in a shell called family. It’s difficult to think broad for something that has evolved out of a baboon, but it’s possible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mistrust In Eastern Cultures</title><link href="/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mistrust In Eastern Cultures" /><published>2019-09-23T08:24:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-23T08:24:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/23/mistrust-in-eastern-cultures.html">&lt;p&gt;The Gulf War, though having one of the best armies in the middle east Iraq lost, and it lost badly. It did to USA the second time, and once again it lost very badly. The Arabs tried to conquer Israel, a tiny nation that had nothing and they lost, and they lost it bad. Long ago in Tamilnadu, despite being brave and having a disciplined military, the Maruthu bothers lost to the British. China lost to western powers during the Opium wars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question here is why? Why do people who are in the East loose to people who are in the West? One reason I can think of is that there is an element of mistrust in the east. Sadam does not trust his generals for the fear that he will be ousted by them. The Arab countries though they are all Islamic nations, they are deeply divided into Wahabi, Shia Islam and so on. During the Maruthu era in Tamilnadu, the Paalayam rulers were in a power struggle and deeply mistrusted each others. All this aided enemy victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did find it recently in the people I opposed, I expected a logical good fight, a debate of ideas, but the other side crumbled. They then I found out deeply mistrusted the people who in-fact came to their aid. They did not respect fellow humans. I, filled with western ideas had an open mind, and they could not deal with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We might think of Tamil villages a good place to live, may be it is, but people over there mistrust their neighbors and envy them. A neighbor will go into deep state of depression, hate and envy if one has converted a thatched roof house to one with tiles. He, the neighbor, will do all he can to spread a bad word about him, how that one earned in an illegal way and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just in Tamils, I find this deep sense of mistrust in Kerala people too. For a Keralite family is important. If a family is headed by a fool, then all the people in family are foolish too. Let’s say that a girl is a Hindu and she falls in love with a muslim, or say she is a feminist and wants to goto Aiyappan temple, that’s it, if the family head is offended, like goats almost all people in the family will be offended and mistrust the girl. Her life is finished. Or she must listen to the family head and mistrust a muslim boy proposing to her. This type of stupidity I find, makes Malayali’s deeply divided and unprogressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we in East must be open to ideas, listen to others and try starting to trust people. Yes some trust might fail, some might betray you, but unless one knows that you trust him and have given the full freedom to work, he or she cannot work for you 100% and be productive.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Gulf War, though having one of the best armies in the middle east Iraq lost, and it lost badly. It did to USA the second time, and once again it lost very badly. The Arabs tried to conquer Israel, a tiny nation that had nothing and they lost, and they lost it bad. Long ago in Tamilnadu, despite being brave and having a disciplined military, the Maruthu bothers lost to the British. China lost to western powers during the Opium wars.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Good Woman Driver</title><link href="/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Good Woman Driver" /><published>2019-09-14T08:46:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-09-14T08:46:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/09/14/a-good-woman-driver.html">&lt;p&gt;Yesterday as usual around 8PM I think I was driving home from office. The roads I drive are quite dangerous, there are lots and lots of potholes, now someone has filled some of them with sand and seems to have compacted them a bit well,  plus you have got these people, Chennai people who do not give a damn about traffic rules. To add to that the street lighting would be awful, most of them would have their headlights turned high beam, sometimes against those  bright headlights it would be difficult to see the roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving in Chennai is not just looking at the road and driving. None follows rules here, some one would cut before you. Overtake you without warning, from the opposite side a scooter or a fast car would over take a tanker despite knowing that it would cause a lot of discomfort to you. You must look at the road, you must look at the eyes, hands, wheels of other vehicles too to determine their next move and drive by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add to the woes you have this Road Transport Officers who are perverts, they make it difficult for men to get license, so there are men who bribe them and get their license and being a pervert they grant license to woman just like that. Because of this people who go in car’s like me, when we spot a woman driver on bike we tend to keep distance. Their driving seems shit, their vehicle could change direction any time, sway from one side of the road to other, brake and so on. You need to get a man drunk to do that feat, woman do it just like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the matters worst, if you hit a woman, or a bike with a kid on it, or even a bike with a family driven by man, you will be blamed for it no matter who has made the mistake. Woman, kids and family are like cows in India, they can do what ever they want. Cows here shit and urinate on roads, drop their dung, stand on the road unmoving and obstructing traffic and none bothers about them or even complain. If you hit them or shoo away, our priminsters Hindu men, will come out drag you out and beat you, because you have abused the Hindu Goddess Lakshmi. These people of so found of cows, one of their favorite drink is cows urine, it like Coca-Cola here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay with all these in mind, yesterday I was driving behind a woman who was on a blue scooter. Definitely I thought she was a crap driver. She was wearing a red saree, black border with golden silk threads in the black woven into intricate pattern. If she did something stupid and I hit her, possibly she was having an auspicious occasion, and hence she was wearing a rich dress, the people would gather around and blame me like hell. I tried to over take and clear her off my mind, but the bad roads and opposing traffic did not permit that. I maintained my distance from her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After sometime I notices something strange. Unlike many woman on road, she did not make a mistake, she was driving perfect. She had a blue helmet too that matched her color of her bike. ‘Woman thinking about road safety? Wow!’ I thought. But I persisted, after nearly 5 minutes and 3 kilometers of this tense follow up I was able to over take her. Thank fucking God, I raced away, and no more woman scooterist I saw ahead of me from then on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roads filled with crap woman driver, I must clap for this one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yesterday as usual around 8PM I think I was driving home from office. The roads I drive are quite dangerous, there are lots and lots of potholes, now someone has filled some of them with sand and seems to have compacted them a bit well, plus you have got these people, Chennai people who do not give a damn about traffic rules. To add to that the street lighting would be awful, most of them would have their headlights turned high beam, sometimes against those bright headlights it would be difficult to see the roads.</summary></entry></feed>