<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-21T08:58:18+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">There is some magic in pure gaana and folk singers</title><link href="/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There is some magic in pure gaana and folk singers" /><published>2023-01-21T08:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-21T08:57:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/21/there-is-some-magic-in-pure-gaana-and-folk-singers.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://yu7.in/Delgv&quot;&gt;https://yu7.in/Delgv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wbYG8T80SOk?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the song above, it was created by Reguman and his team, but you have to listen hard to understand it. It’s a pure Tamil song, but may be the pronunciation of Ragumaan and the girls that sing look like they are foreigners who have landed in India just now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now listen to the sing below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zuVV9Y55gvc?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything in this song is easily understandable, there is nothing you need to concentrate hard. As a Tamil, this song is so understandable to me. It’s a pure Tamil song too. Maybe the singer of this song especially the women could be a pure Tamil girl, possibly a folk singer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now listen to this song:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9PYbz-UpG5Y?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a gaana song, may be because I was born and brought up in Chennai, every bit of this song is understandable and I could grasp it’s meaning just like that without any concentration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is something magical in gaana and folk singers, or may be there is some magic in folk and gaana songs. These songs ae highly understandable, needs no concentration. It’s sad that we have lot of song sung by non-native Tamil speakers, or people who have stayed away from our culture a long time, they suck compared to folk and gaana singers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now here are two songs:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gpVA5mx73UE?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OxDKZ6WfD7M?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a Tamil, decide which is pronounced well and is easily understandable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Short Link: https://yu7.in/Delgv</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The lightness of being a freelancer</title><link href="/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The lightness of being a freelancer" /><published>2023-01-18T09:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-18T09:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/18/the-lightness-of-being-a-freelancer.html">&lt;p&gt;The kind of money we coders demand for quality means we can attract companies that make lot of money. Today if I generate billing for a project, small Indian companies run away. They ask an estimate, and they disappear once I give it to them. The result is people like me who value quality of code are stuck with big corps who like to pay us regular salary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I was working on a ticket, it was a complex one, and I didn’t have an idea how the business worked. All simple assumptions I made became false, my pull requests were rejected. Stumbling and fumbling I thought I would finish my code a day ago when disaster struck. I fell ill. I was forced to take 36 hours or so off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In corporate environments we have to show progress in every scrum call. We have to speak something. You will be paid no matter what, you will be terminated if the business don’t like you. You will be compared relatively with other people. Maybe you might come under a stare of a manager who had bad time with his family today, and your name will be struck off. You never know when the lightning bolt will strike. It’s capitalism to the max.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I were a pure freelancer, I could have had many clients, so loosing one may be a hit, but it would be cushioned by similar paying people. It would be like loosing 20% of your revenue rather than loosing 50%. Plus I can tell to my client to delay my payments till my work is done, or reduce my pay or increase my pay, the billing is what I generate. This justification of self evaluation and lightness of being honest and frank is absent in corporate world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust is very important in doing business. Entire economics is trust. In corporate world, you have no clue how the upper management trusts you, and they don’t connect with people who do the actual work. In freelancing this is opposite, you can gain trust of people and feedback very easily. That adds lightness to life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or may be this is corporate work, maybe I have to be okay with drawing money when I am inefficient, and should be content when I am efficient and the corporate does not want to hike pay for me for what ever reasons that comes to their mind.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The kind of money we coders demand for quality means we can attract companies that make lot of money. Today if I generate billing for a project, small Indian companies run away. They ask an estimate, and they disappear once I give it to them. The result is people like me who value quality of code are stuck with big corps who like to pay us regular salary.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">These boxes don’t move</title><link href="/2023/01/12/these-boxes-dont-move.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="These boxes don&apos;t move" /><published>2023-01-12T16:38:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-12T16:38:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/12/these-boxes-dont-move</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/12/these-boxes-dont-move.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeibf7sr6rfxodeya2nfcjepynmj6lc47ohr3rjvhkcs3tuxdxkmvma.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Universe - 25. Why men and women in wealthy, crowded places don’t behave like men and women anymore</title><link href="/2023/01/09/universe-25-why-men-and-women-in-wealthy-crowded-places-don-t-behave-like-men-and-women-anymore.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Universe - 25. Why men and women in wealthy, crowded places don&apos;t behave like men and women anymore" /><published>2023-01-09T18:04:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-09T18:04:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/09/universe-25-why-men-and-women-in-wealthy-crowded-places-don-t-behave-like-men-and-women-anymore</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/09/universe-25-why-men-and-women-in-wealthy-crowded-places-don-t-behave-like-men-and-women-anymore.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://nftstorage.link/ipfs/bafybeidzr4kn57ytvrduwd45fzbpceloikycy5v6otrjxpntnw36bksim4&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The “Universe 25” experiment is one of the most terrifying experiments in the history of science, which, through the behavior of a colony of mice, is an attempt by scientists to explain human societies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of ​​”Universe 25” Came from the American scientist John Calhoun, who created an “ideal world” in which hundreds of mice would live and reproduce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More specifically, Calhoun built the so-called “Paradise of Mice”, a specially designed space where rodents had Abundance of food and water, as well as a large living space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, he placed four pairs of mice that in a short time began to reproduce, resulting in their population growing rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, after 315 days their reproduction began to decrease significantly. When the number of rodents reached 600, a hierarchy was formed between them and then the so-called “wretches” appeared. The larger rodents began to attack the group, with the result that many males begin to “collapse” psychologically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result, the females did not protect themselves and in turn became aggressive towards their young.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time went on, the females showed more and more aggressive behavior, isolation elements and lack of reproductive mood. There was a low birth rate and, at the same time, an increase in mortality in younger rodents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, a new class of male rodents appeared, the so-called “beautiful mice”. They refused to mate with the females or to “fight” for their space. All they cared about was food and sleep. At one point, “beautiful males” and “isolated females” made up the majority of the population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Calhoun, the death phase consisted of two stages: the “first death” and “second death.” The former was characterized by the loss of purpose in life beyond mere existence — no desire to mate, raise young or establish a role within society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time went on, juvenile mortality reached 100% and reproduction reached zero. Among the endangered mice, homosexuality was observed and, at the same time, cannibalism increased, despite the fact that there was plenty of food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years after the start of the experiment, the last baby of the colony was born. By 1973, he had killed the last mouse in the Universe 25. John Calhoun repeated the same experiment 25 more times, and each time the result was the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun’s scientific work has been used as a model for interpreting social collapse, and his research serves as a focal point for the study of urban sociology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently witnessing direct parallels in today’s society… weak, feminized men with little to no skills and no protection instincts, and overly agitated and aggressive females with no maternal instincts.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iOFveSUmh9U?color=white&amp;amp;theme=light&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;
     &lt;/iframe&gt;
     &lt;/figure&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.the-scientist.com/foundations/universe-25-1968-1973-69941&quot;&gt;Universe 25, 1968–1973&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.facebook.com/story.php?story_fbid=pfbid0zJtXGf53RD3gSmMuPQrykZtJZaawC9UpV2fSjanuU6pKGw4xQ2hju6sp2WPHVYx6l&amp;amp;id=1456000719&amp;amp;mibextid=Nif5oz&quot;&gt;A facebook post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Let’s de-grave marina</title><link href="/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Let&apos;s de-grave marina" /><published>2023-01-06T20:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-06T20:21:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/06/lets-de-grave-marina.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3c/Chennai_Marina_beach_panorama1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am shocked by Stalin’s announcement of massive 80 crore waste to decorate Karunadhi’s grave with a massive statue of a pen on an artificial island. 80 crores is massive money. It could be given to 800 people to start very small business, even if 1% of them succeed, it will be good. But what good does it do decorating a grave?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I truly wonder what gives right to these dravidian parties to put their dead bodies in Marina? It’s a beach, it belongs to people, more than us, it belongs to all nature. We have converted it into a graveyard and have put artificial structures there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A leader might be needed for a society (of people who cannot think well, for a society that could think will be leader less), but I wonder what’s the big thing in having a rotting corpse below a huge concrete structure? It looks childish and silly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the thing that outrages me is that we have mausoleum for a proven criminal Jayalaitha in Marina, and almost none opposes it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly think a person should be remembered for what he had done. Today I know English and interact with the world, thanks to Annadurai. I am an atheist and think rationally, and don’t encourage building temples, mosques, churches and mausoleum, thanks to Periyaar. I don’t remember these people because I saw their graves, but the good things that they have done to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember Abdul Kalaam not because of his grave, but he protected me from invaders, helped our nation become a space power. I don’t even know where his grave is, though I do know they have built one for him. I remember Kamaraj for his honesty and, his ability not to build grave for his mom even though he was a powerful chief minister of Tamilnadu. I don’t know where Kamaraj is burried, I don’t even know if he was cremated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst thing is that the 80 crores that Stalin wants to spend on decorating his dad’s grave is our hard-earned money. It’s not from Red Giant’s or G-squares or some binaami’s loot. I really wonder what gives the right for these DMK and ADMK to waste our money on dead bodies like this? May be if they earned honestly they would know worth of money and spend it better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe we people are powerless, coward, and have too much to lose now by protesting against dravidian rule, but I feel ultimately we must de-grave Marina. All these bodies should be taken out, put somewhere else, beach should be given back to people to walk, turtles to reproduce, crabs to crawl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage the reader to talk about this loot going on in Tamilnadu. I encourage one to think about the good ways of using money than wasting it on dead matter. I wish you would would remeber this blog when you vote again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Think like a farmer</title><link href="/2023/01/06/think-like-a-farmer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Think like a farmer" /><published>2023-01-06T09:19:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-06T09:19:00+05:30</updated><id>/2023/01/06/think-like-a-farmer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/06/think-like-a-farmer.html">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t shout at the crops.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t blame the crop for not growing fast enough.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t uproot crops before they’ve had a chance to grow.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choose the best plants for the soil.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Irrigate and fertilize.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove weeds.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remember you will have good seasons and bad seasons- you can’t control the weather only be prepared for it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Don’t shout at the crops. Don’t blame the crop for not growing fast enough. Don’t uproot crops before they’ve had a chance to grow. Choose the best plants for the soil. Irrigate and fertilize. Remove weeds. Remember you will have good seasons and bad seasons- you can’t control the weather only be prepared for it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Need freshers for a web tech company</title><link href="/2022/12/30/need-freshers-for-a-web-tech-company.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Need freshers for a web tech company" /><published>2022-12-30T10:30:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-30T10:30:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/30/need-freshers-for-a-web-tech-company</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/30/need-freshers-for-a-web-tech-company.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello All,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a web developer for more than 15 years, currently I am serving a client who seems not to treat his employees bad. This is very rare in tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The product we are working on need’s lot of people to maintain, upgrade and compete. So we are open for freshers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;qualification&quot;&gt;Qualification&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You must be an Indian citizen.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You need to love computers and enjoy working with them.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should have self belief.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should know any programming language. You must feel you are good at it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The job is fully remote, so if you are an office seeking person, sorry.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You must have a good internet connection.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;selection-process&quot;&gt;Selection Process&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I (Karthikeyan) will have a word with you, see if you are good. I will give you a small exercise which you need to complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once done, company name will be revealed, and you will be put in touch with my boss who will initiate the official process of trying to take you in with further rounds of interviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send your resume via Whatapp, Signal or Telegram (@mindaslab) to +91 8428050777. If you want to mail, mail it to mindaslab@protonmail.com, but I rarely check emails these days, so give me a ring after you send it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-the-job-be-like&quot;&gt;What The Job Be Like&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You will be given the necessary gear to start coding (I think it will just be a Mac Pro).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You will be thought to how to build web pages and turn them into enterprise apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t want to go into details as there are lot’s of things you will learn.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello All,</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">7 Japanese Philosophies</title><link href="/2022/12/28/7-japanese-philosophies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="7 Japanese Philosophies" /><published>2022-12-28T20:50:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-28T20:50:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/28/7-japanese-philosophies</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/28/7-japanese-philosophies.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-oubaitori&quot;&gt;1. OUBAITORI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never compare yourself.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone blossoms in their own time in different ways. Don’t judge yourself by someone else’s path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-kaizen&quot;&gt;2. KAIZEN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuously improve.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Constantly strive to improve across all areas of your life. Small changes accumulate and make all the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-wabi-sabi&quot;&gt;3. WABI-SABI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embrace Imperfection.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing lasts, nothing is complete. Accept your own flaws and those of others. Find beauty in imperfection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-gaman&quot;&gt;4. GAMAN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have dignity during duress.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard times need to b e met with emotional maturity and self-control. We need patience, perseverance, tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-ikigai&quot;&gt;5. IKIGAI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Know your reason for being.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Define the reason you get up in the morning. Make ti something you are good at passionate about, and that the world needs. THIS is meaning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-shikita-ga-nai&quot;&gt;6. SHIKITA GA NAI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accept and let go.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things simply aren’t within our control. Accept what you cannot change, and move on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-shu-ha-ri&quot;&gt;7. SHU-HA-RI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn, Experiment, Innovate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“When the student is ready the teacher will appear.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;When the student is truly ready… The teacher will Disappear”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Tao Te Ching&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a way of thinking about how to learn and master a technique. There
are 3 stages to acquiring knowledge:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shu:&lt;/strong&gt; Learn the basics by following the teaching of one master. Imitating the work of great masters also falls in this stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ha:&lt;/strong&gt; Start experimenting, learn from masters, and integrate the learning into the practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ri:&lt;/strong&gt; This stage focuses on innovation and adapting the learning to different
situations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">1. OUBAITORI</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dall-E generated mascot</title><link href="/2022/12/23/dall-e-generated-mascot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dall-E generated mascot" /><published>2022-12-23T12:09:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-23T12:09:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/23/dall-e-generated-mascot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/23/dall-e-generated-mascot.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://bafkreic6gajm63qaraepcvkoh4mb7tn3nrk7ppy72prr5binri2f54iuey.ipfs.nftstorage.link/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Dall-E generated pig mascot.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designers do cost, sometimes even more than developers. Designing is a very creative process. Certainly web pages designed by me sucks, compared to one done by designer. Sometimes I need to shell out a lot if I am doing my personal open source project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to write a Personal Micro Blog application to learn Clojure which I named as pig. I have generated a &lt;a href=&quot;https://codeberg.org/pig&quot;&gt;codeberg project&lt;/a&gt; here. I wanted a cute baby pig as mascot. I asked designer and he gave me his budget, it was big. I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://openai.com/dall-e-2/&quot;&gt;Dall-E&lt;/a&gt; to generate the mascot. I used an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.upscale.media/&quot;&gt;A.I tool to upscale the image&lt;/a&gt;, and I used A.I to remove background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I gave the cute pig mascot to my designer to make it into a sticker which you can see in this blog above. I think I reduced designing cost by 70% this time, and I am very happy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Dall-E generated pig mascot.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">IQ of BJP vote bank</title><link href="/2022/12/10/iq-of-bjp-vote-bank.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IQ of BJP vote bank" /><published>2022-12-10T16:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-10T16:20:00+05:30</updated><id>/2022/12/10/iq-of-bjp-vote-bank</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/10/iq-of-bjp-vote-bank.html">&lt;video controls=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
        &lt;source src=&quot;https://bafybeih3q2q22rkfn7fbvvuxwt6o6riuz7ktxw7z7jsagpjenoqvfnp74m.ipfs.nftstorage.link/ &quot; /&gt;
      Your browser does not support the video element.
      &lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the video element.</summary></entry></feed>