<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-01-27T09:09:27+05:30</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karthikeyan A K’s blog</title><subtitle>Hello World, I am Karthikeyan. I eat briyani and worship Boomthata, the creator of God and Satan.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Code Coma</title><link href="/2019/01/26/code-coma.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Code Coma" /><published>2019-01-26T10:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-01-26T10:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/01/26/code-coma</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/01/26/code-coma.html">&lt;audio controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/sounds/Code_Coma_Jan_26_10_35_AM.mp3&quot; type=&quot;audio/mpeg&quot; /&gt;
Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the audio element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">யாருக்கு என் வாக்கு</title><link href="/2019/01/26/%E0%AE%AF%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%95-%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%81-%E0%AE%8E%E0%AE%A9-%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%95-%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%81.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="யாருக்கு என் வாக்கு" /><published>2019-01-26T10:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-01-26T10:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2019/01/26/%E0%AE%AF%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%81-%E0%AE%8E%E0%AE%A9%E0%AF%8D-%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%81</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/01/26/%E0%AE%AF%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%B0%E0%AF%81%E0%AE%95-%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%81-%E0%AE%8E%E0%AE%A9-%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%BE%E0%AE%95-%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%81.html">&lt;audio controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/sounds/யாருக்கு_என்_வாக்கு_Jan_26_6_30_PM.mp3&quot; type=&quot;audio/mpeg&quot; /&gt;
Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Your browser does not support the audio element.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why the Congress shouldn’t be trusted?</title><link href="/2018/12/23/why-the-congress-shouldn-t-be-trusted.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why the Congress shouldn't be trusted?" /><published>2018-12-23T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-12-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/12/23/why-the-congress-shouldn-t-be-trusted</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/12/23/why-the-congress-shouldn-t-be-trusted.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/62/Rahul_Gandhi_%28headshot%29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the recent 5 state election held recently the BJP lost, not by lot of votes, but it lost to the Congress. The Congress is building its image and is trying to project an image that its the nations savior from the Nazi Modi. Modi is a Nazi, no doubt about it, but Congress had it Nazi rulers too called Indra Gandhi and her son Rajiv Gandhi who tried to wipe out my Tamil race in Srilanka. Is Rahul Gandhi any different? I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rahul-is-a-liar&quot;&gt;Rahul is a liar&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rahul is certainly a liar. He lied to the nation about Rafel deal and called it a scam. The congress and team went to the supreme court and lost, yet they don’t want to admit their lies. Pathetic. Can we let such liars to rule the nation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;promotion-for-kamalnath&quot;&gt;Promotion for Kamalnath&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kamalnath is a C.M now, but when Indra Gandhi died its said that he killed lot of Sikhs. He escaped the law that’s a different thing. If a party is run by good blooded people, will a possible killer even be considered for a C.M post? On one hand Congress says Modi is evil because he killed Muslims in Gujrat, but Kamalnath is good because he killed Sikhs during Indra’s death. Where is the logic?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dynastic-politics&quot;&gt;Dynastic Politics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its sicking to know that a 100 year old party cannot find its leaders outside a single family. And they say Congress is democratic. What a lie! These people have allied with DMK and S.P which are parties that follow dynastic politics too. if congress succeeds, we will soon see a nation ruled by few families. Is that what we want?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;not-much-difference&quot;&gt;Not much difference&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from not having Hindu fanaticism right now, congress is no better. Why vote for it?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Will Engineering Colleges Survive?</title><link href="/2018/12/05/will-engineering-colleges-survive.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Will Engineering Colleges Survive?" /><published>2018-12-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-12-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/12/05/will-engineering-colleges-survive</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/12/05/will-engineering-colleges-survive.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mediad.publicbroadcasting.net/p/kuow/files/styles/x_large/public/201506/20150603-boeing-engineer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder weather Engineering colleges in Tamilnadu will survive for long, they are already falling and many have them have closed down or turned into arts and science colleges. The reason, well there are some which I wish to post here&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-culture-of-looting&quot;&gt;The culture of looting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineering colleges, almost all of them were created not to impart education to the masses, but in a hope of looting people and escaping from taxes by creating a trust. Many families in India do not know what Engineering is and they blindly put their kid into one. In fact many of the so called engineers in India do not know what engineering is. Take any person who has studied engineering and put him in a company, he will falter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All Engineering college does is to sells you is a myth. A piece of paper that is worthless, but you buy it for Rs 4 Lakhs or so. With that myth which says you are a certified engineer, you come to the real world and find out that you are not one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact companies like mine employ these non engineers, give them money for free and give them real engineering tasks which the colleges have failed to do. And we find that the so called engineers are clueless and no idea how to complete them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;prevention-of-foreign-universities-landing-on-india&quot;&gt;Prevention of foreign universities landing on India&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;India has been intelligent to allow foreign investment in I.T, but we don’t see foreign universities teaching kids and making them better professionals. Kapil Sibal wanted to bring in foreign universities and offer competition to Indian ones, but these corrupted lot here bribed various channels and stopped it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without competition, our universities have stagnated and are teaching outdated stuff, their collaboration with Industry is almost nil, and even if we in Industry go on to help them, those so called engineers are so so substandard that they become liability to a company than an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have missed an excellent opportunity of skill development because colleges and universities here have excellent bribing power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;comeback-of-foreign-universities&quot;&gt;Comeback of foreign universities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was interviewing for my friends company, I wasn’t interested in what college they studied or what marks they got, but I was interested what work they had done before applying. Students of Indian colleges have done nothing but to WhatsApp their friends, but students who have got degrees from edx, Coursera, Udacity etc seems to have done work and you know it from their talk. So a situation is now arising where though denied opportunity, foreign universities are coming to us via the internet and are increasing our educational quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a tech companies, we want people who can solve problems and work for us, rather than some one who says that “I own a piece of paper that says I am an Engineer”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;do-you-need-to-be-a-engineer&quot;&gt;Do you need to be a Engineer?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believe me, the work I do, if properly trained an 8th standard guy could do it. In today’s world you need not be a branded as rocket scientist to become a real one, there is so much on the internet that you can find out how to do stuff and train yourself quiet easily. Its a myth that you must be an engineer. Remember the first person who might have started an engineering college wouldn’t have been an engineering degree holder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We @ IT companies are not really looking at people who do have engineering degree, but we are looking at people who can do our tech tasks. That’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-cost&quot;&gt;The Cost&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally the cost. Should you need to pay Rs 4 Lakhs and invest 4 years to become an engineer if you can get a better degree with better training by investing just Rs 5000/- on an online degree and spending just 3 to 6 months? I hope you have common sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now small companies are failing to recognize engineers, soon even huge gorillas too will feel the pressure and do the same.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Actor Vijay &amp;amp; Kamal won’t tell about freebies</title><link href="/2018/12/01/what-actor-vijay-kamal-won-t-tell-about-freebies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Actor Vijay &amp; Kamal won't tell about freebies" /><published>2018-12-01T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-12-01T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/12/01/what-actor-vijay-kamal-won-t-tell-about-freebies</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/12/01/what-actor-vijay-kamal-won-t-tell-about-freebies.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.indianexpress.com/2017/10/vijay-7591.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a great promo for this film Sarkar, the film team was able to dip into the anger of AIADMK people thus earning much needed publicity. AIADMK got angry because it teased freebie scheme that was brought in by Kamaraj, Strangthened by Karuna, MGR and continued by Jaya. Kamal even went as far as saying that people who get stuff for free are beggars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many Vijay fans too heard the message and supported Vijay by burning free stuff the government gave them, but here is the catch, they posted it on social networks that was a free service! Neither Vijay, Murugadoss or Kamal opposed it by saying people are taking freebies from tech giants and becoming slaves to them. That’s amazing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming to free stuff given to Actors. The land for MGR film city was given by the people of Tamilnadu to these actors for free. Will Vijay, Murugadoss or Kamal are willing to make propaganda among film fraternity to return the land to the people? We promote a film and promote it in social network for free for them, in return these people won’t even give a rupee for a post. Are they ready to pay us for that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is this &lt;em&gt;Nadigar Sangam&lt;/em&gt; that does help to actors who are not in good economic situation, will Kamal call them beggars? Why not? Are actors deserved to get freebies by law and only Tamil people are deserved to be called as beggars?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must evaluate who are beggars and who are not. Kamal gets sunlight for free, he does not pay for rain water, he breathes this oxygen free, he paid nothing to come into existence. The earth supports plants for free, plants and animals produce food for us free, the Earth does not charge rent for our stay. In fact man created money so that one can claim to be superior to other, else everything we have is free, we have just created an illusion that everything costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are reading this blog because I transmit my knowledge for free, some one hosts my blog for free, and some on e wrote the software tools to build this blog for free. Else information on your screen could cause dear and you will be reading say one highly expensive article a week and brag about the information wealth you obtained to the people known to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So realize that just because some one says something novel or new or out of ordinary, it does not mean that they care about you, all they want is to grab your attention and sell their movie to you and make you their propaganda tool.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Install latest version of imagemagick in Ubuntu 18.04</title><link href="/2018/11/22/install-latest-version-of-imagemagick-in-ubuntu-18-04.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Install latest version of imagemagick in Ubuntu 18.04" /><published>2018-11-22T15:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-22T15:58:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/22/install-latest-version-of-imagemagick-in-ubuntu-18-04</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/22/install-latest-version-of-imagemagick-in-ubuntu-18-04.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/9a/ImageMagick_logo.svg/1200px-ImageMagick_logo.svg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are lot of resources available on internet to install imagemagick. But everytime I struggle when I install it. Sometimes it misses dependency or sometime misses required delegation like png, jpeg etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I thought to write short note about it to install imagemagick in one try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will install it from source so that we can know the exact version. Now, follow below steps to install Imagemagick 7.0.8-2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo &lt;/span&gt;apt-get update&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Install required dependency&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo &lt;/span&gt;apt-get &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;install &lt;/span&gt;build-essential checkinstall libx11-dev libxext-dev zlib1g-dev libpng12-dev libjpeg-dev libfreetype6-dev libxml2-dev&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, go to /opt directory and download latest version of imagemagick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;cd&lt;/span&gt; /opt

&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo &lt;/span&gt;wget http://www.imagemagick.org/download/ImageMagick.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will download latest version of imagemagick. While writing this it was 7.0.8-2 Unzip it and follow remaining steps for installation and configuration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo tar &lt;/span&gt;xvzf ImageMagick.tar.gz
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;cd &lt;/span&gt;ImageMagick-7.0.8-2
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo touch &lt;/span&gt;configure
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo&lt;/span&gt; ./configure
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo &lt;/span&gt;make
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo &lt;/span&gt;make &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;install
sudo &lt;/span&gt;ldconfig /usr/local/lib
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;sudo &lt;/span&gt;make check&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check if installation is successful using below command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;convert &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;--version&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it installed correctly then you can see output like below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;Version: ImageMagick 7.0.8-2 Q16 x86_64 2018-06-24 https://www.imagemagick.org
Copyright: © 1999-2018 ImageMagick Studio LLC
License: https://www.imagemagick.org/script/license.php
Features: Cipher DPC HDRI OpenMP
Delegates &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;built-in&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;: bzlib djvu fontconfig freetype gvc jbig jng jpeg lcms lqr lzma openexr png tiff wmf x xml zlib&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congrats! You have installed imagemagick successfully.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Prostitute</title><link href="/2018/11/13/prostitute.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Prostitute" /><published>2018-11-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/13/prostitute</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/13/prostitute.html">&lt;p&gt;I was at Star Briyani in Chennai One road, the table next to me was a guy bragging about how much gold he is getting from his in-laws for his marriage. It brought shame to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t really understand women, possibly its okay for them to get money for sex, but that guy was a man. As a man I feel that men should not become prostitutes. Its a shame. We fought the British not to get their wealth, but to stop them from seducing us with their power and wealth. We are men!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In India, male prostitution amounts more than female ones. Female prostitutes usually don’t marry and do it with many males, prostitute males usually get a lump sum amount from the females family and try to be dedicated for them by marrying them. In soul both these female and male prostitutes are the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am  a prostitute too :( , yup I usually had a vision of a simple marriage, a calm life. I thought I would marry a girl, i.e we will have a very good understanding, but circumstances made me a prostitute. I should have walked away if I were a pure soul, but I stayed put for my convenience and for the sake of not hurting others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought my engagement would be simple. My family said that it will be in a temple with two families exchanging confirmations of marriage, but it turned out to be different. First there was a expensive suit purchased for me by my wife with my money :(. Okay I thought, she might be intoxicated with the feeling of getting married. There were shoes purchased (with my money). I am in Tamilnadu, a hot country where I see only idiots wear shoes and it sweats. But people do it because copying European culture seems to make them feel secure and superior. Europe is a different region dumbos! Its far far away from the equator, look at the map. Tamilnadu is near the equator. I often wondered why people don’t think, but they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though all was bought, I had a feeling that engagement would be simple. On the day engagement, I was asked to come to a hotel, as soon as I got out of the lift there were photographers shooting me and directing me how I must pose. I was a puppet and not myself. Of-course prostitutes are puppets :( . It was very clear that the lavish expense was just for show off. There were nearly 100 guests, they all ate food while I stood near my wife on the podium could only watch in hunger as they ate and enjoyed. I felt like I was in prison. When I finally came to eat in all hunger, there was almost no food. I left the place hungry and got myself a tandoori in my hotel room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My marriage was even more lavish. it was all about money and show off than about two hearts understanding each other. My in-laws never really knew even my name. My name on the podium was wrong and none seemed to care about it. The irony was I was marrying a to be doctor in English literature, and they did not know to write my name well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a few days after my marriage, just like a horse is stamped they stamped me as prostitute. My inlaws presented me a gold chain, bracelet, I had a engagement ring too. I am supposed to wear these at every function to show off my status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We remember Thiruvalluvar not for the gold he wore, we remember Auvaiyaar for the dress she wore, but we remember them. If we ask who was the richest person in the Pandiyas period, none knows. That’s our Tamil culture. We have never valued wealth, we have valued what one stood form what ones ideas were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I heard the person speak so proud about his dowry in Star Briyani, my prostitute days flashed before me. I wish I had a pure soul.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was at Star Briyani in Chennai One road, the table next to me was a guy bragging about how much gold he is getting from his in-laws for his marriage. It brought shame to me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Finally some one speaks against Single Page Apps</title><link href="/2018/11/07/finally-some-one-speaks-against-single-page-apps.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Finally some one speaks against Single Page Apps" /><published>2018-11-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/07/finally-some-one-speaks-against-single-page-apps</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/07/finally-some-one-speaks-against-single-page-apps.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/c/c3/Ruby_on_Rails_logo.svg/800px-Ruby_on_Rails_logo.svg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was going through Rails mailing list some time ago and something caught my eye. A guy called Greg Navis had written a blog against single page apps. I read it. In my opinion Single Page Apps are a piece of shit. At least shit can be converted to manure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was working in a company that was dominated by people who do not know tech, but they had the illusion that what ever they heard first and thought first was right. They got a contract for developing a financial product and they choose Laravel. Good choice. It was chosen by a guy so that once he got an hold of it, he could leave that company to search for less hellish job. Laravel was good choice and they chose Angular for front end. What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was all done because people over there saw these job requirements peak and they wanted to switch job. I watched the comedy as the team size grew. They employed close to 10 people to build a financial app, I was wondering whats going on, I could do with just 2 or 3 people with Rails. Laravel is good, I have nothing against it, partly because I haven’t used it a lot, but against Angular and most JS front end frameworks I have lot against. Lot of boiler plate and decision making must be done before we start to attack the business of delivering results to clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have used these JS front end frameworks in my work, it does reduce the load of backend developer significantly, all you need is to generate JSON and not worry about the crappy CSS and design. Being a hardcore programmer, design thought was not in me, I am a person of logic, but the project went at a very slow pace. I used to finish a bunch of API’s and watch team of 3-4 front end developers toil with Angular for days. They envied me because it looked to them that I did almost no work, and yes I did almost no work, I used Rails and it di  lot of stuff for me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes if you look at the architecture level, SPA’s looks good. A clean separation between the client and the server, but when it comes to practicality it increases the time to deliver result. The increase in time comes in the form of communication. The front end dev needs to understand the business, the API’s back end devs provide, next he needs to interact with the designer. There is lot of people to people communication and its a bottle neck, consumes lot of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies in India do love SPA’s, that’s for another reason. If you can show many busy programmers to the client, you can bill more. When I was telling a company in Chennai and offered them a deal in which I can reduce the time and money by reducing head count needed for a project, they seem to worry about profit dropping, because their money comes from increasing complexity and head count. It a curse in India where people use tech for their selfishness (like Apple and Microsoft) rather than common good for humanity and the economy (like free software foundation). Its very bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as my personal experience goes, I use middleman for small sites and the moment complexity increases, I switch to Rails (nope I haven’t used Sinatra commercially, but its a good one too). Everything I need is there in Rails, the Database to the Front End, all is there and it works like Rolls Royce. You just don’t need to think about it. Rails migration from version to another too is okay, there are clear migration guides, but yes, if your apps are big and not tested, then you might be screwed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rails is evolving too. It seems to have some process which I don’t really know what, but the community seems to pick the right stuff. When they moved from prototype + RJS to jQuery I was furious, but they seem to have done the right thing. When they moved to Coffeescript, I was very happy at least I may not need to touch this Javascript directly. I wish they integrated with Opal and ended the web developers misery altogether, but….. WHY ITS NOT HAPPENING? I am telling good people on this earth to kill this evil Javascript because I don’t have the power enough to do it. Please consider…..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are saying that I am too biased against Javascript and single page apps, then bloody yes I am. I am because I am biased against inefficiency and things that brings sorrow to programmers. An those who love SPA’s, I curse you, go to hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big companies need something that I don’t understand, I don’t know what they need, perhaps lengthy talks about their app architecture, perhaps lengthy talks about their engineering, bragging to people about how they used their engineering skills and tech insights to have hand picked each and every bit of their application and stitched it together loosing their night sleep. Well, that’s not me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am  a person who likes to sleep at night, earn handsome, do projects to people who do not have deep pockets. How can I go for a SPA?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gregnavis.com/articles/the-architecture-no-one-needs.html&quot;&gt;Gregnavis Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Behaving like a successful rule</title><link href="/2018/11/06/behaving-like-a-successful-rule.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Behaving like a successful rule" /><published>2018-11-06T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-06T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/06/behaving-like-a-successful-rule</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/06/behaving-like-a-successful-rule.html">&lt;p&gt;Its funny what the BJP is doing, its behaving like it has ruled India in a very successful way. It has started celebrating despite adding misery to many, and RSS is trying to use violence to polarize Hindus. Let me tell you what I mean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-patel-statue&quot;&gt;The Patel statue&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes Sardar Patel is a great man no doubt about it, he needs to be remembered for ever, but I think putting a bust of him in parliament is more than enough, yet we have built such a high statue and it costs a lot. It has been built with public money and the public needs to pay Rs 350/- to see it. Yup, we the people of India paid for it and we need to pay further to see what we have created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a Thiruvalluvar statue in Tamilnadu, it too is a waste I feel, we love that man, but spending so much money just to glorify a person hmmm… There are lot of effective things you can do with money so that it can work for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That statue costs Rs 2,989 crores. If you can give 10 lakhs to a business aspirant in a village, then you can create 29,890 businesses, think of it. Even if 10% of them succeed and generate 20% growth, you will get back the money in 13 years. I really don’t understand the value of investment in liability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Patel, the U.P government and idiot Adithyanath wants to build a Ram statue. What for? Bloody hell what for? Ram has been surviving all along without a giant statue and he will survive more. Its this BJP and RSS acting as though they are the custodians of Hinduism and as though this religion won’t survive or become helpless without them is bothering me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;violence-creation&quot;&gt;Violence creation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people knew the BJP because of its violence. All of a sudden we knew it because they bashed a mosque like mads. They bashed because a Muslim ruler bashed a Hindu temple hundred years ago. This savage act by the BJP made people know them and got them recognized by Hindus. Nice PR!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now having got a majority and ruling India for long, they have done things that has plunged the nation in economic disaster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first s demonetization, it caused wide spread chaos and even deaths. Some how we haven’t seen any one getting life sentence or a jail term for possessing black money, and I don’t know how that’s possible in law abiding government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second economic slip-up was this governments inability to to arrest tycoons who have looted us and are hiding in various countries. Rather than taking steps and arresting them quick, they blame the congress rule. If congress has messed up the nation so much that it cannot be recovered by subsequent ruler, then why did the BJP contend in the election saying that it will give a golden age?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the GST. Now small and medium businesses do not know how to file taxes and everything is confusing. The Rafel deal where the french government and Dassult CEO have exposed that its Indian government that wanted to give this deal to Ambani.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how to get support of people when you have ruined the nation? Margret Thatcher got it by a war with Argentina, but Indian army, is it well uncorrupt to face the paks? I don’t know. So the cheap way is to bring in internal war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Hindu men are angry with women because of Aiyappan temple issue, and the case for it was put filed by the RSS, and we see a instability because RSS has won the case. Now RSS is using the verdict to act against it by encouraging mobs to attack women who want to enter the temple. The second is to rake up the issue of Aiyodhya Ram temple. That’s going on. If Indians are stupid enough they will fall into the RSS trap thinking that its RSS that’s saving Hinduism. But none will think from what its saving Hinduism?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-the-alternative&quot;&gt;Whats the alternative?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know whats the alternative. Congress is highly corrupt too, plus they encourage dynastic politics that this nation is still not been able to end. They have become very good in escaping court cases. The DMK, their allies have escaped from the 2G, and congress and Rjiv Gandhi has escaped from Bofors case. The congress will be going into the election like they are the good guys and BJP are the bad ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage the reader to think, think of an alternative. Can you discuss with your neighbors and place and fund some one able to rule the nation as a MP candidate?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Its funny what the BJP is doing, its behaving like it has ruled India in a very successful way. It has started celebrating despite adding misery to many, and RSS is trying to use violence to polarize Hindus. Let me tell you what I mean.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Buddha Posters</title><link href="/2018/11/03/buddha-posters.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Buddha Posters" /><published>2018-11-03T23:49:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-11-03T23:49:00+05:30</updated><id>/2018/11/03/buddha-posters</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/03/buddha-posters.html">&lt;p&gt;Created some Buddha posters in my spare time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_1.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_2.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_3.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_4.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posters/buddha_5.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Created some Buddha posters in my spare time</summary></entry></feed>